On casting, all's live, Adam Curry.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
How are you doing?
Coming to you from the United Kingdom, from Curry Cottage.
It is your daily source code.
Today is Tuesday, November 30th, 2004.
I think we got to stop with this everybody stuff.
There's just too many people doing it.
How you doing?
Uh, everyone?
Got a jam and show for you today, completely filled up with all kinds of goods
that were done with desktop filled with quick time layers and just to wait in here.
And I've adjusted the microphone.
I got some feedback from Dave Winner and also from, well, via Dave, it was Steve Gilmore
who said, you know, where's the reverb?
You said all this cool reverb on your voice and I was thinking,
you should have never done any reverb ever, I don't think.
And then I realized that it was the old castle bar that I was podcasting from in the beginning.
It was so hollow, it sounded like a reverb.
So what I've done is, um, I've added some reverb just so you guys can feel like I'm hanging out
here in the castle, even though nothing could be farther from the truth.
Deadly source code for today.
Well, secondly, just a good one thing I'll set up here.
Starts off with an email in response to my use of this very, uh, track that you're hearing
this drum cadence, uh, Joel Hawksley said that dude.
Thanks for playing my audio of the Michigan cadence.
Of course, I screwed it up, right?
Uh, I called him a drum band.
He said, actually a drum cadence from Michigan State University.
Not a drum band as I commented.
Here in America, he says, most schools middle school through college level.
In fact, I've marching bands.
I myself am, uh, in one of my local high school here in Kent, Ohio.
And, uh, oh, by the way, he says I've played the drums.
Actually, I kind of like it, just listen to that.
Let's crank it up for a second.
A little bit of drum cadence.
The email me back, let me know how you recorded that.
More email that's been coming in, um, regarding English inventions, which seems to be, you know, just a vibe that, uh, that we've caught here.
Uh, we're always taught electricity and, uh, you know, minor things like television.
We're all invented in the United States.
Oh, nothing could be further from the truth now that I'm living in the UK.
We find out that pretty much everything was invented in, uh, in the old country.
Stuart Hunter says, um, of course, this is something that we figured out yesterday as well as John
Logie Bear, the inventor of television.
Don't forget the inventor of the telephone.
Yes, Alexander Graham Bell was born in Edinburgh, Scotland.
Cool.
This is from, uh, so Stuart Hunter who was an Edinburgh native now living and working in Florida.
Alexander Graham Bell was born.
I mean, how long did he live in the United Kingdom?
Should we really look that up?
See, that's another thing.
You know, it's, I guess it's not an American invention, then technically.
Uh, let's see.
Got an email here from Josh.
By the way, all of this, of course, is on the, uh, pod show production notes, which you can find a company with, uh, in the description of every single, uh, podcast, uh,
Beyond the Daily Source Code of DailySource Code.com.
Hey, Adam says, Josh, some of your notes on, uh, November 26,
Daily Source Code.
It says, uh, first of all, New Zealand and Australia, we also use the Bayonet lamps.
That's, uh, what I discovered here that, uh, it doesn't seem to be as common to have screw lamps.
They're easy to put in, but you can't do that trick.
Tom Cruise did a mission of possible where he turned out the light without having to find the switch, and that's true.
And we're to the UK power plugs are, uh, are big because they contain a fuse.
Ah, that's what it is.
So that's switch, I guess, is, it's a trip fuse.
I thought it was just an on-off switch, but apparently, uh, every single, uh,
uh, electric socket in the UK contains a fuse.
So they are indeed very safe.
Uh, and they says, finally, uh, Japan, uh, in Korea, and he thinks in Taiwan,
they use a hundred, uh, 110 volts.
Didn't know that.
And still no one knows.
Was able to tell me exactly why some countries have 220 volts and why have 110 volts.
And furthering to, uh, British life, high Adam, who's this from?
I can't, uh, from Max, Max says, some further info on British life and practices.
First, Sainsbury's, I talked about this on a previous podcast, is not the mega super store.
Tesco has about another 10% market share and Sainsbury's is in financial turmoil.
Excuse me for being so incredibly wrong about that.
Uh, there are switches on UK plugs for safety and usability.
It's not very useful having individual switches.
Okay.
So that was, uh, just a confirmation there that there's actually a fuse inside the UK plugs.
The British transport system he goes on to say is generally appalling with the exception of air travel.
I have to agree, but I also find the British airways very expensive, um, in many cases.
Although they have a lot of choice of where you can sit.
I like that too about British airways.
Uh, there's like three different versions of business class you can choose from.
Uh, so you can have like, you can still be in business class and, but really be a low life in business class and still be cool.
And he goes on to say our friend Max.
I was also slightly disappointed since you were in London that your FM scan didn't involve capital FM,
the main pop radio station in London.
That's interesting because I have seen capital on the, on the radio.
Um, I don't know, maybe I skipped over to call that something else or maybe I just missed it.
He says for what it's worth BBC SCR is BBC South Coast radio.
Okay. So that's, I guess I'm close to the South Coast.
Also radio one is not referred to as BBC one.
That's reversed for TV channels.
BBC one. Oh, that's reserved for the TV channels.
BBC one, BBC three and four.
Okay. And he says, and you were very lucky getting any child into a British school.
And you'd better lose the US accent.
Okay, Max.
Thank you very much.
I feel so welcome once again in the UK with everybody helping me out.
Just trying to get accustomed to life here in Blighty.
Woah, let's say its the first time we've been reciting a second time for college stages…
Yeah, exactly.
Whoa, it's fun.
You believe in miracles?
Yeah.
Play ball.
Welcome to the Sports Park for Friday.
November 26th.
I'm Curtis.
So I can move at 7 p.m.
San Francisco's home.
And I want to hear from you.
Texan voicing males go to Curtis at ds45.com.
That's Curtis.
If you got your new and improved and of course,
and the world,
Hey Curtis, Chris Rickard calling for my,
it better with me while I give you a take without a freaking read.
First of all.
Okay.
That's the Sports Pod.
You got to listen to the sports pod podcast.
Yeah, they've got correspondence and
it's not like, but you know,
Correspondence and it's beautiful. It's just a whole bunch of guys
bunch of guys who you know the exports and just wanted to
Do stuff with sports on their podcast links of course to the iPod or director under
Sports check out the the sports pod or you can go to the sports pod dot com
Now the email here from Lee
Of course again all these all these comments emails can be found in the
Podcast production notes. I was having a conversation with a clerk in a story was telling me that it is a
He's a new XM subscriber because of opian Anthony
I don't know who opian Anthony are but I guess that the I guess XM of course is a satellite
Just like Howard Stern has serious a went to serious satellite radio
XM is another satellite radio company. I think it's the only other one
I guess opian Anthony are two hilarious radio guys
Goes on to say yeah
I mentioned I spend way too much money on iTunes with my iPod
He responded to say yeah, I love my iPod, but I don't do podcasting
I let the casual conversation finish while getting my card hit me this guy mentioned podcasting
Lesson six months and podcasting is already being dropped in casual conversation
No, it was a casual geek conversation, but still
Okay, Lee excellent and that is happening more and more by the way
I just had an interview with the Dutch radio one which is kind of a big deal
for the Netherlands because you know if you get
You know like 15 minutes
To talk about podcasting on a Dutch radio one that that's a a lot of time
I really didn't have to do much talking or convincing because they had some
Girl or some young woman who would basically I guess is their consumer woman and they said here
You know go pot go check out podcasting for a week and she was so in love with what she had heard
That I didn't need to tell anyone anything. She basically sold the whole thing right there. It was it was great
Hey Adam Heather Hollick says love the BBC bit. Oh, this is Heather from from the BBC segment if you haven't seen it
I have no idea how she got into that show by the way
She must know Colin the producer Adam love the BBC bit. I was on the show as well as
One of the podcasting enthusiasts quote unquote
It was a blast we recently moved to London as well and are chronicling the inventor on our blog at living in London
It's a Heather and her friend Linda are now
maintaining that blog and it was cool and now I know a little bit more about Heather
I was kind of wondering you know
Who's this what was that what was the the title again home on the second it was podcasting enthusiast
I'm the daddy of podcasting but Heather is a podcasting enthusiast
podcasting enthusiasts
Cool how they're nice to meet you. Thank you very much. I also linked to your blog and to I guess it's a
The head on Linda site from the pod so pod show production notes
Don and drew were pretty excited about
About being on the BBC and that sparked a whole conversation on the Don and drew show
Love that
Yeah, that's too
Mister drew curry
Mister and Mrs Adam and drew curry all this little hearts it's sad actually. I can't believe you looked in there
That's supposed to be private. You pick the lock. Oh, I don't need to pick a toothpick
It's not much of a lock
I couldn't believe all those hearts. I'm just taking you hours in colored pencil
I couldn't believe the curry castle that place was pretty kickass
And flying into the helicopter
We have a helicopter
Yeah
We have a castle
We just our house is cool the Barbie castle and my little RC helicopter drew our house is a piece of shit
We don't have any money our house is shitty. We don't have house in our house is
Not around
We're sitting underneath water stains on the ceiling and the carpet is all ripped up
What do you want to like what you have to live in some fancy place?
Yeah, forcing now you are because you're on the BBC
Yes, I first since I was on the BBC. I want better things
I'm trying I'm working hard. Come on baby. I'm here for you Don. I can take you away from drew and his
Danki old house
Working to the like fingers to the bone
I'll try to provide and his bony fingers
Okay, you guys
She was doing something nerdy tonight in the website. I'm not exactly sure what it was because it's nerdy and I think that's boring
Therefore
What did did she say boy
Because it's nerdy and I think that's boring. Okay boring sounded like boy
Therefore
Stupid not worth my time
But he might want to talk about it because he seemed to really be excited
What about something nerdy happening? I'm just I'm getting in the opium l
Getting into using radio usually land as an outliner and so
Similar to the way Adam Curry's doing his production notes. I'm kind of doing something similar
Except I'm tying it into my movable type entries
So that you don't have to leave our site to go see the production notes. They're not really production notes
I mean, his show is obviously a lot different than ours
So mine is like what what what do you mean obviously a lot different?
I hope dawn defends me on that 12 minutes in dawn rants about assholes 12 minutes one second
Why are you ripping on that?
I'm just saying it's kind of funny to have production notes when it's just us talking
Then it really production notes. It's more like like I said his or production notes were hey
Don't rip on my boyfriend drew ours aren't ours are like after the fact
Describing what happened in the show
You know I never listen to the shows you do sometimes we listen to it after we record until I lose interest
I have a very short attention span but if you laugh
While we're re-listening to the show then I know it's gonna be pretty good one
You're you're a tough cookie you guys. I got a lot of emails from you people that call me a fucking quitter
You know what this is the thing if you've been listening for the last few months
You know I'm kind of mental so some days
I'm not chipper and full of sunshine
Some days I'm irritable and bitchy and moody
Don't say I being married to her
You should be sending me like bouquets and candy or something
bouquets and candy yeah
What about
For my hardships dealing with your moody this I should be giving some kind of award away for what
Living with your stanky feet
Don and Drew show a bit there on the daily source code for you today
Check them out Don and Drew dot com of course you can find them at the i-potted out org directory
Hello, this is Giliad me down in some Paula Brazil. I listen to your podcasts
Every morning all my way to work. I think they're great. I hope everything's fine with the
move to England and you know just basically settling down in a
different city different country and all that
The podcasting scene down here in Brazil is you know
It's gonna take a while to take off mainly because in my opinion because of the
prices of the MP3 players down here
They go for about a thousand american dollars which is whoa
Hold on a second a thousand american dollars
Dude
What is up with that we need to have more information why is it so expensive?
What I mean an MP3 player cost you can get a $450
Gee please let us know email back. This is crazy
You know just wait to expensive
For Brazil, but there's a few people trying
I'm one of them
There's a guy in Rio at
They're still minds.com.br which has a great podcast
About technology and and gadgets and stuff like that
And well basically I just wanted to let you know that got some listeners down here and we really enjoy your show
Keep up the good work and we're gonna be listening down here. All right. Thanks a lot. Take care
Yo buddy cool. Thank you very much for sending in your comment. Also your email which I put up in the
Production show notes for today's show
Unbelievable thousand dollars for an MP3 player. Yeah, that's
Bad something is like someone that's like some rip off going on there
I don't understand how that's possible is that to import duties or what is it or is it just an incredible opportunity to go sell some of these three players
I caught another episode of one of my pod squad favorites covervill which was an all request covervill once again and
You know covervill pays
For an ass cap and a BMI license to play these songs and I'm hoping that that's that's more than enough
I'm not too sure but you know of course that's it's been working quite well. I know here any complaints
I have everyone loves the show and I want to play a bit of covervill
Which I'll just have to call us fair use because I am playing a recording of a show in in a news oriented show
And news entertainment area into the show and adverse an advertorial
Because you know I am the ed Sullivan of podcasting
But the whole reason I'm playing this for you with with the intro and even a little bit of the outro
From the most recent covervill is because it's it's the it's a version of
Nothing compares to you which I've never heard before of course. I knew the song was written by Prince and
Originally recorded and made into a world smash by Schneido Connor I'd never heard a Prince version and of course
You can leave it to covervill to bring you that but got a an email from
Steve Carter this week who
Said you know the one thing that the list is missing is Schneido Connor's cover of nothing compares to you
And I said well, you know that that's true wrote him back and I said that's true except
Technically her version is in a cover Prince wrote it she she performed it and
And then Prince later covered it himself about years after it went big but I stand corrected here
In the preparation for tonight's show looking up the information
Actually Schneido Connor wasn't the first person to perform it that credit goes to a group called the family and this was a
Kind of a
Prince influenced
group that was made up of a couple members of the time and then
a couple other people
And he
gave them the song they released in 1985 as part of their one and only album self titled down the family and
And didn't really go anywhere so
Schneido Connor covered it in
1988 and made a very big hit out of it and then later on Prince covered it himself
So technically Prince is still covering his own song, but Schneido Connor's version is a cover as well
So let's jump into the
Prince cover of nothing compares to you
Here's Prince on covervill
Start
I
Yeah
It's been sitting
But today, sit you to your love
I don't want every night, sleep all day
Sit you to your love
Listen, then oh I can do whatever I want
I can seem whoever I choose
Eat my dinner and a fancy festival
Oh yeah, but not there, not there, you can take away the spirit
Oh yeah, I think I'm dead
Nothing compares to you, oh yeah
It's been so lonely without you
I'm like a bird, I've done the song
Nothing can stop this lonely rain
Tell me baby, where did I go wrong?
Oh baby, I can put my thoughts around everything I see
Oh yeah, but they only remind me of you
Oh my name for my new children, oh yeah
I went to the doctor, that's going to tell me
What to take, that's what I told me
You want to see
Nothing compares to you
Oh baby, where did I go wrong?
I know that I'm living with the pain and it's so time's hard
So time's hard, but I'm feeling it wrong
I'm feeling it wrong, I'm feeling it wrong
Suddenly I'm living with the pain and it's so time's hard
Yes, like you'll be
And now when you can I'm living with the pain
You know, I would pay a huge amount of money to subscribe to a Prince Podcast.
Seriously, seriously, how cool would that be?
This is so up his alley, you should be so all over this.
Thanks to Coverville for bringing us special rendition of nothing compares to you.
Brought to you by Prince and I presume a new power generation, or parts of it, or something like that,
and I never know what Prince is doing.
Two guys I want to talk about now, who are members of the Pod Squad,
and I'll put a link to the Pod Squad page again,
trying to, well, basically trying to use some technology bits to combine some things.
Now, how vague did that sound?
Anyway, Pod Squad or body is mine, who have been hanging out with since,
since way back in the beginning of Podcasting.
Remember, back in those days, like four months ago?
So one of them is Michael Goat.
Oh, man, I haven't purchased his name in a long time.
Michael Goat.
Welcome to Real Reviews, films worth watching.
Thanks for joining us again.
As always, we are easy to reach on the web at mwgblog.com.
So that's Michael Goat.
Goat.
Let's see, Michael Goat.
Welcome to Real Reviews, films worth watching.
Michael Goat.
Goat.
Hey, Michael Goat.
He's a member of the Pod Squad.
And he is another member of the Pod Squad.
You've probably heard of this guy, Michael Butler.
This is Bama.
And you're listening to the rock and roll.
Geek.
So.
And I am gonna have sex with the hose.
So, you can get to both of those podcasts from the iPod or director of course.
You heard Michael's web address.
And the Rock and Roll Geek Show, of course, can be found at Rock and RollGeek.com.
Why do I play these two bits of podcasts for you today?
Because I caught something interesting on Michael's weblog.
He says, I've agreed to sponsor the next few editions of the rock and roll Geek Show.
Why am I asked?
Because Michael Butler puts on a kick ass show.
He says, one that I listened to at the same time that I keep hearing.
That.
A lot of seconds.
I missed a piece of the posting there.
Let me just go to this page.
Shoot my daughter disconnect your phone line.
Let's see.
You might still have it.
Is it going to come in?
Yeah, there we go.
At the same time, keep hearing.
I'm trying to get a high-income sponsorship.
That's what I thought I was saying.
I think he will.
But in the meantime, since I'm fan and want to support it,
I figured the best way to go about that was to sponsor the show.
And they go into this whole thing about business models.
And the place of success for podcasting.
And there are some comments there.
There's a good.
Some good comments getting started.
Which are kind of a long, some other conversations.
I'm going to just turn this down a little bit more.
I can't go any softer than that.
I'm not sure if they can.
There we go.
Just get it in the background like so.
I saw that Doug K of IT Conversations.com had put out a similar.
A question or request saying, hey, you know, what's it going to be?
Are we going to do commercials?
Are we going to have the tip jar?
Do people want to subscribe?
So that's.
It's an interesting little conversation that's going on there.
I think the more people should weigh in with it to sense worth.
I have really been trying, by the way, to get this highly
Consponsorship for the Rock and Roll Geek Show.
I sent off an email to Jose.
But he might have used to work at Heineken here at the headquarters.
And also, there's a lot of people at Heineken USA.
And he said he was going to get on on it.
And I sent him a logo of the Rock and Roll Geek Show,
which if you've ever seen it in iTunes,
if you looked at the ID3 tags,
you'll see that the Rock and Roll Geek Show
is a Heineken logo with Heineken handily replaced
by the Words Rock and Roll Geek Show.
So it's cool though to see a lot of love
flowing through the Pod Squad.
Another email from Tim Germer,
who points me to 15 megs of fame,
a site that gives listeners a free way
of discovering new music online.
Very cool.
Also, it has recommendations engine.
I looked around for a couple of tunes.
But really, I like getting songs that are recommended
by a source code listeners myself.
But that is one place you can go look.
I've also placed a couple of other links
to some other comments and emails about
non-reabase music, rea being RIA,
even a French song.
So go and check those out and you find anything.
Definitely let me know because I do love,
I do have playing all kinds of stuff on the source code.
Let's listen to Michael Butler.
Rock and Roll Geek Show.
This is Michael Butler, it's Sunday.
November 28th, 2004.
Thanks a lot for listening.
This is take two of this episode.
I've got almost completely done with it.
I was grooving.
Oh no.
Oh no, hold on.
I need to get some of my own scary scary music in there.
What happened? Oh my gosh.
How are we going to find out what happened?
Now I'm not grooving.
So I was halfway through the episode,
almost all the way through it.
It was going quite well if I do say
to myself and I got a Colonel panic.
Oh, a whole computer crash.
So it didn't get saved.
So I was fucked.
Okay.
Oh man.
So Colonel panic, that definitely sucks.
That's like a unique thing.
You're not supposed to get that.
This is why I'm still recording on my
external Samsung app.
150 dollar MP3 player recorder.
And man, the such room for improvement for this stuff.
There really is.
And Michael, when I get my new one in
because I ordered a couple that have been on long long
back order, I will send you off mine.
So you can use that.
You just plug it into the headphone jack
and record straight from there.
It's the safest way to go my brother.
That's what I've found out several times myself.
Many, many times way too often.
It's just not worth it.
Not worth it at all.
So as I've been going through some bandwidth with
draws, I've noticed a couple things that are not
right with our iPodders, with our iPod or
software.
So here's what's happening.
So let's say you go away on vacation.
That's probably the best example.
Because I'm effectively a man vacation.
I don't have any broad band at home.
So what I get to do is I get to go to the
Starbucks here, which closes at 6 p.m. on weekdays.
6 30 on Saturdays and 5 30 on Sundays.
So after helping out with Patricia and today,
man, I like all kinds of boxes up to the attic and
out to the garage.
We're getting very close to having a very
livable environment.
But, you know, so real busy, then around
quarter four dashed off, you know,
started my iPod or download.
And here's the problem is I have to unsubscribe
from a whole bunch of stuff.
Because I know that it's going to hit a feed
that I haven't received updates from for,
well, maybe three updates.
You know, I may have missed one dawn and
Rousseau, but I may have missed five
comonus reports.
I'd subscribe to not just the Gilmore
gang, but all of the IT conversations.
I had to unsubscribe because, you know,
IT conversations comes out with sometimes
two things a day.
And then it's just too much time.
I don't have time to fill my iPod.
The iPod or cannot fill fast enough,
even though the the link is really fast.
I have a team mobile link that I get at Starbucks.
I think it's probably a team mobile worldwide.
So the link is fast, but it's just,
I have too much subscribed to.
And so what I, what I wind up doing is I wind up
just checking the pod squad and getting there,
their latest podcast.
But anything else, I just don't have time for.
So we need some kind of switch, like a vacation switch,
or it has to sense that, you know,
yeah, although probably important
to get a whole week's worth of shows,
I'd like to have a switch to say,
just get the most recent one.
You know, I'm updating.
I've been away for a while.
I don't want to go back and,
and get everything that I've missed.
Just start fresh for me.
You know, start fresh with.
What's this?
Oh, this is probably Lee Wilkins.
He's been bugging me.
Hold on a second.
Hey, Lee.
Hey, I'm in the middle of the source code.
And that's okay.
Can I call you back in,
let me see, like, what's that?
No, you don't.
Who's this?
Hey, just hung up.
I thought it was Lee Wilkins.
I gave him this number.
I said, call me at 9 o'clock.
It's 9 o'clock.
It's 9 pm.
Exactly.
The phone rings.
I pick up and I see a mobile number.
He says, look for a 079 mobile number.
And I'm just talking to this guy like he's Lee Wilkins and it's not.
All right.
That's too bad.
I probably go to got in a whole conversation going on with that guy.
All right.
So anyway, so back to that.
So there's some work that needs to be done,
because unless you're completely on the ball
and can, and can keep your,
your iPod are updated and your,
this guy's going to call again.
Watch on try it.
Hello.
This is Corey.
This is Lee.
Hey, good.
You know, I'm in the middle of the source code.
Can I?
It's funny because someone called like just 30 seconds before you.
And I pick up and say, hey, Lee, how you doing?
And it wasn't you.
Someone who do dialed or completely wrong number.
It was, it was like, whoa, this phone never rings.
So can I call you back in like 15 minutes?
Yeah.
No.
Good.
Okay, dude.
Talk to you later.
Bye.
That's my nice phone interface.
How did it sound?
The sound like it's an air bridge,
because that's exactly what it was.
So okay.
Did you understand the issues with the, with the iPod or,
we need like a vacation button.
That's what we need.
When you go away, it has to,
it has to be able to reset and just say,
you know, basically I think what we're talking about here is
we need better content management for all of our podcasts.
I'm, I talked to Dave and we're,
I'm really thinking about this idea of,
here's an OPML file.
Here's, well, even that would be a cool way to use it.
Wouldn't it?
So if I say, here's the pod squad.
Here's all the stuff that I want.
You know, here's my favorite shows.
And if you drag this file in,
it's going to subscribe to everything I guess.
What you could do is you could drag it out.
Or in an ideal world,
you take that OPML file with you and then you're on vacation
and drop it onto an iPod that's built into the stereo system
at your vacation address.
But of course, that's just me dreaming away, I guess.
Okay, what do we have here?
We've got the Bob and AJ promo.
What the heck was that?
Where is it?
I'm firing this up from my system.
Here is the Bob and AJ promo, everybody.
Hey, Adam, it's Bob from the Bob and AJ show.
A new podcast out of Montreal featuring RIA free music
and banter from two guys who've known each other way too long.
Anyways, here's the promo and just before I go in Canada,
we say Bo Weyer young and A.
This week, on the Bob and AJ show survivor, Father Ted,
Danger Mouse, Phl từ blue, and Krill.
Check it out, WWEW.phob AND AJ.
All right, there you go.
From up north.
And to wind it up for today,
as we do just about 37 minutes into the show,
I'm gonna do a little bit from the American Guide
speaking british.
figure. This is a wonderful web page that was sent to me. Let me see who sent that to me.
Almost second. Oh, shoot. I don't have it. Well, I have a link to the web page. And I have the list here.
So essentially, it's a whole bunch of words that you use in England, which have different
meaning than they would in the United States. So let's just start off with A. We'll do a couple.
And we'll do one or two every single day on the source code. So we start with A's. If something is
A's, it is brilliant. I used to hear a lot of Liverpool. Kids thought all cool stuff was A's or
Brill and Brill will get to, of course, we get to B. Agrow. Or should we say Agrow? Short for aggravation.
It's a sort of thing you might expect to football match. In other words, trouble. There is sometimes
Agrow in the cities after the pub shut. That will be closed in America. All right. I'll just do two more here.
All right. This is used a lot around London in the South to mean, hello. How are you? You would say
it to a complete stranger or someone you knew. The normal response will be for them to say,
All right, back to you. It is said as a question. Sometimes it might get expanded to,
All right. May, mostly used by blue collar workers, but also common among younger people. Okay. So
All right. I guess that's it. All right. All right. I do it. All right. I'm getting there. And then
this is my favorite anti anti clockwise. The first time I said that something had gone anti clockwise
to someone in Texas, I got this very funny look. It simply means counterclockwise, but must
sound really strange to you. Chaps. I think he thought I had something against clocks. This is
a whole set up. Of course, this whole list of words for Americans. Anti clockwise. It is indeed
true. They don't say counterclockwise, but anti clockwise. And then the final one here from the let's
do ours. Okay. That's a good one. Arse. Basically a word that doesn't seem to exist in America.
It means the same as asked, but as much rudder. It's used in phrases like pain in the offs,
and nuisance, or I can't be arse. I can't be bothered. Or you might hear something was
half arse, attempt. Meaning it was not done properly. And then there's my favorite of the day,
and we'll leave it at that. Arse about face. This means you are doing something back to front.
And that's the arse of the source code. Everybody?
We'll be back tomorrow with another edition. That will be the 30 days test of 10
more April 2 of November. There'll be December 1st edition of the daily source code.
Looking forward to that. Of course, your comments are welcome out of a query.com.
Send me those MP3 comments so I can download them at Starbucks and get them on the show. I really love them.
And you can always leave your comments on a weblawedlive.curry.com. And of course, we've got
the website where you can find the podcast team. We can find a little show in the archives.
The daily source code.com. I'll see you tomorrow here on the source code. Take care. Bye-bye.