this is the source code for Thursday August 26 2004. Hi everybody. Good morning, good
evening, good afternoon, wherever you might be listening to this or whichever day you
might be listening to this. I'm Adam Curry coming to you from Curry Castle in Belgium
for as long as we are still here. The move towards the UK is looking good. Hopefully
we'll have some news about that next week. So it's Thursday is always the hardest day.
If you get up really early like I've been doing for the past year, Thursday is just
it's the Thursday dip. It's really, really difficult. So just a quick scan around the
net a couple of things I want to talk about today. After hearing Dan Bricklin on IT conversations,
I'm relaying that the Halley Suit hosts. Dan posted something on his web blog that you
might want to check out at DanBricklin.com.
concept of the iPod platform.
And he writes about IT conversations and basically all the stuff that we've been talking about,
you know, how there are actual programs and shows and how the timing of when you get it
may not be that important as long as it's automated and put onto your play out device.
And of course he does note that the technology to do this has been around for quite a while.
But I think now we're finally catching on and I'm very happy about that.
Yesterday I started with the first of my reviews of audiobooks.
So yesterday, what was it?
Oh, anti-Americanism.
And today a book that I read, again, big quotes there on the red part because I listened to
read all my books through almost all my books through audiobooks.
I thought it might be interesting to let you hear what it sounds like when audiobook
has been read by the author.
In this case, Bill Clinton, his autobiography, My Little
life, which I was thinking about this, I was preparing a clip to play for you today, that
I don't think that I would have been able to get through the entire book if I was actually
reading it. Because I found it, you know, a little bit boring. The way the press in Europe
certainly played it up is, you know, well, there's not much in the book, but there is
this one bit about Monica Lewinsky. And it's dumb, you know, it's interesting to hear
about what went on behind the scenes, how policy was put together. I particularly like
the all the stories about his presidential election. And just a lot of the decisions
that he had to make during his presidency and also before and after. But again, it may be
because you're listening to the president of the United States read these words or speak
these words that it is entertaining enough to listen to the entire thing. But it's certainly
not one that, you know, excuse me, I'm yeah, I know I have to take a bath, but I'm taking
the iPod with me.
It's not a book like that.
part for you today and I'm going to try and keep a little bit shorter than the previous
excerpts I've done, where Bill Clinton talks about the fact that he knew that he was lying
and that he was betraying his colleagues, his family and of course the American public.
And it is nice to hear someone say, you know, I fucked up and I did a bad thing.
So I'll play that for you right now from Bill Clinton's My Life.
broke, I called my attorney David Kendall and assured him that I had not sub-orn perjury
or obstructed justice. It was clear to both of us that Starr was trying to create a firestorm
to force me from office. He was off to a flying start, but I thought if I could survive the
public pounding for two weeks, the smoke would begin to clear the press and the public would
focus on Starr's tactics, and a more balanced view would emerge. I knew I had made a terrible
mistake, and I was determined not to compound it by allowing Starr to drive me from office.
For now, the hysteria was overwhelming. I went on doing my job, and I stonewalled, denying
what had happened to everyone. Hillary, Chelsea, my staff and cabinet, my friends in Congress,
members of the press and the American people. What I regret most other than my conduct is
having misled all of them. Since 1991, I had been called a liar about everything under
the sun, when in fact, I had been honest in my public life and financial affairs, as all
would show. Now I was misleading everyone about my personal failing. I was so embarrassed
and I wanted to keep it for my wife and daughter and I didn't want to help Ken Star to criminalize
my personal life. It was like living in a nightmare. I was back to my parallel lives
with the vengeance.
Okay, Bill Clinton from my life and I purchased it on audible.com. Not getting paid to say
this but that is a good place to get the most recent audible audiobooks. And it's recently
simple. Although you do have to log in every single time you come back which is pain in
the ass and sometimes you know your session expires. Oh well. I want to move on to talk
about Dave Sluscher's most recent work on the iPod platform and his audio post. But first
I've gotten several messages about iTunes for Windows because people have been working
on Windows scripts. Dave Sluscher also has created a new version of the Internet.
created a Windows version of his Perl script of the getenclosures.pl which has the same
functionality as iPod or only actually it's better and I'm using it myself.
But apparently iTunes for Windows which you can of course use to sync up your iPod.
I haven't done it myself but I presume it's more or less the same where you dock your
iPod and it syncs up with your iTunes library.
Apparently there's a calm object for iTunes which means you can control it and this was
pointed out to me by several people and therefore I guess it's scriptable or addressable or you
can talk to it.
So if you're interested in working with us and helping out that certainly would be a
big help if we can figure out exactly what we can make iTunes do and if it will only
sync with an iPod or if we can use some of its API to connect to other devices because
iPods, yeah there's millions of them out there but they're certainly not the only ones
nor should they be.
Is there some kind of industry standard for that?
I mean has anyone even looked into it?
I know I'll look into myself then as well.
So Dave Slusher from evilgeniuschronicles.org,
who's also a radio guy, I know and discovered
from his most recent audio post.
He did an entire 21 minute piece on RSS and enclosures
and monetizing on it and how sponsorship would work.
And I agree with him on a lot of points
and he's saying some really...
I don't know if you guys heard that,
but my eye chat just started talking to me.
He's saying a lot of intelligent things
about the asynchronous nature of the iPod platform.
And I think the monetizing bit
where he's talking about sponsorship,
he's talking about being paid per download.
I don't wanna go quite that far.
I think it's, yeah, sponsorship will come into play.
Maybe someone will say, hey, would you let us sponsor
your review of audiobooks.
And one of the reasons I'm doing it, not only do I like audiobooks, but I'm sure that there's a market there for people to get reviews about audiobooks and here if it's worth worth purchasing.
What we will need a better way of measuring our success and I, you know, yes, there is a pretty broad base and belief in measurement of page views, you need visits with, you know, based on server logs, but they're still.
There's a lot of caching going on and, you know, and quite frankly messages are passed on through other means than hitting the same web server, you know, they're relayed from someone's aggregator to someone's web log.
They're sent via email.
There's so many different ways that it can get, you know, that your network or your content network spreads out.
So we need a better way of measuring that and I think that will always come back to a, you know, your advertising, did you get some sales?
sales.
very basic. That is absolutely the most basic way of broadcast advertising. I think it's
called per inquiry. You used to see it a lot at night and probably do on most local stations.
There's a phone number, you call it, you order something and then the broadcaster gets a
piece of each sale and of course the person who put together the informational or whatever
it is. That's called per inquiry. I think that that may be a way to go.
Another thing that Dave Sluscher talked about is how this asynchronous nature is giving us
the power to really listen to what he calls I think packets of passion. I'll check an
excerpt in a second. We do have control over what we like and so that we can watch it when
we want to and we don't have to invest 12 a day for 12 consecutive weeks to make sure
we don't miss any episode of the story.
of pranos, which gets me to thinking we need some kind of democratic Tivo engine, you know,
so something that can be as smart as Tivo can be based upon all of our behavior anonymously
and that no one controls and can capture and monetize on that.
Because I don't think that's where the money is going to be, by the way.
That's the old way of figuring it out.
I think that they're going to be shows.
If people are going to sponsor them and want to be a part of interesting communication.
Anyway, let's have a listen to Dave Slusher because he did figure me out.
He really understands why I created the iPod or Apple script and I'll just share with
you because he has a pretty good analogy for it.
So as we as has been going on between Adam Curry's web log and some of the other people,
he wrote his iPod or script which sort of challenged a couple other people to it was
kind of Tom Sawyer, whitewashing the fence sort of ploy, challenged several of us,
being us to go out and do, you know,
more fuller featured versions of the same thing, you know, having done a little bit of it.
And making it think it's all our idea. So there is certainly a Mark Twain sort of feel to it.
Okay, you got me. Yes, exactly my plan. And I'm very happy it's working. I'm great that we're working together,
even though we haven't even, I think, really exchange an email. And there's other people out there,
and they're posting stuff, their comments, and they've got all kinds of ideas. And that's very cool.
And just one more bit of what I call it. Some of Dave's personality. And I'm trying to figure him out,
just from listening to his audio blog posts. You can get a real good idea of what someone's about
and where they're coming from. And I think he has a real problem with the record industry,
and maybe just with the man in general. So that was the wrong one. Here we go.
And really, um, fucked it up. That's such a great intro for you, Dave. Here we go.
And really and truly the more I think that's the best.
think about it, this iPod platform and kind of asynchronously downloading for offline
consumption these bundles of passion is so much better than streaming anyway.
And so I'm again, I'm hoping for the world of delicious irony whereby fucking around
and making it so that internet broadcasting was not economically viable.
They brought about a world with something with much worse potential, much more potential
for changing the world.
And hopefully for reducing the record labels role in it, for disintermediating themselves
out of existence because they're such cock suckers and such greedy fucks that they cannot
possibly allow any other business model come in that may anytime now or in the future ever
compete with them.
So these fucking plutocrats may have really really host themselves and so politically
I kind of hoping that that's the case.
But anyway, I'm getting out.
The synchronous is the key.
OK.
My audio cut out once or twice during that.
I don't know if that actually went out that way
on the recording, but clearly very passionate about what's
going on in the music industry.
And I think that the music industry actually
has a way to help us, which I want to get to in a second.
Just some quick emails and comments
on the web log that I wanted to share with you.
Because I'd asked several of you, where do you listen
to the source code?
What are you working on?
Actually, Peter Oferbakke.
He has a web log at iPortunities.nl slash WordPress.
It's iPortunities with double P. And he's
talking about working on a JavaScript version of iPotter
that will work on Windows.
Let's see.
Then we have Eric Rice, who says that he not only
listens to the show when he's driving but he also replied via his audio.
blog. I look for it but for some reason I couldn't find it so I have to check that again Eric.
And Ed also says that there's a way you can use the B script and of course the window scheduler
to accomplish the iPod or stuff. And he points to WarnerFogel's .net tool which he had up in
back in October. I think that we still need to connect to iTunes. That's the magic piece. It's
not just downloading the files and extracting the enclosures. It's actually the final last bits
there is getting it on to the iPod without any user intervention. Then we've really created
something. And Tim Watt who has a radio web blog but just Google is named Tim Watt WATT.
He is blogging the Olympics. I didn't think that they were allowed to do that and he seems
like he's a journalist himself. He certainly has all kinds of great credentials and fabulous
pictures and stories on his on his web blog. And I was in the understanding
that no one was allowed to blog anything at the Olympics.
Maybe he's just hanging out, but he's from England and judging from his blog, he's definitely
a journalist.
He said that he's been listening to the show while he's been there for the last week or
so on the new transport system in Athens.
Going back and forth from the media center each night.
So there you go.
That says a lot about his occupation.
He says, I'm going to quote him here.
I think the Lavino Rolos is something that you've played.
You'll have a special nostalgia for me in the future with the backing of cicadas and hot
weather when he's back in rainy old England.
So wow, you know, I reached out and touched someone with the audio blog and welcome and
thanks for listening, Tim.
So let me wind up with me the song of the day.
I was thinking that it would be nice if we can get the music business involved somehow.
And there's one guy and actually I believe Dave Weiner suggested it to me a while ago.
who would at least understand what we're trying to do and see that there's something there
that needs to be built and can be done and that you don't necessarily have to monitor
it on a better way. And I'll tell you a little story about him after this song.
You sign of the times, it's Prince.
In fact, the skinny man tied up a big disease with a little name.
If I'd chances, gefric came across a needle and soon changed it the same.
At home, now 70 year old boys and their ideal phone.
Is being in a gang called a disciple's high on crack.
♪ I told no machine ♪
I'm gone
Time
Her cane and her rips ceiling off a church and kill everyone inside
Turn on a telly and every other story is telling you somebody die
I said stick you to me because you couldn't afford to feed it
We'll send the people to the moon, except them and my cousin tried to read before the very first time
Now he's doing horse, it's June
Time
♪ Sitting on ♪
♪ I know I get shit mixed ♪
♪ And the body still flies ♪
♪ Good man ain't at me ♪
Oh, at night
Time
Baby, make a speech, Star Wars fly, Navy should shine home
But if a night falls, little bum falls, Would be by sea to dawn
Time
It's a setting note with rocket bombs
And everybody's knew what was like
Something, can't eat
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
Thanks for the time!
Time, time, time, time. Time, time. Best with your mind, for the folks who live, this fall in love, you can have a break, call it late.
It's a bull. Time, time.
That's Prince, sign of the times and I want to tell you why I think that he would be great to work on this.
First of all, we already know he believes in a download platform and a market for downloads because
he's one of the first musicians to really dive into that head first. Check out NewPowerGeneration.com.
Secondly, he's very intelligent and very wired and knows exactly what he's doing.
what's going on and it's very aware.
And I can attest to that because I met him
and was invited to Paisley Park Studios.
I was in Minneapolis doing a commercial for,
yeah, of course, Sam Goody's music land.
And it was like a three or four day shoot
and on the second or third day
in the quarter to 12, he almost midnight.
There was, you know, got a phone call
and someone said, hey, you know,
Prince has a little party going on at the studios.
Do you want to come?
And that's where Paisley Park Studios are
and that's where Prince's from Twin Cities.
And so, you know, are you interested?
And I said, well, let me think.
Yeah.
And I said, well, great,
because the car is waiting outside.
All right, this is cool.
So, hopping the car, go over and it's about,
I guess it was a 35 minute drive.
And then all of a sudden there's Paisley Park,
all lit up in purple, you know, kind of sitting up on a hillside.
through beautiful white metal detector.
There's very indirect lighting
and ushered into a room which was probably,
I don't know, maybe half a football field.
And there was nothing but beautiful people there.
And there was all kinds of Prince tunes
that I'd never heard before.
All kinds of incredible stuff with DJ playing them live
from CDs and mini discs and, you know,
clearly all kinds of unreleased studio material.
It was great, all kinds of healthy food set to one side.
Everybody and, you know, nice,
everything was white and everyone dressed nicely.
And Prince was over there standing by a sound stack
or actually the speakers behind the speakers.
Just kind of checking everyone out and I said,
you know, I gotta go over and talk to him.
No, no, no, you can't do that.
What do you mean I can't do that?
Well, you know, like you're really tall and you're white.
I'm like, fuck you.
They invited me, I'm well, thank you for inviting me.
to win over and first of all he's not as small as you think he is and that's that's like an urban legend he is and he wasn't a
checked you know it wasn't like he was wearing extremely high heels but just from what I'd heard about him I expect him to be
really small and I'm six three almost six yeah six four and just isn't isn't like that
and he knew he'd been watching MTV he knew what the latest shows were that I'd done and we talked about music and
talked about Europe and you know I thanked him for you know for inviting me to this place and yeah you know he's he was just
really much more normal guy than you would think or maybe he comes across in his performance and even I and maybe I'm more
blasay than next but I was pleasantly surprised and you know then I went back had a drink turned around I didn't see him
and half an hour later or maybe it was an hour and a half later you know party was over and that
is indicated by the security guards coming in and just kind of discreetly flashing their
flashlights on the ground, just kind of flashing around everyone knows, oh it's time to go,
and the music goes down a little bit and level, and we all walk out through the metal detector again,
and I was driven home.
my Prince story for you. And who knows, maybe someone will hear this and will say, you know,
yo, Prince, his royal badness, something going on on the internet. You might want to check
out Stranger Things have happened. Okay, I'm going to get this up to the server. Tomorrow
will be Friday, which is my daughter's 14th birthday. So I will be doing a show. I'm not
quite sure what time, but we're pretty, we're excited. We're not half as excited as she
is about to no longer being 13. So I'll talk to you tomorrow on another edition of the
source code and see you then.
Bye.
.
♪♪
♪♪♪♪
Power of the door is gone.