Before we get started, let me remind you of the following results or events predicted on these things,
may be very materialistic from actual results.
Doctors that could cause actual events or results to differ from expectations include
lack of growth, intense competition in our industry,
integration failures, changes in government regulations,
operational failures, or looking to take them to represent.
Alright, some of the volumes of today should not be relied upon as representing our
event of 2015. While we made the lives ofalone the same,
we need to not to disappear from that same process.
You are dressed in falls lá, adam curry!
How do you everybody? Welcome to your daily source code. Sorry to be second there. I forgot to turn on the microphone.
Everything's set up and forgot to turn on the power back. It's Friday.
And not just any Friday, my friends. It is Friday. November 5th, 2004. One day before the longer
coming to you almost live from Ricky's right high in lovely follow up with California.
This is your daily source code. I quite sure of everything I'm going to do today because I'm in my hotel room right now.
It's about a quarter to four. That's PM, Friday afternoon. And in three hours we have our welcome dinner and drink.
So what's in my shirt? If Dave and I were going to have a chance to do a train sequence before the drink looks like that's not going to happen.
He's busy. He's actually over at Stanford right now doing some last minute checks and talking to everybody and making sure everything's all set ready to roll.
So this is just going to be I think probably a relatively short podcast. I just want to talk about a few things. Obviously, I want to talk about blogger con.
It's going to be extremely cool tomorrow. I was over there earlier today with a four partner of mine. His name is Ron Bloom.
Who I invited to come out to blogger con because I think that it's time to get something together for all this wonderful podcast and that we're doing and see if we can.
I don't know start to start some some organized shit, which is always fun and I'm looking forward to meeting everybody who's coming.
I had a I think I said that in my podcast that I did for Thursday just did that last night.
Excuse me.
Is I had a great time listening to some extra podcast at about 14 hours lined up and I fell asleep on the plane of course. So, you know, I got all the information from the podcast but I can't quite recall it.
You know what went into the brain because it was registered. I guess it does.
When you're asleep, you know, you have headphones on, do you still register and remember everything that you're told?
You know, that is a subliminal thing and you know, what happens if you fall asleep when dawn and drew or talking about you, you know.
And boy, where they ever that was so cool to get this whole podcast, which is you know full of lies of course, but it was it was great.
It was awesome looking forward to meeting you guys. So, if you want to get a hold of me while you're out here.
I'm at the at Ricky's height. I'm online most of the time from the hotel room.
So, you can get me on Skype or on I chat or, you know, God forbid you send an email and maybe I'll get the reading it.
So, tonight is kind of just to get together. It's at Mings and 7 o'clock. It's going to have dinner there.
So, that's going to be extremely cool just to start everything off in a nice, you know, low key format.
And then tomorrow at, I guess, around 8 o'clock 830, we start with Dave's Fat Mountain of Bath tub as it or is National Anthem really to get everything started.
And at 9 o'clock is the session start and I'd love for you. Well, you know, if you already registered then you're at the session for pod casting.
There are a couple sessions running simultaneously. I'm saying I have the Cribsites Cribsites schedule here. Yeah, 815, the National Anthem starts.
It'll quarter to nine. Then from 9, 10, 15, I'll be in room 2, 9, 0.
And it's a boy to get there. They're, they look at blogger.org. There is a, under FAQs, there's a description directions on how to get to, to the Stanford Law School.
It took me a little while to figure out how to, you know, just to find campus drive.
But got that eventually and just went over there and checked it out. Real good vibe, real, real mellow out here, everything's really nice.
And actually, I'm sitting here in my room and I've got the, the screen, the screens open. Nice sunlight coming in.
The temperatures wonderful, particularly for a guy coming from the lowlands, the flat country, right?
It's where it's really nasty and rainy and cold this time of year.
I'm really hoping that one thing that we'll, you know, that we'll get kind of synced up on.
And as we'll have a plenty of chances to talk and, you know, if anyone wants to come over and hang out, just, you know, let me know, give me a call.
And that comes into my non-smoking room where I am smoking.
You know, I'm hoping that we can get some, some music shit started because I was just, you know, I wanted to fill up the show with a couple of songs and did find some stuff.
But we still need people to promote bands, you know, we need people who love a certain band and we'll promote it and we'll send all the podcasters, MP3s or links to MP3s and information and get some preclearance on the, you know, that we can play this stuff.
So if you're a fan of a particular band, you know, by all means start promoting it and do it methodically, just like the record promoters do in, you know, how the big boys do.
In fact, I was looking at a site that I was turned on to by, I'll tell you who I was turned on to it by.
It was Sam Levin, who's also going to be a blogger con.
And the site is magnitude.com.
Actually, let me copy that right now.
I'm going to put that into the source code notes.
So I'll put it just an extra note here.
So it's a non- or AA music.
And this is magnitude.com to put the links in there.
And I'll just read the opening bit of magnitude.com.
The story behind it because that really tells you a lot about the music industry and why all these independent sites are really important.
John Buckman is the founder.
I think a tune was born out of some observations I gathered about the music industry along with personal experiences from my wife, releasing her CD on a British record label, personal experience.
When my wife was signed to an indie record label, we were really excited.
In the end, she sold 1,000 CDs, lost all her rights to a music for seven years, even though the CD has been out of print for many years.
And earned her total of $137 in royalties paid, some of it paid to her CD copies of her own CD, which she then gave away for promotion.
The record label that signed her wasn't evil.
They were one of the good guys and gave her a 70, 30 split of the profits of which they were a few.
The label got screwed at every turn. Check this out.
Distributors refused to carry their CDs unless they spent thousands on useless print ads.
Record stores demanded graft in order to stock the albums.
And in general, all forces colluded to prevent this small progressive label from succeeding.
John goes on to talk about some industry observations.
Says radio is boring. Everyone I know is interesting music yet. Good music is rarely played on the air.
I mean, everything from ambient, industrial, Goth, metal to Renaissance, Baroque, Tango, Indian classical, and New Age.
And many other genres. And so many of my friends. Yet these genres are barely visible in record stores.
And totally absent from the airways.
Radio is mostly about country pop and rock, with a little bit of dull, safe classical music thrown in.
Well, dude, this is the perfect opportunity. There you go.
We have radio stations. We have podcasts. We have shows. And you've got to work it just like you worked it.
Now, we don't need graft. We don't need gifts and advertising.
Just help us find it. Send it to us. You know, promote it.
And actually, you should read the whole thing here.
This is it's linked from what is it.
So, magnitude.com and just go to why I created Magnitude.
It's the second link on the left hand side.
And there's it's just good. And it shows you what's so difficult.
And it's a real good guide actually to, you know, how we can make this better.
And each of the songs has a little license next to it.
And you can see what the license is and what you can actually take care of the license right on the spot.
So it's perfect. It's absolutely wonderful.
But I don't have the time to go and download all this stuff and listen to all the songs.
Yeah, there's categories. But what I want is, I want you to tell me.
You know, please send this to me at amercurry.com.
I did run across something really fun, though, which I've no idea who made it.
So I'm hoping that I'm not infringing on any copyrights.
I don't think it's copyrighted, but well, what the hell?
It's well worth it. This is Rick Lyon, Stephanie DeBruzo,
from the album Avenue Q, at least that's the way it shows up in the metadata.
Please enjoy the internet is for porn.
Finally, I get to teach a whole lesson all by myself.
And I'm gonna teach something relevant, something modern.
The internet.
The internet is really, really great.
For porn.
I've got a fast connection, so I don't have to waste.
There's always some new sites.
For porn.
It's like I'm surfing at the speed of light.
The internet is for porn.
I'm doing it.
Why do you think the internet is for porn porn porn porn?
Tracking.
Hello, kid monster.
You are ruining my song.
Oh, miss sorry. You know me too.
Well, if you wouldn't mind, please be quiet for a minute, so I can finish.
Good.
I'm glad we have this new technology.
For porn.
Which gives us untold opportunity.
For porn. Oh, sorry.
Come your own desktop.
You can research, browse, and shop.
Until you've had enough, then you're ready to stop.
For porn.
The internet is for porn.
If me upon my hugging me, porn, you porn porn.
That's gross.
You're a pervert.
Ah, sticks and stones, kid monster.
No, really. You're a pervert.
Normal people don't sit at home and look at porn on the internet.
Oh.
What?
You have no idea.
Ready, normal people?
Ready.
Let me hear it.
The internet is for porn.
Sorry, Kate.
My masterpiece.
All these guys unzip their flies for porn porn.
The internet is not for porn.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Stones, kid monster.
No, really. You're a pervert.
Normal people don't sit at home and look at porn on the internet.
Oh.
What?
You have no idea.
Ready, normal people? Ready.
Ready.
Let me hear it.
The internet is for porn.
Sorry, Kate.
My masterpiece.
All these guys unzip their flies for porn.
The internet is not for porn.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wow.
Now I happen to know for a fact that you,
road, check your portfolio,
and trade stocks online.
That's correct.
And Brian, you buy things on Amazon.com.
Sure.
And Gary, you keep selling your possessions on eBay.
Yes, I do.
And Princeton, you sent me that sweet online birthday card.
True.
Oh, but Kate, what do you think you do after?
Yeah.
The internet is for porn.
Ready.
Drive your dick and double click for porn porn porn.
My internet is for porn.
Yeah.
Yeah, everybody.
That's what it's for.
Of course, we need an updated version now with podcasting in there.
But yep, always dreamed of creating the JOP.
What does that you think?
One of the jerk off platform, of course.
Good news for you.
My potter fans out there just in time for blogger con 3, the iPod or lemon team has released
the 1.1 version, actually got an email here.
Hold on.
Let me read that to you.
So it's released for Windows and for Macintosh.
Some of the features, it's like podcast feeds by using the integrated directories.
So it's the opml directory from iPod.org.
It's working.
Ads feeds manually or from the GUI, choose your own download folder.
The feed list displays title, location, download, megabytes and subscription state for
each feed.
Excellent.
And hands download progress feedback.
Don't want to check all the feeds.
You can just check one feed.
It can run it startup, advance options for power users, automatic setting of grouping
podcast for iTunes.
Windows users, extra debugging code.
Well, I don't know what debugging code is all about.
Don't need that, I guess.
Well, I might, but you might.
I'll also let you know, well, oh, okay, let's, you know what, what goes wrong if a download
fails.
And you can grab your copy of iPod.
1.1.
That's the lemon team.
From iPodter.sourceforge.net.
iPodter.sourceforge.net.
Excellent, guys.
Congratulations on your release.
I haven't downloaded it myself yet.
Since I'm, well, I'm trying to help out with the conference here.
I will definitely do that tonight.
Looking forward to it.
I'm going to play a little bit of a new podcast that came out.
Just want you to be up to speed on it.
It came through openpodcast.org.
It's listed as openpodcast.org.
Number 76.
If you want to go find that.
It's a new show called Random Baggage.
This Friday, October 29th.
It's a little overwhelming.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to my very first podcast.
Broadcasting.
Almost life on Toronto.
That's flatline.
That's really loud.
So you're looking for a good rock show with lots of cool music.
Definitely check out Random Baggage.
That was a little bit too overmodulated to play.
And by the way, people have also told me that my levels are off here and there.
And it's true.
You know, we're still trying to straighten out all the stuff we used to podcast and hopefully
during the podcasting session tomorrow.
We can share some ideas and come up with some cool ways to do this.
This, I'm certainly not using the most ideal set up.
It's not really easy to monitor.
Although during the internet is porn, so I'm all of a sudden.
My monitor fell out the headphones.
That's because the battery was dead on the yep.
So that was a, you know, that's the kind of stuff you need.
Although I, it should have like beeped at me and told me you've got like 30 seconds to go and
I could have paused it or done something like that.
So I had to start a new recording, but I'll just meld the two files together later
before I can press it and put it up on the server.
So, you know, it's not not the most ideal way.
And it's, you really only know if it's working.
If you, you know, if you test something and listen back to your file and see how it sounds.
And so oftentimes when Mike is too soft in the sound, you know, the clips are too loud.
And really it's just a metering issue.
You know, if I had some good meters, then I could probably probably do a little bit better with that.
So working on all that stuff and I came across an awesome podcast, which I'd heard about.
And I heard one of the earlier shows, but it didn't, I heard this one on the plane.
It didn't hit me until I heard this show just how incredibly, well, I thought this is amazing.
If you've ever wondered, you know, how women talk about sex, it's not like sex in the city.
By the way, I think that show was written by mainly gay guys.
I've been told that I don't know if it's true.
But the super smart radio horse sex show definitely talks about sex.
And you can hear girls talking about sex.
But kind of the way guys talk about sex.
Well, let me, I'll let you listen to a little bit of this particular episode,
which is the October 29th version.
It's very informative.
Hello, hello.
This is Cody Shenz, super smart radio horror of the super smart radio horse sex show.
And this is episode, I don't know, like, four show four.
And today's topic is how to have sex.
And I have a barrack, but here was a ray.
But before I get to all that, I want to say a couple of thank yous.
Thank you to everyone who is listening and telling your fucking friends because it's showing.
Tech idea tells me that more and more people are listening to me every day.
And I'm really overwhelmed by how many people are paying attention to me.
It's pretty amazing.
It's a special thank you to everybody who writes me emails because...
Okay, okay, okay, get to the table.
You know, then that's a good question.
And that's a good question for me.
Okay, where's your guest?
And then from the wiff.
Come on, baby.
Here we go.
If you can hear that, that's the special guest.
Giggling there with me.
Oh, just say hi now, where's he right?
Oh, okay, Cody, hi.
Okay, Cody here, last and away.
When we just, yeah, yeah, whiffle houseboys are right now, so.
And oh, and I even had some people offered to come be experts on the show.
So it just makes me feel like people think I'm friendly,
which really can tell you right now, I am very friendly.
Very friendly.
I got many stories on her friendlyness.
Only some of them were true.
So I think the news is that of a new website.
Oh, man.
Very wink a little bit.
I thought that it started immediately with the topic of the day.
I don't apologize.
I'm putting you through this.
Who designed the site?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
I think to it over time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
So, let's see.
Today's topic.
How to score in a bar.
And the expert we have today, you water heard a little bit from her,
is Rosie Ray.
And she's quite the bar expert.
I mean, that in a really good way.
Oh, no, I take it as complimented.
Yeah, like for real quick way.
No doubt.
And you know, I ain't judging.
Oh, no.
You look friends for a long time, baby.
Yeah, that.
Me and Rosie have been friends for a really long time.
And I just, I feel like she knows the ins and outs of the pick-up scene.
She is a really super cute thick Latina girl here in the Bay Area where we both live.
And I think that she has a lot, she has a lot to say that you can learn from.
So, I'm just, Rosie, I think that people listening to the show are going to be like,
what qualifies this girl to be a bar expert?
Yes.
What qualifies this girl?
Why don't you impress us a little bit with you around?
Just Latina girl.
With my fascinating stories.
Bar, bar history.
Bar history.
Why you're an expert before we get to the show?
Now, I should say at this point, this podcast is not safe for work and not safe for
on the kids.
So, put your headphones on.
The story.
Why am I?
Why am I bar expert by Rosie Ray?
All right.
Well, kids, let's go back to a time.
Where it was 2001 and Rosie Ray was just becoming a legal age.
And within that time, there was a good amount of years.
I guess two present times.
Where I definitely explore the San Francisco bar scene.
Definitely, I really, really love.
Two boxes are ultimately important.
When it comes to what bar to pick up that for me anyway.
Even though you're only getting weighed, but the music definitely.
Now, remind you, this is girls talking about how to get picked up.
So, this is good intel for guys who are crews.
Please help.
No doubt.
So, I've been definitely bar hopping for the last four years.
And I also just want to inform a quick note here that, of course,
nobody on the Supercellula.
Supercellula, radio-horosexual.
Nor anyone affiliated with the Supercellula radio-horosexual condones under age drinking.
Oh, yeah.
However, cause the rage did not start the bar scene at age 21.
Girlfriend by 21 was like, I've been to all of them.
That's okay, that's okay.
You know, you know, there's a true fucking nice, a true story.
By the time I turned 21, I was over it.
Yeah, honest, I was just like, wow, so it's legal.
It's okay, so that's a set up right now.
Now, I'm just going to needle drop, because it's an hour long show.
Needle drop into some tips.
When a year ago.
Anyway, so, you know, I'm in like, like, the me high hook or boots, the fish nets,
the really short skirt, the like, boobs greased together,
make up whole mind, like, clearly I'm a girl, I'm just getting laid.
I'm using all the cheap tricks.
I caught to that.
Yeah.
I show leg.
I show ass.
I should hit.
But, you know what?
Sometimes, like, you do all that, and it's still not happening.
So, you know, what can I say?
Yeah.
But, so, I'm really ready to just be like the first guy who's not, like, sexually harassing me.
I'll go home with.
Boy, no.
And so, this really cute guy I'm in the bar.
You know, this really cute guy is like, hey, how's it going?
But, you know what?
He was so raging drunk.
He was like, he was so drunk that I wasn't sure if I fucked him, if it would be paid rate.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like, anyone with any sense isn't going to fuck someone who's like, almost passed out drunk.
And so, I really feel like this guy would have gotten laid.
He would have gotten laid a couple times.
I'm sure.
If he hadn't have been so pissed drunk, I mean, he was like six in, you know?
And I really feel like, if you're going to go out and get laid,
I think you should be sober enough to be positive
that you're going to remember getting laid.
We take a notes here, guys.
No, definitely.
Remember Cody, that's for sure.
Yeah, you got it.
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, slightly buzzed and picking up on a woman.
I think that's good.
But, really just like, stumbling, floppy drunk.
I don't know, man.
The Super SMART radio or sex show.
You've got to check it out.
You can find it through the podcast directory at ipodder.org.
This is Dr. Webgopea.org.
11.02.
Hey, does anyone know what Adam Curry's favorite website is?
W.W.
Dot.
Dot net.
You suck.
Thank you.
And good night.
Thank you very much, people.
No, I drew John because we're going together on that one.
Time for some more music.
This one's from my buddies from Holland, so you won't understand.
One fuck about what they're saying.
But, they're good.
From their 9th album, this is Larry of Flicker.
Yo, thinking to food abuse.
I don't know what you're saying.
Oh, fuck off stuff out and out of her
Oh, fucker the life maker
I will let you away
You go, Oh, ah oh, ah oh...
Oh, oh, ah oh, ah oh yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes get my believe."
I'm a fan of you, I'm a fan of you, I'm a fan of you.
You don't think any of the food or beetles, that's the name of the band.
Love your flicker, which basically means lazy mother fucker.
Some great non-RIAA music for you.
They released it on their own label on their Yovink records, which is just awesome.
Those guys are from a part of the Netherlands, which is still the old old country,
where they love rock and roll.
They kind of like the Hillbillies of Holland.
Just snuggled up there in a little corner of Holland, which is very close to Germany.
If you haven't heard it, I've promoted a couple of times on the source code.
You must check out Russell Holland's trio podcast, mobilepodcast.org.
He's doing something really interesting. He's using a trio, a trio, a trio.
One of those handheld phone, computer, organizer, type thingies,
which is looking like it's an interesting device.
And you should check it out because he's mixing in music and files,
and he's doing some cool stuff with it.
And I like the slogan for the show. It's the podcast from the Palm Air Hand.
You were listening to a special post-election edition of the trio podcast.
www.mobilepodcast.org.
My name is Russell Holland, podcasting from the palm of my hand.
The city is headed for a disaster of biblical proportion.
What do you mean, biblical?
What do you mean, this old testament to the air mayor, real wrath of god-type stuff?
Fire and brimstone coming down from the sky.
Rivers and seas boiling.
40 years of darkness earthquakes volcano.
The dead rise in from the grave.
Human sacrifice, dogs and cats, living together, mass hysteria.
Well, that's certainly how I felt on Monday.
All right. So you get the idea, mobilepodcast.org.
Podcasting from the palm of his hand.
And he's starting those bits. He's doing it all live.
So it's extremely cool. And of course, he can make phone calls and get people on at the same time.
And it's, I think it has Wi-Fi and it's so definitely check that out.
I'm going to leave it for the source code for today, because we're having
done about 30 minutes, which is short, but there will be more.
You know there's going to be lots of podcasts happening.
So I'm already paying attention to what's coming in over the wire and downloading stuff.
I potter running for some crunching everybody's bandwidth.
It's the high end, the riot, the high end.
Ricky's high end.
In lovely part about to California.
So I'll probably do another podcast by this evening,
who knows me with some guests.
We might even do a trade secret.
It's all depends. We're going to play it by here.
And look for other podcasts.
Popping up live from vlogger.com.
Let's get in for a good diversity.
Let's get to the show for now for Friday.
November 5th, 2004.
The early edition.
If you want to send me a comment for your band or your favorite band.
Music, please email me at amercurator.com
or leave a comment at live.curator.com
and of course you can get all the shows at dating sources.
I'll see you all later from the high end. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.