Hi everybody, welcome to the Source Code. I'm Adam Curry and good evening from
It's 9.30 p.m. on, what are we at?
Tuesday already, the 14th of September, 2004.
Of course, I want to welcome you if you're downloading this from live.curry.com.
You might be subscribing, you can find all the archives and of course ways to subscribe
or just download Daily from DailySourceCode.com.
This is the place where you use this.
and had a lot of
yesterday. First of all, what I want to get to is I'm going to let you hear a little excerpt
from a special morning coffee notes that Dave Weiner did in Seattle probably, well, depending
on your viewpoint, even way after his morning coffee or only five or six hours before his
next morning coffee. And this was about what we were talking yesterday, where I was wondering
what all this geeky stuff is I'm hearing about ways to mount Gmail as a file system,
use Gmail as an interface for a web blog, you know, you mail something to your Gmail account.
And my question was, is Gmail doing something special?
There's some special APIs that I don't know about,
or what's going on?
It turns out, and Dave's going to explain this,
and I want to let you hear a good portion of how we responded,
which was great, because I don't think I could have
understood it if it was just written,
is that there really is no special API.
In fact, it's using stuff that's been around for a long,
long time, only apparently it's never really been
interesting enough to use a free service until Gmail came
along, which means there's a whole gigabyte.
And with a gigabyte, arguably, that's
something you want to use as a resource,
but not necessarily for email.
You could use it to serve files from or create a web log.
So Dave actually gave a little explanation
about the APIs and how it works and what Google is
or isn't doing, but what developers are doing.
So check this out.
I just wanted to comment on one.
One of the things that Adam talked about is that Gmail and whether there were more APIs
in there or not.
What's really cool about what's going on with Gmail is that email is an API.
It's a very simple one.
It allows you to...
It's basically a flat directory of documents with enclosures.
The body of the message and the title of the message can serve as metadata.
So can the sender of the message could be thought of as the creator of the document.
Unix has a driver structure.
On the one hand, email either simply or pop is a good API.
Unix has an API for the file system and in fact, so does Windows.
And it allows you to put in drivers that basically do for the operating system the basic operations of creating a file, deleting a file, adding some text to the file, reading some text from a file or data from a file.
And there are a few more operations, but not that many.
Also operations that change the metadata, the data associated with files, the creation date, modification date.
And the Macintosh you have a resource for.
I'm not sure if they have that anymore actually with OS 10 being a unit file system.
So in any case, Google didn't do anything new. They just supported an existing API that's very broadly understood and it's called Electronic Mail.
And that's the beauty of these formats and protocols.
They make.
both kinds of things possible. And the lowest common denominator, I mean Adam, you would
absolutely, I think you would love, you know, how simple these protocols are. They are,
they're all texts for us.
My thanks to, my thanks to Dave Weiner for explaining that. And of course I did look
into the world. I'm pretty sure.
having seen it before on the Unix command line.
And now I understand exactly what they're doing.
And that's why my conclusion is that it's really this one
gigabyte of free disk space that people are building
applications around.
That could be interesting to see where that takes us with
Google in the future.
And also it kind of blew my mind that here we are creating
technology or implementing technology.
And we're basically doing the same thing over and over and
over again.
It's email or whether it's an iTunes, the way we're using
it now with iPodder to look for new stuff that has arrived.
Or even a weblog.
It's all kind of the basic structure.
And now I'm also starting to understand outliners a little
bit better, at least what they can be used for and how
fantastic they really are.
Couple of other things I want to talk about.
And I will talk more about some technology stuff based
upon things that have been flying back and forth on the
iPod.
But today, as I check my download directory,
I have on a server, I have a small program called Nucleus.
And you can just Google it.
You'll Google it with my name, and you'll find a link to it.
And Nucleus is a little Python script that runs.
I have it running on OS X server, which is sitting
at my data center.
And it pulls an RSS feed from Supernova,
which has bit torrents.
And if it finds anything that matches a number of keywords
that I've put in there, it'll automatically download the bit
torrent file and then start up the download of the actual file.
And it'll, it notifies me of something new has come in.
And I have keywords in it like David Letterman, Leno.
I think I've discussed this before.
Had all kinds of different keywords, some MTV stuff
like Pimp for Pimp My Ride.
That also picks up some interesting other torrents.
And I have Michael Moore.
in there as a keyword because I'm always interested in seeing what he has to say and he's been
on different talk shows. And what that did for me is, lo and behold, I wound up this
morning with a full Divix copy of Fahrenheit 9-11, which I hadn't seen yet. So I spent
some time watching that today. And now I've heard all different kinds of reviews and
different thoughts about this. First of all, I was a little disappointed. I thought
I was, you know, this is going to be some amazing editing job. And, you know,
anyone could have done this on Final Cut Pro and most of it was existing
footage. What I don't like, although I think, you know, it's great when you see
the footage that never airs, you know, when people are being made up, when
people are getting ready for camera to go on, particularly people that you only
see when the camera goes on. I love all that footage, which is also just
obtained from newsreels, news footage. I hate it, though, when, you know, there's
all this manipulation of...
It's editing all different types of sound bites and bits together for effect with music
that is either dramatic.
You know don't really need I just didn't need that part
Yeah, that that was the part of the end like a little bit of entertainment show that I
credited what Michael Moore is trying to do with this documentary. Just as a minor example,
is when he talks about the coalition of the willing, which is the United States preparing
to go into Iraq and we have a coalition of foreign countries that are going to help
us out. And then it's like one after another, it's like Morocco and all these countries
that's made out not to matter. And the Netherlands also passes by. And when they're talking about
the Netherlands in the movie, you see not a soldier, but you see someone just leaning forward,
lighting up a hash pipe. And you know, which is funny because I understand what's trying
to be said there. However, having visited with the Dutch Marines in Asimallah in Iraq,
having lived with them for 10 days, doing a live broadcast, it felt a little shitty because
I know those guys were there doing what they were doing.
were asked to do and they were very serious about their part of
contributing to rebuilding Iraq and this to me certainly having been there I
found a little bit demoralizing and it immediately gave me the feeling that you
know like hey even you know talking as a as a even though I have a US passport for
a second talking as a European like you know fuck you Michael Moore you know
we're two guys two of our guys died there and you know no one wrote about
that in the American press you know we're not just a bunch of hash smoking
hippies you know we're pretty serious no way man I am a hash smoking hippie
anyway so I want to play a little bit I think this is probably the most important
bit from this from this movie if you haven't seen it it'll just be a quick
refresher where 9-11 has happened and everyone knows that Osama bin Laden has
claimed this we have to go after Osama bin Laden he's in Afghanistan we send 11,000
troops which turns out to be less than our police officers in Manhattan
And this is when the switch comes, when all of a sudden the administration started talking about Iraq and we got to go to Iraq and Iraq.
I'll just stop this after a certain point.
I don't want to play too much of it.
But this starts off with Richard Clark.
He's on, I guess, Good Morning America, and Charlie Gibbons is interviewing him.
And I'll let it play from there.
Just so you can hear, this is the moment where the administration switched and where all
the bullshit started as far as I'm concerned for us to invade Iraq.
You come in September 12, ready to plot what response we take to al-Qaeda.
Let me talk to the, about the response that you got from top administration
officials on that day.
What did the president say to you?
The president in a very intimidating way left us, me and my staff, with the clear
indication that he wanted us to come back with a word that there was an Iraqi hand
behind 9-11 because they had been planning to do something about Iraq from
before the time they came into office.
Did he ask about any other nations other than Iraq?
No, no, no.
No, not at all.
It was Iraq, Saddam, find out, get back to me.
And were his questions more about Iraq than about al-Qaeda?
Absolutely, absolutely.
He didn't ask me about it.
And the reaction you got that day from the Defense Secretary, Donald Rumsfeld, from his
assistant, Paul Woltholst.
Well, Donald Rumsfeld said when we talked about bombing the Al Qaeda infrastructure in Afghanistan,
he said there were no good targets in Afghanistan.
Let's bomb Iraq.
And we said, but Iraq had nothing to do with this.
And that didn't seem to make much difference.
And the reason they had to do Afghanistan first was it was obvious that Al Qaeda had
attacked us.
And it was obvious that Al Qaeda was in Afghanistan.
The American people wouldn't have stood by if we had done nothing on Afghanistan.
OK, so here's one of those bits that I said that I really disliked where they're doing
a whole Bonanza montage, although very funny.
Let me just stop that, although very funny, totally unnecessary.
You know, just make a documentary and let the funny bits be the irony of the subjects
of the documentary themselves.
That's the way I think it should be.
Anyway, moving along.
It was kind of depressing actually to watch that.
But Patricia came home, she was in Amsterdam.
preparing for a big fashion show this coming Sunday she's designed all the
makeup for the models and
and she said man you're really quiet and I have actually told her that I have it all
queued up and loaded on the
on the show server play out system on the big screen in the living room if she
wants to watch it because it did bump me on a little bit
uh... let's see from the mail bag I got a nice email from Doug Kay he's running
IT conversation
Actually, I'm going to go to the site right now.
Yesterday, I was complaining that I couldn't get my fix of the Gilmore Gang and actually
started tweaking my aggregator thinking that was the problem.
He sent a Mia Culpa email saying there wasn't a Gilmore Gang.
He should have posted a note and he was going to do it ASAP and I'm just checking the
site now and there's no note still.
But that's what happened.
Hopefully Gilmore Gang will be back this coming Friday.
I look forward to it because it is one of my favorite programs that I got on the iPod.
Now I started up the mailing list for the iPod developers which of course is
anything but exclusively for developers.
of introductions.
and I have a link to the email list.
Anyone can join, please feel free to.
It's great to see all these different developers
and users talking to each other.
They've all got different ideas, functionality,
things that they're changing code.
For instance, I'll just read one of these emails,
quickly just the introduction.
My name's Jonathan Green, while I'm not a developer,
I'm an active user and thought out track
what's going on with developments in iPodder.
And the first thing he says,
this is great as a user.
He says, you know, still there's, you know,
there's a lot of trouble with setting up
the schedule of iPodder so that it runs automatically.
And this is indeed, and there's been a couple more releases
of stuff, this is still not completely done.
I think that what I'd like, just speaking
from a Mac user perspective, is just giving one
of those disc images that opens up, you know,
so it looks like I'm installing something serious.
I don't want to know about script.
And this should be maybe just an Apple script.
And you double click on that.
It stalls everything.
You could make it call a crontab command line call
and add a line to it.
It should be relatively simple.
And that's really what the users are looking for.
I just want to put it in.
I want to be able to forget about it.
Let's see.
We got another email here from Pete who wrote Renko.
Another enclosure extractor.
Why don't I have this email here?
Now, he's more a developer also talking about cront jobs
and how do we get stuff set up.
And he was thinking, why don't we connect it to the iCal?
I think that the iPodder is something
that we want no glory on this.
We just want to install and run and for people
to forget about it.
There's this.
Anything else would be too much.
And you can add features to it and do all kinds.
of stuff but I think it has to be kept as simple as possible.
And the another interesting email that came through on the list is from Martin Fenroy.
He is a part of the iSpider team and iSpider is a Python version of iPodder and they've
got it set up at SourceForge.
So the URL is iSpider.SourceForge.net and they've got a great homepage, they've got a logo, they've
got it all set up.
And I actually ran this version and although it hasn't installed script which installs everything
in the right place on Mac, you know, just give me please guys give me an Apple script to
double click on.
They've got some really cool additional features in this which are cool features though I
don't know if I necessarily agree with them.
First of all it's very elegant in the way it sets everything up and the way it moves stuff
over to iPodder.
It also runs on multiple platforms and by the time you're listening to this it should
also do Windows Media Play.
it works with iTunes and with Windows Media Player and since it's Python it's cross-platform.
But it does something else. It also has a screen scraper in there. This I thought was, at first
I thought it was really cool because you can add a URL to an RSS 2.0 file with enclosures
and it'll grab everything from that and place it accordingly in the playlist. Or you can
just give it a URL and it'll scrape the HTML code and any MP3 file it encounters it'll
download. And it's funny because I tried it out. I tried it out on, you know, I wanted to do something that would only have one or two files on it of not very large size.
And so I did scripting.com because I knew that Dave had his morning coffee notes, just a four minute version on there, which I let you hit a little excerpt earlier.
But what it also did is it came across a link to SourceForge from yesterday and said, oh, you know, here's an MP3 file.
So it brought that one in as well, which could be a little bit confusing.
Particularly on which playlist it has to go to, although in that particular case everything worked out fine.
But it's an excellent version of iPodder and I see a lot happening with that.
So iSpider.sourceforgedor.net and I'll also be adding that to the download directory.
Okay, so much for the mailing list.
See, ran across, oh this was actually because of iSpider.
They had a couple additional feeds in their, what they're calling the favorites list,
which is basically the subscriptions that you download.
And one of the sites which doesn't have an RSS 2.0 feed but does have a daily audio blog
is called Lenswork.com, L-E-N-S as in camera lens.
And it's a guy named Brooke Johnson who sells his photography and he has some beautiful
pictures.
But what he's doing in addition to that is he's maintaining a web blog and he's kind
of helping people out by talking along with different tips on photography, which
I think is a great way to, you know, to, I think it's, it's really, it's a good
addition to what he's trying to get across this message with his photography
and the fact that he wants you to pay like $99 for a print.
And here's one of these blog posts.
I'll just let you hear a little bit of it.
I also think he has a great voice for this and the quality is just good.
I think it's something that is worth looking at.
This is an audio blog post titled Toys or Tools.
One of the consumers.
The most consistent themes that's come up in my recent conversations with photographers about their equipment choices
is the challenge that they have in taking digital photography seriously.
Admittedly, because of my personal history in photography, a lot of my friends are large format photographers.
They're shooting 4x5s and 8x10 cameras.
And these are cameras that it's pretty easy to take seriously.
They're expensive, there's a lot of gadgets that have to be employed in order to use them successfully.
It's expensive to shoot sheet film, etc.
And somehow when these people pick up a digital camera, it just feels like a toy to them.
Everything is automatic, focus is automatic, exposure is automatic, bracketing is automatic.
There's no film costs. They don't have to develop the film when they get home.
It just doesn't feel like a serious tool.
But yet, those people who are using these tools in a serious way are realizing that...
that they can do some very nice photographs
and some really interesting artwork.
That leads me to think that when it comes to tools, it's not the nature of the tool
that determines whether or not it's a serious tool.
It's the nature of the photographer's mind.
If we approach the use of a tool in a serious way, if we approach it with a certain amount
of creativity, reverence, respect for what it can do, then it can be a serious tool.
But if you insist that a toy is merely a toy and you don't approach it carefully
and thoughtfully and deliberately, then a toy will be a toy and the results will be likewise.
So that's something that all, everyone who works at a big co-publisher or media company
should listen to that at least twice a day.
Because yeah, it's about the effort you put into these toys, but we're doing a lot of cool stuff.
We've got web logs for publishing, we've got desks.
top publishing. We've got Final Cut Pro for video, we've got all types of different software
packages for audio, although not quite the one I'm looking for yet, but we're getting
there. That's Brooks Jensen. You can check out a new audio blog post. Looks like he's
doing them every single day at LensWork.com. Just a couple more things and I have a song
of the day for you. Still working on this new show that I want to launch.
this week or certainly beginning of next week for sure.
On the technology front, remember now what I want to do is I want to connect other people
over voice over IP so that I can have a conversation with them.
Very much like the Gilmore Gang I guess, only, you know, talk about different things and
maybe only start off with one co-host.
But I don't want to have to resort to using a telephone and patching that into my computer.
I should just be able to bring in a voice over IP call.
That works only what I'm trying to figure out now is how do I route audio both to
the recording side of recording a session on my laptop, excuse me, and also to the
voice over IP client and I think I'm going to use iChat AV.
I figured out that because for some miraculous reason Macintosh has something
called core audio which you can do all kinds of interesting things with and
there are a couple different programs I found we can actually patch the output
of one application to the input of another application.
But it doesn't really work with, for instance, quick time, because that doesn't have a preference
setting for choosing the core audio drive or, you know, I'm probably digressing way too
far on this.
But I'm getting close, because, you know, the final thing is if I play a clip, I want
the person on the other end or persons on the other end of the voiceover IP call, I
want them to be able to hear what I'm sending down the pipe or, you know, what's being
recorded.
I actually got pretty far.
I was able to patch everything together, but then wiretap, which I'm using as the
recording device for all the audio, fails to work when you're patching audio through
with different applications.
So there's some conflict there.
So I'm still working on that.
But hopefully I'll be able to get something up and running within the next
couple of days.
And the song that I found, I can't remember if I found this on BlogDigger or
how I came about it.
But it's a typical, you know, internet kind of spoofie, funny song.
And it's a song of the time.
and I think you'll like it. It's called my JPEG baby.
GAME BACK! GAME BACK BABY! I REMEMBER WHEN I first came and I LOWED!
Shake back, shake back
and that's it for the source code for today as always if you want to leave a comment do
that on the web blog at curry.com or send me an email.
And you can subscribe to the show by going to dailysourcecode.com where you can find all the archives
The power of your influence.