This is Eric from AirCris.com and you're listening to the daily source code with Adam Curry.
Hey how about that for us?
If he started, everybody whoops, welcome to the daily source code.
I'm Adam Curry.
It is October 13th. It's a Wednesday, 2004.
And once again, we're bringing you the best Belgium has to offer.
How are you?
I'm coming to you from Curry Castle in Flanders, Belgium.
It's been another busy morning. I've been working on the directory.
I potted out org man, there's so many podcasts coming out.
Let's see in this show today, we'll be going through some usual comedy stuff.
We'll be talking about OPML directories, which is something that even if you aren't
non-a-geek and not a nerd and not a technology, you'll really like because we've got about six
non-nurdy, non-GET people working with this right now.
If you're in the information and linking, then this is completely for you.
So stay tuned for that.
We also have a couple of bits from Koma 1000, who of course are podcasting all of
there or not all of a lot of their news items.
Let's see a new podcast that we're going to talk about.
Also Chris Perillo about the whole terminology podcasting.
And of course, just a little bit of political stuff.
And also backed by very popular demand and requests.
I'm not going to tell you what it was.
If you remember me playing it on the source code, I've got another one by Durewood
Do-Shay for you.
Stay tuned for that.
So probably by an hour's worth.
It's the source code for Wednesday.
Let's get it cranked.
Let's put some power into this podcast with Ram Jam's Black Betty.
We're back, Betty.
Betty, back, Betty.
You turned Ram Jam into a big, one hit wonder.
It's actually a lead belly original.
I found out just recently.
I was going to play that for you.
play that for you. I had it stored somewhere in a playlist, almost like, let me move
my phone a little bit. There we go. Oops. Sorry. Now, alright. Okay, that should sound
a bit better. Yeah, I had a, I had led Billy actually performing that. If you don't know
who led Billy is, I first heard about him on one of those rock and roll hall-of-famed
dinners where, you know, all the running stones and, you know, feel specter and, and the
kings and Bruce Springsteen and there's all these rock and roll grades come to honor each other
and they're all wearing tuxedos. It was really funny. And it's $1,000 or played dinner
if you can get in and, and all these guys like Keith Richards and Ron Wood and all the, you know,
little Steven and all these guitar grades would all say, you know, led Billy really turned
me on to rock and roll and was all led Billy's influence. That's just really old, I'm sure
he's, he doesn't. He's not alive anymore, I'm sure, but of course he was inducted into the rock
hall of fame and I actually came across a track of him singing Black Betty. It sounded very
different, but you, you know, just, you'd never think that that would later become, it was
a pretty big hit in the 70s. Okay, so this is your daily source code. Well, let me just
reset everything there. Okay, using this sound flower plug-in so I can monitor my own voice
and sometimes it, it, the buffer kind of overstreams or something or gets filled up and then
I start to hear myself with the delay in the headphones, not very cool. Something I didn't
talk about on previous source codes, of course, yesterday wasn't a source code. I had everything
all cut up and I saw the Dave was awake at like five a.m. Seattle time and I was just about
ready to record, I said, well dude, why don't we just, you know, we hadn't spoken a couple of days.
So why don't we just do our rap and we'll record a show and then we had an opening of a new
grandmaster view store about 45 minutes drive and I had to be there on seven, shut up around
730 because I had to eat and you know, so I just didn't really have time to do a source code
release, there was some audio that went out yesterday. So I didn't get to talk about Christopher
Reeve passing away and this is sad, you know, when you think about, it was 1995 when he fell off
his horse. A grant he was doing some pretty high like steeple chase height jumping and that
put him in the hospital and made him quadriplegic and he's been a big proponent of stem cell
research because there certainly is hope that the condition that he had, that there was some help for
that or some fix for that if we can do more research, well, you probably know all about that debate.
And then all of a sudden, man, it's just like boom, you know, you read and actually the newspaper
has always been printed here. So it didn't really hit the newspapers here. It was at Monday because
he died Sunday night and the papers here had already printed from Monday, but it saw it online around
eight o'clock in the morning and it was like, wow, you know, and he had a heart attack and slips
into a coma, it's just sucks. So, but of course, you can trust the web to, you know, to be thinking
about about Christopher Reeve and, you know, just, whereas I used to look maybe five, six years ago,
I used to look in the morning at my email inbox and say, you know, what goodies has it brought
for me today? These days I go to my playlist in iTunes or on my iPod and to see what goodies
the web has brought for me and this is one that showed up.
Christopher Reeve, definitely this superman of my generation. All right, looking at some email
sent to the daily source code, by the way, I'm printing these out now because my screen is so full
with player windows and all this stuff that I have queued up for you and I don't want to run
as few applications as possible to make sure that we don't get any skipping in the recording.
This is from Benjamin Walker, he says he, you know, he likes listening to the source code.
This is a public radio producer in Boston, just started a new show called The Theory of Everything,
which also airs in San Francisco on KL, KALW and also also work for the Berkman Center,
which is Harvard Law and Creative Commons. Now he said, he said, I figured out the podcast
and thing all of my own, the enclosure part was easy. The changing the dot RDF to the dot XML part
was very, very hard because all you smart folks have forgotten that there are clueless people
like me out there and all the how-to sites left this out because it was obvious or something.
Yes. And believe me, Benjamin, there are lots of geeks who do this stuff who are listening
and everyone's trying to do better. So it goes on to him so excited about the invention,
cannot tell him which is who will mean the next generation of pub. Oh, this is actually,
I shouldn't mumble over this. I'm actually all caps. I am so excited about your invention.
I cannot tell you how much this tool will mean to the next generation of public radio producers
who want to find a way to connect with listeners without being tethered to the out-of-touch stations
themselves. Excellent. Excellent. And we already have morning stories from MPR Tony Khan,
which is already officially sanctioned as up and running as a podcast. So here he has a question.
I got myself a 20 gig a month web hosting plan at the beginning of the month. I figured it would
be more than enough. Of course, he's already started his podcast, which you can find in the iPod
podcast directory. Yesterday, he says, the traffic was already at 7 gigs. Today, it's up to 14.
I'm wondering if the podcast in community is growing this fast or if it's a matter of people
trying out the different software and doubting the downloading the same stuff repeatedly.
I only have 45 megs up total right now. Don't want to piss off my new hosting provider in the
first month. Thanks for your time. Benjamin Walker. Benjamin, you hit on something that happened to me
yesterday as well. I was just about to hop on the phone with a couple of people actually a
Doug K from IT conversations. When I got a call from the CEO of, I think it's either
Tiskly, the Netherlands or Tiskly Europe. It could be Tiskly Europe. He was a Dutchman no matter what.
Now, I got to go back a little bit in history. Two years ago, I sold a hosting company that
had called the Data Barn. Because early in 2000, all this ban, all these bandwidth stories were
running about and there was money to be made. Of course, a lot of that was double accounting
turns out in the long run. But really after the bubble burst, there was just no one looking
for, you know, rack space and floor space and the right peering and connections.
So I'd by then acquired, and my partner's also started to flake out. So I'd acquired all
their shares and then I sold the whole company to the employees and to management. And as a
part of the deal, I said, well, I want to have my rack in the facility and hosting and I don't
need much service and maybe a reboot now and then. But ban with just, you know, that's just
for me. Whatever I'm using and we agreed, I think we actually put in writing that I, you know,
I wouldn't start a porn site or something like that. Well, yesterday, I got a call from the CEO.
It was a new CEO because they acquired the company, data barn and cap cave actually.
Tiskly acquired them probably about a year ago. And so there was a, you know, a grandfather
agreement and I'd never met this guy. I think there was even a CEO before him or general manager
of God knows what. And he said, hey, Adam, you know, I do and I'm like to introduce myself.
He was really nice and I knew what was coming and he said, you know, I'm looking at your
bandwidth, you know, mass what you're doing. And I said, well, what he means is, well, you're pushing
35 megabits per second continuously, continuous traffic, 35 megabits. And he says, and our other
customers are complaining because, you know, they, people, their sites are slowing down because
you're kind of filling up the entire pipe. And I know where their other customers are and I know
who complain because they have the national state lottery of the Netherlands and U2 with the U2.com,
all their multimedia. So I thought, you know, I'm already laughing like, all right, my little podcast
is disturbing the multimedia of U2. So I, I said, well, you know, actually I had already anticipated
you calling and I really glad you did. And as you probably noticed, I've already started moving
stuff over to a dot market count because it's, you know, I looked at my own stats and per day,
so just want to compare apples to apples here. Benjamin is now shipping what he says, 7, 7 gigs
on the first day. So doing about 7 gigs a day, which is actually quite a lot. Also he has a good podcast.
It's also the length is, you know, everything counts, right? Every bit counts, every encoding bit you
have at a higher setting, at the file size, and all of that's going to count in these totals.
But I'm shipping out close to 40 gigabytes of data per day, 40 gigs of data.
And so he said, well, you know, I'm looking at, you know, previous agreements, I don't
quite understand what the deal was inside random through it quickly. And I said, but you know what,
I said, you know, it's my understanding having come from the hosting business and having started
that and done a lot of these peering agreements, is that there can be a benefit to top tier
providers to having all the flow coming from one place, namely from them, because, and there are
other people who can almost suck them. So we set my buffer. There are other people who can explain
this much better than I can. But at these network access points or maps, you may have heard of
May East or May West or the, we have the M6, the Amsterdam Internet Exchange. That's where all these
big ISPs come together, and they hand off traffic to each other, and they do it under appearing
agreement. And it's kind of exactly what it sounds like, you know, we're peers. And so I'm going to
ship you like a million gigs of data this month, and you're going to be shipping a million
gigs of data to me. So it's a wash, right? And we're peers and don't worry about it.
And so there's no money that actually changes hand. Now, if you don't have a peering agreement
with the big telco provider, you have to buy transit, which means you have to buy that bandwidth
from some other provider who's closer to that particular pipe that you want to be to. So if someone
wants to get the daily source code, and they're on a provider, particularly in the United States,
that can't get to me directly by peering because you're on, you know, a subnet of something,
you know, this is where it starts to break down my explanation. But your provider will actually
have to buy that transit to help you suck that stuff down, which is why a lot of ISPs use
caching technology. So that means that there's an unbalanced and imbalance, and that power can be
created by having all the demand for particular content coming from one particular area, from one particular
network. That's kind of my lame and explanation. If anyone out there who's listening to the source
code can explain this, please record our an MP3 and send it my way because I think that's the way it is.
And if it is that way, then that could be very advantageous. Anyway, this guy took the bait immediately,
he said, yeah, we should talk about all that. So there must be something there, right? If not just for PR,
for public relations reasons. So I'm going to meet up with him next Thursday. But clearly,
this is going to be a problem. We know Bitcoin is definitely a part of this solution,
but we're thinking about it. So you're not alone. But what I've been doing and this is what I would
recommend for the time being is getting a dot mac account if you're on a Mac. There's all kinds of
free accounts. Accounts you can get that include storage and bandwidth. You know, you just kind of
have to spread the load a little bit. And the way I see everything going, people who have the
type of traffic that we're talking about will pretty soon will be able to, you know, make some
kind of deals so that you can get compensated. The first thing I'm going to lay down in front of this
guy next week is, hey, why do you sponsor the daily source code with bandwidth? That's, you know,
because of course, they probably throttle me down to about two megabits per second now,
which, you know, if you're using iPod, you're still going to get the files,
just going to take longer to bring them in. And as I said, I'm spreading it around to other
other hosting locations. But that makes so much sense, you know, and then we'll find out if they
really is a benefit for them, because he's not going to be giving away something, you know,
for just a handful of thousand people to listen to. So we'll see, I will report back on that.
Okay, it's the source code. What do we add? Wednesday, October 13th, middle of the week,
hump day time for some raster web jokio.
Welcome to raster web jokio for today. Hey, what's the deal with podcast? I mean, you're not
casting pods, right? Hey, what's up with that? You suck! Thank you, thank you, good night. I'm here all
week. Thank you Pete. I hope that brighten up your day like it did mine. Whenever I see a raster web
and it's like 30 seconds, I know it's going to be funny. So the first time you're playing,
it's always the best. We talked yesterday on the combined trade secret daily source code about
the opml directory. Don't roll your eyes in your hand right away, because I think if you like
web logs, you'll really like what opml directories are all about. So on ipod.org, I started
a directory of podcasts. Now creating a directory, if you're seeing the demos or if you're seeing
Yahoo's directory, and we talked about this, Dave and I talked about it yesterday on the source
secrets. Let's call it that the combined show. There's a lot of politics and what's the top level,
what are the top categories? And the great thing about the opml directory is that everybody can
be the top level. It's just like a web log. There's no top level to the internet, to the web.
Anyone can have a top level. I'm sure I want you to see ipod.org as a top level, but if you don't
like it, you can just follow the tree and connect, I'm sorry, you can follow the tree down
to something you do like and you can put that into your own top level and you can be the top level.
Let's all copy paste stuff because it's done in outlines. If you're never using the outline
or go to outliners.org and look at and see what the history of outlines, you've probably done
outlinings in school. At least if you're educated in the states in Europe, they don't,
they've never taught the concept of outlining at all, which is amazing to me. Or at least not that
I've found in my European education. And so it's real simple. You have, you know, the outline is
just like the directory. And if you want to create a new category or subcategory, you just
tab the next node underneath that. And you can collapse stuff. So it's easy to organize. It is easy
to keep track of it. And if you want to point off sight off of your directory, just like you
would a link with a weblog, then you do exactly that except it's not a dot HTML link you're
pointing to. It's a dot OPML link, which stands for outline processor markup language, just like HTML,
hypertext markup language. And what's cool is so now we have six different categories on the
ipodder.org podcast directory, which are handled by other people. And if you look at the music
directory, the minute you click on the music directory, you'll see that the owner of that link of
that node is someone else. It's not me. And if you click on the suggest the link, the email is going
to go to that person. Now under that, you'll see a category mixes. And you'll see the mix of the
week. And you'll see, so that's maintained by yet someone else who's also just basically posting
an OPML document on a web server, just like you would an HTML document. So the whole thing kind of
flows together, and you can traverse it left and right. And if you want to know more about that,
then definitely listen to yesterday's daily source code, because they've given a very good
explanation about the power of what this could be. And once we get the search engine guys in, then
life will be beautiful. And I do believe that. I came across Port-Lets podcast today, the fifth
in the series so far. Port-Let is one of the contributors to the OPML directory. So I thought
maybe we let it better to let him talk about how it's working. Then me, because it's just right
me promoting shit that I'm doing. So please listen to what else. One of the things I think is
more really interesting that's going long is now there's a the director of podcasts come along
and I'm taking part in that. And I'll be managing a couple of lists. I decided that I'd like to see
more comedy. And I'd like to see more interviews stuff out there. So I'm taking part myself to help out.
And submitted my suggestions for subcategories to Adam Curry, the guy that's run in the
ipotter.org list. And you can find it if you go to www.ipotter.org. And then look on the left hand
column. You'll see if you haven't seen the site before. Just look on the left hand column. For those
of you who've been there before, you'll actually notice it's got a new design. Look for the directory,
click on that button. And then look for the categories. And you'll see not just comedy and humor
and interviews, but you'll see if quite a few other categories and you'll see the directories growing.
And it is filling up. There's still way more empty categories I think than there are actually
shows. But it's easy to contribute. So especially, one mind, if you've got something out there
that's funny, or you've got some interviews of something the podcast you want to do. Just submit it.
Go the ipotters.org site. Look for the directory link. If you have a feed, just look for the
Submit link. And if it's classified as comedy or if it's an interview, I'll get the listing.
And I'll be able to update my list. It doesn't have to be those categories. There's other ones
there like food and technology and stuff like that. And when you submit your site, your feed,
whoever's running that list will be able to update the list. Some of the categories I've got started in
comedy thing is, let's give you more or less my topic. Tonight, I've got sketch, song,
parody, political, satire, commentary, current events, the absurd, the last category. I just thought
kind of, I hate the word miscellaneous. Okay, so you see how people can really get involved in
maintaining their category. I mean, and you're a part of the whole system. So if you want,
if you're interested, or you want to find out more about contributing to the ipotter.org podcast
directory, it's completely open. Go to ipotter.org, go to the podcast directory, and there's
a sub directory there that's titled contribute. Yeah, we thought about this stuff. Okay,
here's a bit from Koma 1000. I picked up on the podcast that I like the one to share with you.
It's really so incredible. It's hard to explain. DDPR, saying Torx songs and jazz clubs in St. Louis and
Chicago using stage names like Little Girl Blue and Laurie Allen. But it was her voice that
captivated a record producer in the 50s and convinced her to record 12 songs. The company went
to the point, as soon as it was recorded, obviously, and I thought it was totally lost.
Like the bubbles in a glass of champagne. After the company shut down,
Pierce went on with her own life, raising two daughters and marrying, while the songs which
were never published were forgotten by just about everyone. But some research on the internet
unearthed them owned by a small record label that specialized in obscure recording. He's
was delighted to put the bits and pieces back together and here it is. It's a dream come true,
although I feel like I'm standing here in my fuzzy slippers.
Pierce is now expecting to hear of her work from 1957, will be nominated for a Grammy.
And after decades of suspense, she's willing to wait a little more. It's like going back
and being a ghost at your own past. It's really been incredible. So I have one foot in 1957 and
one in 2004. John Rapp, coma, 1000 news. Isn't that a great story? Isn't the internet great?
Isn't the web great? We can find that stuff. Well, we'll see what happens with the upcoming Grammy
awards. I'm going to kind of mix it up today, a little bit of podcast stuff, a little bit of political
stuff, a little bit of music still on the way. This is, I wanted to play this just the intro
of this podcast for you because a lot of people are talking about, well, what's in the show? Do I really
want to listen to the whole thing? You kind of should just treat it like radio. You know,
use that away from the station if you're bored. And that's what those of us that are making these
shows are going to have to realize that if you're boring, people are going to zap to the next show,
maybe fast forward through your show. And it works that could unsubscribe from the feed. So there's
a number of different ways to do that. Right now, we don't have a lot of MP3 players that
can really display all the meta data. And I just don't know how we're going to solve that. But
the simple way is just to tell people upfront, here's what's in my show and maybe even like this
example, what you show is about. Wow, to tech rad terrains. This podcast is coming to you just
east of San Diego, California, in the city of Oklahoma. I anticipate that the target audience with
this show is seasoned information technology professionals and power users. There you go. So that's
one way to do it, which works very fine. And I knew in just seconds, I knew well, maybe this isn't
for me. And by the way, I don't know if I subscribed to all this. I tried to subscribe to just
about everything, but I've got stuff coming in from so many different directions. And this showed up
on IT conversations in the iPod this morning. And I didn't recognize it. It was called, what was it
called? Voices in your head and the name of the track in this case was James Patrick Kelly.
I was like, Voices in my head, what is this? And especially from IT conversations. And I gave
it a listen and you'll probably be surprised when you hear it, but check it out.
Good music, right? You figured this is something going to be cool.
Hello and welcome to the introductory episode of Voices in your head. I'm Dave Slusher.
Whoa. Dave Slusher. Dave Slusher's got a gig. Cool. So apparently Dave Slusher is doing a
show for IT conversations. Let's hear all about it. Your host and my guest this week is author
and columnist James Patrick Kelly. As the science fiction writer, he's been nominated for all
of the highest awards in the science fiction field, winning the Hugo Award for his stories 10 to the
16th to 1 and think like a dinosaur. As a teacher, he's frequently taught at the Clarion
writer's workshop, where he's inspired young writer such as Cory Doctoro. In the 1990s, his before
mentioned story, think like a dinosaur was adapted for a radio play by the sci-fi channel
scene ear theater. He writes the internet column for Asimov science fiction magazine amongst his
many responsibilities and is experimenting with making his work available as downloadable MP3s of his
readings. Thanks and welcome to the show, Jim. I'd like to be here. See, that's very cool and I
heard about this. I knew you, I think this is what Dave Slusher did before on public radio or
I don't know if it was public radio or he was doing some kind of radio thing just recently
maybe a year or so ago that he wound down that show. And so he's basically interviewing
nonbleness writers of science fiction. So this is something that's a great show. If you're
in a science fiction, you're going to want to subscribe. And what I can't wait for is to see
IT conversations split up. So we can have, I'd like to subscribe only to memory lane,
Hally suit or only to voices on my head or only to the Gilmour gang. I'm sure Doug's thinking about
that. So that won't be long coming. The other day Dave made a comment to me. He said about Chris
Perillo and I guess I'd missed that I maybe I didn't see his weblog posting or some thread that
I should have been following. But it wasn't till something showed up this morning in my iTunes that
Chris Perillo put together in a Chris Perillo. I believe he organizes Nomedex.
His weblog is locker-nome. And so the title of this podcast is locker-nome trends. And for some
reason, and this is the comment that I didn't pick up on earlier, he's got a stick-up as that's about
the terminology of podcasting and IT potter and IT pot platform. And I can totally understand
where he's coming from in some regard. And lots of people have been talking about, well,
you know, maybe you should call it something else besides anything that has the word iPod or the word
pod even. And yeah, that may be true. That may be true, but you know, it's stuck. It's done. I don't think
we can we can change it. And I don't think we should have to. I think that particularly when it comes to
iPod or technology, you know, iPod or stuff is just going to come built inside. You know,
I'm hoping that, you know, some companies will license some of the code that these teams have
been working on so diligently and put them into their hardware. You know, make, make cell phones have
this built in so that when we have, you know, when your cell phone kind of a Bluetooth connection
or an ultra wide band or Wi-Fi or UMTS or the GPRS or ABC or Aluminopi connection that, you know,
it knows the start sucking stuff in and knows what your subscriptions are on your preferences.
You know, power to all that. I don't think it'll matter what that's called anymore. And people are
going to get, you know, if pod casting is to broadcast, what web logging is to journalism, you know,
it's like we went through the same thing with blogging. Is it web logging, blogging? Is it a blog? Is it a
I don't just don't think it matters, but I did enjoy what Chris Perlode did. First of all,
he talked to his girlfriend. He sounds really cute. He talked to his girlfriend about, you know,
pod casting and did she understand what it is? And apparently she, she doesn't know much about
technology or at least she's playing that way in this pod cast. And, you know, what, are you compelled?
Would you like to have this and that explains it? Well, you'll hear a bit of that, but what he also
did is he had a whole bunch of people he knows, called into a voicemail box, which sends off MP3's,
kind of a, you know, voicemail service, sends off an MP3 of the voicemail recording to his email.
And he put the, he's drunk those all behind each other. And there's some great names in there,
some great people who called in all have different things to say. We're going to listen to that together.
And maybe we'll have some comments on bits of it. But first let's listen to Chris talking to his girlfriend
about pod casting. Why can't someone else collect it and get it together? And then I just pick
what I want. I want it to scrape for me, I guess, or I don't know what the terminology is.
You shouldn't have to worry about the terminology. Exactly. And that's what's pushed the discussion
where it is now. Pod casting is really bored as a word. And I have to use that word now because
it's all right. Yes, it is. And I can't get around the fact that it's so
trying into an existing product, an existing community, it's still going to leave people out.
Okay. So that's what I mean. That's what Chris is problem is. He feels that people who don't have iPods.
And he actually talks about money somewhere or can't afford iPods. Like this was designed to be
some elitist group that the names all wrong. But nowhere have I heard an actual good alternative
from him. But let's keep listening. Question is, if we can't get all these great internet minds
to start thinking together and use a word that transcends the iPod, what else can we do?
I think that we all should send our ideas to Chris. Let him pick the one. I'm all for it.
Could you just take on a responsibility there? No, I'm just asking the question.
I like his girlfriend already. Not mainstream yet. So it's still malleable. In my opinion,
the more you stay podcasting as an example. Podcasting, podcasting, podcasting.
In the more you enforce that name. So should I just call it broadcasting and then stick with it.
You have to be consistent. Podcasting. If you're going to change, you have to be consistent.
But understand when you make that change, the changes to include everyone.
Okay, here's what we're going to try something just a little bit different. I've got a voicemail
system that when someone leaves me a message, it gets sent to me in MP3 format. So I thought,
why not ask a few of my friends to send me their thoughts on podcasting? Mind you, I wasn't on this
mailing list. If it works, it works. If it doesn't say no big deal, we give it a shot.
But let me apologize for the audio quality of these voicemails. It's better than nothing.
Hey man, this Robert Skobel, and I think podcasting rules. I'm sitting here listening to Adam
Curry talking from bosom. Apparently we've worked out technology. So the smoke actually can
affect you if you're wearing earplugs. What's up, Skobel? And I think, you know, this is just not.
It's how the world's going to run. It's going to, you know, anyway. I'm hiking things that's
right on. I needed 20. But tonight I was at a geek dinner and talking to JP Stewart. And he
has pimped out his car with a windows XP machine. He has a little screen at the front and a
TPS and a Wi-Fi antenna. And he, you know, it dialed home through Bluetooth and his phone.
I think I need to get me one of those phone. It's pretty neat. But he's listening to podcast now in
the car. I mean, you know, I can see a world where this is going to be normal stuff. And this
is going to be how you get different kinds of audio and video content. Anyways, let's know next.
And how do you think? So I'm just going to keep playing these because these are great. There's
some big names that come through. That was Robert Skobel who was, uh, I call him the resident
blogger at Microsoft, uh, good guy. Let's see this next. This is Jake Lettingson from
Jakelettingson.com. And I think the thing for me about podcasting that is most confusing is
probably the name podcasting. And it implies that you need an iPod to do it. And you know
this guy's a shill right. You know, you know, this is a shill. I frankly, you don't need an iPod
or a Mac or it's really a platform independent way to download content on demand.
Whether that be audio or video from the internet, using a system that's kind of a
TV-like system to subscribe to specific content channels and have them automatically download to
your computer and then be able to come with a device. I actually created a tutorial showing you
how to do it using Windows Media Player and the iPod or software that's currently available
at iPod.org. Yeah, we actually pointed to that. I think it's a good how to.
Because it's so far all of the all the tutorial information has been geared towards people wanting
to do specifically using iPod and iPod iTunes. And I was looking at it and I don't like
six different devices that all can support audio, but none of them is an iPod. So I was like,
well, how do I do this? I went through the process. You can look at that on Jakelettingson.com.
And this is actually something that Microsoft sort of made in attempt at doing.
Now, this is interesting. Listen to this because I actually recall all of them. My mic was
crackling. I actually recall Microsoft doing this for for their, um, I think it was their Puck at PC,
but listen to the onto the objections. In like this, about three years ago, and they released a product
called Sinken Go as part of the Plus Digital Media Edition Pack. And basically what Sinken Go does
is, unless you subscribe to one of the 20 content items and have them Sink automatically to
a Puck at PC, each time you like connect your Puck at PC to the cradle. Now there are two
problems with that. Number one, they don't want to work with Puck at PC, so you rule about everyone
who has my pot or is a creative bend or del BJA real karma. Many of the, like dozens of other
devices are available. And it also is a closed content loop meaning that only the content providers
that Microsoft has selected are able to do every content. Right. So I think that's a real
important part there. And I'm glad that Chris is putting this up. Because, you know, yeah,
we may not have the name right, you know, people may not agree with that or may, you know, drive you
towards certain thoughts, but we have an open content pool and anyone's allowed to come and party with
us. So yeah, we're not as hit the Sinken Go. Now the big difference with podcasting is that
anyone can set up a podcast and make it available for people to consume. Now that doesn't mean
all of the podcasts are going to be great or a lot of people are going to say this.
Let's go to the next caller. I know you're thinking about doing this yourself.
And the rest of the story is really good, but you're going to listen to what he said.
Okay, okay, do you stop the year content that? Okay, all right, Chris, Steve Gilmore. Okay,
of the Gilmore gang, here we go, a fresh face in the crowd. Leaving you a message about podcasting,
which I think is the single most important thing going on in the past,
uh, at least two weeks. It's sweeping the RSS space and because it's fundamentally the same thing as RSS,
being RSS enclosures at the heart of the matter. It's going to quickly generate a lot of
attention around specifications as attention to them. Then XML, let me try that again,
attention dot XML, which is a attention metadata standard, which I hope will allow for the
evolution evolution. Excuse me, have the Roch Motel effect, which is going on with some of the
major players in the Roch Motel effect? RSS space, namely the metadata goes in and it never comes out.
Okay, so I hope this is enough for you to do a test and see how this, you might be able to
remove the screen. Hey, this is Steven Cohen from Library stuff. Thanks, Chris, for contacting me.
I just don't know what you're going to do. I know, I'm bored.
Yeah, I'll put a link to it. You can get, you can subscribe to this, but there's a whole bunch of
people that show up later on. Dave Winner shows up and it's just a whole, I thought it was going to be
interesting listening to a second time. I think you just have to go get it yourself, but it's
it goes on for another, let's see, oh man, it goes on for another 15 minutes of people calling in,
but it's a very interesting way of doing like comments, it's really what struck me about this,
and it could either be a one to masses type comments, but probably the other way around,
and this must be very easy to set up, Chris, if you have a minute, set up a pointer to
whatever service you're using, because if they're really firing off MP3s, that would be
beautiful. I could set up a rule in my mailbox that'll dump it into a folder and it'll make it
into a podcast so that it would just be for me, it would just be like an answering machine,
literally, or comments, or stuff my assistant wants me to remember, and I could put that on
and listen to it in the car, and cool way of creating a podcast feed. Okay,
I got a question that came in, an important one. Good evening Adam, curious, now I'm
off to go from the Linux link text show and dance rants for meeting my way through the earlier
episodes of Daily Source Code, and one thing that is really caught my curiosity is whether you have
a license to broadcast the Android Distribute, the commercial music or media files that you play,
and what your opinion is, those who are just getting into podcasting, who obviously look
to your work as one of the pioneering people in podcasting, and what your opinion is on them
including commercial-based content, what concerns us or me and also discuss it on the text show
is that it might draw unnecessary or unwanted attention from bodies like the R, I, A, A, and the NBA,
and force their hand to crack down on podcasting for illegal distribution of commercial products.
Just curious is the what you think about that, and what you might have to say to other people
who are out there podcasting now. Thank you for taking your time to listen to this and look
forward to the next Daily Source Code. Right on Dan, thank you very much, I appreciate the
question, and to answer it right off the bat, no, I don't have a license. I have done licenses with
a particularly with BMI, I think we wrote probably the first BMI license for online music,
and that was for, but my client was Budweiser, I think, and we did something with the Budweiser site
and they gave a specific license, and at the time I believe it was a percentage of revenue.
So the answer is no, now most of the podcasts that you're hearing are just spoken word,
but just about every single podcast that I've seen come by in the past couple weeks,
does begin with an opening tune, and even if you're just using a few snippets or just a little bit
of a song in the real world outside of podcasting, you're using somebody else's intellectual
property, and they have rights to that, and that should be, if not compensated, at least this should
be an agreement about what kind of use that is. You're right about perhaps the leadership role
because I do see people emulating the format, however the rules where I live are a little bit different.
There are no people being sued by the RIA in Europe. In fact, the European Court is still
trying to figure a lot of these issues out, although we're probably not winning the war, we have,
well, maybe we are winning the war, and we lost a few important battles, but on software
patents things are a little bit different over here. There's a reason why Kazah was, I don't think
they were, they were probably founded wherever Nicholas and those guys live, but they built a company
in Amsterdam. They're just different rules about technology and peer-to-peer sharing, and we don't
have a couple of the laws that have been passed in the United States. That doesn't mean that
I think it's right, and I think that it should change. Now, conversely, I've talked about this a
couple of times. In Europe, in the Netherlands, at least I know 100% for sure, but in most of
Europe, I'm quite sure, radio and television stations pay a percentage of revenue to the licensing
organizations, which would be ASCAP BMI. Here, it's Buma Stemna. Every country has something, but they're
all tied together in some weird bizarre way, and only they know how that works. They pay a percentage
of revenue, and then they can use whatever they want. There are some restrictions, but they
can even use it in their promos and in their shows, and there's just a whole bunch of ways that
they can use that. Radio stations, exactly the same. In the States, from what I'm led to believe,
radio stations don't pay that type of royalty because it's seen as advertising. That's really
important because if we're going to have to be broadcasting, like Chris Perillo says, and we're
not podcasting, we're broadcasting. I'm all for that, but then I want broadcast rules, and I want
to have the same benefits. I think I could convince and make a pretty good case for most music
industry executives, who I'm sure are listening, that this is the radio of the future. Screw
the connections you've got with clear channel, and who you know there. This is where the new
radios coming from. Don't you guys have kids at the RIA? I have a 14 year old, and I see her
14 year old friends, and they're trading music all the time. Christina has crazy about good
Charlotte, and they're taping videos and sharing those with each other, and they, and it's just
as humongous build up that they witnessed together online to the release of the next album, and then
my daughter's cutting school to go by the good Charlotte album, which by the way, it comes in a
double set, so it's two CDs, exactly the same only one is called the life album, one is called
the death album, and each one has a separate bonus track. I mean, you got that part of the marketing
right? You're getting these kids to buy two CDs instead of one, but you know, see that you're
building up to it. Give them the tools to share. Give them the opportunity to let them work on
this stuff, and help you, and you will sell music. I guarantee you that, that's just you have to
figure out new ways of packaging and marketing this stuff. So, you know, I want to be treated like
like a broadcaster in that case, and I want to have the same type of deal, which means we shouldn't
have to pay anything. There is, by the way, a fee for MP3, which we discussed earlier, I posted that
a couple times, a pointer to it. With MP3, if you make over a hundred thousand dollars using MP3
as your delivery mechanism, you're content packaging, whatever the hell, however the lawyer specified
that, then there is a, I think it's 2% of gross revenue that you have to pay in licensing fees.
That's about it. You know, that's all that it should be, and just think of the opportunities.
But you're right. You know, there's a very big chance that some people will say, hey,
you know, this is crazy. This is, this is running rampant, but I don't know. I think that if I look
at the evolution of web logs, then at the beginning, a lot of journalists and a lot of newspapers
and big publications were saying, you know, this should be outlawed. You know, you can't have people
just writing a word at whatever they want on on, on woops. Oh, wait a minute. I violated like a free
speech thing there. No, but that's what they wanted to say, and that's how they were feeling,
and that was the vibe, and it's going to be the exact same thing with this. Only this is,
I think the speed at which we're evolving in which this is unfolding before us is going much faster
than the web logs, and it's because the concept is the same. We're not really learning anything new here,
except for the production. The, and in fact, in many ways, the, the consumption side of what we're
doing is easier than the web logs. And perhaps more convenient than the web logs, since you, you know,
it doesn't take up your web logs space. You can take up space of where you were listening to
boring radio, perhaps, or had nothing to do, or, you know, listening to your, the same music
tracks in a different order over and over again, and seeing if your i-cut pod could pick out a song
that matched your, you know, your mood for the day. But I do think that it's possible to get this done.
I know that MPR, Tony Khan, got the, for the morning stories, there's three up there now,
and they'll be adding more. The licensing was taken care of. So it's clearly someone knows how to do this,
and licensing is possible. And I think it's right, and it's fair. Even if you pay nothing,
we have to have an agreement because you're using something. Now, of course,
there's already all kinds of licensing models out there when it comes to like what I'm doing.
I'm playing, you know, geez, I'm, I'm like violation on top of violation. I play someone else's
podcast and a bit of the music that they're already illegally using. So, you know, this, it's,
I don't think anyone will disagree that we can make money on this. We should pass off some piece.
And I think that, because it's not exactly the same, it's certainly not the same as, uh,
streaming playlists of songs. It's not the same as sharing individual MP3 tracks, you know,
just like on, in American broadcast, you're not allowed to pre-announce a new, you're not allowed
to pre-announce a song. Well, you're not supposed to. Let's put it that way. You can back
announce, or you can tease with commercials in between. There's all kinds of rules so that
it stays within the realm of, you know, people that people could A be ready to record it,
or there could be deemed as a complete commercial. You know, so there's all these rules that
need to be looked at. And I think we fit into that very well. And if that's so, then maybe
just like Chris Prilas suggested, we will become broadcasters instead of mere podcasters.
And I'm going to violate those rules. Once again, I'm going to violate the rules. We're going
to stick it to the man. By major requests, I once played, uh, everybody's, uh, fucking with me,
by Dura Wood do Shee. And I got so many requests for either that song. I have a, I have like,
I have no whole album. Um, and it's, uh, you spell it, uh, as you would do, uh, DO, U, C, H, E,
do Shee. And, um, the next track is from that. It's an audience participation track. If so,
if you're in, in a, in a lyrics, then you can participate in this. Um, it's a good combination
of adult humor and, uh, some nice big band kind of blues tunes. And it is no matter what, definitely
not safe for work. Good evening, ladies and gentlemen. And welcome once again to the lovely
sewer supper club, located deep in the bowels of our fair city, where the wine is fine and
the food divine. Tonight's special is plump, juicy, boned, milk fed sewer rat, floating in a
piquence cilantro scum sauce. Okay. Now it's time for the audience participation segment here
at the pristine chapel bar. And that means that it's time for your favorite song, The Limerick
Blues, written by our very own house piano player, or perhaps I should say, outhouse piano player,
Derwood, Du Shee accent acute over the E. You all know the routine, the band plays the Limerick
Blues theme once. And then when I point to you, you recite your Limerick. We're going to leave
the second Limerick spot blank for all you listeners out there to fill in your own Limerick.
So think of your favorite Limerick, title up to the band stand and get ready to blow them away
with your poem. Ready? Here we go, a one, a two, a you know what to do.
A lovely young lady named Grace, gave me head through a piece of black lace.
When my seamen was scattered, I saw I had splattered white freckles all over her face.
Man she looked go.
Set a Japanese hooker from Kobe, to a wedding-down sailor named Toby.
No charge for this trick, that's a whale of a dick, and it's white, so let's
Chris and it in the movie, almost as far as we were going.
There once was a laugh from Nantucket, who was in the face with a bucket, too ugly to lay
shit this to say, if you don't like my made one, it's fucking it!
A fox a young lady from Rio, walked up and said, are you a Leo, and now she retorts
the fuck in my shorts with a splatter that real come to Rio.
I tied up a nympho and king-ta, the warps held but barely a string-ta, when I let her
loose, she gave me a goose and bit off my cock-oomed eye-lain-ta, right between the fucking
one.
Don't do shit, the limeric blues of one live in front of a Randy audience.
Alright, I'm going to leave you today with a bit of politics, this came through on the
feedster video and closures feed, which iPod Rex also hampily picks up for me, I always
scan through the videos, also a lot of data that comes in and gets storage, you got to do
it in a pretty regular basis.
This is a bit, I think it's in the house, where Tim Ryan, who's a Democrat, is, and you'll
find out at the end, is talking about the story that's been served, I've seen served
on the internet a couple of times, and the past few weeks, is that there is a probability
of a draft being instated, and it's really important to think about this, I remember in
90 when the first Gulf War took place, and I think I mentioned this before, I was 30
at the time, and I was pretty sure I wasn't going to be drafted, but they did ask me
to register for the draft, and I was thinking like, damn, that would really suck, besides
the fact that my sorry-wide ass wouldn't last two minutes, and no goddamn desert, as it
turns out, I found out that my ass did last for a week, but trust me, you do not want
to be there, certainly not if you're being shot at and blown up, and people who are there,
I don't want you to be there because you're not really helping them, and you don't want
to be there if you're confused, so I wanted to play this, because what this guy, he's
a young guy, Tim Ryan, it's so compelling what he says, and he's so much emotion, and
if you are old enough to vote, you're old enough to be drafted, and I suggest you vote
for John Kerry to get George W. Bush out of the White House, and here's why.
I thank the gentleman, I rise in opposition of this bill, but I would like to clarify something,
we're not trying to scare kids, this president's foreign policy is what's scaring the
kids of this country, and that people have said today, why are people believing this?
Why are people believing this big internet hoax?
Well, it's the same people that told us Saddam Hussein had something to do with 9-11,
same people that told us Saddam Hussein had weapons of mass destruction, same people
that told us we were going to be able to use the oil for reconstruction money, same
people that told us that we'd be greeted as liberators, not occupiers, same people, same
president that told us the Taliban is gone, same president that told us that Poland is
our ally two days before they pull out, same president that tells us a rack is going, just
great, same president that tells us the economy is going, just great, same people that
told us the tax cut was going to create millions of jobs, same people that told us that
the Medicare program only cost $400 billion, when it really cost $540 billion, so please
forgive us for not believing what you're saying, please forgive the students of this country
for not believing what you're saying, not one thing, not one thing about this war that has
been told to the American people, or that has been told to these college students has been
true, not one thing, Bremer says we need more troops, the Pentagon says we need more
troops, and this president can't get them from the international community, there's only
one option left, let's be honest with the American people, I yield back the bounce of my
son, whoa, all right, there you go, Tim Rines, I'm very very very clear words for you to
think about vote for John Kerry, and that's it for the source code for today, I'm
Adam Curry from Belgium, thank you for tuning in, as always comments are welcome, Adam
Curry.com, please I need more email, and to my weblog, Curry.com live. Curry.com, of course
you can get all the archives in the latest source code at dailysourcecode.com where you can also
subscribe to the podcast, RSSSP, and that'll do it for today, perfect one hour and three
minutes, so I'll be back tomorrow for another source code as we say in France, Viva, let's
have a new show