Hi everybody, good morning, good afternoon, or good evening, wherever you're checking
in from.
I'm Adam Curry coming to you from a rather balmy Belgium.
It's a power of the door.
I like the way that sounds. Balmy Belgium.
And actually just as I said that, the sun's starting to shine through.
We had a beautiful day yesterday, about 26 degrees centigrade,
until the very end around 7 o'clock.
And all of a sudden I knew what was going to happen
because our satellite reception went out and I said,
oops, we got a real big depression here.
And we just had a cloud burst almost directly above the castle.
And it apparently rained through most of last night.
So really, and let me start off with this, actually.
I apologize about yesterday not getting a source code up on time,
but I'll walk you through just some of the events of the day
and then hopefully you'll understand.
So it's the source code where users and developers party together.
Today we're going to be talking about Howard Stern.
I'll listen to a couple of audio blog posts.
that I've picked up. Also I'm going to give you finally my review of John Stewart's audio
book. Look at the iPodder. Oh, I finally I can say this word the iPodder space because
now next to iPodder I found there's another company doing something or actually a company
not another but a company doing something very similar. I got a song of the day that
I picked up from from around the net and some quick feedback on Skype. So yesterday
and I had all the full intentions to do a source code either from the road or once
I got home but you know because I had to go to Amsterdam sit down with the with
the bank and financial advisors and some tax lawyers because of our move to the
UK there's certain benefits that stem from that financial benefits obviously.
You know so it's kind of an important meeting and also you know the bank will
help me make that move.
It's, I just don't, I don't look forward to changing all that stuff.
What a pain in the ass.
So anyway, so hopefully they're going to take care of it for me.
Oh, they will take care of it for me.
And so I can concentrate on fun things, which was, you know, I wanted to do my
source code yesterday.
Didn't work out.
I drove back after swinging by, uh, swinging by Amsterdam.
Um, I was home around five o'clock, uh, Patricia wanted to eat early.
So we had dinner.
And then I got to put together the exercise bike.
Man, talk about developers who make these things and don't really think
about users who have to put them together.
Uh, it took me a little while, but I finally got all the pieces to
fit together exactly as they should.
And all the pieces were there and it did fit perfectly.
Um, but that took me in, uh, into the good part of the evening.
And then I just, uh, you know, I just didn't have the energy left.
Hey, it was Friday.
What can I say?
So I do apologize.
I'll try to do a better job on that.
Um, as a, um,
I'm a former member of the Bridge and Tunnel crowd in New York City.
I really came to appreciate Howard Stern on the radio, on K-Rock.
If you sit in traffic for an hour and a half or two hours in front of the Lincoln Tunnel
every single morning, then even the best of Sterns start to grow on you.
And I've always really liked the stuff he's doing in the morning.
I feel that particularly, and it's totally a guy's show.
I don't think it's necessarily intended for women, female listeners at all.
But there's something that I think, and lots of guys like,
is just giggling about stupid stuff, which of course usually is about farting
and about sexual stuff.
But it does kind of get you day off started right.
And his audience numbers prove that.
He truly has an amazing audience, very large, and a very valuable audience.
because Howard Stern is without a doubt, no matter what you want to say, very very successful
and I happen to like his show.
So I was elated when I read that Howard Stern had struck a deal with movielink.com to distribute
uncensored versions of his E-Channel television show which is basically his radio show,
only the cameras are hanging up in the studio.
So they do the radio show, they shoot that with multiple cameras and that's
aired on each channel so it's a great reappropriation of the content they're already making.
And obviously lots of stuff that goes on in the Howard Stern studio is censored.
So making an uncensored version available over the internet I was like,
way to go and of course I'll pay 4.95 for the privilege of watching that.
So I went to movielink.com, now remember I'm in Belgium and just entering the URL
movielink.com brings up the following page that says thanks for your interest in movielink,
the leading source for movies del-
delivered directly over the internet.
We want you to enjoy our powerful movie download experience, but it is presently unavailable
to users outside of the United States.
Well, that blows.
I kind of forgot about it, and then as I was looking through my aggregator, and this is
how these things work these days, I have keywords put in there for all kinds of stuff that
I'm looking forward to catching.
Once in a while, there is a Howard Stern eShow taped right off the air from the e-channel
that will come by as a bit torrent in one of the TV torrent RSS feeds.
So it's automatically downloaded to my directory where I have all the new stuff that comes
in.
And lo and behold, someone had taken the movie link video, I presume, and I don't know
if they copied it or transcribed it or what they did, or if they just took it verbatim
if it's not copied or protected.
I don't know how movie link works, obviously, so I can't get to the site.
But it downloaded, it was sitting there on my...
drive for free. And I'm thinking to myself, you know, A, outfits like movielink.com should
be looking at how they're delivering stuff, because this works, you know, connecting RSS
with enclosures and BitTorrent. It is actually just kind of working. It's bringing stuff
to me that I'm interested in. So it's a very, very, very poor man's very primitive
Tivo version of a network Tivo, but it is working. And, you know, and I'd still
gladly pay if there was a way for me to say, hey, you know, thank you very much. I got
this. I'll pay a subscription, I'll pay whatever, no matter how I receive it. But,
you know, that's up for the business model makers of the future to figure
out. Of course, the same goes for the iTunes music store, although available
in Germany and the United Kingdom, I believe. And I'm not quite sure how Germany
snuck in there, because the rest of the European Union can't download from the
iTunes music store.
store yet. They say that the EU, in the last keynote speech that Apple held in Paris, they
said that the EU was coming in, I think, the first half of 2005. But still, these copyright
boundaries that are very, very, very complicated legal situations. And we're just routing
around it. And I'm not even doing it intentionally. This stuff just floated into me. I didn't
go out looking for the Howard Stern e-show uncensored version. It came to me just through
technology. So this stuff's tough to pay attention to. And I read something horrible this morning
that Catherine Zeta-Jones, the beautiful actress who was married to Michael Douglas, that she's
shooting a movie in Mexico and that a gang of kidnappers tried to ram her limousine off
the road and her bodyguards, which she had, you know, were able to foil the kidnap attempt.
I mean, damn, what's going on there?
And they say that in the report that I was reading that about 2,000 people a year are abducted
in this fashion.
Of course, you only really think about it or hear about it when someone of celebrity status
is abducted or kidnapped.
And then it becomes an issue.
We've got to do something about it.
In the meantime, there's 1,999 other people a year being abducted, which is happening
all over the world.
It's happening in the Middle East.
It's happening in Iraq.
With the discussions that I had with people over there, it was already a common place
at the beginning of, I'm sorry, the First Gulf War when things were just really falling
to shit in that country.
And sometimes you'd be kidnapped and if the person who was kidnapped, if their family
was influential enough, they could actually scare the kidnappers with all kinds of connections
and family networks into...
giving the person back and actually paying a fine to them.
It's crazy what's going on.
The value of human life is anywhere from zero to a million dollars or more.
It's crazy.
So anyway, we're happy that Catherine Zeta-Jones is okay,
but man, she's probably going to be a little bit shaken up about that episode for a while
and I think she has to stay there in Mexico until the shooting for the movie is done,
which won't be until the end of the year.
Okay, cruising around the net, listening to some programs, some audio blogs,
and as you know, my blog digger media subscription, that's the blogdigger.com media feed,
brings in, and actually I did look it up, what Blog Digger does
is it basically crawls through RSS feeds and I presume that when it either finds a URL,
whether it's not entirely clear if it'll take any URL that...
comes across an RSS feed or only ones that are encapsulated as an enclosure, it'll then
bring that in and publish it or publish it into a separate feed.
And so it's all kinds of interesting stuff that comes in and I have a couple of bits
lined up for you today.
But first I want to take something from Raster Web.
Now we've listened to Raster Web's audio blog post before.
He says something really interesting about how iPodder is working for him and what his
media client is now turning into.
Let's just listen to this for a second and then we'll discuss it after.
And the important thing is we're automated.
Can you hear me?
Can you play?
Play what?
more and more as I'm using my version of the iPod
that curry calls it, mine's called Braco.
Some pro code I whipped up that I'm seeing iTunes
being more and more like an email application.
I mean, I sort it by, you know, they add it,
so every time I pull it to the front,
I basically see whatever it's been downloaded
and stuck into iTunes.
Later I sit down, iTunes comes, I bring iTunes to the front,
and I go, oh look, there's a new daily source code.
There's a new evil genius Chronicles or whatever.
So, kind of cool.
And again, you know, I see conversations,
which again, great stuff that Ducay and his buddies are doing.
That's all good stuff.
Okay, so this is interesting.
When your iTunes or your Windows Media player
starts to become an email-like application
where you look at that and say,
oh, something new has been added,
and think about the interface, at least I've seen it.
iTunes is very, very similar if not if it probably uses a lot of the same classes, object classes
as the male client on Macintosh's OS X. And same goes for Outlook and Windows Media Player,
I'm sure a lot of the same technology should be leveraged at least underneath the hood.
And I've come to learn that if something new on the Internet looks or feels or works
like something that already exists on the Internet, then we've probably got a good
thing going because the same things were being said with RSS news readers.
So that's interesting. Even though we're working on getting new types of content
and bundles of passion and whatever we call it, you know, programs, shows,
discussions, interviews, audiobooks, we want to get them directly onto the
mobile devices. Now we're seeing that our media players are becoming kind of
the database. And of course we're addressing them exactly like that.
When the iPod or code, when that code runs and it adds something to either the iTunes or the Windows
media player database. It's actually doing that. It's doing a very informal type of call saying,
add this to that database so you'll be able to search it and find it, retrieve it, etc.
So interesting observation there from Raster Web.
Okay, John Stewart. Since I did do some driving over the past, actually yesterday as I told
you, I had a chance to finish up. The John Stewart presents America Audio Book, which
is an excellent, excellent piece of work. It is produced specifically as an audio book.
I don't even know if it's available in a paper version. I don't think a paper version could do it
justice. We listen to it. It's put together almost like an old-fashioned radio show with bells
and whistles and sound effects, different voices. Clearly everything is script, but it's...
And of course this edited wasn't done live as they used to do in the old days.
Oh, listen, we've got Pittsburgh on the wireless. But it's an excellent piece of work.
It takes you through the...
history of the United States, how democracy was born and came about.
And of course he does get some historical perspective back to ancient Rome on that.
And then also explains the three branches of government, goes into all different parts
and aspects, but in a very humorous way.
And listening to it, having worked with John a little bit in the MTV days when he still
had the John Stuart show and we were hanging out at the beach house doing some stuff together.
It really, you can tell it really is John Stuart.
It is totally from, I'm sure many people worked on this, but it is totally John Stuart to the core.
And here's a little bit where the Congress is being discussed.
And you listen to this one snippet and I think it will just blow your mind in its humor, its insight.
And it's perhaps its accuracy.
The Strom Thurman filibuster August 28, 1957
Senator Strom Thurman, Republican South Carolina,
set the record for longest filibuster
with this 24-hour 18-minute speech
railing against a civil rights bill.
The marathon-speaking session left Thurman so drained
he could barely have sex
with the underaged black woman in his family's employ.
Thurman's oration obliterated
the previous filibuster record,
a 13-hour description by Daniel Webster
of the massive dump he had just taken.
Discussion questions.
One.
If Khan is the opposite of pro, then isn't Congress the opposite of progress?
Or did we just fucking blow your mind?
I mean, that did blow my mind.
I was listening to that on the road.
I was like, whoa, progress, Congress.
Okay, point taken, point made.
Excellent.
I'm going to play a little bit more of the John Stuart Presents America audiobook
in a second.
First, another bit I picked up online from the blog digger media feed.
Unfortunately, there's no title other than 1933.mp3.
Clearly it's from an audio blogging service.
It's done through a telephone.
And this is a gentleman who is extremely pissed off at George W. Bush.
And the reason why I want you to hear this, and I'm also going to do something, another
piece of John Stuart, is as opposed to when you would write about how pissed off you
are about the current administration or perhaps about anybody, it doesn't really matter.
This is very hard to convey the emotions that you can with the human voice, or at least
to receive the emotions, even though they're probably not even intended to be transmitted
that way.
They are transmitted.
And this gentleman is definitely angry.
So it's a different world today than it was yesterday because he has now been caught and
his administration has been caught.
And you know what?
George Bush's allies have made an issue of John Kerry service and we are going to make
an issue of the president's credibility as it relates to his service, to the conduct
of what he has done in Iraq, on the issues of his credibility on jobs, healthcare and
education.
So this is on the table and it's going to be on the table from now until November 2nd.
So think about reading that as a web blog post.
You could certainly receive the same type of intensity
that you heard there, but probably not.
And I think this is a definite advantage
of what audio blogs can do.
All we need now is different ways for these to be aggregated.
And I think the most obvious way
is to have people do that, have people be content routers.
Like what I'm trying to do here
is let you hear different aspects of what can be done,
how we can produce things on our desktop,
how we can distribute them ourselves.
Because I think there is a valid place for audio
within the internet being a communications device,
certainly in the manner that we're using it.
So, and I'll be on the lookout for anything
that comes from the other side
of the political equation in the States.
If that shows up on the blog digger media feed,
I'll be sure to give them equal time.
Back to John Stewart's book, John Stewart Presents America.
Now this is a little longer piece,
about three and a half minutes, but I think it's...
Well worth listening to first of all I'm trying to entice you to listen to the entire things you can go off to
I'm sure I don't know if Amazon has it. They probably do
Otherwise audible.com to buy this book
Prices range from 495 to 795. That's Dave. Dave. Why are paid 495? I paid 795
this next
piece from the book really is the core of what John Stewart and
We all know him from the Daily Show what he is all about about the media
What the media's role is in the democracy how it's supposed to function?
And of course we know that John Stewart sees this and the Daily Show
Really plays off the fact that we don't get what we deserve as a democracy
What the free press should be delivering to us?
I'll just let me just back this up a second
And and again you'll hear a very
Passionate John Stewart of course none of this is safe for work, but
But, you know, we've discussed that before.
Oh, by the way, I'll talk about the copy protection in a second.
First let's listen to John Stuart.
He says it's about three and a half minutes talking about the media and the free press
in a democracy.
Chapter 7. The Media. Democracy's Guardian Angel.
chapter you will learn how to identify political bias in today's liberal
bleeding heart Jew and gay run media become an unnamed source create your
own no-spin zone discover which media conglomerate now owns you not have your
opinion of Geraldo Rivera particularly improved upon
A free and independent press is essential to the health of a functioning democracy.
It serves to inform the voting public on matters relevant to its well-being.
Why they've stopped doing that is a mystery.
I mean 300 camera crews outside of courthouse to see what Kobe Bryant is wearing, when the
judge sets his hearing date while false information used to send our country to war goes unchecked.
What the fuck happened?
The spineless cowards in the press have finally gone too far.
They have violated a trust.
Was the president successful in convincing the country?
Who gives a shit?
Why not tell us if what he said was true and the excuses?
My god, the excuses!
Hey, we just give the people what they want.
What can we do?
This administration is secretive.
But the last season of Friends really is news.
The unmitigated gall of these weak willed.
You're supposed to be helping us, you indecent piles of shit!
I- Fuck it!
Just fuck it!
This is the editor again.
We sincerely apologize for this false start.
The authors have assured us it was a momentary lapse.
restrained caused by a deadline-induced red bull binge. In no way was it meant to
portray any sense of anger and or disappointment in the behavior and
standards of the modern media.
Chapter 7. The Media. Democracies Guardian Angel.
What's the role of a free and independent press in a democratic society?
Is it to be a passive conduit responsible only for the delivery of information between
a government and its people?
Is it to aggressively print allegation and rumor independent of accuracy or fairness?
Is it to show boobies?
No.
The role of a free press is to be the people's eyes and ears, providing not just information
but access, insight, and most importantly, context.
It must devote its time and resources to monitoring the government, permeating the
halls of power to determine who is doing the people's work, who is corrupting the
process, and who will promise to be a mole in the State Department if their
homosexuality is kept secret.
Only after that, and only with time permitting, should it move on to high
speed freeway cases.
For government to truly be for the people, inner workings must be exposed for
the public to see.
This lofty goal is known as transparency, and while this could be
accomplished by sheathing all elected officials in public buildings in
Saran Wrap, this is
has been deemed unwieldy, expensive and creepy. Instead transparency is achieved via a free
press, something so vital to democracy it has historically been given equal stature
to the three branches of government, hence its nickname, the Fourth Estate.
No less an authority than Thomas Jefferson wrote,
If it were left to me to decide whether we should have a government without a free
press or a free press without a government, I would prefer the latter. Now if you'll
excuse me, I have a lunchtime appointment with a fine slice of brown sugar.
So the audiobook is titled John Stewart Presents America and well worth the
three and a half hours that you'll be listening to it. Excellent, excellent
stuff and actually a very good refresher course in in what this great country is
all about. And oh yeah, something about a little bit about DRM and copy
protection. Of course I purchased the book off of audible.com. It downloads
as an Apple AAC file which has the advantage of bookmarking.
which work automatically with your iPod, but also should include
And instead of, since I can't really queue anything up in iTunes, except for like one bookmark,
I wanted to play two different clips.
What I did was I recorded it through wiretap, which is a beautiful little application for the Mac OS X, OS X 10.
I just played the bits that I wanted, recorded them, which are then recorded as AIFF files,
and just opened those in QuickTime.
And it worked perfectly, so much for the big DRM and impossibility of copying.
Not of course that I want to encourage any of you to do that, but it's that simple,
and they really want to stop copying copyright protected works.
We've got to find a device of different schema.
Okay, let's talk about iPod, or just briefly, of course,
iPod.org is where you can download one of many different applications and scripts
that will enable you to automatically download programs like this one onto your mobile device.
We have it set up for iPods, we have it set up for...
anything that works with Windows Media Player and even have a version for Linux.
That'll at least bring everything in for you.
And someone, a couple people actually pointed me to a company called Audio Feast.
Let me just bring this up now.
Here we go, Audio Feast, which you can find at
serenadesms.com, so S-E-R-E-N-A-D-E-S-M-S.com
Audio Feast, I'll just read this to you, delivers 300 plus news, sports and entertainment radio programs to your MP3 player and PC.
Sync all the programs you want, listen whenever and wherever you'd like.
So essentially they have exactly the same idea.
In fact, when I go to the What Is It page, which I'll surf to now and I'll read along with you,
Audio Feast is a service that delivers extensive programming choices for MP3 players.
It's easy to use and deliver time shifting.
flexibility at an affordable all you can listen prize. Subscribers can choose to listen
to their favorite programs directly from their desktop or sync to their portable audio devices
and listen on the go. So it is exactly what we're doing here only I think these guys
have it completely backwards and upside down. What they're doing is they've created
another gateway, they're gatekeepers to getting stuff onto your mobile device and
that's what you pay for. You basically pay for their technology to work on your
system whereas we've created you know little scripts some fewer than a hundred
lines long which do exactly the same thing. Now here's the here's what I
really don't understand and these guys are funded they have VCs on the board
so they've got money. They have providers so you can become a
provider which means you probably pay a license to use their technology to
get onto their distribution system and they have here as providers A&E
AARP, Animal Talk Radio, BBC, Beatles Arama, Blue, Bloomberg, Cape Cod Radio, Consumer
Reports, C-SPAN, Discovery Channel, Dow Jones, Fox, Grateful Dead, John Hopkins.
They've got some smaller providers in there as well, but the fact that you have to become
a provider and register with them just makes no sense to me.
We already have this technology available at our fingertips and it's working now and
it's free.
All you have to do is work out your own copyright issues.
So although I applaud them for what they're doing and for the thought behind it,
it just doesn't make any sense to me because we're doing exactly what Audio
Feast is offering here.
Only we're using the existing technology.
You know, I don't think we should be locked into anything that gives them
power over access to whatever we want to have.
Also, I don't want to have to pay anyone more than my provider for
whatever bandwidth I use to publish something.
But I linked to this on my weblog at curate.com, so check it out.
And if anyone actually decides to sign up, subscribe and use it,
we'd love to have a review and see if there's anything that we can use in our own system.
Okay, time for our song of the day. Already 30 minutes into this,
so I have a few more things I want to talk about after the song of the day,
which will be about iPhoto and about Skype.
And this one came in through the Blog Digger Media Feed.
It's a classic song from the 80s.
I wouldn't have chosen this one if it hadn't come in automatically,
but I've decided to try and do as many sounds around the net as possible.
I don't know if they're doing another reunion so I can do it about once every year.
I won't make the love of you, baby
You won't make the love of me
Baby, I can't make the love of you, baby
Then you can't love me tonight
you
Kiss! I was made for loving you. I think that was 1979. Maybe the right time now to tell
my one of my kiss stories. I was working at MTV. Let's see, this was 1987 or 1988 at
the time I believe. And I was one of the, actually I was the only air talent as they
called it, who wanted to sit in the music meetings which is basically where we
decided what we're gonna play and what rotation videos are gonna be played. Very
much in fact it was run exactly like a radio station certainly in those days
using the same type of music scheduling software and there were radio
people who were basically doing the programming lineup. Of course this was
MTV played videos right and we had our music meeting I want to say it was
Tuesdays and Kiss had a video out. God I can't remember what it was now but we were
all sitting in the music meeting.
and all of a sudden the door bursts open and in comes Gene Simmons
and he's got knee pads on
and he jumps up onto this big conference room table
and we're all sitting around it right being really serious
picking the music videos deciding whose career we're going to make or break
and he hops up and he goes over to Abbie Konowicz
who later went on to co-found Madonna's record label Maverick
and he's on all fours and he's right in front of Abbie Konowicz
and says alright who do I have to blow around here to get this video played
hilarity ensued and of course the video was added goes without saying
so to wind up things for today's source code
I want to thank everyone for the feedback I've received on Skype
so no Skype and SIP, those are two different protocols used for voiceover IP
they're also not compatible with each other, at least not yet
can't talk to each other. There's no super advantage behind using Skype versus some of
the other VoVIP systems from what I gather. Other than that it does just seem to work,
which is exactly what they advertised. You can't get any inbound service, that I already
knew. They have the Skype out, which I'm fairly happy with, works very well. Because
the peer-to-peer nature of how they do things, it is suggested in some cases, although
I haven't witnessed it personally, that there can be a lot of latency in the
phone calls. And also so far no one has really been able to give me any solution
for what I'm looking for, which is a voice over IP provider that will let
me use a software phone as well as a voice over IP hardware to connect my
analog phone. And I want a local dial-up number in Los Angeles, in New York, in
Amsterdam, in Antwerp, and in London.
That's what I want and I'm willing to pay for it. So please, if you're working on a service,
just keep my wishes in mind, will you? And the largest advantage that Skype has over all the
voice over IP setups that I've come to understand is that they have the firewall issue solved.
And of course, they were able to solve this because they're using their kaza technology.
It's made by the same guys who created kaza. And they had the firewall issues all sorted
out there. So that's the number one thing that Skype is really good at.
And to wrap it up for today, I wanted to talk about iPhoto. Don't know if you recall that I was
really running out of disk space. I was continuously deleting stuff from caches.
We all know the drill, right? You go searching for files larger than 5 megs.
What can I do with this? And either way to move some stuff off. And the two largest
collections of data that I have, excuse me, are without a doubt my music folder.
and my pictures folder. And the decision about music was pretty easy because I really need
access to that at a moment's notice on my hard drive for the type of work that I'm producing
like the source code. So I've been cleaning up my iTunes library as I go, you know, just
pulling out old shit, old audiobooks that I don't need anymore, which are huge files.
You know, we're talking 80 megs for some of them, and that's just, you know, in
three different parts. So I've been able to find a lot of space there, but the pictures,
which is all in the iPhoto album folder, that was about six gigs. No, a little less,
I'm sorry, about four and a half gigs. And I knew that, you know, if I could move those
off, at least if I have them on some kind of safe storage device, I know that I'll be
able to use them later on. I wasn't too sure how easy that was going to be, but I
just wanted to say that with iPhoto it's really phenomenal. Now I'd never used the DVD
burning capabilities of my power book. So I didn't know, you know, I was total newbie at
this and went to...
the store and of course promptly bought the wrong DVDs there is a difference between plus R or plus
RW and minus R or minus RW for two different technologies of how the DVDs are burned and if
you you know do it incorrectly then they won't play on different machines and God knows what.
So I went back same place by the way where we bought the exercise bike.
It's a great store and I got the minus RW because I can actually use optical discs that are
rewritable. Now this was pretty cool I've never erased a DVD and I actually practiced with that and
it worked and worked perfectly and so then in iPhoto there's a little button you just select all your
pictures and I couldn't get all of them onto one DVD because it would it just it would take up
too much space and I guess it's 4.7 gigs that fit onto a DVD and with some overhead I couldn't quite
get everything on there from 1999 to 2004 to date so I split it up into 99 through 2003.
three, just click the burn button out to select those pictures.
Actually, I made a little smart playlist that says, you know, select all photos between these
two dates.
Burn that to DVD, popped it out, did the other one for 2004.
And of course, I checked and made sure everything was working.
I had a whole backup copy on a firewire drive before I deleted the iTunes, the picture,
the iPhoto library references.
And what's cool about it is now when I insert one of those two DVDs, it automatically fires
up iTunes and presents me with the pictures exactly the way they were when they were on
my hard drive.
And the speed between getting them off the DVD and the hard drive is slower, but it's
certainly manageable and I can whip up a slideshow and all the albums are still intact.
So that is absolutely well done, very happy.
And again, I think that sometimes those guys at Apple, man, they're probably smoking
the same stuff that we are here down on Earth.
And that's it for source code for today.
We'll be back on Monday.
If you want a response, send me email to adamanturi.com or leave a comment on my web
The power of the author.
Daily source code dot com slash rss dot xml.
See you Monday!
The power of the author.