Ladies and gentlemen, Islanders of iPod, behold our new sovereign leader, bow down for the
Earl of everybody, the Duke of Doyle, the parent of broadband, the Sultan of Starbucks,
the king of his castle, and the tyrant of peace-pilling, but most of all, the prince of
pod, Mr. Adam Curry!
Adam Curry!
Please obey his rule for he shall punish you at SIGTO YOU AGAIN!
Get ready baby, oh Adam, Adam, oh, it's the daily source code!
Everybody, it's Monday, it's December 13th, 2004, welcome to the daily source code where
users and developers party together on feeling good friends, family, world leaders.
I know you're all listening to this podcast.
It's time for your source code.
I got everything I want, right here, right here in my cottage, baby, I got my tea and
I have it on the other side of the wire, so we won't have the horrific tea-spilling accident,
reprise the low-echatars, cannot handle it whatsoever, man, I got a jam-pack show for you,
actually took a screenshot of my flat panel display that I have on the low-echatars, so
you can see how many different sound clips I have lined up for today's show.
It's about 20 hours, it's about 20 hours, it's about 20 hours, it's about 20 hours, we've got
comments, we've got music, we've got feedback, we've got lots of stuff to talk about, particularly
well, we've got so much feedback on the trade secrets that the David I did, I got to talk
about that a little bit, see what else do we have lined up.
It's just an incredible amount, you know, particularly because on Friday I did the podcast
from Studio A8 with Anneli, Anneli Nuitts, who, by the way, she's not a reporter from
wired, she's a journalist and she's a writer, and she was hired by wired to do this particular
piece.
Ah, this profile on me, the profile of the Prince of Bob.
Okay, this actually tells you a little bit more about this show.
Greetings, program!
It's not any time for a drum song, because we use it.
I'm completely operational, and all my circuits are functioning perfectly.
I'm certainly in the mood for a party.
No time for that now, the computer's starting, can you please program us out of the system?
Shall we play a game?
My user has information that you can make this a free system again.
It's party time!
Yeah, for me the RT, why?
Because I got up!
This is your daily source code.
Yeah.
Hey, bud!
This party!
Wow!
Your users and developers are party together.
Oh, I can't thank you guys enough for all the shit you send in to me, it makes
my job so wonderfully easy.
One of the things that I've been getting a lot of feedback on is download issues with
the source code.
There's about time that we talked about this on the show, because at first I thought,
well, look, there's so many people subscribing, there's got to be a certain percentage
that will just fall by the wayside, and I think that's still a part of the issue here.
But I have seen myself, and we're also using the same servers for Don and Drew, and
I know we've offered it to cover Bill, I don't know if cover Bill needs any help yet.
But I have seen some intermittent download issues, and I'm not quite sure, I'm pretty
sure it's not our server, because we've got a server that's doing nothing else, but
just sitting there and serving up files.
We have an unmetered pipe on that server.
Now, granted that there's a limitation to it, and I think that we're, see, they're 20
30 megabit pipe, which should be enough.
I mean, what's happening here is there's so many people trying to grab these files at
the same time that it is slowing down.
The slowness is not a problem, when it stops, that's when it clearly is a problem, and
something that we've got to figure out.
I really don't know what could be doing this other than, well, it's still, of course,
it could be the server itself, although I doubt it, it's just getting hammered by requests,
but it's not really that.
I have my doubts about it being the bandwidth provider, because that seems just like,
it's okay, the bandwidth is there, somewhere there's something taking place, it's not
right, and there's another thing that we probably should look at, and lots of comments and
emails about this in the production show notes for this particular source code, is we need
resumable downloads, because I, you know, with my, as too far as of thus yet, still deprived,
or bandwidth deprived situation, I've had a lot of time to play around with what works
and what doesn't work, and most podcasts, by the way, are so popular, and I guess even
more than a couple hundred people subscribing is popular enough to crunch most pipes
throughput, that they're really not coming in that much faster than modem speeds, depending
on when your iPodder is grabbing this stuff, of course.
So if I run my iPodder at night, I pretty much get everything I want in the morning,
even though it's coming over a phone line, because it's still bringing it in sequentially.
So if you sleep eight or nine hours, I pretty much get the podcast I need, because it could
take an hour for, an hour for basically a 40, 45 minute to an hour podcast to come
in, depending on how it was encoded.
But sometimes shit does just happen, particularly on dial-up, you know, you get kicked off,
bandwidth just goes away temporarily, and I think that's something that we need to look
at in our iPodders in the, you know, basically the iPod, catching the podcasting clients
is, how do we ensure that if it's something breaks, that it continues to try and get it,
or at least gives up after a smart, something after ruleset, something that really means
it's not available, because if this is happening to me, it may be happening to Don and
Drew, and it could be happening to a number of people.
And I actually, I created my, my really real poor man's iPodder in OSX on the command line.
This is a wonderful command called Curl, CURL, and if you give it a URL, and so let's
just say I give it a URL of an MP3 file, what you want to do is you want to give it an
OSWITCH, a capital O and a capital C. The capital O, so basically you do Curl space minus
capital O, which means it's going to output the same name as, as it is when you're downloading
it, and then the minus C switch means it's going to check and see if it, if it, if it
has to resume this download, and it works really, really well. I've been using it, so I had
this whole list of URLs that have stuff that I want to download that aren't necessarily
iPodder subscriptions, just stuff that I've seen, maybe coming through an audio.weblogs.com.
So I added to this list of URLs, and if I want to do something else, because of course,
that's the problem if you're downloading MP3s, you don't really have a lot of bandwidth left
over to do anything else, or basically you don't, certainly not the porn that I'm used
to do on download. So then you just hit Control C, and it stops that, and then you can
fire up that process again, and it picks up where it left off. So, resume will download,
something we definitely got to look at in the iPodder community. And so Melts, we got
to keep our eye on, is these damn mashups, man. I love them. Check this out. It's a mashup
from SmashUp Derby. What the fuck is going on? Jet Lady Joe. On the source code.
That would be your day to source code, but Monday, December 13th.
What the fuck is going on?
They be Madonna. You're natural feet. Wonder how you manage to make ends meet. Who finds
the money? When you pay the rent? Did you think that money was so good?
They'd be Madonna. Baby have to rest. Wonder how you manage to make ends meet.
They'd be Madonna. Right on the bed. Listen to the music playing in your head.
Said I ain't going to remind you.
Baby, Madonna. Baby, Madonna. Baby, Madonna. Baby, Madonna. Baby, Madonna.
I could see you. Oh, baby. But you are with me. I can't help. I know we got
but to save the money to get away. Yeah, be my girl. Be my girl. I can't help being my girl.
Be my girl. Be my girl. I can't help being my girl.
SmashUp Derby. Jet Lady Joe. What the fuck is going on?
I'm listening to my own show. I listen back to it on my iPod.
I'm going to rewind that. Listen to it again. I suggest you do the same.
Welcome back. How good was that?
I have to apologize because so many cool things were sent in.
I thought I'd kind of organized a lot of the emails.
What happens often is someone will send something like this Jet Lady Joe.
This mashup, smashup Derby.
And it'll come in an email and then I will save the MP3.
And I thought I'd save the email that went along with this, but clearly I didn't.
This is my pathetic attempt at an excuse.
Podcast. Podcast. Podcast.
Podcast. Open Podcast.org. Podcast.
Podcast.
Hey, this is Alan Joyce from the Heavens Digital Podcast.
And if you're interested in hearing the latest technology news with some non-RAA music
to go along with it, then head on over to everythingdigital.org and subscribe to the
Heavens Digital Podcast RSS feed at everythingdigital.org slash RSS.xml.
I've got 75 gigabytes of bandwidth just waiting for this guy.
So, come on over and check it out.
That's the new pickup line by the way. Hey, baby.
I got 75 gigs of bandwidth. Why'd you come over my blaze and dig off your dress?
This is your daily source code. I'm Adam Curry.
The Prince of Pod. Oh, we're going to get to that later.
There was another Prince of Pod thing. Oh, I have so much to do with unbelievable.
Lots of responses to the trade secret podcast that David I did.
First of all, about the sound quality, I have to admit we did a test with my with my phone recording
it before we did the show, the whole show.
And the test did sound better than the way the show came out.
Part of that is Dave's voice is completely just shot.
Actually, this is a recent podcast that he's done.
It's to call the Dave sexy voice demo.
Just listen to how he sounds. It's not very good at all.
And this is a more higher quality recording than the one you had on the trade secrets podcast.
I'm very intense evening of schmoozing and hanging out with the people at Berkman and Kennedy School
and Joe Trippie and Zach Rosen.
I have almost no voice left. It's a really getting ridiculous.
I'm asked to go see a doctor.
Luckily, they have good doctors here and they know me.
So probably if it doesn't give much better signal probably going anyway.
It's one of the demos you all could hear how sexy one of the voice sounds.
Oh, maybe I got 75 gigs of bandwidth for you sexy boy.
Okay, so we got a lot of comments about the sound quality.
Also, when you, if you don't talk directly into the phone, you know, when you kind of,
I don't know, I think it's, we weren't paying that much attention.
We're having a good conversation actually.
We weren't paying a lot of attention to the sound quality.
And this is, now you're seeing how hard it is to really make sure you get something.
You know, maybe you appreciate the sound guy.
It's a little bit more.
When you see him with that big boom microphone and all those meters and dials.
I mean, this is what's about.
It's very difficult to get good audio.
And particularly if it's more than just one person talking in a space and you want everything
to kind of sound the same and everything to be, to be legible.
And some people actually had no problem at all.
You know, it's, it's all a matter of what you can here actually.
But anyway, the, the content of the conversation is what really it was good for me.
And the fact that we, you know, have these, have had these plans to start a company.
It's really good to be able to just talk about it now.
Just say, okay, so we don't have a name for it yet.
But otherwise, you know, we're pretty far along with, with what we want it to do.
And, and you know, as we were talking about the three, you know, there's basically three parts to it.
But the most exciting I think we all agree is, is the podcast is the content itself of these shows that we're making.
And, you know, what is it?
I mean, I'm still trying to capture, you know, this magic.
I don't think it's capturable.
It's, you know, the magic is something that's out there and you can't really define it.
And, but somehow it's, it's working.
It really is working.
And, and I got to tell you, if for someone who's been in broadcasting so long, I'm totally used to people saying,
Oh, you know, saw your show or heard your show, yes, they would ever.
But now when people say, I heard your podcast, it's, it's, it's great.
I mean, it is, it's the same.
It's basically the same feeling is, is, you know, the first time I was really on big time radio or on, on MTV.
But it's, it's a fresh new feeling because it is something new.
It is something fresh sky.
I mean, that was a, what the hell we're doing.
But, a lot of people certainly want to help, even if they do or don't understand it.
And I'm going to play a bit of this audio comment that that I got from, I think it's,
Todd and I'll interrupt him here and there to talk about some of the topics he's producing.
Hey, they're out of Mrs. Todd.
And, I just listened to the latest trade secrets.
All I can say is, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring, boring boring.
boring boring boring boring boring at any rate i'm really excited about you guys getting
the ball rolling with a company and i'm sure it's early for this but i'm gonna help out
i want to do whatever i can i'll make myself fully available to you guys so if it's for
brain storming or any little bit of coding that i might be able to do or whatever i'm there
find me at studiogeek.org and uh yeah this thing's gonna be great thanks
i was um i was thinking of a different comment that's gonna come in that was talking about
some OP mail stuff but uh Todd thank you very much for your generous offer and boring indeed
and this is what we're what we're seeing all kinds of people are saying hey you know count me in
and whatever we could and it's not like i'm looking for a job that's what i what i like about it
i've also heard some uh some negative noises you know like oh i thought you guys were only
you know trying to build a vibe in in podcasting and like well that's exactly what we're trying
to do and wouldn't you rather that you know people are gonna make money in podcasting so
ones and people are already making money and if it was just about money believe me either i or
Dave could have started to make money in a number of different ways lots of people are offering
sponsorships and you know but that's not what this is about there's something much
much bigger that that that is coming it is truly it is the people's media it is the people's
network um when someone said a long time ago the internet is like citizens banned fucking you know
it's it is it's true only the you know we're not limited to the 40 sandals channels uh and uh 40
upper side band and 40 lower side band remember the SSB oh man i was so into that i was so
in the SS single side band uh CB radio when only we cut cut resistors in the next the chipset
and it would give you another or a diode i think it was it would give you another 120 channels
anyone out there you should do that it would use to sit on those upper frequencies near the 28
megahertz band anyway um i should almost replay what i just said to figure out what i was trying to say
yeah uh my point being that you know if people are gonna make money on on podcasting and they're
gonna create companies and uh i think anyone would want to at least have a company in the market
place that is open and and you know and honest about what they're doing and what their intentions are
and is basically trying to party with everyone else to figure out what we need to do so uh but right
after um right after Christmas um when my uh when my conveniently with my in-laws are here
that's when i take off to the states i'm gonna hook up with uh with Dave and Ron and uh we're gonna
you know get some uh get some shit going so i'm extremely extremely excited about uh about that
and throughout the podcast hope to touch out in the gosh already 20 minutes i gotta hurry along here
i'll be touching on more more stuff as we go along and this is Chris Chaffey in Richmond Virginia just
want to say i love the show and make a comment about the religious podcast that you've been
shined on your show i think this is the first time that religion has found the technology on
the internet before pornography uh i just thought that was really interesting and um so anyway keep
up the great work and y'all talk to later uh boy oh yeah religion found well but what is religion
and what is pornography and are the interchangeable here's a clip from the new dawn and
drew movie road to ruin so tonight at the dawn and drew um house the cause the dawn and drew
house what you're listening to is the dawn and drew show right but there's the dawn and true house
and the dawn and drew car and the dawn and drew barn that's right so this is taking place in the
dawn and drew kitchen that's in the house everything has brand to do see i see i i gotcha okay so
i'm with you don't interrupt me okay okay remember okay i talked about this okay
true okay i'm not going to talk go ahead are you going to not interrupt me i will not interrupt you
promise promise can you make that promise i'll try all right
or more sounds like these subscribe to found sound dot net audio fragments from around the web
that's like some kind of really twisted performance art but i'm totally digging that and there you go
it's the dawn and drew house the dawn and drew kitchen it's all sponsored everything's brand
is that what we're going with dawn and drew i don't think so um and was it um Wednesday or Tuesday
i was taught well spoken about uh dawn many times of course because yeah she's like my girlfriend and
um the fact that she said something to me at bloggercon that has been such an incredible
stimulus such a motivating factor in me staying away from all types of tobacco now remember i still
like the holy herb but very little of it but no tobacco and it was very easy actually to go back
through the production notes on dawn and drew dot com which are also an opml which and which is
this outliner format if you if you haven't seen this before um we're hoping david and i are hoping
you get an open source outliner out there so you can play with this yourself but essentially
that's that's how the production notes are made and that's how i can you can look at them on the
web that way and it kind of an outlone outliner rendered format but what i really like is looking
at them in an outliner and you can just you know click stuff and it's all kind of a one place
but it also makes searching this outline very easy and so i just you know when and look for some
references to smoking and i came up with a December second uh podcast uh dawn and drew show and
actually the bit that well the stimulating um piece that the dawn said that um i want you to hear
because it it really has helped me stay away from tobacco um it really has let's uh drop it
to the conversation you're only being heavy that i could contribute to this earth okay so basically
talking about um about uh dawn's mom she would be a smoke in our baby's face and i said that too
i said grandma cannot blow smoke in baby's face and my mom said i blew smoke in your face and
you're a baby to make you not want to smoke cigarettes which i don't smoke it's a good thing then
and i'm quite anti-accus smoke yes i am because it kills you yeah and your boyfriend alluded
today in a show that he put out yesterday that uh he's still and that he still hasn't smoked
now isn't this nice don't we have a beautiful open relationship
it's so nice to know that you know drew recognizes that i'm dawn's boy
good job Adam you guys if you smoke cigarettes you're totally sucking on the
cock of big brother that was it that was the entire line listen to it again because it will help you
as well it is beautiful if you smoke cigarettes you're totally sucking on the cock of big brother
and that that is that goes so deep in so many ways just sucking on the cock of big brother
yeah i i should play this over and over in my life if you smoke cigarettes you're totally
sucking on the cock of big brother there you go play that over and if you're smoker play that
over and over again and think about what that really means and that's your choice and you're right
because it's your body but go for it there's gonna be drew and I and Adam gray whatever one i'll
that's right all right a clip for the archives ladies and gents here's the uh the longer
uh comment that came in that i want to discuss a little bit about uh this is from uh coanbremor
Adam hi this is coanbremor uh calling from the new forester a few miles to the south west of
you at the moment uh just a few things first of all by the way it's a colleague from the UK
all uh i wanted to say thank you for playing music by the lascivious videos on the daily source code
i heard you play famous by them and thought that a few seconds of that will be a fantastic intro
and outro to my own podcast um so following your example i emailed lianne uh west over uh who
replied with a lovely email uh among other things given me permission so respect to yourself for
making me aware their music respect to them for saying yep you can do that and i was
chuffed a piece is to hear that they're uh they're selling tons of CDs as a result of your
plugs so uh so well done everybody who's uh bought CDs from them i was also uh interested in
your comments about iPodda and some of the drawbacks when you're in a restricted bandwidth situation
man i got to put this whole thing up so you can listen to him talk about uh he has so many good
ideas that i'd hope that the iPodda developers listen to this oh put this uh up as a separate
MP3 file i want to move ahead because he's he started to talk about OP about what the second
thing is i was wondering whether i was actually missing a trick with the OPML file whether it was supposed
to be used in some way with the um with the MP3 file uh i suspect probably not but then i've got
to thinking well what if you could you know what if now check this out because this is what i've been
trying to figure out i've been trying to figure out the you know these OPML files basically it's
perfect for for production and i've and i've you know i've done radio production for a long time
so to have an outline or to be able to do that works beautifully now the thing about these
about OPML and and what what Dave and i call the uh he calls the internet outliner so i've
picked up that that word the internet outliner um because it's all connected and i can open up
the outline to someone you know to someone else's outline it's exactly the way if if you're
maintaining a node on the iPodda or directory or if you want to i mean basically all i need to do
is is create an OPML file and these are all linked together so it seems logical that that's
exactly what we're going to do with these production nodes how that ties into the actual RSS feed
and the actual um ID3 tags i'm not quite sure that's what i'm looking to figure out what if the
technology was clever enough to to consume the OPML file while you're actually playing the MP3 file
so for example you could embed the name of the OPML file in one of the ID3 tags and then a suitable
client be that a software application or media player of some sort or a hardware device like
a you know an ex-generation iPod or something like that could for example display the appropriate part
of the OPML nodes when you're at the appropriate part of the MP3 file or possibly even interacts
depending upon your um security settings right i'd like to start simple first of all i mean that
that would be that would be the best part that would be the easiest and it's all just about ease of
used really i mean this is just to be able to to see something simply um and it's really um i have
all these tools that that i've collected and i've been working on um that allow me to just basically
hit a button and any MP3 files that i've thrown into this one folder on my desktop is then loaded into
an outline and it's loaded in with you know uh by the ID3 tag so it's the artist the album which
is usually the person uh and then you know uh sometimes they'll have their URL as the album uh and
then the actual sound clip itself which of course when i double click that sound clip and uh again
i have this uh this great screenshot that i'll uh that i'll put up for you uh that i should
did of uh just before i started today's podcast when you double click on that no then uh it opens up
the appropriate MP3 file in a quick time player and it starts playing it uh so it's just it's just
an interface basically and ease of use i really see this ease of use but we can connect it all together so
that's the kind of stuff that we got to figure out um and i'll make a note here that i also
put up uh cones entire uh wait there's also an email version of his comment oh that's cool okay so
I'll put that in the uh in the production notes as well and moving right along more promos
hi Adam this is Andy McCaskey from slash.review and RV business review going through some podcast
music i found this track uh on garageband.com and it just has source code written all over it give
a listen alright hit it then
i'm starting singing on i'm singing right now
starting writing just a minute and go i'm almost done and just and goes to show
don't have to wrap the words before recording
this is a song about it
down yeah let's hear the song about it and say
doesn't make any sense it's not supposed to
oh
hi i'm Mads Weinstein and you are listening to yeast radio
today i'm just doing a quick promo so that everybody can hear how wonderful yeast radio is
and how wonderful i am now you may not know me if you don't read the tabloids but i am a very
famous lesbian and the rock band manager for the famous girl band that's girl g double rl
goddess ria too as well today i'm gonna just give you a quick sneak preview when i'm gonna play one of
these phony phone calls that we love to play over on yeast radio so uh here we go let's have a listen
so this is um another promo that came in for yeast radio yeah you got to listen to all the
phone gags i wasn't too crazy about most of them but um this whole Mads Weinstein never really
intrigues me the things like getting it now oh hold on oh no that's a quick preview i need to
not say for work everybody video we took primarily about vaginal yeast but you see we also talk
about other things like getting it out i hemorrhoids high five basirial and why they make
you shit such big chunks that you can hardly flush down the toilet we have all kinds of fun
on yeast radio i'm Mads Weinstein and to get to this for now anyway you go to my weblog
match underscore Weinstein dot live journal dot com once again match underscore Weinstein
dot live journal dot com excellent um magic uh forget the phony phone calls
Mads just do a podcast just talk just you know say whatever's on your mind that'll be beautiful
uh let me see uh what i have so many things left that i want to play i guess i have to
save some of this for tomorrow as is usually the case except for uh i'll get to play some
rest of web audio for you
this is uh web audio for about four well oh eight you want drum we got drum
this would be the old kind of block high school band i believe and we're coming up to the
drums drums are the crystalian loudest part of the band and you can hear it right loud
guys with the trumpets don't need to be doing much we have a number of two more players doing
nothing and now there's some girls holding some brightly colored things in their hands
actually okay cheerleaders and there's a rack you're terrorizing your child
coony actually codes hey coony that's coony right there I guess play it to us
and there goes the uh we'll be getting in the parade basically we'll be back after these past
those are cheerleaders those are cheerleaders dad for asked a rare audio good ill beat
and actually um uh peaked did uh another rastware audio they want to play for you which i want
to try and do you know some christmas stuff now that we're getting into uh the season uh to be
this this season to be jolly uh it's really big here in in gulford everywhere you hear it's it's
all holiday cheer um so if you got any of that send it on along uh to the source code um i'm
going to do uh bit of rastware uh which was actually it's a pretty serious and lovely message
like we couldn't expect that from peaked all right this is rastware audio for
well 11 you know we we have a lot of fun here you know we like to joke around we like to have a
good time but i want to be serious for a minute here feet the world yes feet the world it's very
powerful message i think it brings great hope to people you know it's it can kind of bring us all
together for a great cause and i try to do what i can i try to do what i can for that cause i try
to feed the world you're wondering how i do that well i provide to the world and rastest
2.0 feet and atoms 0.3 feet and rastest 1.0 feet and rastest or 0.91 feet and most importantly
rastest 2.0 feet within closures yes so this holiday season i want to ask you all please
feed the world thank you and good all right actually um you know band aid do they know it's Christmas
oh shoot i should play that um and i did buy it that is now number one in the 9 kingdom and
basically would bob gild off and and everyone who's worked on the record this is a second time
has been down the second version i guess it is is it 10 years later since uh since live aid i
must be yeah 90 no 20 years since live aid i'm sorry um is they just said to people hey you know
it's a really expensive cd uh or a cd single um it costs you more uh than usual but that's because
all this money is going to feed the world the feed people in africa and uh Britain's are
really great about that they go out and they buy this thing and now it's number one and bob gild off
was on tv at top of the pops you know it's the big the big music show uh and he was an africa
and he said i'm gonna actually do something really weird he says i want you to go out next week
and buy the record again please uh as you was thanking everyone for it uh going the number one
and these guys have done some amazing work they they really have um uh it's it's made a difference
it has made a difference um so feed the world um and yeah if you do that with your rss 2.0
feed that's cool okay i can i can contribute no problem or that's very transmats very transmats
next person says Merry Christmas to me i'll come hey Adam it's Kevin from scouts.net Merry Christmas
i just wanted to let you know the scouts.net will be featuring nothing but Christmas music
for the rest of December from the obscure
what can you get i wouldn't care Christmas when he already oh i call the classics
so this is christmas
and what have you done to some stuff you've never heard before
so tune in to the scouts.net christmas cast excellent oh that's a uh a low phased boring let's hear
that one again that was good that was pretty good that was a bad one okay scouts.net got some good
stuff going on the christmas cast um and i was talking to uh uh to analy new it's um i don't
we've talked about on the podcast on Friday or not but we certainly talked about it at Starbucks
how how shitty it really is you know that we can't play music that is associated with you know
with with our memories um which you know it was what sharing sharing music should be about
and that especially when it comes to christmas stuff man there is so i mean so many different christmas
songs or holiday songs in general um uh or just songs. it means so much to so many people and you
know if i if i were to play a certain song right now it would mean something to you it would mean
mean something to me and and at that moment it's uh it's very powerful it raised up a lot of emotions
and the fact that we can't do that is is really a bummer um sucks i think i think i don't know if
i'm gonna be able to make it all the way up until the new year without playing something that
maybe not sanctioned i don't know and of course i'm not gonna get away from the prince of the pod even
though i have uh kept my vow not to release and not to let any way slip out of my hands uh the
MP3 of my version of the prince of the pod you can uh count on people like bill to um and that's
bull uh bill uh dovet i believe the DOU THET to do his own version um with his own music and with
his own new lyrics. it's only about two minutes if you want to skip ahead or just hand out
i ain't got no internet of uh two hours of Don and Drew puts us all into the moon and uh
male of feeds by our means prince of the pod she's a good good Larry new copter on the way
day
go for UK
or that my can choose i don't pay no or i do this one
that ones i have found here i can't find them around them uh
man of means by all means
prince of the pod
all right thank you very much for the love
that's gonna do it for today's daily source code uh left with lots more comments and uh
pod safe music that we got to get to tomorrow and also as we move into uh into the holiday
five we'll be uh recalling some memories right we've played some two two matches
okay so those uh this is a good start for the week lots more to do lots more that needs to happen
stuff happening uh around uh the cottage uh we have to find stables for Christina's pony who's
still been uh he was left back in Belgium got to work on that more dimmers to be installed
but do a lot of dimmer work of course still going back and forth to Starbucks but it looks like
December 20th the band is new and we're all over the world okay one other thing i want to mention
um i'm working on uh new server and consolidating some of my uh my different website infrastructure
uh so uh keep your eye on curie dot com i'm basically gonna fold everything down the curie dot
com let's keep your eye on that that's we can leave a comment or of course you can always
email it to be out of a pretty dot com if it's under like you know five mags go ahead and just uh send
an audio attachment metal cash overnight take care see you tomorrow
you