We are casting all's life, and I'm curry.
Hi everybody and good evening.
Or good afternoon.
Good morning.
Whatever it is, where you are.
Welcome to your daily source code.
It's Thursday, October 21st, 2004.
I'm not a curry coming to you from Flanders, Belgium.
We're back in the bar slash studio here at Curry Castle.
It's been a long day today.
As you know, I stayed over at the bunker last night in Amsterdam,
and I had the shareholders meeting today.
Sat in plenty of traffic, although I did contemplate reporting the source code in the car.
I had so many clips and bits I had set up and wanted to play for,
but I decided just to wait till I got home.
We've got the in-laws here tonight.
Oh, my pie has a little bit harder hearing,
so that you might be at the TV in the background,
because we like to crank it up for him.
Can I say hello?
And you may hear some keyboard rattling in the background,
as well as Christina.
What are you doing, huh?
What are you doing?
And TV message board.
Don't tell me you're posting good Charlotte stuff.
Okay, she's yelling at people for saying good Charlotte.
That's right.
Anyway, so we've got the source code cranked on this side of our community space here in the castle.
And the first thing I want to say is,
there is almost no way to express my thanks,
but also that of my family for the incredible outpouring of good thoughts and prayers and love.
And just wonderful words and hundreds of emails and stories that you shared.
Weblog postings.
It was really absolutely phenomenal.
And there were so many audio comments that came in.
We were all just totally dumbfounded.
It was absolutely beautiful.
I thank you so much.
And I could fill three daily source codes with just the audio comments alone that were said.
It was so beautiful.
And so I'm not going to delve on it too long and play too much stuff.
I can tell you, though, that mom underwent her PET scan today.
That's the radioactive fluid.
And I spoke to her after the test and she sounded great.
She was really happy with her first volume experience.
And she's really extremely positive and everything you've said and done really, really helps.
So I'm not going to, I do with this one particular audio comment I wanted to say,
I wanted to play for you that was sent in because there were just some things that really picked me up and gave me a lot of energy, a great energy boost.
And the bit I'm going to play for you is from Raymond Port, who, well, if you don't remember,
I met him just a couple of weeks ago for the first time while on the road in traffic.
Here's what he sent to me in light of yesterday's source code.
Hello, world.
Anyone there?
Sounds kind of funny to start.
I know the recording of like this, but I think it's appropriate being the first audio recordings since,
I don't know, five, six years.
It's supposed to be an audio comment to the daily source code of 20 of October, 2010 and 4.
Adam, yes, so that you got me in probably many others wondering, what does that mean?
Why is there no daily source codes?
There must be probably a very good reason for that.
Well, today in the show it turned out to be actually a very bad reason.
Didn't use about your mom.
Well, you're telling sharing actually your feelings and explaining why and how and what it got me,
also emotional and probably others too.
It showed actually that there's one thing that you really have what it takes to get the reality of life into the show.
And this has happened many times before.
One time, I remember as the day of two weeks ago almost.
And that's when we kind of met when you were doing your daily source codes recording from the car.
And I was passing by in traffic jam.
It got me to the energy boost that you were talking about.
And I thought it would be nice to give you a little bit of energy back.
Take care in coming days, weeks, months.
And remember that many are with you in thoughts.
See ya.
So, but it was cool and college radio is cool.
And this podcast...
Hey, someone's holding up his iPod.
Hold on, roll on your window.
Exit the net, thank you all for the name.
Here, come here.
What's going on there?
Rainbow boards.
Okay dude.
Dude, we checked out a guy just drove up next to me.
And he's honking his horn and he's holding his iPod off.
And he's saying, I'm listening to the podcast.
God damn, I said, I'm recording one right now.
It's a Raymond.
Buddy.
Oh, that's very cool.
See?
This is what I mean.
This is what it's all about.
Oh, that gives me a boost of energy.
So, you can imagine that I got another boost as I heard that again.
And remember that, you know, I have a new friend.
His name is Raymond.
You know, we met two weeks ago on the highway.
Thanks to the podcasting.
And just so much good and positive energy coming from all over the world.
Really, really appreciated.
And so, as I was alone in the bunker last night,
and I had the bandwidth all to myself.
Of course, we have a high-speed connection there as well.
Only there's no bandwidth limits at all.
So, I was subscribing and checking out audio.weblogs.com
and listening to everything new is it popped up, you know,
refreshing the page.
Like, oh, what's this?
You know, it's a new one.
By the way, if you want to get on audio.weblogs.com,
it's real simple.
All you have to do is ping the server.
And it's a great place for, it's a great resource
to go and check out what's, you know, was just updated.
So, even if you have iPod or, you know,
just anywhere browser will let, you know,
if one of your favorites is updated or you might find something
that's completely new that you didn't know about before.
And there's information on how to ping the server
either through a web form or there's some technical information
there about how you're blogging client and blogging tool
can do it.
And there's lots of people all over the place who will be willing to help you.
So, as I was checking out the new shows and the regular shows,
my day completely, completely was made.
I mean, I was just, I was bugging out.
I was so happy.
I was listening to the Dawn and Drew show from two days earlier
because I was catching up.
And I heard, I mean, I heard just the most beautiful,
beautiful poem, and I want to share it with you.
I need an iPod.
I need it so bad.
I would give blow jobs on the corner.
They'd be the best you ever had.
If you gave me an iPod, I'd suck on your wiener.
I'm half with a wiener and half Colombian being here.
Oh man, that really made my day.
So, as promised, some indie music for you.
I'm going to kick it off with some Dutch guys.
Oh, we're way happy that they're on the podcast.
Recording entirely on a Macintosh in their attic.
It's my Jones and TV junkie.
Oh, I can't tell you now.
What's your long childhood dream?
I can't take it in the world.
But something keeps me there.
And I'm all alone.
I'll treat you turn it off again.
Maybe it won't come to an end.
Oh, I can't take it in the world.
I can't take it in the world.
No, no.
But something keeps me there.
I'm all alone.
I'll treat you turn it off again.
Maybe it won't come to an end.
Oh, I can't take it in the world.
I can't take it in the world.
Oh, I can't.
Oh, I can't take it in the world.
I like gotta carry the whole dog you've been free
Channel 1's got a new vision to discuss for
Channel 3's got a new vision to discuss for
Channel 4's got a new vision to discuss for
Channel 2's got a new vision to discuss for
Channel 3's got a new vision to discuss for
Channel 4's got a new vision to discuss for
Channel 3's lacking to discuss for
Go Jones on the source code TV junkie. You can find them at mojones.com moj.
Two brothers from the Netherlands who have been just touring around the country. Also parts of Belgium for the longest time.
They recorded this in their attic on a Mac. I don't know if you heard the Mac fanatics will have heard the start-up long sound there midway in the track.
I really think these guys are really really kick-ass.
And if you want to get your band or your song or it doesn't have to be rock and roll, it can be any style.
Let me know where I can download an MP3, check it out and make sure you also give me permission to do that.
Christina was actually sitting here listening to me sing along with mojones. She said, well, play some good Charlotte.
Very hard to explain to her that we're going to get in trouble when we can't actually play that.
And what was I supposed to do, go top to epic events?
Blackmail them. Oh, baby, what a great idea.
All right, moving along. A little bit of semi-techno nerdy stuff here. Of course, try to make users and developers get together and party on the source code.
I ran across a great use of podcasting.
From the iPod or developers mailing list and anyone can join that. You can see the link on the iPod.org homepage.
Join up and you can contribute. You don't have to join all the conversations. You don't have to understand that all.
And that works both ways by the way for users and developers.
And the iPod or developer team is using, well, let Garth kid explain it himself.
They're using their own technology while building the technology. Listen to a bit of this podcast.
Good morning. Welcome to the introductory iPod development team podcast. As we scale the team and power users start contributing code,
we need a way to keep each other up to date, despite incredibly flooded mailboxes.
And the way I figure it is, what better way than to eat our own dog food.
This won't be a daily half hour, thank god, to probably most of you.
It's probably going to be more intermittent small items, maybe once every few days or sometimes a few times in one day.
Who the hell am I? I'm Garth kid. It's Garth K at Gmail.com or GDK as as far as the CVS updates are concerned.
Radio, user land, early birds might remember my big mouth.
For a change, guys, I'm contributing as much code as I am would.
Actually, probably more. And to give you a break, I intend that the other developers are going to be dropping items into this cast as well.
I'm not going to be on 100% golf taking it off.
Okay, Garth, get ahead of yourself there. So he goes on, he goes on for quite a bit longer.
And actually, at the end of that first podcast, he let slip that they're working on a new release.
And then now getting everything together and figuring out what features they want to put in there.
And I suggest, if you're interested in you use the iPodder that they're working on, iPodder 1.0,
or Windows Mac, you should subscribe to that and check it out because maybe there's something in there that you have an idea about that you couldn't contribute to,
just from your own experience in using their iPodder program.
Something else that I thought was interesting set-up wise came in from a podcast.
Let's see, I wrote it down here.
Oh, shoot. I forgot what it's called, ITT.
It's a gentleman who comes.
The number one rated podcaster in the entire town of Bottle Washington.
Right on, the creator of In the trenches.
There it is, yeah.
Your host, Kevin Devin.
Right, it's In the trenches, okay.
And he's setting up Skype recording on a podcast.
Interesting way of putting it together, though.
Because apparently, it still takes two computers to really deal it right.
Good morning, good evening, good afternoon, whatever it may be where you're at.
Welcome to this edition of In the trenches.
As far as that intro goes, I have to say, I like it.
And it's mine, so until it gets old, I'm going to go ahead and keep it in there for a while.
I altered it a little bit this week just to kind of play around with it a little bit.
But I get others, I'll maybe put those in in this place, but for now, I'm kind of liking that one.
So I'm just going to keep it there for a little bit.
So anyway, I had intended for this podcast to be done entirely.
Via Skype.
I've been working on a method to do it.
I had done it once before, and I was pleased with that, but I wanted it something a little better.
Unfortunately, tonight's attempts turn out to be worse than what I had done previously.
But it did introduce a couple of cool elements into the whole mix, which I'm going to go ahead and play a clip of that anyway.
I did save some of it, I didn't throw it all on the floor, but I want to play some of it and just check it out.
It's actually kind of neat.
All right, with me tonight, I have Chad Davis.
Chad is a consultant working out of Konosha Wisconsin, and the operator operator of a blog.
Now I know what you're thinking, right?
It sounds really noisy this connection, but wait until you find out what these guys actually have hooked up.
That's very cool.
What are the interesting things of this podcast and what makes this one different from the others?
Is the equipment that we're using in this instance?
Now, many people have talked about using Skype to facilitate the creation of a podcast interview or conversation.
But I've noticed that folks have had a lot of problems either getting Skype to either capture both sides of the conversation or be able to route the audio internally,
and almost impossible on a Microsoft or on a PC, a little bit easier on a Mac, but still there are some challenges.
Now in this instance, I'm cheating.
I'm actually using two computers to facilitate this evening.
I'm actually using Skype on my PC to create the conference call, okay, for one.
The conference, I conference in the members, and I open up another session on the Mac.
It's an iMac 17.
I launched the conference call, answered on the iMac, and then mute the mic and turn the volume all the way down on the Mac.
Now the key piece of software here is a program called Audio Hydeject Pro from Rogue Amoeba, software.
I simply hijacked the application and began recording.
When I'm done, I end up having an MP3 that's ready to go with the entire conversation, getting up course both ends,
because all that Mac is doing is just recording.
So it's really slick in that aspect.
Now I know what you're thinking, so why didn't you just use the iMac to do it all?
Well, my thing is I want the ability to conference in more than just one person at a time.
Right now you can't do that with Skype on the Mac platform.
So, but I can do it on the PC.
So, what I'm doing is I'm just using the best of both worlds.
So, that's how I've got to set up and one thing I'm pleased with is the audio quality of Skype.
It's better than the way I was doing it before, which was just solely on the PC on my laptop,
but I was utilizing the speakers on my laptop to get the sound back up into the mic so that the other person could hear,
and I could pick up both ends of the conversation.
So, it's really kind of a cookie way of doing it there.
And I didn't really like the speaking to my screen rather than having a headset.
So, I wanted to use Chad for this initial Skype podcast for a couple of reasons.
First off, this guy's been working on a logo for the show now for nearly the past week.
Okay, I want to ask if I want to go for that.
Okay.
The stuff that he said to put up, let's do something else.
Yeah.
I don't know if I can get it to come on.
You know.
And it's a problem.
I don't like that idea.
So, I just want to say, I appreciate it.
Yeah, I don't know if it is.
Let him talk.
Hi, Pack.
Yeah, here it is.
Check out at least what his Skype call is on.
He's using an iPad on the other end of this line and you'll hear a lot of noise in the background.
But that's because he's using an iPad with Skype loaded.
So, in this instance, we're in this podcasting experience that we're doing tonight.
We're using an iPad, a laptop, you know, a Toshiba laptop, and an IMAX 17.
Okay.
All I can say about this is, damn cool.
What do you do?
Chad?
Yeah, it's a pretty elaborate set up to do a pretty simple thing.
But it works and it's only going to get easier and better.
I'm sure.
I have a community.
And the other thing that's kind of, you know, meat on this end.
I'm just saying here, I mean, using my Pack and PC is, you know, I'm just running over a Wi-Fi connection.
So I'm basically, you know, free of anything.
Okay.
So, um, and now a lot of you have been sending me emails about the Skype development team,
because, you know, the Mac software for a Skype is significantly behind the Windows version of it.
So I now, I now know that Skype Windows can do conference calling.
Now, I already used Skype to do with Skype out to actually, you know, make actual telephone calls.
It is almost the perfect piece of software.
We shouldn't have to be stringing up multiple computers together to make it work.
You know, and lots of people who are trying to, you know, get me on the leads with the development team.
But they must not have their ears on or something, man.
Because they're, look at what people are willing to do and to what lengths for willing to go to try and use your software.
I hope you hear us, you know, reach out so that we can start giving you some real feedback here.
You know, I've looked around.
Yeah, I know that their developers apparently are in Estonia, but I can't find any, any developer lists or whatever.
I just have nowhere to look.
So I hope that they're listening because, you know, their software could be a very important integrated part of what podcasting is all about.
So that comes from in the trenches, a great podcast.
You can find it, of course, from, uh, or through iPod.org in our directory under the technology section.
See, what else do they want to hit? Oh, I've got so many cool things.
I've got different all different user podcasts in today's show.
And some more great RIA free music on the way by a well-known established man who've done something cool.
But first, a little bit of podcast history for those of you just kind of tuning into the source code and new to the whole podcast phenomenon.
Hey, it's only what? Two and a half, three months old.
Bill kind of sums it up and there's next audio comment that he sends it to Dave and myself.
And check out somebody else to say.
And I'm Korean Dave Weiner subject to this audio note is podcasting takes off. Thanks to Adam and Dave.
I've been listening to, to you and Dave, audio blogs since they, since you really ignited the movement and podcasting, which, if you can believe it,
it was only back in mid August, as I recall for Adam, it was Friday the 13th.
Why would you pick such a beginning? Anyhow, no sign of what was to come because things have been great.
Adam, you're, you're podcasting is a bit more polished than Dave's.
And I'm sure it's because you're experiencing the entertainment.
I'm also much prettier.
But both of you are just really set apart from the rest of the crowd.
Mainly because you're attitude, you're both so excited and it comes through loud and clear in your, in your postings in your podcast.
Something that I might add would be nearly impossible to convey in the usual blogging fashion with text.
The excitement carries in to the intellectual domain as you guys feed off of each other, talking about the future of podcasting.
How the momentum is building the multitude of possibilities, trade secrets show.
It's for the naysayers that you're still kind of hanging around out there, but I think seller falling by the wayside.
You know, they keep whining about I did an audio blog, back in blah, blah, blah, blah.
But I might point out that you're just in what you do not what you say.
And YouTube guys, certainly have done it for the rest of us.
Set in the example day after day, sharing your growth with us on the HowToSide, establishingipider.org.
And all the enabling infrastructure that that entails.
Don't know if or when I might start podcasting, but for now I'm really enjoying the ride.
As I listen to you guys and Dave Slusher and others,
Hammy some truly enjoyable tracks to entertain and educate me when I, when I choose and how I choose.
Anyhow over and out, this is Bill Riskai.
You can email me at bill at riskai.biz.
All right, Bill.
So this might have sounded a little bit like a strokeathon, which of course is always appreciated.
But the point here is that, you know, this is really the history of, of, of, of, of, of, I bother and podcasting and just about two minutes there that Bill sent in.
And, you know, I've been doing a lot of interviews, a lot of people have been calling me and Dave for publications, you know,
What's going on with this podcasting? What's it all about? What is I potter?
And, you know, I found that as journalists start looking more and more into it into the phenomenon that's happening here, what's going on.
You know, that, yeah, there's been a lot of people putting up stuff in MP3 form on the web that is not necessarily, you know, a track of a song, you know,
That's being used for all kinds of different purposes in audio.
Go look at archive.org.
I mean, there's, there's just amazing amounts of, of great sound available at the MP3 format.
And it's been available for years, of course.
The only thing that was added here was, you know, just a couple of connections in the distribution.
But I do also want to point out that Chris Leiden, who Dave worked with about a year ago,
was definitely the first person to put up a regular series of MP3s in an RSS feed as enclosures.
And I'd been receiving those through my radio, userland aggregator.
So, you know, it's, it's been a process. It's not just Dave and I.
It's been the process of, you know, a lot of things working together and some important protocols and formats that were established along the way.
And it just seems to be growing, you know, I keep saying,
When is the hype going to be over, but it doesn't seem to be slowing at all,
Particularly when I see the kind of content that's coming online and I have to, and this would definitely qualify as content this next podcast.
I'm not quite sure if it's something that's repurposed that is already being created.
It sounds like it could be, but then again, maybe not.
And it is qualifying as a podcast and it's a weekly show and it's brand new.
I caught it off audio.weblogs.com.
It's the agriculture news weekly.
And I love the whole sound of the show.
You kind of get to get that Dallas vibe here from their music.
Perfect.
Come on.
Great job.
Congratulations to Texas on the campus of Texas A&M University.
It's active weekly for Monday, October 18, 2004.
We've got a hype about 90 degrees here in Texas and College Station.
High humidity.
I could take with the high humidity rate is right now, but it's, it's pretty sticky outside.
Got a lot of good stuff going on today.
In particular, our key news item of the day is,
look at the U.S. exports to Cuba.
They've more than doubled from a year ago, according to Dr. Parasin,
who's our extension economist in the director of the Center for North American Studies at Texas A&M.
Paras.
I don't know if you want to know all that about Cuba and agriculture,
but obviously the point here is that this is an excellent use.
What a incredible information value this can have.
I can just see all kinds of guys rolling around on the prairie with their iPods and their side holsters,
but it's great.
I'm really happy to see this kind of stuff come along.
And also, we've been talking about different languages coming online.
A lot of German podcasts have counted five or six that have come up in the just past week.
And some exciting news from our German friends who are responsible for the poet cast.
Hello, Adam.
This is Christian Hesman from Germany.
I'm the host of the poet cast, German podcast about poetry.
And of course, normally this wouldn't be that entertaining for your audience,
but today I have the chance to introduce a guest on my show,
Bratty Chapman from the U.S.
And here I'd like to participate on my show on a regular basis.
I hope at least once a week, and to read English poetry.
Which means I'll do a complete English podcast from time to time.
And I thought this might be something the international community might be interested in.
You might check it out at www.hesi.org-potcast.
This is h-e-s-i.org-s-potcast.
And keep up the good work.
Goodbye from Germany.
Okay, thank you very much, Christian.
So that's German podcast, which now will come to you in English.
And you can subscribe to it.
So it'll come into your iPod, your MP3 player completely automatically.
Now, we found out that there is indeed a language element for the Finnish language in RSS 2.0.
And it looks like our Scandinavian friends are really catching on with the podcast,
because just when you heard a podcast from Helsinki,
which even though it was in English, there was a real cool Finnish accent going on,
check out what I found on audio.weblogs.com.
It's a Swedish podcast, let's say.
It's a bit of a scene that is on the afternoon,
I think it's February 8th.
And I also think it's my favourite book.
I love this.
I can understand some of it.
I really like it.
I like it a little bit.
How do you like it?
I like it.
It's a podcast.
There's something weirdly sexual about this, listen.
I like it a lot.
There's something great.
You feel audio-blogger.
Swedish podcast.
Alright, moving right along.
Pick something up from a ko-mo 1000.
I think I mentioned before that we've had a hows of Amsterdam,
I'm up for sale for about three years.
But the market is so completely dead.
It's like, they sure there people look in,
but no one is buying anything.
Certainly not in the upper regions of the market.
it. And when we bought it, we bought it from a gay couple who would just recently renovated
the entire thing. And one of the features that, although we didn't really necessarily
need that or never dreamt about it, but one of the features was the toilets that were installed
in this house. And you have to admit, this was a guy house. They even had in one bathroom
that had a urinary automatic urinary just kind of walk in, do your business and walk
out into flushes automatically. And the toilets, when you sit down on the actual toilet
seat, the first thing that happens is there's a suction that kind of just very nice
thing silently, suction's off any offensive odourers that might be floating around. Then
I'm talking about our toilet. I just said gay men, a gay couple, yeah.
They're gay couple, could be a good one. Oh no, those are lesbians. They're not gay.
We won't enjoy the toilet too. Yeah, well, but lesbians don't like urinals. Okay, thanks
on. I got a little crib sheet here, Patricia's wrote on it and says, hey, it was gay men.
Make sure you mention it. Thanks on it. So anyway, so after you've sat down on the toilet
and the suction, this kind of vacuum, I should record this. Next time in Amsterdam, I'll
record all the sounds our toilet makes. So anyway, when you're done with your biz, whatever
it is, then you hit a button on the side and then a little water spout comes out, kind
of right underneath, you know, it's positioned pretty well actually. And then it squirts a nice
stream of warm, welcoming, room-like feeling of water. And then when you let go of the
button, then, then, of course, the dryer comes on. You get nice little warm kind of thing
and y'all, you dry off and then when you're ready, you're done and you're done, right?
So it's a full service toilet. And lo and behold, what do I hear on Como News this morning?
Contractors have built homes with glorious woodwork, spectacular layouts and spared no
expansion nearly every room. And when it came to the bathroom, just throwing one of those
hundred dollar toilet jobs and everybody uses. I think that they're better ways to do
just about everything. Thomas Crapers invention is morphing into a more comfortable and cleaner
experience. Never not quite fit on a standard toilet seat. For a large person, there's nothing
more comfortable. A ton Levi invented the big John toilet seat, making the job more comfortable
for the larger person. It's got stainless steel can do metal, never trade. Along with bigger seats,
there's now a lot of extras. He didn't toilet seats. We've got seats to do all sorts of things.
Dan Sherman is my tour guide at a better bathroom kitchen in Belviewee. He says Japan has
been using high-tech toilets for years. And that's not something that we've had traditionally.
Let's go to the bathroom. Let's go to the bathroom. Introducing the new toe toe,
we arrest. When you walk up to it, it opens automatically. Press this button on this infrared remote
control. Whoa man, infrared remote control. Then we get to the cool part. You see, the new arrest
has a built-in but day. It automatically adjusts to you and you control the temperature of the water.
There's also a built-in dryer, a built-in deodorizer. Now that may be too fancy for some of you,
and the price tag of five grand may be too spending. But you've got to admit,
taking care of business. You'll never be the same again. Brian Carr, comma 1000 news.
Oh, clearly I have an outdated model. I don't have a heated toilet seat. What's wrong with me?
All right, so more cool music for you right now. This was uh, I got turned on to this by the
indie feed podcast. The Beastie Boys have released a track in MP3 on the internet. Free of all rights,
clear of any RIA, shit, whatever you can do whatever you want with it because they have a real message
in this song. And that's why they said, please, play this anywhere you can. They didn't specifically
say podcast, but I'm sure they meant it deep in their heart. Check out the Beasties in a world
gone mad.
Screens and lines
Just like a politician
Put the action by the scars
Nuts and arms to pick it
Like back in the days
With the cocaine and the thoughts
Yeah
You feel more positive
You can get more bold
That you're made like crazy
It's more unfold
What you want to do
Is they hit strong up with that access
That you must get on hold
I'll see you soon
Number 2, 2018
Polychensions are shady
So people watch you back
But think they're so crap
I don't doubt it
It's a hell of an act
We don't want to go mad
We want to be better
Say you want to fly
Let's see
Let's fly
We want to go
All day
In half two
Time will fight
The man will fly
It goes
For some more
Jair now
We're in a rap
We're reaching our point
We're the can't turn back
Let's lose the gun
The less lose the bomb
So stop the corporate
Culture business
If they're built
The ball
We're sleeping on this
Did you tell us
Stop the snorkees
Cause I'm weak
And it goes
Oh
I'm a little
Beast of the little
I don't get a strong
Cause we love the barricade
But that's no reason
It's their request
And then the end of the zero
We're bringing bout-fills
We ain't having it
We don't want to go mad
The power he brought
Say you want to fly
We say
It's both
We're going on
We're getting up
Do it
We fight
We're going on
We're going
Sweet.
Bobby, Bobby.
Beasty Boys, in a world gone mad, you can download that from BeastyBoys.com and
as I said, you can use it on any podcast and any manner, that you wish because they've
released it completely free of all royalties, rights are immediately cleared, you can go ahead
and play that on your podcast if I liked it. It's a typical Beasty. But the words definitely
have to have some meaning to it. All right, 40 minutes, that's about my tax for the show,
so we're going to leave it here for today's source code, 40 minutes to see is just about the
time it takes for Dave Wyner to make his entire walk around the Seattle whatever his daily
walk is, and he says 40 minutes about growth, so keep it a bad for now. Hey, at tomorrow
by the way, Dave and I will be on the Gilmore gang, which will guess it'll be out over the
weekend. So you can check that out, tip to IT Conversations.com. All right, comments
out of Maccurry.com or leave comment on the weblogs.org.curry.com, and of course you can get the
archives and latest, daily source code on dailySourceCode.com, and don't forget to be checking
out iPodder.org, and audio.weblogs.com for all the freshest podcasts. I'll talk to you tomorrow.
I'm the source code. I'm by everybody.