Good morning, good morning, good evening, wherever you might be, checking out the source code.
I'm Adam Curry, it is Monday, August 30th, 2004.
And sorry about the weekend, I just didn't feel like doing anything really.
And quite honestly, I liked that a lot.
So why don't we agree that the source code is going to be a weekday feature.
And I will as often as possible, try to have something up Sunday night so that you
can listen to it on your Monday morning commute.
And God, I'd always like to have it ready for you for your morning commute.
So it's Adam Curry coming to you from Curry Council in Belgium.
Tomorrow is the very last radio show that I do on the very last morning show that I do
for Veronica Radio.
As a big party afterwards.
last until late probably. So that being said, you may not expect a source code tomorrow
just because of all the festivities. But otherwise, I'm going to turn this into a daily feature
that should be up every morning between 7 and 8 New York time.
And the source code, as we discussed last time, which was last Friday, it's where users
and developers come to party, right? And when I thought about that over the weekend, we
have so many things that we can be doing. And there are projects that we're working on.
One of the projects, of course, is iPodder. And by now we have a shoot, I don't know,
we must have five different versions of it, all kind of doing the same thing. And I think
that what we probably need is some central place other than a weblog where we can, especially
when we branch out and do a project like this, we can keep track of it all because there's
a stuff is falling between.
the cracks, we don't have a central place. And I'm notoriously very bad at organizing
that kind of stuff. And then I thought maybe we should start a source forge page, a source
forge.org, which is, I presume is really good for managing projects, development projects,
because we've had a new release of iPodder for Windows, which I will talk about a little
bit later. But that's exciting because now we have something that actually does the same thing
that we've been using on our Macs for a couple of weeks now. All you do is you run the script
that goes out, it checks a file of feeds to bring in the enclosures, it puts them all
into their own directory, and it actually controls iTunes on Windows. So yeah, with that
script, and I will talk about that a bit later because I have a couple of, I have some thoughts
about it, with that script and an iPod, you can automatically have your iPod updated.
So it seems like we're talking more and more about technology from a user and a developer
perspective.
And actually I wasn't going to mention this until Gmail went live, but I was so hurt
up until this morning that I didn't have a Gmail account.
It seems like everybody in the world had a Gmail account.
Everybody got one from their friend.
Personally, I would have expected one from Google themselves, but didn't get that.
And it wasn't until this morning when my co-host on the radio show said, hey, I got a Gmail
account.
Would you like one?
Can you be my Gmail friend?
So I'll be looking into that.
And I'm sure that as that goes live, there will be a lot to talk about.
Google seems to be doing some pretty exciting stuff.
Let me think about video and audio blogging.
I had some thoughts about that because more and more is happening now.
I've been checking out more audio blogs and video blogs in the past couple of days.
And to me, it is crystal clear that we can make a huge jump start with our video.
with distributing bundles of passion.
That's Dave Slusher would call it.
Or content or whatever,
just this kind of shit.
The shit we want to share with each other, thank you.
That is it.
And the infrastructure is already there.
If you have a web,
if you're going to a video or audio blog,
you're going to post something,
you want to distribute it,
you want to publish it,
you want to get out to the world,
you may already,
you probably already have a,
some kind of blog software.
And all the bits are there,
with RSS 2.0,
the enclosures,
the aggregators aren't quite there yet.
Of course, we're now building our own aggregators,
essentially making our devices aggregators.
And then I think is where we have to take our mindset,
we have to get beyond the computer
so that when someone who just doesn't need to understand
how it works is told,
well, you can subscribe to this show,
all they should have to do is think of,
okay, I installed this software.
I don't know where it went, it's gone,
it says thank you very much, it'll work now.
have to do is jack in my iPod every day or charge it as usual and new stuff just shows up.
So that is where we have to get to that part. And everything in between I think can be done
at the desktop level with, well, they'd be communicating to a blog server or it could be something
just as simple as putting up an RSS feed on an FTP site. You know, there are all different
versions of that that'll work. For publishing, for receiving, we really have to take out all that
all that middle stuff. Excuse me. We're very, very, very close. But still, it feels like,
by default, and it's not wrong, but it feels like we are approaching it from
possibly a difficult angle. Because what I see people doing is saying, okay, I'm going to make a
weblog entry and then I'm going to attach a video blog to that where really what you want is you want
your DVD player or whatever it is, whatever device is going to be...
sitting in front of your viewing station.
Now that could very well be a computer,
but in some cases maybe it should be your television.
And that device also has to be an aggregator.
It has to be perceived as an aggregator
in order for people to understand what we're trying to do.
Because that's the simplest.
You just don't have to think about it.
It shows up.
We're going to hit all kinds of speed bumps
when it comes to subscriptions.
I mean, we already saw that with web logs.
Because eventually you're going to have to tell people,
please copy your L, paste it into this file, and then it'll be OK.
And even that's too much.
Do we go with preference pains or how do we do with that?
So these are all thoughts that we need to talk about.
And I really would like some feedback on that.
Oh, by the way, I've lowered the bit rate on source code
so that the quality should remain reasonably decent.
And the file size will just go down a bit
because, man, we're really eating a hard drive space doing this.
I mean, that's exactly what I knew would happen.
Once.
minute you get into something and you're developing and you want shows to be there for
other developers to work on nothing's worse than creating an aggregator and nothing coming
in, right?
And on that point, consumer note, about a year and a half ago we did a reality show about
us, which was broadcast here in the Netherlands.
And what was cool about it is we also produced it ourselves.
And we did the entire thing on Final Cut Pro and used the Firewire drives and DV cams.
And the only, I think, real professional part that we used was besides people who knew
what they were doing, professionally trained people, a lot of experience and video production.
Well, we bought some good wireless mics, the one I'm using right now.
We also bought about two terabytes worth of storage data from Lassie.
And I just wanted to touch on that because I'm not too happy with the way, well, first
of all, with their product.
We have a whole slew of the, you know, see how big it is.
these are 80 gigs, I think.
Yeah, I think it's 80 gig drive, LeCise, which are fire wire.
They have their own power supply, which is kind of a drag by itself, but it didn't matter.
These are, they look at, they look the part, you know, of heavy duty industrial hard drives.
We also got a couple of the two of the half terabytes, like 550 gigabyte drives, which we
affectionately called the big swinging disc.
And within a year's time, and some a little bit longer, usually just outside the warranty,
80% of these drives has failed.
80% which is a real hassle when you're in the middle of producing something that has to
get on the air and you just have to move on with stuff, particularly when you're using
Final Cut Pro where you render everything after the fact.
So you're always working up against the deadline of knowing that you'll have to have at least
an hour or two hours or sometimes long depending on how many layers of video and audio you
have for it to render.
out. And then you select to go through post audio and sound sweetening. So it's a real
drag when you have to stop in the middle and something's fucked up and you've lost
your data essentially. Well, it turns out you haven't lost your data with these LICI drives.
The bus, the firewire bus, this is according to LICI, burns out very easily with max because
of a discrepancy in the voltage of the Macintosh firewire port. Now, I know that these things aren't
quite fleshed out as a standard, but they definitely sell the C drives as a Macintosh compatible.
And they know about this problem. So it really pisses me off that we've had so many failures
in all such sort times as well. And they won't replace the ports. They'll give you a new drive
if it's under warranty. But they won't just say, okay, well, because my data's on these discs,
right, it's just sitting there and it's spinning and it's happy. It's just not getting any joy
from through firewire. So it's just not being asked to do anything.
And they don't want to replace the ports.
They say, well, you could buy another drive, and then you could switch the actual platters
or the drives and you, you know, like fuck that, fuck that.
This is me off.
This should be better.
Anyway, until further notice, I strongly recommend you do not purchase LaCe FireWire drives
if you're intending on doing anything that you do that, where you care about your data.
Quite honestly, that's just about everything.
Okay, down to iPodder for a second here.
Now, as I've been looking around the net, looking at what people are doing, there is an incredible
amount of work that already has been done on iTunes.
I mean, just a massive amount, all kinds of scripts to do the most wacky things you could think
of and not one single person except for the people who have been working on iPodder has
come up with anything even close to it.
So this, I mean, first of all, there's a lot of people wanting to make iTunes and I.
iPod, do more stuff, and I'd like to try and capitalize on that and get people interested
and excited in being able to spread shows around and subscribe to stuff simply and make
it easy for people and really connect your iPod to something and pull out all of the fodder
of downloading and transferring and updating and creating playlists.
Now, we'll do that all for you and make it completely automatic.
In fact, I was thinking that if we could come up with three versions that we all love of iPod
or whatever.
It could be for a Mac, for Windows, for Linux, whatever we need it for.
That a site that or someone who wants to distribute audio, or in this case, audio, that they
could actually distribute that program or any version of that or link to a download page
that would come with only their feed file and then you could add to it yourself.
We should be able to open that up somehow and make it work for everybody.
Now, Peter created iPodder for...
Windows and I'm really excited about this because what I did is I took the
time to work on to work on it. Check it out on Windows 2000.
Professional have that running on a laptop here. I haven't worked with Windows
in a long time. That's worked pretty snappy compared to the Mac. It's a little
bit faster, but anyway, that's a whole different discussion. So you download his
script, which is runs on Windows. Something Windows scripting. There is a little
note about it in the readme file. And all you have to basically do is just make
sure that you have the scripting engine on your machine. Mine had it, so I
presume that's probably the fault installed these days with Windows, although I
don't know for sure. And I also need iTunes, which I didn't have yet. So I downloaded
iTunes, that ran. Then I fired up the script. I saw it go out. It has little
Windows telling me what it's doing. And then it failed because I hadn't set the
download directory, which you have to do manually in the feeds file. I was set to
D, colon, back.
I said it to my own download directory, my own download drive.
So then I ran it again and boom, it worked.
I brought the stuff in, it updated the iTunes playlist.
Fucking fantastic.
And this is so important because as much as I love my Mac,
it's death if you think we can do anything just doing it on the Mac.
We've got to get Windows involved.
So the only thing I'd really like and maybe there's something we only talk about
after we get some kind of page up or we work on this development together.
So if we have a source source, source for page or something of the like
is if we could just take one little step and if we have an installer.
And this is the way I dream it.
For Windows and Mac doesn't matter Linux or whatever.
You download this program, you've got to be very clear what it does.
You know, the description has to say, turns your iPod into an aggregator.
You know, connect to show subscribe whatever it is.
We've got to work on that language.
You download it, you install it, it says, okay, here's what I'm doing.
I'm doing where do you want the files to be downloaded?
You select a directory boom.
That's your download directory.
It checks to see if you have iTunes installed.
It checks to see if you have the right scripting environment
on Windows or whatever it is.
Just run through a couple of checks.
If not download it, do it seamlessly.
That's the thing that the only thing that's really wrong
with iPodder for the Mac is you have to download
this X and L tool in order for it to work.
That should be automatic for people.
They shouldn't have to do anything,
but double click and just answer one or two questions
and maybe select a download directory.
And then it is, and by the way,
it should also set up a cron job
and we should explain what we're doing.
That maybe you can make that configurable for the user
later on.
I want to check that these intervals
are these times to see if there's new shows.
Maybe we don't tell them about it all,
but we have to let them know that we're making
the computer do something, obviously.
And that should be all set up automatically.
And it should download a first couple of files.
And then notification is something.
else. Personally, I don't think we need a notification, but maybe we could just create a
smart playlist, which I've done in my setup. Whenever there's new content, new shows
that bundles of passion, Dave, that come in from out there, that particular playlist is
updated as well. So the different ways to do the notification, maybe there's more options
in there. Maybe you want to receive an email that, hey, the new show is up. So that would
be just wonderful. I'd love to get some feedback on that. Particularly on what we should do
on centralizing some of this development works. I don't want it to just kind of dribble out.
We need to get this going. And then we need to talk to people, getting them to support
what we're doing. IT conversations is already great. Dave Liner's coffee notes. He just did
an update the other day from the cars. He's driving through Madison, Wisconsin. Dave Slusher,
there's so many people already getting into this that I think we're still on a good track.
We just need to centralize some things.
Okay, here's something that's interesting about the big rock and roll dudes.
MTV Video Music Awards were last night in the States for the first time for Miami.
Of course, now I have a 14-year-old who's even more interested in the show than I am.
Check this out.
Even though they pertain to have a global television network, which they do, of course, and they
have lots of potential viewers, the show did not air live in Europe on any of the MTV stations
as far as I'm aware.
It won't air until Wednesday, mind you, when everyone already knows who's won.
The disappointment, the good Charlotte didn't win.
Viewers Choice Award was pretty big this morning in the Curry Household, but so all of
that's already been done.
Then they're going to broadcast like an edited or watered down version of the award show,
where I want the full three-hour, raunchy, whatever shit goes on show.
In fact, I'd actually pay money to have the totally unsensored version, if there wasn't
anything to be censored.
So, I'm hoping fingers crossed that someone out there recorded it and we'll put it...
up a bit torrent because it's just ridiculous.
And MTV should be doing that themselves.
They're crazy.
Now, why do we have to wait three days until we can see it?
It makes no sense to me for any award show.
The Academy Awards aren't that dense about it.
And actually, BitTorrent works great for those moments when you want something big like Windows
Service Pack 2, which was also distributed via BitTorrent, which has appeared to be your
sharing system.
And really, it's what they call it, file swarming or whatever.
And it adds funny because I spoke to Dave briefly.
And remember, he wanted to load up on some movies for when he got the Canada.
And well, basically, I said, you know, if you're looking for older movies, take a while
to download, because you may only have one or two or three people or maybe only one seeding
that particular file.
So it could take a long time to download what really works great when something's new or something's
really...
popular. And then I gave him of course a couple of torrents to some new porn movies.
So he understood that and he came back and said, well, if I just want some old Saturday night
live episodes, how do I get that? I said, well, you can probably find it. There may be someone
seeding that online, but probably unlikely. And he came up with an idea is, well, maybe we
all have to just kind of put a weblog together and we'll update each other and say, hey, today
Saturday night live day and we all put our stuff up online and we become, in effect, the transmitter.
You know what? Ad hoc transmitter gives everyone a zippy download who joins the group.
You know, it's interesting to think about because that could be pretty powerful if you can create
that kind of bandwidth. Ad hoc and just doing it as end users are not someone in the middle.
Not quite sure how it'll work, but I do think that we all could, yeah, we can definitely all get
together and make it happen. She wears it take, you know, run a little script somewhere or just open
something up and leave it running. Shouldn't be a problem at all. And likewise, for the song of the
And I've already gone way over my time limit, but I do want to play a song of the day for you.
It was very easy to download this one.
I had 53 hosts within seconds, and yet it's a song that's over 20 years old.
The unfortunate news reached everybody, just the other just yesterday, that Laura Branigan
passed away.
She died in upstate New York, East Cog, I think, 47-year-old, 47 years old of an aneurysm.
I didn't know her very well, but we had met a couple of times, both in Holland and somewhere
in TV.
I'm thinking Marty Grah.
So that's why I probably don't remember very well.
But it's shocking when someone that young goes.
Anyway, we have our music to remember by.
Not many hits from Laura Branigan, but this is one that everyone remembers.
And I just wanted to play it for you so we can all think about her, her self-control.
It's the night, turn around in the night
Look, roll, do the world something break
Where in my eyes you're walking down the street
I'm not so good
Take myself, take myself, roll, roll
Come here, and only do the night
You take me to you take my down come close
I love the night I love the night
I let the sky, I set you on the earth
But you can't do it, you can't do it
You take the sun, you take the sun
Hi! I'm a creature tonight
I hope you lose the wings
Against the moon, the marks I can't stop
I need it, tomorrow I'm not allowed
I'm really not
I know the light is new
I'm a spirit, I'm a spirit
Something's fun, make myself believe it
This night will never go
I'm a spirit, I'm a spirit
All the night, it's like a pain to go
In the day, nothing matters
It's like a time of time
I'm on the Greece of the Philippines
I have a number of women trying to fight
I'm a person, a mouth, a white, a sound just leaving
To my old, a ghost
I said, night, I really didn't know
I'm a lady, it's not a day
I must leave, something's wrong
Make myself believe it, it's night, we never go
I'm a woman, a woman
Oh
So just imagine everyone running off to the record store trying to buy that single by Laura Brandt again just to remember
By no way wouldn't happen. It's just not in stock. It's not possible
Through Peter Peer. It was very easy. The download was amazing. It only took about 40 seconds to bring it in.
And they're going to wind up the source code with that today. So tomorrow of course I have the final morning radio show
That could mean that there may not be a source code up or maybe may very very late
And as of September 1st that's when we start
new life. And tomorrow, by the way, I'm going to play a new song in my wife made. She's
working on a DVD of her career, which spans 40 years, and she's recording a couple new
tracks. And I've got one that I will share with you tomorrow. So we'll see you then on
the source code, everybody, until then, take care.
If you'd like to respond to sports code, then send an email to adipocurry.com or leave a comment
on live.curry.com.
Because of the time when we're all together, we're not allowed to be together anymore.
I've been bored of seeing you every day and time.
But you're not allowed to be with me.
I'll stay by your side.
I'll stay by your side and time.