Well, good afternoon everybody. It's Monday. It's October 4th.
to power all the door is closed.
And I got a lot of partying to do, another fabulous weekend,
although I was actually in the United Kingdom.
Trish and I went over to check out the new house,
we'll be moving in, oh man, it's coming up quickly.
Somewhere around the third week of November, so this,
you can imagine there's so much to do,
and meanwhile I'm sitting here,
three quarters of my waking hours with headphones on,
talking into microphones, talking to other people
by my computer, I have to divide myself up a little bit more.
So this is your daily source code,
and I've been actually doing interviews about what we're doing here,
podcasting, getting calls from, particularly from the West Coast and the States,
and I'm really excited about everything that's happening.
There's so many things I want to go through today,
I'm going to try and make the show a little bit shorter than the normal.
I tend on having a guest on the next source code, which may even, I might even release
that right after today's show, kind of have like a today plus one.
Hugo Shotman, I've pointed to him before and we've spoken about him as really leading
a lot of the charge, certainly in documenting ways of setting up podcasting software.
And so I said, you know, why don't we talk on daily source code and we'll see if we
can come up with something.
I don't know.
Now, I've been going through more set up shit and I did another trade secrets with
Dave last night.
Now granted, I was probably a little bit tired just from coming back from the
UK, you know, a little bit of car travel than flying.
And it was around 9, 9.30, 10 o'clock my time when we recorded the show.
I was so unhappy with the quality of his sound.
You know, we've tried just about everything and the best quality by far
of all the different chat.
that we can use cross-platform is Skype.
It's bar none. It's great quality.
The latency is, it appears far lower than anything else.
Mind you Dave's on Windows and I'm on a Mac
and we're just, you know, guys just want to use something.
So we're not great technologists.
tweaking everything and it seems that we have almost tweaked everything but Skype is still
in beta and it won't let you choose a virtual audio device at least not on the Mac.
So until that's in there it really isn't 100% what we need but we're going to continue,
we're going to try and use Skype from now on even though it does once in a while also
just kind of quit.
Anyway, so I was really pissed off about that.
It just it bothered me so much and I started to work on new setups in the meantime.
I discovered something very important as we were doing the show last night, the quality
of his call degraded significantly and I couldn't figure it out and he says actually we could
understand him okay but he couldn't understand me and it's like what's going on and it
wasn't until much later that I realized that I'd become victim of my own success
in a way because it was iPodder that kicked in and started downloading stuff at whatever
desig-
time it was. And that of course used up all the bandwidth and crunched the connection.
So whenever we come up with some software or something that helps you record a podcast,
we need a big old red button that turns off all iPod activity because it's like that
has definitely messed up a lot of the recording of the show.
I had a couple of new podcasts that I wanted to point to and I have met a resolution
by the way that when I post a new daily source code I will have to put up some
links on the weblog portion of it and I'll refer it I guess in the somewhere in
the ID3 tags I'll refer to the promo link of that weblog post so you should be
able to find it because there is just too much stuff you know going on now and
there's good stuff that I don't want to get lost in the shuffle so I want to
start creating some some links to some of these new things.
I'm seeing how I didn't have GeekSpeak here.
I have enough for three shows, believe me.
Actually, I'll start off with this one.
This one was announced through the iPod or dev list.
I'll just play the intro of it because it's kind of cool.
It's got some good production value and I think it's...
Particularly if we're looking at the audience that currently is using iPod
or I think this will be a show that's going to fly.
of missions to explore both homes.
figure out what that word is that shit
the software lands
let me just listen to that I get it
what is it 5 4 3 2 1 and then shift
let's listen to that
what was that
shit
hold on a second
hi young
what?
new?
okay I'm coming
alright
looks like we're gonna have to pause this recording
I'll be back in
a nanosecond for you as I eat my dinner
okay most excellent
that was a nice
35 minute break had some dinner and I'm back
and now everything's almost actually
on track I think that in about 15 minutes
I can
give Hugo a shot in a call
and we'll talk to him
so let's play a couple of things
before we get to that
I already played you the program one there
the brand new podcast
Michael Men's
brand new podcast
I'll make sure I point to that in the notes to the source code for today.
Something else I found that, and a lot of this is coming through on the BlogDigger media feed,
of course, now that I have iPodRx 2.0 running on my Mac, and it's really, it's quite wonderful.
I just got to say I love the way it installs and how it sets everything up. Although,
I think that probably something that all iPod developers could think about is creating a
a default feed. It's a feed that is already in there just to show the user what even what a
URL looks like. Hold on a second, my dog wants the little dog. Come on, so I'll be back. Let me go.
And maybe that's a feed that only has one small, kind of like a hello world. Welcome to my iPodRx
MP3 audit. So, you know, just the first experience doesn't necessarily have to be with a 20 or 30 meg
download from something like the day.
And I got a... what was this that I found?
Oh, it was probably an audio blog post, but it was just kind of... well, you'll hear it.
It's interesting how technology, even though it's supposed to be so slick, can really,
really fuck you up when you're traveling.
This is titled 10.0238.mp3.
So don't know where it's coming from. No.mp3 metadata, but check it out.
Hey, good morning. It's 4.20am and I'm in Des Moines.
Here's another reason to hate United.
When I booked this flight to get home this morning, I decided to have it automatically add the flight to my Outlook calendar.
So it told me that I was leaving at 6.12 in the morning.
The trouble is I'm leaving Des Moines at 6.12 in the morning, Denver time, which means I'm leaving Des Moines at 7.12.
So I'm here at the airport way earlier than I need to be and needless to say.
I'm a chap that annoyed.
So that's another way you can use this kind of technology to just let us know how you
Also, it appears that podcasting is breaking through in other countries.
I posted on my weblog, I posted to an Italian explanation of iPodder and today comes iPod
soft audio.
IpodSoft.
Hello. The first audio news from IpodSoft.
Let's see how it goes.
First, computer test. Left, right. OK.
So if it works, we'll do it regularly.
Oh wow, that was tricky. Did you hear that?
Did you hear that go from left to right?
That's like, that's how they start their show off.
Say, wait, hold on.
We're going to test you now. Left, right, left, right.
That was cool.
Left, right. OK.
We'll keep.
Anyway, so some German iPod news.
And I could understand most of it being,
I could speak Dutch pretty well.
But about at least a third of what they're saying is in English anyway.
So I was going to scoop the Gilmore Gang,
on the Gilmore Gang, by uploading,
or actually by playing a little bit of the,
what's that, huh? Two balls?
Two balls. What kind of balls are these?
We have cream balls.
Do you have those in there?
They do now.
I like our donkey balls.
No.
Who's that?
No, whipped cream balls.
Filled with...
Filled with whipped cream.
Thank you.
Thank you, cream sushi.
Right on.
Okay.
So I said I was going to scoop the Gilmore Gang,
who did their show live from Nome Dex,
which was in Lake Tahoe, I believe.
Oh, shit.
Now the other dog wants to go in.
Come here, Jess.
Come on.
Come on, go.
Now, I'm telling you, it's been like this all day.
The phone's been ringing, people interrupting.
I just can't get down to doing a show.
So anyway, I knew that Doug Kay was down there
doing the streaming stuff.
So I actually recorded the stream of the Gilmore Gang
and I wanted to play back a little bit
because they were talking about iPodder
and iPod platform and podcasting was great.
Now it's jumping up and down as I was.
in our inn, the room at the inn in the UK where
was really cool but then raster web audio scoop me to the scoopage
well
the Gilmore Gang. I think John Udell said something really significant here and I
just wanted to share that with you.
I can't believe I hit the ball.
Quite impressive.
It landed in the water.
Yes, but the splash was quite impressive.
This place is so beautiful. I can see just coming here to think or read, though that
probably defeats the purpose of the holes with the flags and all.
There's something rather serene about walking around here.
You come here every week?
No, when I can.
I'm often working on the weekends.
Bummer.
Isn't it?
Crap. Okay. You know what? I'm pretty sure that that wasn't the Gilmore Gang.
I don't even think that was John Udell.
I think that was the Gilmore Girls.
I'm sorry, everybody.
I'm forgetting.
Hopefully that had the same effect on you as it had on me the first time.
I was like, what the hell is he playing?
What does nothing do with the Gilmore Gang?
Indeed, the Gilmore Girls.
Always.
Nice to have pizza, rice, and humor on the daily source code via raster web audio.
So I do have a bit of the Gilmore gang.
This is kind of cool because this in effect is bootleg.
I think I may be posting it before it's even posted on ITConversations.com.
I'm just going to play a little bit at the end of the show of what Steve Gilmore said
was so incredibly nice.
Just like Hugo Shopman, I'm going to ask Steve if he'll let me interview him on a daily source code.
He clearly understands the opportunity that is in podcasting and iPodder, etc.
And he's very vocal about it.
Check it out.
Final bit from the Gilmore gang soon to be up at ITConversations.com.
You know, as somebody, the second executive at a major software company asked me the other day
when's the Gilmore gang going to go, you know, national?
And I said it's all...
Where did he go?
Act it.
What do you want?
I mean, as Chris said, we're being broadcast through the iPod
platform to anybody, anywhere, who has access to the network.
The streaming audio that Doug Kay is doing
is we had questions on the first day of this conference
from Australia, from New Zealand.
Georgia.
Even Georgia.
And I just want to say one thing about professional content.
I've been a record producer.
I've directed films.
They may not be professional in the sense
that they weren't Hollywood blockbusters,
but I know how that stuff works.
And I'm telling you that what Adam Curry is doing
and what Dave Slusher is doing from Conway, South Carolina
and what Robert Scobal is doing from pulling it
out of his ass.
Wait a minute.
Never underestimate the bad.
with the Robert Scoble's ass.
It is just as professional, if not more so,
because these technologies, as they boil down
and virtualized into a Mac today and a PDA
or some sort of cell phone tomorrow,
this is the recording studio of the future,
and the future is now.
This is happening today, and it is going,
when people say in four or five years,
when the iPod platform really takes off,
they're missing the boat by about four or five years.
It's happening right now.
I really encourage you to listen to the entire Gilmore Gang,
and I'm sure they'll also have other bits of the conference
from NomeDecks up on ITConversations.com.
I listened to a bit of Will Wheaton.
Dave and I got to figure out a way to be able to record that
and comment at the same time, because it's funny.
You listen to something together and you comment.
You come up with...
with wacky stuff and there was also another conference. It was the future of content.
session that was and there was also a lot of iPod or talk so make sure you catch
that it'll probably be another day or so until they get all of that encoded and
sorted out you know and this conference is can be pretty grueling
particularly if you're doing streaming stuff. So let me see I got about five
more minutes till we can call Hugh.
past seven right now in Belgium. And I believe he's either in the Netherlands or Austria,
but we're going to find out where he is. But while I was in the UK, I was looking around
to see how the British citizens reacted to the presidential debate. And you know, from
one thing leads to another, and I stumbled across a piece of video, which is, it's all animated,
but I want to let you hear this because the voiceover is self-explanatory. And this, I think,
is something that will be, well, you'll have to check out. Just listen to what this is. It's
only about a minute and a half, and it's simply titled, Barry.move. This is how stuff comes
along, and unfortunately there's no metadata whatsoever, but in the credits, and I'm
going to link to this from my weblog for this source code posting, in the credits
there's all kinds of information about who's behind this and what their drive is. But I
think it gives a view of what...
But Britons think of the United States in general and perhaps of the presidential elections
and the world at large.
The United States of America is the most powerful nation on Earth.
In itself, this goes a long way to explaining the things it does around the world.
At present, it's conducting a war on terror.
Or more accurately, a campaign against opposition to US domination.
Others prefer to call it the beginnings of the Third World War.
United States has an insatiable appetite for conflict.
career in the 1950s.
one or other in some corner of the globe non-stop right up to it as a day.
This drive is now led by the weapons manufacturers themselves.
It's a highly dangerous project.
It's the door of a new fashion being pushed open.
The reality, as we see from the Iraqi invasion, is that the presidency has been...
And this ghastly molecule aims to turn the world into its very own enslaved global mark.
by Al Qaeda on the World Trade Center. It's just one response to it.
Is this a conspiracy? Quite the opposite. It is a high-profile project known as the
project of the new American Century. People like Dick Janie, Donald Rumsfeld,
Richard Pearl are the major players among politicians right-wing thinkers
and
The project is a neoconservative manifesto, which includes in its toolbox the unbridled
use of war and clearing a path for US interests.
Iraq came entirely from this visible yet sinister group.
And so who's next to wonder Iran, North Korea, France?
None of us really matter to them.
So then it goes into some credits.
Barry McNamara, I know that name from somewhere.
That's who did the voiceover.
And then there's a final credit here, knife-party.net, directed and produced by knife-party.net.
So you want to check that out.
I've heard this theory before about a new world order and the new world movement.
And I, yeah, it's the wonders of the internet that gives us the power to have this stuff
put together, all this art, you know, and be able to play it for you.
So, you know, this is, keep more of it coming.
I don't think we'll ever, you know, this is the election.
This is the chance where we have to use all these digital media tools to really get our
point across and say what we want to.
You can also, of course, just do it in traditional song.
I didn't know I was an American
to give a damn
Or on patriotic
For Darren to take a stand for what
Looks like freedom to me, expressions of liberty
Warning our America to be a responsible agenda.
Didn't know I was a communist
But wanted to share the wealth
So are you than what I believe?
I didn't know I was un-American and uh, just a nice little tune on the daily source code for October 4th, 2004.
Would it be this way?
I hope I can find out who that is.
Okay, it's time now, I'd say, to see if we can get Hugo on the...
We're calling him via Skype.
There we go.
It's like it's working.
Hi, how are you doing?
I'm good.
I'm recording already.
That's good.
So welcome to the source code.
Thank you very much.
You know, Hugo, you blew me away.
Hold on a second.
This is, I'm trying to get the, this is exactly why I wanted to call you because I want to
make sure we get, we get squared away on the best personal setup for this kind of stuff.
Okay.
Well, you're kind of breaking up a little bit.
How am I on your side?
Yeah, you're coming through okay.
I'll say what, I'm going to try calling again.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay, we're, we're back and we've, I think now, by now we actually have it set up so
that not only will you hear me talking, but we'll also hear Hugo talking.
I mean, Hugo, I mean, I've had so much, you know, success and failure and all kinds
of crap with this.
I mean, what?
I mean, help me out here.
Where, where do we have to go?
Who do we have to talk to?
How do we get to the end of this?
we have to get this working better and do you think that there's something we can bootstrap
that'll get us further than where we're at right now because this is giving me many sleepless
nights?
Yes.
Well, one answer is with the things that we have right now, we can write down different
setups and lessons learned and exchange the best setup with each other so that we can learn
and record it somewhere, which I have started on my side.
We have to ask developers to actually create an all-in-all all-in-one
Don't come up with a service.
You've mentioned this service, and probably we've only recorded the fact that you mentioned
it once.
So, we've talked about it three times.
Tell me about what your idea is, because I've heard a couple of other people mention that
the idea of a service, how do you envision that?
What would that be?
What kind of service can we make?
Can we develop that will bring all of the technologies that we're trying to figure
out, all of the audio routing?
Can we make something that will bring that to the people who want to do the show
and not worry about the rest?
Yeah, I think so.
Just like you had a web log service right now where you post to.
For instance, Radio Userland, it can run on your own machine, but it can also run
completely somewhere else.
Now, getting text to that server is...
easy and we have lots of tools to do that already. Audio to it is a bit more
difficult and intuitive for just users. Now you could SPP it to the service or email it or...
Well you're talking about it is really is really a publishing system though.
That what you're talking about? Yeah but maybe also a recording system because
the next step is you open a line with the server through something that we are all
familiar with like iChat or voice over IP and have that be the recording.
And okay and so then the server will record can this in the server or this
service will also be able to combine stuff so say I want to talk with you we
don't have to restart this thing 25 million times it'll just combine those
sources okay
I also, yeah, I'm listening.
Yeah, you'll have a chat with multiple people
or a conference with multiple people
and it'll record everything.
So shouldn't Apple be doing this
or shouldn't AOL Instant Messenger,
shouldn't these, I mean,
is this something we really wanna jump into?
Is this something that we as, you know,
mere mortal developers and users
really wanna put our foot into?
Well, we can use those tools already.
We only have to put the pieces together.
For instance, with SIP,
there are SIP routers, SIP routers,
that you can reprogram to almost anything.
And it would be easy to add
publishing capability and, you know,
those are automatic enclosure generation MP3 encoding.
You can put everything.
in that same server.
So I think, well that's a, but I think this is an interesting thought, you know, because
I have to agree that there is, I mean there's such a high barrier level of entry on doing
this stuff, figuring out how to connect all the bits so you can record the audio and your
microphone and someone else and maybe a phone call.
Is this something that maybe, what's that PBX software that everyone keeps raving about
it's open source.
Yeah, I have a link.
I forgot the name.
Actually, I had a little time the last week.
It's too bad that it's bad timing.
Because I was traveling.
I was like in the Netherlands when you were there
last Wednesday and until Sunday.
Oh, OK.
Well, I mean, is this for work related stuff
that you're doing?
Yeah, I was there for a perfect person.
And then I went to a family.
And I kind of...
Well, you're allowed to do that.
You're allowed family visits.
I think there's no such timing as really good timing.
There's all kinds of stuff that always comes and goes.
But I'm so happy that we could just
want to reach out to you and just say hi.
And let you know that I certainly
appreciate all the work that you're doing
on figuring this stuff out.
And I'm fascinated by the service idea.
And now it's...
Is this something that you would involve your employer with maybe?
Is that something that Siemens would be interested in?
Well, I'm in a small division of Siemens.
Siemens is really, I'm not in the right division.
So it would be difficult.
Okay.
If I wanted to do something with it, then it would mean something from my job.
Right.
Right, all right.
So what is your background?
What are your hobbies?
What's the kind of stuff you like to do?
Background from school actually is very technical.
But I started to do consulting early on.
I've been to Cambridge Technology Partners.
Yeah.
I remember that.
I worked for them in Amsterdam in the dotcom years.
I went to Accenture here in Zurich and went to Austria for a PhD instructor.
So that's what makes me take as well.
Okay.
And came to Siemens.
And what's it like to live in Vienna?
No, Zurich.
I'm trying Zurich.
What's it like there?
Is it nice?
Yeah, it's the Amsterdam of Switzerland.
It's...
I don't know if that's a compliment or if that's good or bad.
media. You know, you've got lots of international people, you know, it's
well, I could get away with, with not speaking German. You know, it's,
it's lots going on, lots for single, you know, expert type people. Yeah. And
the quality of living is just, it's good. Plus, it's close to the
mountain. Where you like to ski, right? Exactly. Perfect.
Perfect. Well, you know what, we're following your, your research
very, very closely. And, you know, I'd like to, now that I've kind
of figured out what the best way is to contact you, maybe later
on the week, we can hook up again. And then by then, I'll
have had some responses, and maybe there'll be some questions
or reactions. And we can
Sure, I'd be happy to.
Okay, so on email we'll set up a time and a day and then we'll chat a little bit more.
This is a great introduction.
Alright, can you play me a song of the day or is it I'll set up?
It's not set up so that you'll hear the song of the day, but I can certainly play
a song of the day.
Well, I really like Prince, but I just bought the Supper Club 7 and that's like really relaxed.
Have you heard it yet?
No, no, I haven't heard the...
I think I have Supper Club 2.
I certainly don't think I'm anywhere near 7.
Anyway, no, no.
But my setup is bare bones.
I don't have the regular setup subscribed on the site, so I cannot play you any music
either.
Well, hopefully next time.
Okay, I'll make sure we find some Prince to put on for you and we'll talk to you in a couple
of days and we'll check in again.
All right, thank you very much.
Okay, here you go.
No, thank you.
Thanks for your time and have a great evening.
All right, bye-bye.
And my thanks to Hugo Schottmann.
this time.
I'm a common happy fat
Disagessing not to want to pass me
Physicality
Gotta keep body moving
Back to culture
Cheap to old school joint
I'm a full to full soldier
Physicality
Ha ha ha
Right
Wait a minute baby
Sha Da Da
Don't you miss the feeling music gave you
Back in the day
September
Er reviews Bayard
Up Thanks
öl Bach Chains
Slice Don't web guy
Familiar Keys and Truff
To learn, take, learn, or a bang
Oh, ain't your T-Jet master playin'
Know what? They loosin'
Cause we got a PhD in it
Bang, it's a lot to move in
Bang! Keepin' by the moonin'
Just like a dojo
Keep the old school joint
I can fold it to four coaches
Musicology
Alright
Hold down, baby
Oh, give me that!
Music counting!
I gotta get out!
Let's do some water troupons, don't just...
Come on!
Fire!
Keep keep keep fighting!
Music!
Keep fighting!
Keep keep keep fighting!
Don't stop dancing!
Tch!
Alright, on one y'all.
You hear this old school joint?
Don't you ever touch my stereo.
This set up got good and plenty
of what you need the most.
And that's
TRI
P
Yeah.
Okay.
And so it just keeps on
jamming and jamming and jamming and jamming.
And it's kind of like,
you know, it's kind of like the
gods were playing with this because I've been talking about
Prince. I think
I think Dave and I talked about it on trade secrets.
We, you know, we said, you know,
Prince would totally understand this stuff, right?
He'd be so completely into it.
And
lo and behold, if I wasn't interviewed
by Julio
and Julio works for
it's kind of, it's a night-ridder publication
in Minneapolis, St. Paul.
Uh, hold on a second.
Julio, here we go.
Julio Ojeda Zapada works for the, oh there it is, the St. Paul Pioneer Press.
And so I said, you know, as Julio was interviewing me, I said, you know, I think this is all
meant to be because, you know, Prince is going to read this and then he's going
to listen to the source code.
He's going to call up and he's going to get it and he's going to want to use this
for the distribution of his music.
Okay.
Maybe I'm just rambling on a little bit too much.
I'm going to leave you with one last bit that I found online.
My gosh, I'm not sure where this came from, other than the
blog digger media feed, right?
You've probably read about the number of times during the
Republican National Convention, how many times different words like
Osama bin Laden, no, I'm sorry, Saddam Hussein, Iraq, war on terror,
etc., but not Osama bin Laden.
All these different terms were used.
over and over and over again and maybe you heard some audio of it. I don't know but someone finally
Went through the trouble of putting this all together into a video
Let me just see I think the video is from
It's live. It's probably from C-span and what I thought I'd do is I'd play this it only lasts a couple of minutes
But it'll really freak you out when you hear how many times they're they're repeating these words and how many different people
And who these people are and so if there's a caption that comes up
Maybe I'll just break in and tell you that what it says like here
it says, how do you run a convention on a recathive failure and
so now it starts off with of course
Invoke 9 11 the heart of this great city. We saw a tragedy arrive on a quiet morning
September the 11th September the 11th September the 11th September 11th September 11th September 11th September
11th September 11th September 11
September 11th September 11
September 11th
11.
September 11.
September 11! September 11 September 11
September 11 September 11 September 11
This is Giuliani by the way. Now it says no your enemy.
Saddam Hussein
Handle the bin Laden matter appropriately.
And that's just got crits playing and everyone being quiet.
Above all, spread fear.
And danger.
Continuing danger.
Power of danger.
Very, very dangerous world.
Brave new threat.
Horrific acts of atrocities, murderous regimes.
Dedicating to killing us.
Tyranny and terror.
Slaughtered thousands of weapons of mass destruction.
Weapons of mass destruction.
Weapons programs.
The deadliest of weapons.
Terrible weapons.
Nuclear weapons.
Poison gas.
Torture chambers.
Mass graves.
Deadly technology.
Radical ideology of hate.
Terror of threats.
Terror.
War on terrorism.
War against terrorism.
Global war on terror.
Global terrorism.
Global.
God Giuliani's unbelievable.
He's the best one of all of them.
They continuously have thousands of quotes by Giuliani.
Global.
Charism.
Terrorism.
Terrorist, terrorist, terrorist.
George W. Bush. Keeping America Scared.
That's what it winds up with there.
Wow. I like Barbara Bush's the way she speaks.
She has a nice accent.
Terrorist, terrorist.
Anyway, that's your food for thought there.
I'm going to wrap this up. What are we at?
All kinds of ideas and stuff so
I'm midst all of this. I'm sure we'll pump out another source code sometime tomorrow. I thank you very much for listening
Thanks to Hugo Schottman for being on the show and I'll check you tomorrow
As always, you can send a comment, but you may let me add them at curry.com or leave
me a comment.
All the current shows in the archives and also, as I promised, links to top of
this discussed in the show at DailySourceCode.com.
The power of your Insta-Code.
And you can subscribe to the iPod or feed the RSS to
DailySourceCode.com.rss.xml. I'll talk to you tomorrow. Take care. Bye.