Do you like people?
No I don't.
Do you like all kinds of people?
That's wonderful.
Do you like adult films and other visual material?
I'm looking for a book and television.
Steadily expanding correctional.
I think we can help it.
You do?
That's good.
There are just a number of positions.
You will find that there can be great variety and interest.
But you will be rewarded with real pleasure television.
People like you.
On wheels.
Did you get me an advertiser?
I don't understand a quote.
I'm asteroid.
And it's like a medic head.
It's a quote.
Let me answer for the order.
A yes doctor.
Here it is.
Well, and though everybody.
Welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Talking in undertones here.
Because I don't want to make up my fellow passengers.
We are on British Airways flight 442 from San Francisco to London with continuing service
to Amsterdam the Netherlands.
The power of the intercourse.
So this is the, I'm a way home from blogger condition of the show.
But also we have to tone down the energy.
But I really can't be screaming here.
I'm sitting in my seat.
I've got everything all hooked up.
I've got the laptop, cracked open.
The AC power is the wide plugged in.
So I can get 110 volts out of the power of the laptop.
I'm holding onto my microphone.
And it is dark.
Anyway, let's see.
It is.
It's the show for.
This is for Tuesday.
No, for Wednesday.
For Tuesday the night.
For the hour.
The hour.
Yeah, that's what I meant.
It's Tuesday.
November 9th.
2004.
In London right now it is 2.30 pm.
So I ended up on another hour and a half of flying to do.
Okay.
So it really, really sucked.
Major league.
But my flight was supposed to be SFO at 7.30.
And hang out with Don and Drew.
We went to tower records.
Pick up some stuff for Christina.
Of course.
And we had some coffee with Robert's goal.
He was hanging out with us as well.
And then Robert went to Microsoft.
Microsoft to go to work and Dawn Drew and I 1-0 to Stanford to meet up with James.
And we're talking about James on trade secrets.
That's their friend to guy with the cool big low piercings.
It was like a shotgun made the holes.
And so he's at the super genome sequencing establishment.
And that got a little tour of everything that he's got.
That was absolutely amazing.
That is a sun.
Super computer that.
I don't know.
It was almost like.
So I want to take into a sunwork station and just, you know,
blown it up by, I don't know, 200 times the size was unbelievable.
And from there I grabbed a cab to the airport.
My flight was at 7.30.
So I arrived perfectly around 5 o'clock.
I only defined out that the flight was delayed.
It wasn't leaving until 10 o'clock.
So, well, luckily, luckily, luckily, luckily.
Wi-Fi, probably available.
And I was able to chill out in the lounge.
And download everything.
I had been able to download it at the right height.
Because of poor Wi-Fi.
And I did tell them that by the way, I'm away out.
So I was checking out.
I said, you know, I really had a good time here and enjoyed it very much.
But, you know, you really should do something about your Wi-Fi.
And he was going at all.
But you knew that a bridge for better receptionist,
I said, look, I'm technical.
It's your provider.
You know, it's just, it was not good.
And he said, well, did you call them?
And now, now, I'm telling you.
And I don't know if they'll ever get that fixed.
That would be a reason not to stay at the height in the future.
Otherwise, I liked it.
I liked it very much.
So, blogger con.
Oh, man.
We had a good time.
I'm not going to make this source code too long.
I think the polygons are bringing breakfast by in a second.
And I don't know if that, well, I won't have room to have breakfast
and keep the laptop open.
And there are priorities, you know.
So I want to talk a little bit about the trip.
I had to have some stuff to play for you.
I was able to queue some stuff up.
Not everything that I'd want to, and tomorrow, when I kind of get turned around,
there's so much cool stuff in podcast-wise that you've got to hear.
It really is just so much coming out, including radio dramas.
And it's just awesome, awesome stuff.
But for today, a couple of things that I did find, you know, hanging around the net.
We didn't really have much chance to talk on the source code about the results of the election,
but there's always something to play.
I know I'm doing it.
I just just let me do it, alright?
Well, I'm the type of guy who sees life in black and white.
You know I think it's better to be certain to be right.
I took financial surplus and got rid of all that green.
To grow the greatest deficit, the world has ever seen that call me the squander.
Yeah.
The squander.
I'll take a stab and down and down and down and down and down.
Oh, there's tragedy in Washington and New York and PA.
Thousands gone, wars begun, got to make someone pay.
The goodwill of the world is something I flushed out on the dream.
When I said, forget oh, silent.
Let's go get sedan who's saying, they call me the squander.
Yeah.
The squander.
I'll take a stab and down and down and down.
Oh, well, I go from state to state.
I'll along that campaign trail and I'll avoid a true debate.
Because the more you look, the more you'll see.
I was born to fail, oh, I'm the type of guy who decide in every bush.
And I know what I want when I point a judge.
The billarights have surely seemed a good thing at the time.
Now take those civil liberties.
Put them where the sun doesn't shine.
They call me the squander.
Yeah.
The squander.
I'll take a stab and down and down and down and down.
Oh, I go from state to state.
I'm making water out of wind.
And the people disagree.
I'll close my ears or else.
You'll see me start to scowl and whine.
Oh, I'm the type of guy who will never say I'm wrong.
Don't bother me with facts.
I'm right or I belong.
My dad stayed out of Baghdad.
He was all concerned.
But what the heck does he know?
He'll be served wonder.
They call me the squander.
Yeah.
The squander.
I'll take a stab and down and down and down and down.
Yeah.
I'm the squander.
The squander.
I'll take a stab and down and down and down and down.
Right on.
I'm not quite sure.
I'm not sure.
I quite sure where that came from.
But clearly, very used parody of the wanderer.
The bush squanderer here on your daily source code.
And we're at, actually, I could probably check that out.
I can tell you how we're doing right now.
Let me just open up my onboard video entertainment system.
There we go.
Let me turn on.
Okay.
Right now.
So find out where we are.
Time to destination one hour 32 minutes.
We are 844 miles from the destination.
We've got a 96 mile per hour tailwind.
And currently.
Let's see.
It's not going to tell me how, what the altitude is.
And it'll tell me that in a second.
I'm sure.
Okay.
My next one here.
We're just woke up.
You looked at me really nicely.
She's getting some stuff out of the overhead bin.
Ooh.
So we are.
Yeah.
I can see now that we're about.
We're just underneath the Iceland right now.
I'm going to tell you what our altitude is in the second.
About half an hour ago.
I felt the descent.
They started to descend.
Okay.
It's taken a long time for that to come up.
So.
Good one more second.
Can I just have a fucking altitude check, please?
What's our altitude?
Uh.
Okay.
It just shows maps over and over.
And it doesn't give me the information I want.
Okay.
If it pops up, I'll let you know.
Um.
Blogger com.
Boy.
Don't know where to start.
Um.
But I've already started to call some stuff from.
Uh.
From the I potter.
Stuff that has.
Has.
Come in.
Oh.
37,000 feet.
There you go.
About time.
658 miles per hour.
It's our ground speed.
Good.
Outside air temperature.
Mine is 72.
Okay.
Who's that?
It was so nice meeting everybody.
And I can't even begin to.
To.
To thank.
You know.
Everyone for all that they've been doing in podcasting and.
And just for.
You know, putting together an awesome.
Session.
At.
At blogger con.
And besides the podcasting part, just blogger con.
General was.
Um.
It was good.
I really enjoyed it.
We talked about that on trade secrets.
So if you haven't heard that.
Check out secrets dot scripting dot com.
But also met people who have been sending me stuff over the past.
There are a couple of weeks and months.
Including.
Um.
An announcement about a brand new podcast.
This is from honey buddies.
Hi Adam.
My name is.
I'm about this.
I am Mexican.
And I leave in the Bay area in California.
In Sunnyvale.
Well, first of all, I wanted to.
Uh.
Congratulations for the show.
And so now here's a.
Uh.
A Boeing.
But in.
All right.
Second of all, I want to.
Obviously.
Uh.
Tell you that.
My prayers are currently offered for your mom's help.
And all of your family as well.
So that you can all get through these difficult time.
Uh.
In the best possible way.
And.
After that, I wanted to.
Tell you that I managed to create my very own podcast.
This one is in Spanish.
And I've uploaded it to my website.
It's www dot.
Butis dot or g slash podcast.
Uh.
Butis is spelled.
Be a symbol.
A T is in teenager.
I.
Z.
So, um.
It was a liberal of love.
Took me.
Uh.
I'll say three hours.
To get it going.
And man.
You should see my setup.
Um.
Totally.
Regimentary.
I don't even have a mic.
Um.
Using my powerful G4 to do all these.
And the most weird software setup in history.
But.
Anyway, managed to put it up.
I think the worst part was.
Trying to figure out how to set up an RSS.
Feed.
Never done in my life.
Had no idea.
Started copying and pasting a bunch of things.
I found on the web.
And then actually on your site.
Just to get me going.
And.
Well, I don't know if it's working or not.
As a matter of fact.
So.
I'll appreciate if you could give it a shot.
See if that works for you.
Well, I'm going to be.
Uh.
Right on and actually we didn't meet, which was very cool.
And he was apologizing for a few sleeve for having sent this five.
Uh, megabyte.
Uh, audio comment through my email.
It made it through the email, which is actually kind of surprising.
I thought there was a five megabyte cut off.
But no problem at all my brother.
And it seems to be working.
And I love the fact that Jaime, what he did is he didn't.
I didn't have a blogging tool.
He just copied and pasted.
And that's why RSS is really simple syndication.
Because you can look at it.
And you can read it.
And you can understand it.
And you can see what you have to do.
And you can create it with a text editor.
Um, and, uh, it's working.
So check that out by teased.org slash podcast.
Um, someone else who I was really looking forward to to meeting.
Uh, at BloggerCon was Michael Butler from the Rock and Roll Geek show.
And he, it was great.
Um, he hooked me up with the, all the American heartbreak CDs.
And put in the new one that hasn't come out yet, which I'm not a chance to listen to.
But I'm sure you'll be hearing some music from that on, uh, on the daily source code in the future.
Because I do like that man.
And Michael is exactly what I thought he would be.
And, and actually even, even more satisfying than that.
And he recorded, um, uh, a podcast on the evening before BloggerCon.
Uh, at the, at the Ricky's High at, and I just wanted to play a little bit of that.
Because it, it really, it really tells you a lot about Michael.
It's cool.
So I went to BloggerCon yesterday.
Left for the show.
The show.
Yeah, I guess it was kind of a show.
I had a good time to felt like being in a show to me.
I went on Friday because I got into a huge fight with my wife.
Really uncomfortable night.
So I grabbed a bunch of beer.
Went down to Ricky's High at,
drank myself a 12 pack of Heinrich and buy myself.
I don't know if you ever sit in a hotel and buy yourself and drink yourself to sleep.
But it was all right.
Sometimes it's kind of fun to do that.
Plugged in my power book.
Got on the internet.
Up pops.
Um, well, I don't know if you have a Mac, but if you have iTunes, if you have people who share
in their playlist, you can see their songs.
So, uh, pops.
Adam Curry's playlist and I think Dave's slushers playlist as well.
So I kind of went through their stuff and see what they have.
And killed the time doing that for a while.
Watch a little television.
Finish the 12 packs a lot past out.
I think it was about a half a beer left when I woke up in the morning.
All my mouth was all dry.
But I know it is when you pass out drunk.
I don't do that too often.
But that was one of those nights where you just have to do it.
I have to talk quite now because the subject in question is in the room with me.
If you get my drift, I don't want to get into another fight.
I'm going to bother by the way.
The fight is pretty much over.
And that was the part I wanted you to hear.
A lot of people were quite concerned about the quote fight that Michael had with his wife.
So everything's okay.
I think he went home and painted the front of the house and kind of got out of the dog house by doing that.
It was nice to meet you, Michael.
Matt, it was awesome and good luck with the show and with the course with the band and everything else.
And he's also looking for a, for a sponsorship from Heineken.
I will try to hook you up, my brother.
Maybe they can't at least get you some free cans.
Shouldn't it be something like that at the very least?
And now we're promo on the daily source code.
We're on the day.
Three minutes.
Six, two seconds live.
And by door five and six, don't forget to put the earphones on.
Here's the microphone.
There's this thing on.
30 seconds.
Is that a yummy?
Hello?
Check it.
Make it up.
10 seconds.
Okay.
Let's have a shot.
We're on it.
Five.
Yeah.
You like it.
I'm sending the globe via the internet.
This is the radio brothers broadcast.
Hi.
This is Ray Edwards.
Risk a little bandwidth.
Check out the radio brothers podcast to get reviews of the newest hottest podcasts.
Lighthearted commentary on the news and blogs.
The occasional rant.
Look behind the scenes of the broadcast radio business, some comedy and some great pod music.
100% free the distributed share.
Plus, we delivered all in small files in crystal clear 64 KBPS MP3.
With complete show notes and links for every show, set your iPodder to radiobrothers.com forward slash index.xml.
Visit us at radiobrothers.com and download the show directly or just look for us on audio.weblogs.com.
Excellent.
So check that podcast out.
Radio brothers.
And if you have a promo for your show, just send it to me.
Because that's what I'm trying to do.
By the way, people are waking up now.
They turn on the lights.
Which means we're going to have breakfast and a little bit.
So I'll have to clear off my table if I want to eat.
And I got to tell you, I'm freaking starving.
And I had the shitiest meal, man.
It was like the dinner.
It was just chicken, chicken, stuff.
Why don't they just make on air planes?
Just make it simple.
You know, make a grilled chicken or meat and potatoes.
But you don't put all the saffron and it's all that crappy stuff in it.
And I do, I like culinary food.
I just don't think that on air planes is the best place to try it.
So I went to tower records.
As I said earlier, before we got to the front left for the airport,
we're done and drew to pick up some good Charlotte stuff,
which is the band.
My daughter Christina is told he nuts about.
And I think I told you in the last source code or before I left.
I think we need an energizer drink.
An energizer drink?
What's this?
This is the energizer?
What's in it?
Fruit?
Okay, thank you.
Excellent.
I have an energizer, fruit drink.
Hmm.
Okay, that totally makes up for the shitty dinner.
That was really good.
Anyway, so Christina has been in touch with the manager of this band
that is going on tour with Good Charlotte.
And they're an unsigned band, non-R-I-A-A music.
Hmm.
That really is good, this energy drink.
And I'm trying to find a place to put it down.
Don't have enough hands right now.
Okay, there we go.
And so she sent me her favorite track,
MP3, which of course is totally clear to play, which I'm so happy about.
So look for these guys on the road opening up for Good Charlotte.
As they come through the United Kingdom from the UK themselves.
Here's three quarters.
Check out Madeline.
Yeah, it's the reason they're excited.
And all our songs we care.
Can sense them whenever then.
Stop it.
It's silverware.
You trying to listen to rained, it's nice sand.
And we don't say it through it.
For we don't say that it's one way
Try to know whether it goes bad.
To break my heart
And tell the girl back to bed
To set me apart
I promised that I'd never meet
The whole life broke no thanks to me
This isn't always out for one more time
Here's your new baby
Don't say things to the girl I know
Something we're supposed to find inside
And we don't say another word
Please don't say this moment
Tell the girl back to bed
To break my heart
And tell the girl back to bed
To set me apart
To set me up
I told the girl back to bed
To set me apart
Set me apart
3 quarters.
Madeline and the be out on the road with good Charlotte check them out at 3-quarters.co.uk
and thanks for watching.
We're plug-in those guys here on the daily source code.
The post-collection on every side, everyone's sick of everyone else and they're all
turning snipe.
Set John Kerry as Bush's vote count was kicking back.
I can't believe I'm losing to this idiot.
Republicans have not been much more tactical though they won.
You turn on many Arnold Schwarzenegger almost came undone when he refused to hear Democrats
attacks from Puzzles, saying why listen to losers when my next office will be
oval.
Though she's gone to raise a Heinz is not forgotten.
Some say she's a hypocondriac, her opinion's not carry advisor sports just rotten.
They wish to migrate to stage to deadly or attack.
Even Dr. Rockin France has been rude to George W., he visited a era vet but if the U.S.
lights here he'll snab you.
George W. wanted was to reach out to the people of Europe.
He didn't mean to stir up.
Back to con syrup.
Oh, hatreds when this time as electoral votes really were up.
Stay tuned for late breaking.
Oh, damn.
Actually, yeah.
That's the snap.
Damn, damn, damn, damn.
Sorry, didn't mean to interrupt the tap dance and podcast for news but I want to make
sure you caught that little bit of the wonderful service here on British Airways and
they're going to hook me up with my breakfast on the chair next to me for a few minutes.
I can't do that.
I can't do it.
Yes, lovely.
Thank you.
I'm getting ready to English here.
Tea.
Lovely.
You can sugar.
So one thing at blogger calm that there were a lot of people were talking about was, well,
I was like, maybe just trying to sound here.
Okay.
Hold on.
I'm trying to get my utensils at mean time.
See, I got a close mic, but otherwise you'll never hear me with all the airplane noise.
Hold on.
It's not great.
Still getting plastic knives and force.
It's just a good idea.
Okay.
Right, too.
Nap can in place.
Nice little muffins and nice little fruit here.
Oh, it's looking so good.
Thank you very much.
I have to say, by the way, that British Airways has this great service.
They have all different kinds of classes of service.
So there's economy class, but there's three different kinds.
And that all has to do with the size and of seats and space between your seat and the seat and front of you.
Oh, I got to get my sort of crust on here.
Hold on.
I hope I guess not.
And so in first class, I think I'd like condos up there.
I don't know what's going on in first class.
But in that business class, they also have three classes of service.
And I took the lowest one.
And it's great because you're still going to sleep or seat and they actually slept for about five hours.
I'm not that comfortable, but even, and I'm a pretty tall guy.
I mean, I could totally stretch out and it was good because I feel reasonably refreshed.
So anyway, back to blogger con for a second.
The ground rules were very clear that vendors could not talk about their own products.
Excuse me, does need a cup of tea.
And so there was some action in a couple of the sessions.
I wasn't in the overload session with Skobelware.
I guess the Kaka hit the fan.
But I thought that what the iPod or lemon guys did was the smartest thing they could have done.
By releasing iPod or 1.1, just before blogger con.
I don't think any of the developers were there.
But they certainly had their announcement flowing through the iPod or, I guess, the iPod or podcast feed.
So if you missed it, I just want to play that for you because I love it with the way these guys do their marketing and promotion.
So it's upbeat and it's positive and it's cool.
The iPod or development team is happy to announce just in time for blogger con.
The availability of vision 1.1 of iPod or Windows and Macintosh.
Grab it now from iPod.sourceforgedomnet.
Yeah, it was there you go now.
I've been using it tested it out on the Macintosh and I got to say it's pretty cool.
They've got the directory in there and yeah.
It's amazing how far we've come and just a few short.
We will actually just a few months and how we have this software that is maturing.
It's beautiful.
And I'd like to remind you that Koma 1000 from Seattle as a podcast feed.
You can find it at the iPod or directory or if you go to audio.weblogs.com.
That's actually a great place to sample.
If you don't have an iPod or if you just want to see what is this podcasting all about or you want to see stuff that you may not be subscribed to.
But you might want to audio.weblogs.com.
That's the perfect place to go check out all things podcast.
And Koma 1000 is a radio station in Seattle and her voice bound is the consumer guy.
And I'd like to play his stuff once in a while because today I even learned something about cameras and megapixels.
How many megapixels do you want?
4 5 6.
Go shopping for a digital camera and you'll need to answer that question.
The pixel count is a way to let you compare picture resolution from camera to camera.
The more megapixels the better.
The bottom line of megapixels is they matter but they're not everything.
Paul Reynolds with consumer reports says a high pixel count matters most.
If you plan to make a lot of enlargements from the shots you take.
The more megapixels you have, the more flexibility you will have to edit your shots and say take a small part of that image and make it into a full print at an eight by ten or a large size.
But Reynolds says for a lot of people and entry level two or three megapixel camera is just fine.
If you're taking snapshots if you don't intend to do a lot of editing or cropping or make them into poster size,
a two or three megapixel camera will be fine for most people and of course it will be a lot less expensive than paying for more megapixels.
By the way, every Monday at this time from now through Christmas, we'll be looking at another digital product that just might be on your holiday shopping list.
I'm her voice bomb, the consumer man.
Looking out for you on Komo 1000.
Thank you very much.
Oh man, the timing is perfect.
Keeps on showing up right away.
Something's over.
Thank you very much for her voice bomb.
For that info about cameras and what to do and what to get.
At the foot football dinner, I sat next to the author of podcasting from software land.
And I tell you,
blogger cameras blogger calm is really inspiring because people are going home and starting all kinds of new and cool projects.
I got inspired to help people figure out how to do podcasting.
I've set up a new domain, www.howtopodcast.org.
Not much there yet, but I'm planning on creating step-by-step instructions and links to various software downloads.
And hoping to get it up before Thanksgiving.
And finally, I got so jazzed by the energy I got from all the people of blogger calm.
I'm inspired to do some other podcast besides software land.
Once I get them set up, I'll tooth the horn for them.
The plan is to do a series of one to two-minute podcast and try to do that daily.
And then I'm also going to set up a music-only-related podcast featuring music that I've done,
as well as music that my daughter, Lindsey Taylor, who's much much better than me, has done.
And so, as I always say, that's it for now, from software land.
Thank you very much.
And we're looking forward to howtopodcast.org.
Which I think it was actually setting up for Mickey.
If you were at blogger calm, you know, there was one girl who stood up and said, you know,
I'm actually getting paid to blog.
She works for a movie company that makes movies about social issues and actually wants people to participate
in the conversation about the topic of the movies.
And I think what was interesting is when she stood up and was, you know, someone said, oh, and he's Mickey,
and she actually gets paid.
Or she, I think she introduced herself a thing I get paid.
When she stood up, I could hear 15 guys in the room in their head go.
Pointing around around around around.
She's the most beautiful Picasso tattoo on her arm.
And she was sitting right next to him.
When he was, so this, that's the thing that's how the whole howtopodcast.org came up
because Mickey really wants to learn how to podcast.
And, well, you know, there's so many gallon guys that I'll always jump in and want to help her with that.
A lot of people commented on mojones.
I've played mojones a lot on the show.
And people have said that they really wanted to buy the album.
Couldn't get a hold of it, which sucks.
So I fired off a mail to the guys and I said, look guys, you got to figure out how we can sell your CD,
where people from the states can get a hold of it.
And I asked them, and this is based upon Steve Gilmore's,
not even recommendation, but almost his demand.
He wants a live unplugged mojones mini concert from the castle.
Before we leave, check it out.
So I sent in the request and I said, guys, come on.
Let's do some cool.
Let's mic it up.
Let's do a little mini concert.
And we'll put it out there for everybody to enjoy.
And of course, they should also figure out how to sell their CD at the same time.
Because I think that people would love to have some live material and also get their CD,
which is good stuff.
And on openpodcast.org, number 127, I came across a different mojones.
The mojones that I know is mojnons.nl actually.
And this is M-O-E, space J-O-N-E-S mojones and a cup of Joe.
I'm only cup but Joe.
I crave a plane of table and a door of junk.
Don't put anything on.
I'm talking junk of George.
I sit for mug of dust.
With the cream and a spoon.
How many orders that we need.
Give me a pile of sky.
We top a pair of stands.
Throw in a handful of things.
Bad and do everything.
To the crap on matter.
On a tray you'll break.
I'll make the spoon of short.
Do I need to go on?
I want to get but Joe.
Yeah.
Don't add that done.
I'll pour a glass of chairs.
Do a tub of Bob.
I'll smoke a pack of Jack.
While I'm burning my back.
I'll eat and drink.
I'll pour glass of chairs.
Do a tub of Bob.
I'll smoke a pack of Jack.
While I'm burning my back.
I'll eat and dish a crisp.
Another bowl of Joe.
All on a saucer a team.
Would you rather have him?
Just feel me up with.
Fred, feed me your fork of Frank.
And while more healthy a team.
May it all rise and take him.
Oh, man again.
Damn it make a meal of Sam.
But don't give me no more.
Because what I really want to come for, Joe.
Don't add that done.
I want a cup of Joe.
I'll grab a plate of Dave.
Open a jar of John.
Don't put anything on.
I'll charge a jug of George.
I'll sit for my cup done.
With the creamer of steam.
How many more does that leave?
You beat a bottle of sky.
Heat up a panel stand.
Throw in a handful of things.
And you every train.
Or in a can of Dan.
Make a meal of Sam.
But don't give me no more.
Because what I really want to come for, Joe.
I'll play it all, Dave.
We were off steam.
A cup of Joe.
And what was that?
A handful of Dick.
Interesting lyrics there.
Well, that's just going to wrap it up for today's Mile High Edition of the Daily Source
It's still talking in undertones.
People don't look at me like saying, shut up.
You want peace and quiet on the plate.
When I get back, it's going to be a second noise.
Guys coming back again.
When I get back, I probably won't be in until 10 o'clock.
I want to get home in the castle until 10.
And that means that Wednesday, as of Wednesday, I have almost exactly one week.
To get everything ready for the big move.
So that means that I got to spend one of these days back and up the bar.
I'm packing up all of my stuff because that's like the only thing left that hasn't been packed up yet.
So I will of course be bringing you a source code every single day as we try to do.
And when I get back, I'll have more thoughts to stuff about podcasting.
What we learned at BloggerCon and where we're going.
And of course, always ready to promote any new stuff that comes out.
So thank you all very much for checking it out.
The source code for November 9th, 2004.
And as always, if you want to leave a comment, add a MacLeod.com.
Audio comments are welcome.
You might want to just send me your L to the MP3 instead of the whole MP3 file.
And of course, you can leave a comment on my weblog live.cure.com.
And you can find a new source code.
No, the archives at dailysourcecode.com and the podcast fee.
A source code.com slash rss.xml.
All right, everybody.
We'll be landing in about an hour.
And tomorrow I'll bring you another daily source code from TheCaston.
Take care.
Bye.
We'll be back.
The hour is up to zero.