The power of your own power is infinite.
What? Good evening, everybody!
Yes! It still exists!
to redo on Saturday the 18th, and here we are, 10.36pm on Sunday the 19th.
36 hours that I had so much to...
which is where I had my office.
A spaghetti factory has exploded and anyone who's ever tinkered around with audio and patch cables and wires probably knows exactly what I'm talking about.
It kinda looks like my room when I was 6 years old too, you know, stringing wires all across the room.
So let me see, of course life got in the way of having some actual real fun here.
I had to go up, I was being interviewed for a TV show so I had to be...
And there's some financial meetings I could do and actually I really wanted to go back to Belgium
And then possibly even fly back up to Amsterdam or even stay there
for the 27th annual
reunion of the pirate radio station I worked at in the
very early 80 81 79 through
27th annual reunion Christ. So I drove back down to Belgium and it being a Friday,
usually traffic is a little bit heavier. It takes about an hour and a half to get from Belgium to Amsterdam
and vice versa from where we live. And there were a couple of accidents. So I wound up spending about
three hours on the road. Didn't get it until 6.30. And I said, well, screw it. I'm going to have dinner here
with the...
That's my daughter Christina.
She said, what are you doing?
What are you wearing?
Mom's Uggs.
OK.
So it was 10.
Oh, so it was about 7 o'clock.
We had dinner.
And Christina was out.
She was training for horse riding.
So we hung out, watched a bit of TV in there on 10.15,
10.30.
I said, OK, I'm going to go record the source code.
And Patricia said, well, why don't you do that tomorrow
when you're nice and fresh?
I said, no, it's Friday.
I've got to do this.
I have to do it every single day.
And it was like five or six minutes late.
I was thinking about Saturday morning.
And I was humming a tune, which is Chicago Saturday
in the Park.
So I'm humming this tune.
And I'm singing along with the lyrics.
And the Patricia says, no no no no, it's uh, Saturday in the park, I think it was the first of July, and of course!
Yeah, after 17 years of marriage, you say, wanna bet?
Right, so obviously I won the bet, which I knew I would.
You never want to bet with a disj-
And, um, as sometimes will happen between consenting adults, you know, they'll make some kind of...
Maybe it's insurable for broadcast, no matter if it's on airwaves or on MP3.
So needless to say...
Anyway, so to make it up and then of course I'll tell you what happened on Saturday morning and Sunday all the stuff that I went through
Oh, we're gonna play a couple s-
It was the father July
It's Saturday
The year on the park
I said it was the father July
It's been you
I've been waiting such a long time
you
People talking, me that's not it
Singing for a star
I've been waiting such a long time
you
from Belgium.
Okay, so Saturday morning, I got up bright and early,
had all these songs all chosen, of course,
you know, it's gonna make total sense
to play that on Saturday
and to make up for missing out on Friday.
And I was up at 7.30, got everything together.
I reverted back to the old way of recording.
And I was figuring, you know,
I'd get one source code down and then, you know,
I'd really work on my audio setup
to make the new show, Trade Secrets,
much, much better from quality, of quality.
Because, you know, I was sitting in the car
for so many hours, it had my iPod with me, of course.
And it had the first, the inaugural Trade Secret show
loaded up on it.
So I had a chance to listen to the show
and I was not happy.
I was happy with the content.
I thought it was very good for a first co-host show.
Particularly if you've known each other for a long time,
because the risk, and Dave Slusher pointed this out
on the evil genius chronic.
There's a risk that you get a little buddy-buddy and then the listener is sitting there going,
what are these guys laughing about?
But as you get to know us better, then you'll understand our humor and you'll pick up on stuff pretty quickly.
It always happens with that. I've done a lot of radio shows with co-
And, yeah, so I really, even though technologically we had a set up pretty interesting with recording via wire tap, which records all of your Mac OS audio,
and using, we tried Skype, Skype didn't work, and then we tried iChat with the AOL Instant Message client.
And what's nice about iChat is you can route the input and the output.
How can we do this, like a real highly produced show that you do live to MP3 on your computer?
And do we have all the bits to do that with?
Because my mic sounded really good on Trace Secrets and Dave just,
because my mic sounded so hot and so processed and his volume was soft,
that it just sounded almost like talking with a person on the phone,
which is not what I wanted it to be. I wanted it to sound much more like we're
more or less in the same room. So I wanted to figure all of that out, but I just cut a quick
source code. Do a nice 40 minute show, whatever. So I was in the 30 minutes into it,
then the computer froze up again, just like it had done three times when Dave and I started
recording the first Trace Secrets, which was so hard man, because your energy is gone.
It's hard to tell the same story again because it's just not fresh anymore.
And still, I think we did a pretty good job, but it was so frustrating Saturday morning and it
froze up and then I'd say, okay, I'm...
to go back to the bare basics and what are going to use wire tap and just a little bit
of microphone processing and the quick time player and then that start crashing.
I said, you know what?
Screw it.
I'm going to figure out how to get this audio stuff working the way I want it before I record
another show.
Well, have you ever been trying to get somewhere from anyone with like a train or an airplane?
We need the connection.
And someone eventually will say to you, excuse me, you just can't get here.
Get there from here.
Well, let me move my life out of the way of my necklace.
There.
Hello.
You know, so this is kind of the same with what I'm trying to do here with the
audio set up on the Mac.
You cannot get there from here, at least not with the tools that you have.
Hold on.
Let me just stick that inside there.
There we go.
Here's what I wanted.
Now anyone who's who's worked in a radio studio or in any type of audio
studio, you know that you have all your outputs and you want to have
sends to send stuff to, you know, rather.
it to a different place and trying to find the combination of being able to route audio
into the right places and to record it all and to be able to shut off the mic selectively
so that it doesn't keep on recording was very, very difficult.
There is no application as far as I know for OSX, for Mac that will let you do exactly
what I want to achieve.
So here's how I had it set up at a certain point and I have seen the limits of the G4 processor ladies and gentlemen.
I have been to the edge and it doesn't
to do and I'll tell you what the solution is. So what I want to be able to do is, well,
basically there is no program that I could find that would let you address more than
one audio interface per channel on a mixing console because that's really what I need.
Now there's all kinds of virtual devices that you can set up. You have Soundflower
which gives you two channels in, two channels out of a virtual device. You have Soundflower
16 which obviously gives you 16 channels. These, and they work very well.
Also you have something called Jack Tools. Jake Savin from Userland sent me an email.
knows damn well what's out there and what's available.
He also pointed to Jack Tools and he said, you know, this stuff is open source.
It's come from the Linux world, but still all pretty much cutting edge.
Yeah, boy is it.
It does work.
You know, you can actually route the sound out of one application into another application.
And at a certain point I had it all set up.
Everything was working.
I could selectively route things left and right.
The problem was you're sending all of this audio through virtual audio devices and delay
builds up latency.
It starts off with maybe just a millisecond or two.
And then before you know it, you know, you do something else, you move your mouse and
then, you know, it's going to start caching that and storing it in different places in
memory.
And then basically on the headphones, I'd hear my voice delayed, which makes it very difficult
to talk because, you know, the machine had it.
I opened up a terminal.
window and I did a top command that was running like an average of 11 or 12 on the load on
the machine.
And the first thing I thought was, oh, I need to do a processor now.
But then I was like, no, you're never going to get it exactly synced up.
There's always going to be a delay.
Now my PowerBook, as with most Macs, has an internal device, but you can only switch
between your internal microphone or your line input.
And it only really has one real input device.
So I had to break down.
I didn't want to, but I guess there's no other choice.
hardware device. Now I happen to have sitting around, I've had it for a long
time, never really used it. It's an M-Box from Digi Design. It's just a little, and
thank God it's not too big, so it's still portable. It's a little plastic box.
It connects by USB to the computer. It has two inputs. One mix output and it has,
hold on a second, let me just see what I've got here. Yeah, and it has a volume for
headphones. I can also provide phantom power 48 volts if needed and you can
switch those inputs between a line or a mic or a MIDI instrument.
So, I believe it or not, I now have it so that,
and I purchased DJ 1800, which is like, I think it's $35.
And it's, you basically have a visual interface of four playback decks.
And they pretty much look like either a digital deck or a,
it has a very VCR quality to it.
But it looks a lot like studio CD players that we've used on radio studios.
And you can cue up stuff real quick and it automatically detects the beginning and the end of a track.
And you can, you know, loop it.
There's a countdown timer.
You can speed through it really quickly, step through exactly what you want.
With four faders for outputs, you can route stuff to a different output for,
if you know, if you want to cue something up so that it's not being recorded.
Now I'm sending the output of that just to the regular speakers.
I'm using GarageBand for the mic processing.
Also, so that's just grabbing the microphone in and that literally is.
Let me see.
Oh, that's grabbing from the M-Box because the microphone is plugged into the M-Box.
It gets crazier.
But here's the way I did it.
So somewhere I had to build one routing, one connection between two different devices,
and neither of them could be a virtual device.
So indeed, I now have, from the headphones, going out is a 3.5mm stereo jack, going
into two XLRs, which are the, you know, if you've ever seen those, those are professional plugs.
Often you see them on microphones.
It's a round plug with three big holes, or if it's a male connector, three prongs in there.
And that's being fed into the DigiDesign hardware box.
So that's now become an input.
And all of that eventually routes into Audio Hijack Pro, which I also purchased.
Otherwise, after 10 minutes, you get this really nasty hissing sound.
And that is recording everything that's coming off of that box.
So in theory, I can send all this.
information I can write, you know, a whole bunch more of applications output to the
inbox because it's all sitting there in a chip, I guess, in theory. There's no
memory that's being swapped from disk or anything that can really slow down and I
think it can handle quite a lot and it's really only getting, you know, one
signal that's already mixed. So I think that I should be able to do quite a
lot and of course now I can add a either an iChat call and I can route
back to it from anything that I want to. So for the next trade secrets, I should be
able to not only get Dave's quality equal to mine, but I should also be able to send
it when I play something. He should be able to hear that on his head, on his end,
even if I'm playing an mp3. Okay, so you can only imagine that this took all of
Saturday up until 1am and that's when I finally gave up. You know, actually I
thought I had it all running at 1am and I was still, excuse me, using wiretap and damn it.
killed it, like 30, again 30 minutes into it.
So, there's nothing more damning than having recorded something
and really put some effort into whatever you're saying
and then just have that crash and be totally gone.
So I needed something really stable
and I think I have this set up.
And I'll really list this and take some screenshots
so everybody can see what the setup is
because I know that not many people
are on this path trying to make this happen.
But it can be done.
It's just the external box that pisses me off
that I have to have that.
But until I have two different sound devices in my computer
or if anyone makes one like that that's portable,
just have to live with this.
Let's see, what I want to talk about.
Oh, it's funny because so this morning,
again got up really early
because we had to go to a big fashion show
that Patricia does every year or every season actually
with Paul Schilter.
He's a...
a big fashion guy here in the Netherlands, actually in Europe.
And he has a huge, so 750 people.
And she designs the makeup, works with the models.
She also has a big influence on all of the clothing stuff that he does.
This year, we had our flat screens, the Grand Master View flat screens.
I'm a shareholder in the company.
These are flat screens that are 2 meter 20 diagonal.
That's the consumer version.
We can make them so big you wouldn't believe.
So I was there selling screens.
Patricia was there with her cosmetics company.
And she also did something very cool.
She did a song.
She performed a song at the very end of the show.
And all the models came out and danced with her.
And I played that one for you because it's just kind of cool
and it's rather short.
That's my wife.
My husband.
Italiano.
I'm a source girl.
Hey Goomba, I love how you dance so Goomba
That's where you never gonna be nowhere in the-
She can love you
And I'm gonna say to you
Mambo
Italian girl
I don't know what to cook into the night.
She's taking me by the pizzeria down the way to Monteria
Don't you tell your mom, mom's gonna tell her about it
There's nothing to it, come and baby listen to it
Mambo Mambo, Italian, oh Mambo Mambo
You mixed up with Jesus
I'm not sure what to do with this.
I'm always at the unknown.
My wife.
On the source code.
Go figure.
Man, if I played my wife's song on the radio, people would be so pissed off.
No, no, no, you can't do that because you know, that's like...
Anyway, my show, do whatever the hell I want.
Okay, let's switch gears here for a second.
Need to talk about a couple things.
First of all, as I was on the road a lot, I also caught Dave Slusher's source code
for yesterday.
I'm on the source code.
And he came up with something. He caught a refer which was hitting his or was it his bit
torrents? Well, you'd have to listen to the latest show to get all of that. I don't have it queued up
right now. But he saw in his refer log, I think it was a podcaster.net and he's coined podcasting.
And I'm like, I'm all for that. That sounds good. We're podcasting everybody. Of course,
you have to all agree that pods are MP3 devices. I don't think Apple can see us for pods, can they?
So podcasting, I'm digging that. Like it. Which brings me from the bit torrent brings me to the iPod
list. I also haven't had a lot of time for email. Haven't even posted anything on the web.
deep into the core audio of Mac OS X that I did skim through most of the messages on
the iPod developer list.
It's a great, great vibe that's there.
Everyone's using each other's code, commenting on how we can make it all better.
I see that we kind of want to have some set definitions as to what an iPod is so we can
all make a version with some either multiple versions with the same functionality or maybe
we come up with some common gold standard that everybody uses and tomorrow I'll be able to
focus on that and see what I can contribute.
But some great iPod versions are out there.
It's hard to even keep track of at this point.
I think I spidered on evil gene.
which I have tried now it has an install package for OSX.
It adds a cron job.
See there was some other great features that it has.
Oh, it also understands BitTorrents.
This is really cool.
So if you attach a BitTorrent of your show,
then it knows to go out, download the torrent file
and then put that in your items.
And woo, I gotta try the new version of iPod tomorrow
because that's exactly what I'm looking for.
really hookin' this all together. It's just phenomenal.
See, there was something on IT conversations that I was listening to. It wasn't the most recent Gilmore gang.
On the road I listened to about half of the show and they were talking about, it was about
IT and law and although sometimes very technical and a bit over my head, I do like listening
to those types of conversations.
And this one focused a lot on the three different music services, of course IT Music Store from
Apple, Microsoft and Reel.
And as I was listening to this, I'm like, how, here are these guys, these big companies
and they see the music businesses in trouble and it's as if they're trying to say, oh,
you know, it's up for grabs.
I'm going to go, you know, we're going to go get this market.
I don't think that's, you know, that's where the big money is, you know, look at,
look at what's happening all of a sudden with, with the, with the iPod platform.
Look, we're using this as completely not in the way they ever thought over the
way to design it.
And as long as we keep using MP3s and keep that to ourselves, then we're going to
be, we're going to be pretty good.
Although there's a lot to say for other formats and a lot of people are looking
at AC files, which is.
I guess proprietary compression which includes DRM and also some nifty features like bookmarking.
But I'm going to keep it with MP3 because I think that's the format that we have to protect and have to serve.
There was so much, you know, I've started this show so many times over the past couple of days.
So much to talk about.
Darn.
Well, I have a couple other things queued up and ready to go for you.
I was thinking about the George Carlin bit that I played, how long was that?
Must have been last week, maybe the beginning of last week, and I played the bit about stuff.
And as I was working with this new DJ 1800 program, which I'm just really happy about how it performs,
it also integrates with iTunes so you can just drag something out of your iTunes playlist right onto a player and it works.
And it'll eat anything that...
that iTunes does or the QuickTime does, I guess.
And I ran across a show from 1999, George Carlin,
I believe it was on HBO, and I had an audio file of that
for some reason, well, because I like it so much.
And he does this one bit, which now, of course,
this is pre-911.
And the bit is about airport security.
And although, you know, not if you thought that this was
done just yesterday or anytime post-911,
you might be offended by some bit.
So you have to take into consideration and keep in mind
that this is from 1999, at the time when I was traveling
a lot in America, I was on flights all the time.
And then George Carlin comes out with this great bit
about airport security and think,
and just listen to what he's saying
and listen to how insightful he was at the time
and also think about where we are today
with security in general,
and certainly when it comes to airport security.
George Carlin.
with airport security.
and it makes the world a lot easier to sort out.
First thing on my list tonight, airport security.
Tired of this shit. There's too much of it.
There's too much security at the airport.
I'm tired of some guy with a double digit IQ
and a triple digit in...
haven't found anything yet.
Haven't found one bomb in one bag.
And don't tell me, well, the terrorists know their bags are going to be searched,
so now they're leaving their bombs at home.
There are no bombs.
The whole thing is fucking pointless.
It's completely without logic.
There's no logic at all.
They'll take away a gun, but let you keep a knife.
Well, what the fuck is that?
In fact, there's a whole list of lethal objects they will allow you to take onboard.
Theoretically, you could take a knife, a nice pick, a hatchet, a straight razor,
a pair of scissors, a chainsaw, six knitting needles, and a broken whiskey bottle.
And the only thing they're going to say to you is that bag has to fit all the way under the seat in front of you.
If you didn't take a weapon on board, relax.
After you've been flying for about an hour, they're going to bring you a knife and fork.
To they give you a fucking knife
It's only a table knife, but you could kill a pilot with a table knife
Might take a couple of minutes, you know
Especially if he's hefty, huh?
Yeah, but you could get the job done. You really want to kill the prick
But there's a lot of things you could use to kill a guy with you could probably beat a guy to death with a Sunday, New York
Or, suppose you just had really big hands.
Couldn't you strangle a flight attendant?
Sure you could probably strangle two of them, one with each hand.
You know, if you were lucky enough to catch him in that little kitchen area, before they
give out the fucking peanuts, you know?
But you could get the job done, if you're really cared enough.
So why isn't they allow a man with big powerful hands to get on board an airplane?
I'll tell you why.
They know he's not a security risk because he's already answered the three big questions.
Question number one, did you pack your bags yourself?
No.
My bad
He and Martha Stewart and Florence Henderson came over to the house last night,
fixed me a lovely lobster new burger, gave me a full body massage with sacred oils from India,
performed a far way around the world, and then they packed my bags.
Next question.
You're back been in your possession the whole time. No
Usually the night before I travel just as the moon is rising
Place my suitcases out on the street corner and leave them there unattended for several hours
Just for good luck
Next question
As any unknown person asked you to take anything on board
hmm
Well, what exactly is an unknown person?
Surely everyone is known to someone
in fact just this morning Karim and you said Ali Ben Gabbá
They didn't know each other quite well
They kept joking about which one of my suitcases was the heaviest
And that's another thing they don't like at the airport jokes, you know, yeah, you can't joke about a bomb
Well, why is it just jokes what about a riddle?
How about a limerick?
How about a bomb anecdote?
You know, no punchline, just a really cute story.
Or, suppose you intended to remark, not as a joke, but as an ironic musing.
Are they prepared to make that distinction?
Why, I think not.
And besides, who's to say what's funny?
Airport security is a stupid idea that's a waste of money
and it's only there for one reason to make white people feel safe.
That's all. The illusion.
The feeling and illusion of safety.
Because the authorities know they can't make an airplane completely safe.
You'll notice the drug smugglers don't seem to have a lot of trouble getting their little packages on board, do they?
No, and God bless them too!
By the way, an airplane flight shouldn't be completely safe.
You need a little danger in your life.
Take a fucking chance once in a while, will you?
What are you gonna do? Play with your prick for another 30 years?
What are you gonna read, People Magazine and Eat It Wendy's till the end of time?
Take a fucking chance.
Besides, even if they made all the airplanes completely safe,
the terrorists would simply start bombing other places that are crowded.
Porn shops, track houses, city bars and gang bangs.
Hello.
Entertainment venues.
The odds of you being killed by a terrorist are practically zero.
So I say relax and enjoy the show.
You have to be a realist. You have to be realistic about terrorism.
Certain groups of people, certain groups,
Muslim fundamentalists, Christian fundamentalists, Jewish fundamentalists,
and just plain guys from Montana.
continue to make life in this country very interesting for a long, long time.
That's the reality.
Angry men in combat fatigues talking to God on a two-way radio and muttering incoherent
slogans about freedom are eventually going to provide us with a great deal of entertainment.
Especially after your stupid fucking economy collapses all around you and the terrorists
come out of the woodwork and you'll have anthrax in your water supply and sarin gas
in your air condition that'd be chemical and
enjoy the show take a fucking chance put a little fun in your life
to me terrorism is exciting it's exciting
I think the very idea that you can set off a bomb in a marketplace and kill
several hundred people
But we also know that most Americans are soft and frightened and unimaginative and they
don't realize there's such a thing as being...
certainly don't recognize a good show when they see one.
I've always been willing to put myself at great personal risk
for the sake of entertainment.
And I've always been willing to put you at great personal risk
for the same reason.
As far as I'm concerned, all of this airport security,
all the searches, the screenings, the cameras,
the questions, it's just one more way.
As long as you put up with it.
Which means of course, any time they want.
Because that's what Americans do now.
They're always willing to trade away a little of their freedom
in exchange for the feeling, the el-
obsessed with security and safety and crime and drugs and cleanliness.
There's another thing, germs. Where did the sudden fear of germs come from?
In the country of Harlem.
1999, about airport security, about terrorism, and about your personal freedom, fellow Americans.
Holy moly, what an insight. 1999. I wonder if he'd do the same routine again today, and if he'd change anything, what he'd be changing.
Okay, it's now 11.13. Unfortunately, I can't use Audio Hijack Pro to cut.
because once again I'm taxing the processor and it actually starts to skip little bits
of recording which blows.
So I'm recording it to AIFF which is a format that I have a nice little Apple script for
that.
M-A-A-M, which is MPEG to AIFF or AIFF to MPEG.
We actually wrote that script when we were doing our reality show because we had so many,
we put all kinds of great tunes in the show,
and of course they were all downloaded from the internet,
and we had to get them into Final Cut Pro,
which I don't think the new version eats MP3s yet.
And AIFF is just much easier for it to work with, less processor intensive
because it's file, you know, there's so much more information there,
it doesn't have to go through so much compression and decompression.
And so we, you know, we just have a script, a little droplet, you drag MP3 onto it,
turns into an AIFF with the same name and vice versa.
So I have to do the conversion and then I can upload it to the server.
So it may even be Monday the 20th by the time the show gets up on the air.
And again, I apologize for the radio silence or the podcasting silence.
I will be sure to do a little more coherent show tomorrow, also it won't be cool.
quite as tired. It's been a really long weekend and I got a lot of cleaning up to do. There's
wires everywhere. And of course now for the next four days, I'm Mr. Mom. Patricia stayed
in Amsterdam with her sister at the bunker and they're off to the UK tomorrow to go and
look at houses. And she's got the video camera with her. So, yes, Jesse, hold on,
the dog wants to go out. So depending on the footage that she brings back, maybe
you'll post some of that online. Go ahead.
I said, just gonna walk out the back here for a second.
Ah, it's a lovely night.
If you can hear that, that's our fountain over on the other side of the courtyard.
Total silence here. I'm gonna miss this
Our nice castle in
Flanders in Belgium I
can see
Fred and ginger are two black swans with their six babies which aren't even babies anymore
They're walking on the grass back here. They're gonna start flying pretty soon
They're gonna try to start flying which is always hilarious
Because they you know sometimes it's it's like the keystone cops. You know and they they even fly into each other
You done Jess come on
This is Jesse one of our three dogs. Good
So tomorrow morning to some more techno talk because of course
The credo of source code is that we try to make the place where users and developers party together
And there's a lot more to talk about these are the iPod or the iPod platform podcasting and all that other groovy stuff
And I've got to go put my daughter to bed right now
So again, mr. Ball be real busy. You know we have goats and chickens and
horses and really start to appreciate what someone else does in the household.
So I'm going to leave you with that for today and I will be back.
We're the new source code for Monday, September.
As always, if you want to respond to-
code on the website.
The power of the door is lost.
If you're subscribing to this or you want to subscribe, the URL for the RSS 2.0.
And if you're new to the old iPodder concept, check out iPodder.org.
See you tomorrow on the source code!