Welcome to your source code for Friday, October 22nd, 2004, brought to you on Saturday, October
Good morning. It's really early here in Belgium. I'm reclined in the big green thing, which is the
chair that I've slept with me for most of my life, a huge leather recliner, a green leather recliner.
Everyone's still asleep. I was up really early this morning around six o'clock for a number of reasons,
which I'll be happy to tell you. Obviously, didn't get to have sex last night. Otherwise,
probably would have slept a little bit longer. That was my excuse for not bringing you a source code,
so I figured, didn't get any, might as give you some, right?
So we're going to make a kind of a mellow source code for this morning. The reason I was, well, first
all I went to bed last night, we all went to bed around 11 o'clock, and I had a splitting headache,
which is probably cold and dozed. You can hear a little bit of nasal sound this morning on the
old Kermister. Patricia has also been kind. I was just a flu bug. It's been going around. She even
got a flu shot, but she still has a little bit of a sore throat and Christina Porkid. She stayed home
the first two days. In Tuesday, she stayed home from school, and she went back and she was standing
next to her bed around 615 and she got already breezed. She was so stuffed up and had a headache and
a throat ache and sucks when kids are sick. So of course, you know, when that happens, I wake up.
Actually, I didn't know what day it was. I woke up like, oh, that was probably time to get Christina
to school, you know, 630s when we usually get up, 637 to clock. And I was downstairs. I was
ready to turn on a morning radio show, you know, listen to some guys I know, like, oh, wait a minute,
Saturday morning. And it's raining. It's, uh, it's not, well, I'm sorry. That isn't rain. That's
liquid sunshine. And it's not a very nice day here in in Flander's Belgium, but I figured we
just do a nice cool relax Saturday source code. Hopefully you're listening to this in the morning
yourself. Um, and let's see last night, um, well, I had a whole bunch. I got to tell you, I have to
stop setting meetings on Friday because at the end of the week, I'm already tired. And if I get home
late and I'm stuck in traffic, it's so hard to, you know, to get up the energy to record a show.
Even though I usually have everything all prepped and ready to go, it's like, pool. And then
last night at 9 o'clock, which was 12 noon West Coast, three PM East Coast time. I was a guest
with Dave Winner, Michael Budraying, Craying. On the Gilmore gang, which I've been waiting for,
for that to happen for a long time. Really, ever since I heard the Gilmore gang, like, yeah, I
wanted to be on that show. So Steve Gilmore invited Dave and I on the show. And so that was an
hour long taping. It's, it's life to, to tape or live to disk, actually. Uh, so it had to be done
between 9 and 10. A couple of quick observations about that. So of course, it was about podcasting.
The show was already up. So please go check it out. If you haven't already gotten through your iPod
or subscription. Um, uh, a special guest is what on the show. And Steve was really excited about it.
As were the other members of the gang, was the fire sign theater, or three guys from the fire
sign theater. And I have to be honest, uh, so you call into this, this telephone system right
and you hear like beep beep and you already hear people talking. And, uh, and, and Steve was really
excited that he had had the fire sign theater on. And to be quite honest, I'd heard a fire sign
theater, but of course, I'd never heard it. This is from the 60s. These guys were, you know,
apparently they really revolutionized radio and, and are pretty much the fundamental building
block on which even podcasting is, uh, is based today. Uh, so while we were getting ready, I was
like surfing the web and Googling and trying to find out as much as I could. Um, uh, and what was great
is, and you have to listen to show. These guys got it within like 33 minutes. They understood
podcasting. They went from zero to podcasting in, uh, in half an hour. And that was just phenomenal.
It's a good show to listen to. Something that was very interesting though is that before, um, we actually
started the show and people, you know, we're just kind of like talking on the conference call.
Everybody was ranking on, you know, all the elections in two weeks and fuck, we got to get
rid of Bush and I'm, you know, the country's going to be hosed if he gets reelected. And no one spoke
with the same passion during the actual taping, even though the elections did come up. So I just
wanted to want to say that. That was always, it always amazes me how the minute the microphone
turns on, then all of a sudden it's like everyone takes a stupid pill and we're not
real anymore. So trying to keep the pod cast really y'all. So yesterday the reason why I got home,
oh wait a minute, first of all, wait a minute, I'm making a big mistake here. It's early in the
morning. We have to do the brush your teeth song. You brush your teeth. Come on, you can sing
a lot. You brush your teeth. When you wake up in the morning, it's a quarter to two and you want to
find something to do. You brush your teeth. I do a podcast, a real podcast. You brush your teeth.
When you wake up in the morning, it's a quarter to three and you mine starts humming
through the lead. You brush your teeth. You brush your teeth.
All right, thank this up, guys. When you wake up in the morning, it's a quarter to four and you think
you hear, run, knock on your door. You brush your teeth. You brush your teeth.
When you wake up in the morning, it's a quarter to five and you just can't wait to come all
out of your brush your teeth. You brush your teeth. You brush your teeth. You brush your teeth.
Good morning. Now we're all awake. Yesterday, I had to open the eye trends, lifestyle and
technology fair in the Utrecht, which is about the central part of the Netherlands. Not just
for any old reason. I'm waiting to go around opening up fairs, but grandmaster view. Our
flat screen company was displaying our wares there, so that's always a great way to get extra
publicity and attention. Grandmasterview.com, by the way, and also available in the states now at
florida.grandmasterview.com. And so I was hanging around for a little while, and it will
a little while. It takes a couple hours before you get home. That's why I was late. But I got an email
about my appearance there, and this is from Yutun for Croast. I'm just going to read this to you
because there's an excellent email that I saw when I got up this morning. Hey, dude, that was
pretty weird. I was listening to your daily source code on my iPod. When I turned into the parking lot
at the Yarnburgs, next thing, you know, I see you live, grabbing a very red drink from a walking
human video billboard waiter at iTrends. That's right. They had waiters with flat screens on their
head and shit. Since you were sitting down at a little table in the company of some serious
looking people in suits, I figured that it might not be the best moment for me to yank out my
iPod and slap you on the back and yell, didn't source code rules, dude. You'd probably say,
hey, what do you want from me? Visualizing that did make a click on my head. He says, I decided
to send you a song in appreciation instead. So first of all, the guys in the suits were like
company sales guys, and one of them was my partner and grandma's review. And we were actually
just talking about a podcasting and iPod, or because I know where we were sitting when you
probably saw me. So please, anytime, you know, feel free. If you're driving in the highway,
I want to roll down the window and honk at me, or if you're anywhere. And just the thing that you
were seeing that listening to the source code while I was there, you really should have
a relationship come out to me that would be an cool. So he decided to send me a song instead.
Oh, I was sick. I just want to make sure I've got everything all cute up here.
I was listening to your take on indie music just then. I wanted to send you a song that was
that was recorded by my band. It's 100% RIA proof and royalty free. I do grant you and anyone else
that wants the podcast that writes to do so, download it, share it, any other way necessary,
all writes and clearance taken care of. However, it's 5.5 meg, so I didn't want to
nail it to you. That's appreciated. It says, why this one? Well, check out the lyrics. You
probably see why click in his head. I hope you'd like it if not just to take this at token
to my appreciation if you don't want to play it for it. Play it on the show. Actually, you're doing
I really liked it. And I'm going to play it right now. This is, I guess your band's name is Paragon.
That's what I'm getting from the, from the MP3 file, from the ID3 tags. It's titled,
dig in your fame. This is coming to you from Holland. I'm the source code. Very cool.
Do you want for me? Hey, you're a kind of way to be grateful. What do you want for me?
No, the little time you came by, realized that my body's too cold.
I'm too lazy. I never thought I'd know them to say, no, no,
baby. Keep on digging you out.
So you think you have decided what do you want for me?
Hey, you know, you can't hide it. What do you want for me?
Hey, no, the little time you came by, realized that my body's too cold.
I'm just on your back side. Never thought I'd know them to say,
shout out, baby. Keep on digging you out.
You'll find you. Yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I, alley right across the goal. Right on your right-line, right on to the goal to the goal, okay?
Baby, keep on big in your eyes
Fine, I'm digging in your mind
What?
Whoa baby
Have a nose, what I've been keeping now
I'm digging in your mind
Whoa baby
Have a nose, what I've been keeping now
Babe
Yeah
Haragad, digging in your fame on the source code for Saturday, October 23rd 2004
And you can download that from
Erunds sites, it's for crost.com
That's verk-r-o-o-o-s-t
You can download that from Erunds.com
Paragon, dig in your fame
Excellent song
Really like that very much
Thank you for sending that beautiful, little present
Let's see
I wanted to mention that I played mojoins
Thursday on the source code
And whoops, little mistake there
I said you could find there their website at mojoins.com
That turns out to be Mother Jones
certainly be playing more by Mod Jones in weeks to come because the whole album is just so good.
They have a couple albums out, I only have one, and this guy's really just rocked.
More indie music on the way, of course, in today's source code.
Also, I've got something, let's see, am I on schedule here, am I doing this right?
Yeah, because I have a whole list of stuff.
Actually, I think we're probably gonna run a little bit longer.
If you're taking a walk-dave liner, take the long way.
It's gonna be an hour today.
I heard Dave's morning coffee notes, and I was talking about making the show 40 minutes
long.
And just as he was walking in his door, I said, well, it's 40 minutes time to end the show,
and that really tripped him out.
Tony Khan, talked about him before Tony is a radio legend and public radio and MPR,
and I've been keeping very close tabs with him.
He's working very hard on getting all kinds of MPR people interested in podcasting,
which is really what I want to see, because there are a lot of MPR shows that I love.
I can't receive here at all.
The time, if you think it's tough to listen to an MPR show when it's a broadcast in the
States, try and add six or nine hours to that, you know, and try and coordinate your life
around that.
It's very difficult.
But Tony, of course, has his podcast morning stories from WGBH in Boston.
And there was a great one that came in into my iPod the other day, and I want to play
the whole thing for you.
These are stories that are actually, these are podcasts by themselves.
Tony does, as he helps people with their stories, if it's their own story or gives
them a story.
But it's normal people off the street, basically, who then record these stories and tell
them in their own voice, and he does some great production around it.
And this next one was so funny, and you can imagine, anyone can imagine this scenario happening.
It's called In the Buff, and it's a great one.
I'm going to turn it over now to Tony Khan.
This is Tony Khan, I'm the producer, the director of Morning Stories on WGBH in Boston.
And today's morning story comes from a very funny lady named Erica Forensic who talks
about a very unfunny situation, maybe, being on the rebound in the buff.
I'm not sure what I was doing when I agreed to go to a nude beach with my new bow.
For one thing, I'm shy stepping into a shower naked, much less on to pearly sands and
in front of crowds.
For another, Dan was my yoga teacher, besides I just got divorced.
Dan couldn't wait to whip his clothes off and sprint into the sea with a giant waping.
What's this guy?
I thought wrapped up tight in my one piece under my summer wrap, under my wide brim straw
hat, under the beach umbrella, under the nude-seeking sun.
After a few body surfs, Dan galloped back to the blanket and shook his head like a dog.
He flopped down on his back, the bronze gifed to the heavens.
I sighed, entire naked families, phallicked in the sand, a couple in their 80s centered
by wearing only matching straw hats, led over the dunes by a naked docksand.
There was even a naked dauzer, dauzing for naked treasures, and just so the left of us
are rather a game of naked volleyball.
Okay, I thought let's just do this.
I got to my feet, took one strap down, then the other.
Step out of my suit and body slammed, face down on the blanket.
Dan laughed and said, now that wasn't so bad, was it?
An older couple crested a dune, then made their way toward our blanket.
There was something about the woman, a sort of side-to-side gate.
Dan, I guess.
I know these people.
So why don't you say hello to them?
Because I'm naked, okay?
Because they're naked.
Because they're my ex-in-laws.
10 feet.
5.
Erica?
Vivian Arthur!
I wanted to die.
Hi!
I wave stiffly from my face down on the blanket position.
They turn to Dan, who will be handed a vigorous sun-cell mutation, jump to his feet,
and shook their hands.
And this is your new yoga teacher, I choked.
Wonderful.
We were looking for a few more bodies for the volleyball game.
Erica?
Are you?
No.
I'm pretty wiped.
I'm scared or relaxed.
But Dan was already on his feet, brushing the sand off him.
Self.
I waited a moment, then slowly reached back from my suit and pulled it on.
I wondered why I had said yes to this in the first place.
I didn't even like the beach.
And when I thought about it, yoga kind of bored me too.
Only cobra, so to Dan.
I mean, please, bumping and spiking in the buff.
How do you keep your eye on the ball?
Morning stories.
Come see you from WGBH, FM, Radio Boston, and we podcast you with a new morning story.
Every Friday.
Great morning story.
Only imagine that really taking place.
And of course, these stories are all true.
Excuse me.
Patricia just walked in a couple minutes ago during that morning story report.
And she said the Christine is really feeling bad.
And it pisses me off, man.
You can't get any good drugs here.
Like Nyquill.
You know, all that wonderful, sneaky, coffee, achy.
So you can rest medicine.
It's not available in Europe.
So I'm glad I'm going to blogger Khan.
Pick up a whole suitcase full of good over-the-counter drugs from the States.
A new podcast I wanted to turn you on today was, well, it's very appropriate.
It's about baseball.
October 21 in baseball history.
Today in baseball history is brought to you by sports history.
Bringing you the most interesting informative and intriguing facts.
Yeah, the world.
A little bit of commercial.
Love that sport.
In 1845, New York beat Brooklyn 244.
Okay.
I'm not going to bore you with all the baseball history, but that's a great podcast.
So, of course, I had this prepped from two days ago.
It's today in baseball history from the 21st.
And it looks like baseball history may be rewritten again.
Who knows what the red socks are going to, how about those red socks, huh?
And last night when I came home, and I actually put this up on my podcast feed,
because I thought it was so funny.
And I got some mail about this.
People thinking that, you know, hey, man, you can't play this on the air,
because this girl's really in love with you.
You're like, you're like messing up her head.
What am I talking about?
Well, of course, Dawn from Dawn and Drew.
Dear Adam Curry, this is Dawn from the Dawn and Drew Show.
And I wanted to talk to you about something,
but I don't know how to bring it up, so I'm just going to blur it out.
Okay, here we go.
I noticed that you didn't do anything for me for sweet this day.
And I thought we had something.
I thought we had something special.
And it hurt really bad.
But then I started thinking, Adam Curry wouldn't do that to you, Dawn.
Adam Curry's cool, right?
He wouldn't break your heart.
And so I came to the realization that you were just waiting
until we were together at Blocker Carme.
And I know you're going to take me out to dinner,
and we're going to have a fantastic time,
and maybe we'll even ride Mopeds.
We're going to ride Mopeds, Dawn.
I can't wait.
I'm sure it's going to be great.
What are you doing over there with my computer?
What, Drew?
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Are you sending a note to Adam Curry?
No.
Yes, yes I am.
I knew it.
You can't keep us up the heart.
We're so busted.
No, Adam.
Goodbye.
You guys are too much.
That's great.
I can't wait to meet you guys in person at Blocker Carme.
We're going to have a really good time.
Okay.
Some cool technology stuff, because, of course, on the source code,
we try and have users and developers party together.
Different ways of podcasting, different machines to do it on,
always interested in what people are putting together.
I don't know if you know what a trio is,
but it's a cell phone.
Apparently, you can record a podcast on that just perfectly.
Good morning.
This is Russell Hollandman.
Thank you for tuning in to my trio podcast.
For those of y'all who haven't heard,
this is like day three of an experiment of mine.
I'm trying to see if I can produce a decent podcast
using as much of my trio 600 cell phone as possible.
As of today, the entire process is being handled on the cell phone,
including the fading in and fading out of music, as I talk,
with the exception of the MP3 encoding.
I still haven't figured out how to do that on my cell phone yet.
But everything else is done.
Once the broadcast is complete, the way file is sent from my phone
to a server.
Upon receiving that, the server initiates a script,
which then encodes the file just this morning.
I figured out how to add ID tags to that file.
I then generate an RSS file on my trio,
and I upload that directly to the server,
and so far that's where we are.
Yesterday's broadcast, podcast, I guess I should say.
So how cool is that if you think about it,
that you can do all this from a handheld device.
Yeah, you've got a script running on the server
to actually get the podcasting stuff in place,
but that should be a service quite frankly.
Now what I'm interested to do is, can we do the reverse?
Can we make the handhelds?
Can we actually make them do all the iPod or functionality
without the computer?
If we have a handheld wireless device that works with Wi-Fi,
well I know the pocket PC already has an iPod or for it.
How far can we take this?
How much hacking can we do on our MP3 devices
to actually uncouple the computer part that's sitting in the middle?
I'm getting pretty excited about what a lot of people are doing.
Another MPR show that I want, or another public radio show
that I want to play just a little bit for you,
is future tense.
John Gordon produces and hosts that.
And I came across an interesting little gadget
talking about on future tense, which is something that,
well, something that could be quite handy if you find TVs
and monitors in your life and living space annoying.
This is future tense from American public media.
I'm John Gordon.
A fast-selling new keychain gadget lets people turn off
most any TV.
It's inventor sees TV begun as a sort of gorilla solution
to the problem of attention demanding TVs in bars, restaurants,
airports and other public places.
The tiny remote control works by sending a burst of infrared
off-coads until it hits on the right one.
It's basically a universal remote with just one function.
TV begun sells for $15 and is available only at the TV
begun website.
The website has been down intermittently after being swamped by traffic.
Inventor, Mitch Altman.
There's so many times when I'm in a restaurant or at my laundromat
and a TV is on and no one's really watching it.
And I certainly don't want it on.
I always thought it would be great if I could turn it off.
When I first thought of the idea of sitting at a table at a restaurant
with some friends and we were there to hang out with each other
and yet a television was on in the corner.
And the town wasn't even on just the flashing images
kept drawing our attention away from each other.
And none of us wanted that.
We wanted to be with each other but we couldn't really help ourselves.
It's just so compelling that way.
And we were thinking wouldn't it be great if we could just turn that off?
You need a remote because a lot of the television's can't turn off
or unreachable or something like up in a bar or something like that.
Yeah, they're usually out of reach and the remote control is who knows where.
And the thing with TV begun, it's just a remote control
so you can turn TV back on again.
It doesn't hurt anything.
And one of the things that I like about it is it can bring on dialogue
about whether a TV should be on or not,
whether people actually want it or not.
And one podcast in all's life.
Adam Curry.
And to me Kasky from slash.review.com.
One of the thank you for the opportunity to place a brief announcement
to hear on Open Podcast to let people know about slash.review.
Basically it's ten minutes summary of highlights from recent contributions
to slash.
Each day I try and round out the program featuring a song from a creative
Commons license artist to highlight a track that I find interesting
hope that other people do as well.
I'm also looking for external comments and participation on the audio program.
I've got phone in line.
732 357 3682.
And also can take network based zip calls from the
Assip phone network 74766733006.
Once again, I appreciate your contribution here.
And I hope that you have a chance to take a look at slash.review.com.
So that's from Open Podcast.org.
You should subscribe to that because it's got all kinds of great
promos and commercials for people's podcasts coming through.
Multiple files per day.
Quick check of the email.
Let me see how to another.
You can hear the email rustling in my paper, right?
From Jock Gill.
He says, hey, I'm coming to you from northeast kingdom of Vermont.
Enjoying your podcast.
Everything they imply.
Here's a safe prediction.
He says, by 2006, every modern politician will have a campaign.
Podcast.
He says, a bit of history snuck by you.
October 20th was the 10th anniversary of the launch of the White House website.
I was one of the project leaders on this, which is why I make the
prediction above with confidence.
He says, really appreciate your support of John Kerry.
I've been urging Dick Bell his webmaster to start a carry podcast.
Maybe if you mentioned it dot dot dot dot.
Well, you know, now I think about it.
What a great opportunity for John Kerry.
I mean, why wait for your, you know, your equal airtime or your radio address or
you know, whatever you want to do and isn't this just great for all the candidates or
any, well, for John Kerry screw the candidates.
We only two weeks away.
For John Kerry, who has no time, as he says, and is busy schedule to, you know,
to actually blog anything.
Well, this is perfect, you know, give us your stump speech for all I care.
Just say something one minute every single day and have somebody throw it up on a podcast.
And imagine, you know, the thought of the day from the president or the inspirational
message of the day, I would rock Michelle and her group walked along Capitol Hill.
I found a lot of people actually in the end of rush just walking first glance.
It just looked like a pile of leaves and maybe some garbage.
But there are people sleeping there.
Though she counted were curious at times.
Some even grateful.
A couple of people were like, wow, well, I'm homeless.
You can count me.
After the volunteers covered their areas, they returned to Operation Nightwatch on
and handed in their numbers and their reactions.
They were normally walking on the street.
Makes you appreciate a warm bed.
Yeah, it's an eye opening.
The numbers have been tallyed and Rick Reynolds says there's 12% more people living on the streets in King County this year.
Another trend?
The Seattle core count area is somewhat down while the outlying neighborhoods and suburban areas are up somewhat.
When you add in the number of people in shelters, you get a homeless population of around 8,000.
Soaring news for Doug, a counter this year, with a very personal connection to last year's effort.
Yeah, it was one of the people that was out on the streets.
He remembers being approached.
It felt good because he knew somebody out there cared.
Greg was also homeless.
He's concerned not everyone was counted this year because many homeless people don't want to be found.
As a homeless person, if you draw attention, it's only on one eight attention.
But he's glad to have helped and knows that the numbers will help collect more money to help more people.
I was sleeping on underpass.
Now I'm willing to help somebody else because that's what it's all about.
Brian Calford, coma, 1000 news.
Now the reason why I played this bit from coma 1000 news, which of course comes through in their podcast.
And you can find all this stuff at ipodder.org, of course, is I was amazed, you know, Seattle.
I don't know how many people live in Seattle, but I bet there's not as many people that live in Seattle's live in all of the Netherlands.
17 million people live in the Netherlands.
I think the total count for homeless people in all of the lowlands is no more than 800.
Because it just doesn't exist in the Netherlands.
Of course, it's all, it's because of the way the social benefits are set up.
And there's a lot of pro and cons to be said about that.
But listen to these people, I'm like, you know, this is not the, this is not what I would expect to hear from someone who's homeless.
You know, there's a lot of stories behind this.
And it's quite frankly when I see what's going on with the government and what Bush is doing in Iraq and the whole, just the fact that they were there.
And it breaks my heart to hear that what's going on at home, you know, 8,000 people homeless in Seattle alone.
This is, this is major, man.
We've got a lot of shit we've got to take care of here back at home.
It's mainly music for you now that I found on, I think, was GarageBand.com.
Stars, the big fight.
The living.
Yes, I am a ghost.
The mirror is cloudy.
I love you the more.
You threw out the pieces.
These did things we did and I'm just dead.
We've got a lot of shit.
I don't let me know, I love the door, but you can't walk away from me
It doesn't wanna go, it just won't let you go
It's time to make a much stronger way to show
It just doesn't make a much stronger way to show
It doesn't wanna go, it just won't let you go
I might just be somebody that you can relate to
Or at least somebody that you find interesting
And if you do, God help you
Because I don't find myself the slightest bit interesting
Give yourself a little more credit there, Jimmy
He has a cool podcast, check out JimmyJet.com
Or find his podcast feed in the iPod or directory
Also got a couple audio comments that I want to share with you
This is from Phil who you probably know from
Engaget.com and the infamous Engaget.com podcast
And he's moving this stuff along
He's already known to the next step
Hey Adam, it's Phil Throne from the Engaget.com podcast
Wanted to say thank you for getting this out in a big way
You've been doing some monumental work and I really appreciate
By the way, it's clear that if you want your comment
Played on the source code, that's the way to start
off isn't it?
We have all this technology and all this ways to connect up
We may as well use it for the greater good
I did want to say two things that are probably of some interest
To the folks out there.
First, about last year
I started an experiment with video feeds
And using RSS 2.0 closures to get video around
The bad news was there wasn't any portable video players
At least there wasn't any ones that are released
But now there is.
So there are some of these video players
Running around like the creative zen that you can get video on
And I had written an article about getting podcasts on these
But you can also get video on them
So why don't we take a leadership role
And start talking about that
And I think podcasting personal
Option digital broadcasting should encompass everything
So maybe we can start out in feeds that have video
So one, I'm curious if anyone has any video feeds out there
And two, if they don't, how we can start doing this
I can probably start throwing together some videos that I have
Around and maybe we can start trying it out
Because you know, ultimately iPods will have video
We all know eventually everything is going to have video
So why don't we start doing this now
At least having the ability and the people who are building the software
They can at least start thinking about this now
Well I tell you if you look at the iPod or developer
There are already people thinking of this of course
You should also check out Steve Garfield's website
He's he's been doing video
Video blogging and attaching
I think he's been attaching
Quick time movies to his RSS feed
I'm not quite sure
So a couple of comments on that first thought
Yeah, I mean it would be beautiful
To get to that point
There are a couple of things that aren't quite in place
The way they are with podcasting
One is we don't have a set format that everyone has
And everyone agrees on
Whereas we have MP3 for audio
Do we want to use quick time to want to use
Empag doing use divics
Do we want to use AVI
You know there's all these different choices
And I'm not sure that the handheld videos it players out there
Support you know that any of them support all of
You know all of these protocols all these different formats
And also
I was talking to Paul Bootan
Is that his hyper Bootan
Yeah, he's a he's a reporter
And he's a I think he's working on a piece for slate right now
And he says you know you too is supposed to be a part of this big
Apple new color iPod release
It's just you know why is you too interested in that the only thing I come up with is
Well, you know if you got a color iPod
Well shoot you might as well
You know let it play quick time videos
And that would kind of make sense to have a color screen to do that with
So we may find that some of the stuff is going to fall into our lap again
I don't think there's enough devices out there
And really the biggest problem which is which I'm already running into
Hard disk space problems and and bandwidth issues although they're not problems
With with these MP3 files now any video file is going to be at least ten if not
A hundred times bigger in file size than what we're dealing with now
And although it's technically perfectly capable
I think that you know just imagine all the shit we're going to run into
I mean you know right now
If you are new to iPod and you download it you know you probably get
The the most recent the three most recent shows from each feed that you subscribe to
And eventually you'll receive everything that's in the feed because it you know the iPod
It goes around and starts picking up older feeds as it
With each with each cycle that it runs through
So imagine all of some instead of having a hundred megabytes that you downloaded a gigabyte
Or two gigabyte so I think we just need a little more
Disstorage particularly and still some more bandwidth before we can really go full on digital
But I do support you know I support
Trying this out and seeing what the limits are now of course
And it's completely possible the entire infrastructure is exactly the same
It's all in place
In fact, I put up my was it the daily source code commercial video that caught you
I made for me
And a lot of people receive that since I put it into the iPod
Feed people received it on their iPod
And you know it's kind of funky the way that iTunes handles that
Because you get like the cover art is the is the is the poster frame from the
Quick time movie and you can hear the audio but you can see the video of course
So I think it's all going to kind of flow and fall into place
But still I'm a little concerned about all of the storage and the bandwidth issues
And oh wow what are we 44 minutes Dave you're back from your walk time time for a comment from digital bill
Hey Adam it's digital bill from the Wizards of Technology podcast
Of course like everybody else
So I want to go ahead and tell you what a great job job you guys are doing
And putting this all together and the speed that it's evolving
And I'm just so excited to be involved in it
And even just the tiniest little way of putting our weekly wizard to repod cast out there
Here's an interesting thing that has been coming across my desk that I've been thinking about the last few days
Since I started subscribing to podcasts which arguably I might be coming late to the party
And I've only got maybe half a dozen subscriptions
I'm looking here in my I made a meta playlist and iTunes which is very cool
You know how I potter and I potter X create individual playlists for each subscription
So I created an automatic playlist that combines all those playlists together
It's just called podcast and each option that you add to the automatic playlist is another playlist
So basically I've got all my podcasts aggregated into one monster list if I want to look at it that way
So it's kind of interesting that you know in about a week or so I've got
107 different audio files here. I'm sure you've got lots more
It says 2 days 17 hours 17 minutes and 9 seconds about 1.94 gigabytes of audio
I'm getting inundated here in content
I mean I can't listen to all this. I'm looking at my playlist and there's Will Wheaton Part 1
There's Steve Wozniak that I want to listen to. There's the Dave winers stuff
You know all the IT conversations
You know I used to audio hijack Leo show off KFI every week and listen to that
And I don't have time. I mean barely I can listen to daily source code
And I'm a week behind but I mean I can just about keep up with that
And I'm not making a headway on Dave's slasher. I'm not listening to
You know any of the other good stuff done and drew you know anything that you're
Stumping on so
They're just aren't enough hours in the day because if I try to listen to it at work
Obviously I'm coding I'm doing stuff like that during the day
I can't think about listening to that
You know what I listen to during the day just occupies my ears
So I don't have to think about listening so I don't want to miss what I'm listening to
And you know when I come home I've got my Tvo full of programs that it's recorded for the day
And you know and yet I potter X is bringing me yet more wonderful content
How do you cope with the inundation of content without walking around with your iPod plugged into your head all day
Anyway, that's my my fuck for the day and I appreciate you listening
And I appreciate what you guys are doing
And it's just like I said it's just also exciting
So keep up the great work and I'll keep listening
Thanks man appreciate it. Hey Bill no problem. Thank you for sitting in the comment
Well, I think everyone is having this problem now and and it's what a problem to have
You know Bruce Springsteen makes a song called 57 channels nothing on and here
We are we're like there's too much. I don't know what I'm going to listen to it all
I mean that's a lugs look at the quality of your problem
But it is a real problem. I have it too. You know, I'm sitting here
I've actually unsubscribe from a number of feeds
Because either the shows were just way too long or I ultimately found myself making decisions on you know what to listen to
And those would fall by the way side now again audio dot weblogs dot com is still a great place
To go and and you know find when there's new podcast out
So and you could just click on the on the MP3 link there and you can listen to it in real time
And what a lot of people are doing is they're saying okay, and also if you mouse over the the actual podcast names
Up pops a little balloon that shows you all the information about that was posted along with the files
You can see what's in that particular show
I think we probably shouldn't get too hung up on making daily shows. That's part of it
So you don't and Drew I think they're doing it pretty well
They they have their shows down now to a hole on let me just check my my iTunes
I can tell you how long was their their most recent show was 20 see that was that was that's an old one
Let me see
Drew so the one from the 18th yeah, I mean they're they're getting down to about 18
Some times 14 sometimes 20 minutes
So shorter shows is is definitely going to be something that we're all going to have to start thinking about
And here I am right on us
They were the really long show running almost an hour
Also I think that we'll see
Excuse me we'll see more shows
That are aggregates and telling you about other podcasts that's what I'm trying to do
I'm trying to point you to stuff and we'll see more short form features
But also you know if you're doing a podcast don't get hung up on on doing it every single day
You know this is unlike traditional radio as long as people are subscribed to your show
It's going to pop up and they're going to be just as happy when they get it now. I know that a lot of people saying oh, you know
Oh, I all sudden the source code wasn't there and I'm freaked out and what am I going to do? I can't take my walk
I don't know what to do with myself
This will all flesh out and it's it's I think that this is just Darwinistic
It's it we're all going to figure out the way to do these things
And it's probably just that we have to get stuff you know shorter
I too find myself in the in a backlog on IT conversation stuff
I yeah, luckily I listened to the wheel wheat and stuff live. I caught most of that live and didn't really
See a need to go and listen to the you know the parts that I missed
But Steve wasniac you know you just got to you got to find your space and hey
Maybe we should start finding time for ourselves
Maybe that's a really good thing, you know, maybe you should plan to tune yourself out for half an hour a day or an hour a day
Well, you know what next time you're sitting in front of that fucking television set
Maybe you could be doing something different maybe you could be listening to a podcast which probably could give you just as much
Entertainment value and maybe even as much news value or possibly even more
Final thing that I want to say on today's podcast because I'm still receiving so many beautiful emails and audio comments from people about my mom
So appreciated so many personal stories that you've been sharing and I've been you know and talking to a lot of people and so much good advice and
It's just the really is quite a lot of love in the in the pod universe
Mom had her PT scan and besides the fact that her ATM cards wouldn't work when she was holding on to them because she's still radio active
Apparently she's clean. There's no other
No other spread and it looks like she will be able to be operated on and I gotta tell you we're all pretty jazzed about that
It's still of course still a very heavy road that has to be traveled
But the news so far is good and again, thank you all very much for your thoughts and prayers
And that'll wind it up for your Saturday source code
Thanks again to everybody who contributed in the show for the RIAA free music
Please if you've got a band if you've got a song if you're doing stuff
Let me know about it send me a link to it because I'm more than happy to play it
If I dig it of course, and I'd be happy to share with the source code listeners
As always, you can leave your comments at my weblog like I'll create a calm or through email
Adamaccurry.com and you can always find the latest source code of the archives at datingsourcecode.com
And the podcast feed datingsourcecode.com slash rss.xml
Dave and I are probably doing a trade secrets Sunday should be going to look out for that
Because it's a lot of cool stuff. We talk about what's coming up at bloggercon
And you have yourself a great weekend. Take care. I'll see you Monday on the source code
I'll see you tomorrow. I'll see you tomorrow.