Once again, it's the Source Code. Good evening from Belgium, from Curry Castle, or good afternoon,
or good morning wherever you're happy to be checking in from. Thank you very much for
tuning in for downloading the Daily Source Code, always available. The archives are
DailySourceCode.com and of course you can subscribe through your RSS 2.0
enclosure compatible news reader. Man, that's a mouthful. It's DailySourceCode.com
slash RSS.XML. So the source code for today, a lot of today was spent driving.
Patricia and I came back from Amsterdam, her mouth operated on, which is a never-ending story.
Not everyone has a stand at the front of the perfect teeth line.
Man, we've really done a lot of work on her mouth.
Anyway, so that was a little less fun for her, but I had a reason to be relaxed day, just
chilling out, visited a couple people while I was in the city.
And I wanted to focus on a couple of things on SourceCo today.
First of all, man, talk about users and developers partying, in this case not partying, maybe
crying together.
Murphy really hit hard on the Genesis space capsule that crash landed in the Utah
Desert.
I was just thinking that.
It's so typical.
You know, here they were, they had worked this thing out with, I guess it was Hollywood
stunt helicopter pilots who were going to string a net between two helicopters to catch the
capsule as it floated down on its parachute and then to bring it down to an ultimate
soft landing.
And of course, everyone was really concentrated on the helicopter pilots and, you know, were
they going to be able to catch this disc falling out of space and how fast would it be going?
And that also has potential.
dangers you know if you have just imagine two helicopters with a net strung between it if
something hits it too hard it's going to pull those helicopters together and of course then there's
all kinds of stuff you don't copter pilot like sheets and wires known as a parachute but then
of course I was concentrating on that and no one really probably thought you know hey maybe the
parachute would deploy you know that's technology that we've had for for 70 years and no one figured
that would fail so it's really sad that that happened and I guess they can't get any samples
or everything's useless because of the contamination and the disc really hit hard I don't know if you've
seen a picture I'll be sure to link to one on my blog but man that was rough for them.
Let's talk briefly about iPodder I think yesterday I mentioned that there was a
cocoa version on the way as well as I guess yet another windows version and there was just
Peter just updated the windows version.
today very cool now it supports apples aac files it automatically detects whether
you're running Windows Media Player or iTunes and basically does everything else
for you so that's perfect all we need to do now and now put my user hat on is we
need to create really one-click installers this is something that is
often you know just added the very last moment of the process I've noticed
even on my own iPod or script you still have to download the XML to tools or
yeah that's what I call XML to tools and you have to install that into your
into your library folders so that's that's a real pain and really that also
happened by itself so I'm hoping now that everyone who's made a version of
iPod and I'll make concerted effort myself this weekend to create an
installer so basically you just double click on something and it installs
everything now here's the final the final piece that no one has really done
And I think I know how I can get it to work on the Mac,
is we have to have a cron job running.
We have to have a timed operation of iPod,
or preferably at night.
Or see, I have mine set up at four times a day, which
actually is too much, probably, because at a certain point,
during the afternoon, then the script will kick in
through a timed cron job.
And it does really sometimes noticeably slow down
the performance.
Well, certainly the performance of my internet connection,
depending on how big the files are that I'm sucking in.
So somehow I need to make that automatic as well.
And of course, we have to have an uninstall set up,
or if someone wants to change the times when it runs,
that would be perfect.
So that's the final thing we need.
And then I believe that we have the receiving side all set.
And then I'm going to start talking about how we move this
a little bit further.
I'm not quite sure what we need to do first.
Do we need to work on the publishing side, which
could be a much bigger project than the iPod?
receiving side or do we want to perhaps look at the distribution side which may even be
smarter because my feeling is that we might want to look at instead of uploading mp3 files
to servers at integrating BitTorrent into this. I've noticed that BitTorrent works really
well when something's fresh and everybody wants to have it because everyone's out
there clicking the download link of course it's always going to be one link
right there's always gonna be your your your first node which presumably will be
your own computer and then the minute other people hit lock on then you have
more peers to connect to and thus more people can download it and that really
works that was it they call file swarming technology it I think it
really works well with the with stuff that's fresh and new so it would
probably be perfect for programs like this so then of course we'd run up and
do a couple other things you know so
well you can imagine
and all the things we're going to run into.
But I do believe that BitTorrent has a spot in this iPod platform.
And of course, if we can successfully implement the iPod system of bringing in files,
bringing in enclosed files, and then instead of bringing them in from a web server somewhere,
actually have it work through BitTorrent, I think we'll be setting ourselves up perfectly for the next step,
which is quite a ways off, I think, but that will be, eventually will be video,
and we'll probably do it the same way and BitTorrent seems to work great with big video files.
So that's just some stuff to think about.
Because one thing we're missing, we're missing good audio feeds with enclosures.
I mean, they are out there. There's lots of people doing audio blog posts,
but just not enough for integrating them into their RSS feeds.
So that's the other side of me thinking maybe we need to work on some kind of publishing system,
but just food for thought, I hope.
by Monday to have had enough feedback from folks and figure out which way we
should go with this. I did catch a couple interesting bits across the net on the
iPod or I love the blog digger MP3 feed. It brings in just it's the most
serendipitous part of my experience is whatever that brings in and I actually
caught this one guy before and this is his latest, well I guess it's
kind of like an advertisement in the form of a audio blog post and he's got a
business model and I think you should listen to it only lasts about a minute or
so but you know get your pen and paper handy because you're gonna want to
write down these URLs. Check out this Internet Guru. Welcome to volume 2
number 36 September 7th 2004 edition of current awareness happening John the
Internet. Your truly Marcus P. Zellman. This week's edition will be discussing
RSS Rich Sight Services. It's a site that
we all need to take a look at.
It is a categorization registry of library services
that are delivered or provided to RSS slash XML
to be delivered to Adam or other types of web feeds.
RSS is the initialism for RDF site summary,
rich site summary, really simple syndication,
depending upon which nomenclature you are using.
And in general, for each entry,
the home institutional library is listed
and is hot linked entry for the item.
When available, a link of the RSS feed
or an associated information page is also provided.
RSS is compiled and maintained by Gary McKernan,
Science and Technology Library and Bibliographer,
Science and Technology Department, Iowa State University,
Library and Ames, Iowa.
This is a terrific site when it comes to looking
at various rich site services,
it has information about administrative and...
announcements, acquisitions, cataloging, circulation, collection development, databases, instruction,
interlibrary loan, internet resources guides, new books, new journal issues, news, online
public access catalogs, reference services, table of contents, and a general bibliography.
Greats align.
You need to take time to bookmark this site and go through and take a look at all of
the great resources that are available from this site.
Now, give us the URL.
This has been volume 2, number 36, September 7, 2004, edition of Current Awareness Happens
on the Internet.
Current Awareness Happens on the Internet.
Spotted by eCurrent Awareness Resources 2004-5, offering you a 41-page business intelligence
research.
And he just keeps going on and on and on and on.
But interesting use of audio blogs.
I wonder if he's making any money that way.
Maybe one of these days I'll be lucky enough to have him on as a guest.
Something else I picked up.
Now, I remember that you'll remember...
if you're old enough, the old CB radio days, they used to be all kinds of parody songs and
joke songs about CB users.
And of course, when it comes to weblogs, there's just too many analogies to go into right now
and too many parallels between weblogs and CB radio.
And it's been mentioned many times before.
There's some obvious benefits, of course, with the internet and weblogs.
But it's about that time in the life cycle of something that hits pop culture as hard as
weblogs have for the parody songs to come out.
And this is actually not even that bad a song if you just take it at its merit.
Again, picked up through the blog digger media feed.
Now this is something that apparently has been circulating around the internet because
I did a Google search on it and came up with, I even came up with remixes of the
song, of course, typical.
Check it out, it really sounds good.
Ginger, is it your Lorraine?
You're cat, doin' it again.
You post the lyrics when you listen to a song.
Are you a liviant to watch it doin' wrong?
Jump straight, you're gonna know
Love life, tell us blow by blow
I love certain pleasing forms of what you're going to eat
Without that knowledge, then my life is ain't gonna be
This is not your vlog.
We don't wanna hang out with you.
It's hard, I am feeling blue
So what? Who the hell are you?
You are insincerity self-impact shmuck
What makes you think we're going to give up playing fuck?
This is not your vlog, this is not your vlog
If you're lonely for your mommy it's wax
Not your vlog
Very uh...
not your blog. Well, it's actually my mic up a little bit. It sucks. Hold on. Okay. Yeah,
not too bad. I kind of like that song. This is not your blog available all around the
internet now also in a remix version. A couple more things I want to talk about just bopping
around from topic to topic today. I picked up on a story I think Dave Weiner pointed
into it about Microsoft MSN radio. This is really interesting. Apparently what MSN
is doing is they started up a new service where they purchase the playlist information
of see in total. I think they have probably 1200 radio stations in the States, Canada
and Puerto Rico. Now you can get these you can buy these from from Nielsson broadcast
data systems and radio stations subscribe to these services all the time all kinds of
services so they can see what the competition is doing basically so it's
very it's very normal to subscribe to this. But what they're doing is they're
taking
the playlist, not necessarily the format. I'm not quite sure if they're onto that.
The format as we discussed before is what type of song you play at what part of
the hour or what part of the day. In fact radio is split up into day parts.
And they're replicating or they're attempting to replicate each radio
station. Let's see, there's a couple of examples here. None of them that I can
have heard of. But apparently, let's see, Oakland San Jose, KYLD, Wild 94,
Alice 97.3, K101, Star 101, which is Star 101.3. So you have the exact same
music mix, presumably in more or less the same order. They're even claiming with
less repetition. Think about how they're really trying to make radio here.
Only don't have the commercials, the weather or the local community affairs,
and of course the disc jockeys. And this is supposed to be like this huge
benefit. And I'm thinking, why?
call this MSN radio. They clearly do not have a... They have... There is clueless about what
radio is about as clear channel is from what I'm reading here. And there's one program
director who was quoted in this piece who actually hit it right on the head. Here we go. This
is from John Aller's program director at KCNLFM, known there as Channel 104.9. He said, and
I quote, I appreciate them calling attention to us, to those who may not
have discovered us yet, Aller said. But he added that if you're trying to take away
our listeners, the programming that makes a station's personality and connection
to listeners can't be duplicated by a computer. Hallelujah. That is right on the
money and absolutely true. Hold on. Let me just crank up the mic here a little
bit. And the reason for that is that radio is not just about records. Yes,
that's a very important part of it.
important part of it and that's going to bring in the age group of listeners that you're
looking for.
But radio is it and I think we discussed that here before as well.
Just like this is actually a kind of because you relate to an audience and you talk about
things that your audience is interested in and usually that's a geographic audience
with radio because you only can broadcast so far with your signal.
So you're going to talk about local weather, local things that are going on.
You're going to have times to like local promotions into local retail, into concerts.
I mean, there's all this stuff.
It's not just about, you know, Madonna's in town and we have the concert.
We're going to promote that and we're going to play her records.
That's just not what it's all about.
And it's certainly not only about we're going to play the best of the 70s, 80s
and 90s without the DJs and all of a sudden that's going to work.
People really do like and need some type of human element to a radio station.
Sure.
Non-stop jukeboxes work still work.
very well. And there are many radio formats where there's a hell of a lot more music and
less talk. But still, it is even if it's the local weather report, it's absolutely critical
to the success of any radio station. So I'm not quite sure what MSN is trying to do.
I don't think that they're liable for anything, because I still don't think that they can
really copy the format unless they've got some radio guy working with them on this
who knows what he's doing. Because it's not easy to copy a format.
And formats are also something that kind of evolve on the fly. You'll often see a
program director or a music director or sometimes even a general manager just
going into the computer. The system they use, almost every radio station he uses
is called selector and will be manually changing things on the fly. And all the
lists are always checked. And it's something that really comes from the
gut more than just from a computer, at least on radio stations that I think
are really good and usually the ones doing well.
see that type of hands-on approach.
So interesting that they're trying to do that, but again, I think quite clueless.
And if they're trying to market that as radio, then they're making a marketing mistake.
Speaking of marketing, we know as, what was that, we heard the interview with Hallie and
David Weinberg.
I think it was, yeah, we said that the language of politics today is the language
of marketing.
And there's another bit of marketing out there.
I don't know if you've seen it in the states yet.
Probably it certainly, it's not airing anywhere in Europe unless you happen to
catch it on a news broadcast.
This is an advertisement which was paid for by Texans for Truth.
And it's very short and there's only two captions in it, two titles.
I'll read those as they come on the screen.
And this is basically the counter-attack of John Kerry's
about the truth or whatever the swift boat controversy of his tours in Vietnam and now
they're counter attacking on George Bush about him possibly having been AWOL himself.
So I'll read the captions off and you can listen to the audio.
Was George Bush AWOL in Alabama?
George Bush was up and say I served in the 180th Civil Air National Guard in Montgomery,
Alabama.
Really.
I mean that was my unit and I don't remember seeing you there.
So I call friends and I did you know that George served in our unit?
No, I never saw him there.
Tell us whom you serve with Mr. President.
It would be impossible to be unseen in a unit of that size.
George Bush has some explaining to do.
There you go.
So it ends with George Bush has some explaining to do and that was, let me see, I can get
that title for you and see who that was who was speaking.
Lieutenant Colonel Robert Mince of the 187th Tech.
a practical squadron Air National Guard in Montgomery, Alabama.
And he's claiming that he can't remember any George Bush and he called a couple other
people neither could they.
So interesting bit of marketing.
Has nothing to do with politics or the future of the United States?
I guess.
I think there's other more important things we'll be talking about, that's for sure.
Briefly on audiobooks, one of my favorite topics.
And here's something that I did not know.
You probably heard of the Gutenberg Project, which you can get to through Gutenberg.net.
This is a collection of all literary works that have come into the public domain.
So you can basically download the text and many are an HTML version and some even in
PDFs of some excellent, excellent books that you can just download and put on your
ebook reader or you can read it right off your screen.
I've seen...
Lots of times I've seen people who have used text to speech processing to try and kind of make an audio book into it.
I've tried that myself a couple times and it just it just doesn't work.
I mean you can't get the nuance, the human feeling, the emotion depending on what kind of book or if it's a novel or
biography you need a different approach and
computerize the speech synthesis, at least on the level that it's available to users today.
It's nowhere near what it needs to be. But I actually found
that there are also some folks out there who were
making these audio books free of charge and uploading them to the Gutenberg project.
And I want to give you two examples just to give you an idea of the quality
because the voice on the first one that I have no idea if this is homegrown or if this is maybe something a little bit
a little more professional. Check out this reading. I'll just give you a little piece of Sherlock Holmes.
The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes.
by Sir Arthur Conan Doyle
A scandal in
email.
Sherlock Holmes. She is always the woman. I have seldom heard him mention her under any
other name. In his eyes, she eclipses and predominates the whole of her say.
So that's just a little bit of Sherlock Holmes. I was blown away by that speaker and I've
actually downloaded this. It's on my iPod and I will get to it because it sounds like
that would be a pretty relaxing listen to Sherlock Holmes book. And I found that original
audio recording. It's just all kinds of audio stuff here today. And this also came
off of Gutenberg. This is an actual recording of Watson discussing the
events that unfolded and how the telephone was discovered, which of course was
done by Alexander Graham Bell. But listen to a bit of this recording. You should
listen to the whole thing. It's about six minutes long. It's a fabulous piece
of history. And the recording is, well, needless to say...
shit listen to the scratches
telegraph netizens over one wire at the same time
so just a bit there of the birth of the telephone and
again, both of these can be downloaded for free and they're completely
royalty and copyright free from
Gutenberg net excellent resource on the internet and one of these days
I am just gonna have to you know break down and actually record an entire audiobook
I've been looking at a couple different ones that are read as a kid
And I don't know, I just have to have got a, I wonder how long it would take.
You know, I remember we did, there was a collaborative audio book effort that was done several, like,
well everyone took a chapter.
There were 13 or 14 different bloggers that all read a chapter of Lawrence Lessig's book.
Maybe that would be fun to start that up again or as I said, maybe I'll just do
one myself.
Okay, let's see, we're 25 minutes.
Why don't we just round off today's source code with a song.
This is one that I picked out of the iTunes library.
Never can get enough Joe Walsh.
Rocky Mountain Way.
I
SNAKE
Oh
you
I
Joe Walsh, Rocky Mountain Way on the source code.
And I was just thinking, I apologize if I sound a little discombobulated.
It's quarter to 11 here and I'm just tired.
I got to do these things earlier, that's for sure.
What we didn't talk about today was something that's pretty high in everybody's list
who's been responding, namely naming conventions for the source code.
So should it be year, month, day?
Should it be day, month, year?
Should it be daily source code or just DSC?
All different kinds of opinions based upon.
I think probably different user experiences, different MP3 devices.
So I'm still kind of trying to work that out in my own little world here.
So for now I'm going to keep the naming.
convention as it is.
And I'm going to leave you with that for the source code for today.
Of course, as always, if you'd like to respond, you can send email to adamantcurry.com or
just leave a comment on my web blog, which is located at live.curry.com.
This was the source code for today, September 8th, 2004.
And we'll see you tomorrow.
Bye-bye.
I'm going to leave you with that for the source code for today.