The Lays there began as you reach Web Chapel.
There were tons of hits shut out of your text.
That's right.
Your final score last night at 9.
First on 635 OVJ.
To Pete.
Oh, Justin.
It's Adam Curry.
Adam Curry.
Thursday the 30th of December.
Hey, do you hear that?
That was like an official pukered radio voice.
Hey, everybody.
I am doing welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Coming to you from Curry Cottage.
It is Thursday, December 30th, 2004.
Almost at the end of the year.
Yet again, 40 minutes of users and developers partying together on MP3.
The power of the Lord is the Lord.
What are you partying together on MP3?
In MP3 on MP3 with MP3?
God knows.
Welcome readers of BBC's website or the Boston Phoenix.
You may have happened upon this program or podcasting.
Thanks to one of those two articles.
Daily Source Code.
Where I am, the effort is so little podcasting.
Everybody now.
So that means we got promos.
We got potsafe music on the way.
We got some mashups.
We've got new podcasts.
And of course.
Fun.
Actually, what I wanted to say was, of course, we got some countdown, right?
There's something about, you know, that this, and we've played the sign-in-out live Cowball,
Skit.
A number of times on this show and people have commented on it.
But that's really quite a cult following a, about this whole Christopher Walken.
I mean, Bruce Dickinson Cowbell thing.
I dig it.
I totally dig it.
So, once again, some techy stuff to talk about.
But really, I'd say there is no source code that can really,
100% complete without a drum cadence.
Yes.
Indeed.
Today's drum cadence comes from our drum, aficionado extraordinaire Joe Husky.
Here's the friend's drum cadence from the movie Drumline.
Enjoy this.
It's about four minutes if you want to skip past that.
But I would suggest checking it out.
This is the first time I've ever seen a drum cadence.
I've never seen a drum cadence.
I've never seen a drumstick.
So if you're new to the daily source code, new to podcasts, and you're probably saying,
what the heck is this?
It's addictive.
It's drum cadence stuff.
It really is.
You know, I'm still looking for more hits.
More big hits done by high school bands, college bands, professional bands.
I think we should make a whole podcast just out of drum cadence.
There's clearly an enormous community.
I'm getting more drum cadence and B3 sent to me than rock and roll.
Either the community is tighter.
The community is more active or there's just more of it.
But when you think about it, every single school has some form of a band.
It's pretty easy to record these things.
Let's get some hits going.
I think it's addictive.
When I'm walking, I love listening to good drum cadence.
I can't help it.
It just helps me out.
And of course, the great thing about podcasts is that if you don't dig it, just skip ahead.
That's why I told you about three minutes skip ahead.
Actually, this was supposed to be four minutes.
I'll just let it wind up here.
Let's hear how it ends.
It's a classic drum battle.
End of show.
You know, we have this sky television set up, which is satellite, which is, I guess, analogous to.
Actually, it's kind of like direct TV and TV.
Put into one, because you can pause live TV.
You can record multiple shows.
The whole thing.
It has the guide.
What it doesn't do is it doesn't give you the suggestions that the TV does.
On the second we just do our little latency thing.
Okay.
It's better.
More about the latency later on the show.
And I think it's, is an MSNBC.
Maybe it's one of the multiple sky channels to every night, every weekday night.
I think at one thirty AM, David Letterman is on.
And I love David Letterman.
I also, you know, there's also the late show errors on MSNBC and the weekend.
So I don't really know if there's a, or the tonight show with Jay Leno.
But the late show would let him in errors every weekday night.
And because of the sky box, you can basically subscribe to the show.
So that's why I don't even know what network it's on.
I'm subscribed to David Letterman.
So it's sitting there waiting for me.
And it has little info button.
And it can tell you look at your recorded shows and it tells you which guests were on.
It's like the show notes.
So I saw that Howard Stern was on.
I guess he was on probably last week, just before Christmas.
So there's a two or three day delay.
And when they re-are them, or they broadcast them here in Europe in the UK.
And Stern, of course, was on talking about his move to serious radio from traditional broadcasting from,
I think he's still with infinity.
Isn't he?
Infinity or did he move?
Well, anyway.
Doesn't matter.
He's going from traditional broadcast over to a subscription model.
And I say subscription model specifically because podcasting is the same thing.
It's a subscription model.
Do not let the word subscription freak you out because you don't have to pay anything for the subscription.
But you are basically subscribed.
And it was great.
I mean, it was really wonderful because, and I, and I, and I still recorded.
And now, of course, I have to figure out how to get that off of my, my sky box.
I guess I could Jerry rig up the audio somehow.
Maybe I'll just hold up an MP3 recorded in front of the TV.
But I do want to let you hear a couple of excerpts from that.
And maybe someone else recorded, they can hack it up for me.
Because he was talking about all the same reasons why podcasting is as exploded.
But more from a broadcaster standpoint.
It was really interesting.
But here's where it got kind of sad.
Because he can't make his move until 2006.
That means there's a whole year, a whole year, right?
Where in a lot of shit can happen in a whole year.
Look at how fast podcasting took off.
You know, just a couple months.
Of course, it'd been brewing for years.
But you get, you get my, my drift there.
And he can't really talk about, and he can't promote the subscription nature of the service that he's moving to on his own radio show.
Which is just one of the many things he can't talk about.
So, you know, it's, it's a, it's very frustrating for him.
I'm sure.
So, if I just compile all the data in my head and I didn't take notes, but I did watch very closely.
And Patricia was sitting on the couch next to me, by the way, saying,
God damn, he'd be perfect for podcasting, like, uh-huh.
And in fact, he's doing that.
He's moving over to a podcast model, a subscription model.
And I potter kind of model, although it's not.
Because serious radio will still be live radio.
When Howard Stern is broadcasting, less it's a best of, it'll be broadcast live,
and you'll have to be in your car at that moment to receive it.
And I specifically say, car, because that's pretty much where serious works the best right now.
And this was one of the sad things is that besides the fact that Howard, for the next year,
will have to go on all kinds of external media, which he always, you know,
didn't do.
He refused to do interviews except for David Letterman, of course, and the odd line of appearance.
And of course, he, he'd do appearances, but he'd like to pick and choose him.
And now I think he, you know, part of the deal is that he does have to promote this.
He's trying to get people to subscribe to serious radio, uh, this Christmas season.
I don't know if that helped or not.
They have about 750,000 subscribers.
And what he did, and this is the part that really freaked me out.
He said, you know, I brought something day.
This is for you, because serious is not just for the car anymore.
It's also for at home.
And he, and he picks up from behind the chair.
This blue boom box.
It could have been made by Philips.
I swear to God, it was so freaking ugly.
Um, with, you know, the two round speakers had a little bow on it.
And he says, this is it.
You know, you can receive serious radio in your, uh, in your kitchen or in your living room.
Like my god, the man actually has to sell the freaking boxes.
This is sad.
And Patricia said, and this was what I, I love her so much.
She said, but, you know, well, why doesn't he just use the iPods?
I mean, there's millions of iPods.
She said, it's a yep, bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo.
Of course, um, I'm not offering him $500 million for a five-year contract.
Yet.
I say yet.
But if you look at it, 750,000 subscriptions.
And I'm sure that of the 15 million listeners, um, he reaches.
I don't know if he actually has 15 million listeners, but his audience is, uh, at least,
well, maybe it is 15 million.
It wouldn't surprise me.
That actually, that, that probably sounds about right 15 million listeners.
Yeah, let's say that he has 15 million listeners.
I bet you of those 15 million listeners, a large, um, segment probably has an MP3 player.
And I think that, you know, what was he talking about?
He was saying 40 cents a day gets you serious radio.
And that's probably about right if you, if you work it out to a monthly payment.
And he said, he's Hawking all this, right?
He's basically doing a QVC on Letterman.
And I think in myself, man, I would pay 40 cents a day just to Howard for only a Howard
Seren podcast.
And it's funny because when I just started out with OnRent, my company in New York,
which later, uh, went on to become thinking of ideas and what she took public.
Um, I remember calling Don Buckwell.
I think it's Don Buckwell.
His, uh, his manager is consultant, etc.
And I said, look, um, yeah, of course he, he took my call in New, uh,
it was.
And I said, you know, the internet is where it's going to be.
It's going.
This is perfect for Howard.
No restrictions.
And basically, I got the gruff answer, like, you know,
we're not interested in internet and, you know, unless we make money off it.
Which is completely fair.
I think that time is coming.
And we need a Howard Stern.
We really do need a Howard Stern to come over to our side.
Um, and it's too bad he didn't do it.
Uh, I can't blame him again for the, you know, for that offer.
I don't know if the, if the, if the offer will remain open for the next year,
if we can still come in with a different offer.
I don't even know if it's actually 500 million in cash.
Somehow I doubt it's going to be 500 million cash.
It's probably a combination of stock and options and, uh,
based upon upside and future results and stuff like that.
Doesn't matter.
I think Howard has enough money, uh, to live comfortably, um,
but he deserves to get paid for it.
Whatever he does.
But I think there will be more options.
There's going to be more media companies that will be interested in, um,
um, in that kind of talent.
And it may not be Howard Stern, maybe there's a young Stern out there,
that people will gladly pay money for to subscribe to a podcast,
or maybe we can work out some advertising or maybe not at all.
Maybe someone will just do it just because it's fucking fun.
Kind of like what we're doing.
So, um, I will get some of those experts.
If, if you recorded that, if you have it at home,
uh, hack it up, put it into MP3, please let me know before I go and,
and start streaming wires throughout the cottage,
which gets Patricia so incredibly pissed off.
And of course, after I usually do that, then nothing works anymore, right?
13 minutes into your daily source code.
Um, this is today's source code is sampled at 44.1 kilohertz,
which is the original sample rate.
We've been talking about this yesterday's was, uh,
I forced it with the new with the lame brain filters.
If you remember yesterday's show,
to go through it, uh, 22.05.
Oh, kilohertz sample.
Um, which was a little lower on quality, I fell.
So, and the file size, it was only like a meg difference, I think.
If you, you know, normally it's about 19 megs for a 40,
19 and a half to 20 megs for a 40 minute show,
and yesterday's like 18 and a half.
So, it didn't make a lot of difference.
So, what I'm doing now, uh, today's show is compresses 44.1.
So, the file size will be bigger.
What I put in the production show notes is an excellent comment by, uh,
FLEB, uh, no other identification for FLEB.
But really, uh, goes into great detail about the MP3 wobbling
about the sample rates, about the bit rates.
Um, I put it in the show notes because it's way too complicated to discuss,
uh, just me to, to pair it back for you or to, or to read it.
But it is, if you want to know what this is all about,
and you want to know, um, what, what the difference certain settings
make, please go look at the show notes for today.
And, um, working with the, uh, with Drew and, uh, with Dave,
had another great chat with Dave last night on, you know,
how we can best, um, put these show notes out there, you know,
and what should we make, uh, what should we make, uh, a podcast,
you know, post look like I guess.
All stuff that we're working on.
All stuff we're working on.
Um, the Asian crisis.
Can't talk about that enough.
Um, last night, Patricia and I, uh, after we were done,
did I already tell you about this?
Was it last night?
It was it.
I remember I told Dave about it that you were sitting in the kitchen
and the radio was on.
And, of course, we have perfect lighting in the cottage, right?
Everything's on dimmers, which I installed myself, by the way.
Um, and so the lighting is nice.
It's just like a movie set.
My life is like a movie set.
I got to tell you this.
This is totally what Patricia does.
She always says, women above 50 have to have dimmers.
We need special lighting to look good.
Men above 42, I got news for you.
So, and we have the radio on or the wireless, as it's still known here in the UK.
And people do listen to the wireless quite a bit, which is, you know,
is nice.
People really like their radio and the, and the talk shows.
And the news came through and it was just like we were in a fricking movie with like
Will Smith, you know, or, or, or, um,
What's this name?
Bruce Willis.
You know, here on the radio, 100,000 people perished.
And like, Jesus Christ, you know, what is this?
What, what has been happening?
How, how did we get to this point?
And Michael Lopez sent me an email, said,
Maybe we need to come up with some kind of emergency pod system, pod cast system.
It says, we need one.
Maybe it would be checked every five or ten minutes instead of twice or thrice daily.
Could warn you of upcoming catastrophes like the tsunami and save lives.
I don't, I don't know.
I don't think that's going to work just with the pure time shift of what we're doing.
In fact, whenever, um, if I'm ever asked in an interview, you know,
So, well, because that's one thing reporters and journalists always will say,
It's like, well, you know, but your news is always going to be a day late.
And usually, I say, yeah, if we find Osama bin Laden,
Please don't go running to your iPod because you probably won't get the news there immediately.
In fact, I think weblogs will be much, much, much better for that.
But the answer, I think, to the, to the whole idea of EPS is that RSS,
really simple syndication, which is, you know, the foundation of what,
What this distribution is all based on,
is that is the answer to an early warning system like that.
Absolutely, absolutely. And that's, and I'm sure that there's stuff out there already.
I know there's the Amber Alert, which I subscribe to.
Um, we, uh, we blogged about that a while ago, which is missing kids.
Um, and I, it's like the milk carton. It's like the virtual milk carton.
It comes through every single day.
And what I like about the Amber Alert is they also, uh,
Post when the kids have been found. You know, it's not just the horrible news
in kids we can't find them. It's also, hey, guess what?
That kid that was missing found the kid is alive, all as well.
This is the sound of the day.
To sound of the day for today, you.
And that was the sound of the day.
Toon in again tomorrow for the sound of the day.
And my Bob, uh.
All right. This comes from openpodcast.org.
And, um, if you've never checked out openpodcast.org or if you're new to podcasting
and want to get your feet wet, this is an excellent way to do it. Openpodcast.org.
Let's you call in through a phone number or email an MP3 file or just email a link
to an MP3 file. The, I mean, the interface is actually it's wonderful for newbies.
If you don't know how to do an RSS feed and you just want to get stuff out there.
Um, you, it's open. That's the whole point.
And, um, it's just a great place to get stuff, um, played.
Uh, it doesn't have a hell of a lot of subscribers I saw today.
Only like three or 400 people who subscribe to the feed, but I'm one of them.
And, uh, I used to get the, uh, podcast or tap dancing news off of that all the one second.
Um, also, uh, well, there's a number of things that you used to get from that feed.
I haven't, uh, really, and it's something that the Dave said.
He said, you know, um, I miss some things in your show, and I think it's because of the bandwidth.
And yes, of course, bandwidth is, is a problem, although, you know,
I've been solving it and been learning a lot and the problem will eventually go away.
Um, but, uh, openpodcast, I don't know, I just, I just want to make sure you know about it.
Because that's, if you want to just send something out there, get some creativity flowing,
and people will definitely respond to you.
And, uh, it's also a good place to send stuff for me to listen to because I'm back on it.
I'm re-subscribed, um, and it's, uh, and I'm all caught up.
So now whenever something new comes through openpodcast.org, I'll definitely, uh, catch it.
So it's a, it's a good way to, to get your podcast chops down if, uh, if you should so wish.
Um, let's see. Oh, of course, a news, uh, Ken and Squip show is, uh, is out.
And, as usual, Ken has built a little promo for it.
Hello, this is Kenster J from the Ken and Squip show.
Please join us this week as Squip and I take to the skies over Manhattan for our first,
and most likely last annual Ken and Squip show toy drop.
You're just flying past some place on the upper west side of Manhattan,
not far from the Ken and Squip broadcast plaza.
Is that a goat I see on the roof?
It's Donald Trump.
Oh, the Donald high, everybody wave.
Wait, don't everybody move to one side at once.
Ken is on the left side of the chopper throwing out presents.
I've got a CD player right here.
I'm about to let go.
And, and all sorts of gifts like I'd like to.
And there it goes.
Wait, the shoots.
Oh, the shoots not opening on that one.
Look out.
No.
Oh.
Ouch.
That probably hurt safely back in the ground.
I asked Squip to reflect back on her holiday.
How is your holiday?
And then we discuss how to handle that awkward situation that happens when someone gives you a horrible gift.
Then it had this thing hanging off the end of it.
It looked like a pork chop.
Well, I said, hmm, where did you get that?
So I can return it and get the gas.
We also offer up in your reverent review of the very latest in religious soft toys.
It, it, it hugging Jesus.com.
Christ, I hate to give them a plug.
Now, first of all, it looks like a piece of roadkill.
It looks like pancake Jesus.
It's the ugliest piece of shit that I've ever seen in my life.
Spread the love of Christ today.
I could just throw up.
And Squip and I finally error differences over the official Ken and Squip show cock.
We still haven't ever resolved our dispute over the cock though.
One of these days, we're going to have to have a cock off on the air.
Well, people can vote for cock number one or cock number two.
It's the only time she's ever really gotten mad at me ladies and gentlemen.
It was over that damned cock.
I really liked my cock and you took it away.
No, because you'll note I didn't take it away.
It was in the last show and my cock was in the show before that.
Ken?
That didn't sound right at all.
Plus, as always, we feature a great new band.
All of this and more are in this week's Ken and Squip show.
That's available at www.dustingmybrain.com slash k-a-s-s-s.
Oh, right.
The casting may never be the same.
That's right.
Ken and Squip show.
These are the two folks that used to work with me at my company.
It's just, I love hearing them.
All though, Ken, make the promo a little shorter.
Okay, try and make it one minute.
This is valuable source code time, ever rainbow day.
Hey, check this out.
It's a Beatles mashup medley.
It's just, I love hearing them.
Did you think that money wasn't true?
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, come, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
I never used to go away
But I was like that, it's great
But I never used to go away
I never used to go away
of medley damn that was good I love that that's actually that's probably a three or four
boinger isn't it it's like a lot of response to little talk we had about Firefox the new
browser from the Mozilla Foundation I guess is that from the Mozilla Foundation what's the
open source browser and now I know how to scroll all the way to the top of the bottom of the
page so if you want to go up or down one page if you're on like a big scrolling web page it's
the hold on it's on your power book it's function or on your regular key it's the control key I guess
CTRL key so arrow upper hour arrow down gives you one page if you do arrow left arrow right
that'll take you to the top of the page all the way to the bottom of the page so now I just need to find
out how I can actually what keyboard shortcuts can rotate through the different tabs okay and also
people are now downloading the Firefox the optimized Firefox for G4 G5 Max whoa
got a lot a lot of real happy people on that one man I'll tell you it's fast it's a good
browser I'm liking it the thing I don't like of course as I have to reenter all the the form
automated fill-in forms I love having that I use that all the time because I subscribe to stuff
all the time with different names and numbers and data whatever and of course having to
re-subscribe to all the sites that that I had password username pairs for but it's worth it
I'm doing it and also thank you by the way for explaining how to import the bookmarks it's so far
you guys have been really helped me out I really appreciate it and a more good news remember I told you
that it seemed like David fixed his recording problem and it turned out it was the I think it's
called replay radio that that he had installed which essentially records streams off of
known programs predominantly NPR programs and turns those into MP3's I guess and puts him on your
drive for kind of like an iPod or you know so you can listen to him later it's a it's a time
shifter and he had recorded the world where the clerk boy did an interview with me at the star
bucks in gilford and it had the same kind of gaps that people had noticed on his podcast and so
that led him to pretty much discover that this was the problem and he uninstalled and I think he's
fixed it but then he went on and did this awesome test while he was an amerala Texas and I knew
he was going to amerala could I told him a couple days ago because he calls me on the road you know so it's
around 2 p.m. and it's later at night here and we're talking and it's great the GSM connectivity
is fricking awesome you know it's just he drives and we talk and it's the connection is great
and it's actually cheaper for me to call Dave in Texas from cell phone to cell phone that it is
for me to call a landline in the Netherlands just want you to know that so anyway I said you know
I've been to amerala Texas I think I was there once when I was promoting my syndicated countdown
radio show that Adam Curry's top 30 hit list and so the way that worked is you go to all these
top 40 radio stations and if I made an appearance then they would run my show and basically they'd
run my show for free but of course I would sell national commercials because it was on an x number of
stations and I don't remember what the top 40 station was in amerala Texas but I do remember they took
me the DJs and the program director because this happened every single town too it was like hey
come on man I'm going to go take yad to strip joy man it's always cougars or cheetahs or you know whenever
I said today I said I know there's an awesome strip barn amerala Texas with tumble weeds like rolling
outside but it's it's a lot of fun on the inside and he took that to hard I guess in his test
of his new setup this is a test I am I'm using let's see so first he's going to talk about what he
fixed which is actually pretty important stuff because that was you know it's a bug it's a
fucking bug in this replay radio software I guess you might Sony laptop which is the computer that I
have out and ready to use all the way isn't it nice to hear Dave with a normal voice again and so
that Hawking squeaky Brady bunch like voice change thing and it's nice to hear this way amiga
I'm driving and frankly if I can get this thing to do the to you know record stuff then
that I'm going to be able to do more podcasts while I'm on the road which I will be on the road
excuse me for at least like the next two weeks maybe three weeks so it's a good thing to sort of
figure out and I had a it was interesting when I recorded when Adam was on the the world with BBC
I recorded that on this laptop using replay radio and everybody said that it had the the gaps you
know sort of the breaks that that are typical of this computer when it does it's recordings and
I thought well maybe the problem is the uh maybe the problem is the um the replay radio stuff
uh yeah exactly so then Dave goes on to read like local literature exotic dancers
sweet and personal escort for all okay hmm hmm okay how about some she males days here's
best rate escort they might have some sweet yeah they have celebrity look like males wait is there an
Adam curry for rent yeah that I just did that oh okay well shelly this sweet and personal it's just
if you haven't heard this you've gotta go listen to it it's uh it's probably still uh in the RSS
if not because scroll back to like yesterday on scripting news it's hilarious you got to listen to the
whole thing and I think we should have a podcast about escorts and strip bars in different towns you know
if you're going somewhere and I'm not really someone who goes to strip bars or or makes use of
professional services such as escorts but hey there's a business there right and what where is the
first escort podcast I have a feeling it can't be too far off I really do I was thinking to more
about uh let me see how much time do we have shoot oh man I'm gonna leave I'm gonna leave that thought
for tomorrow that'll be good it'll be a that's a great think on it's Friday uh thought okay
back to well let's talk about the tsunami disaster for a moment there's some emails that came in
all stuff that is pertinent to the conversation that you'll find in the production show notes
certainly from hell's bellboy who sent me an email and listed actually a number of
horrible disasters typhoon and tsunami related disasters that have taken place in the region for instance
November 13th 1970 a massive typhoon hits Bangladesh 24th tidal wave struck the shores of the
gangest delta November 13th uh wreaking lethal damage 120 per a mile per hour cyclone more than
an estimated 100,000 dead 150,000 uh total of 150,000 dead the centuries largest disaster and he
goes on to list a couple more and I guess well hey it's just um interesting to you know to go back and
look at history and probably also you know this is what what most television broadcasts are gonna
start doing themselves and they're gonna go back and see if they can get footage from 1970 etc but
uh we have had these events you know these horrific events and it does seem they just they do seem
to kind of fade from from memory after a while don't they which is I presume human nature I guess that's
kind of normal I also asked um the uh actually there's uh I said you know so I said what what can we do
what is the best thing to do a lot of people pointed me to city.org cidi.org which is the center for
international disaster information they've actually got an MP3 out there which's gonna play for you
right now and which they tell you what they'd like you to do and how you can best help uh the victims
them countless victims of this horrible disaster. Humanitarian groups need your help in southern Asia
I'm John Butler thousands of people have been killed and many thousands more are injured or left
homeless in nine countries across southern Asia the tsunami touched off by the most powerful earthquake
in four decades ranks as one of the most devastating disasters in history. Americans wanting to help
maybe tempted to send food or blankets but caches the best way to help those affected by the tsunami
Suzanne Brooks director of the center for international disaster information cidi explains why
caches best. Cash offers relief agents is the most flexibility with cash disaster relief
professionals can work directly with those affected by disasters to get out exactly what is needed
such as medicine and food quickly. Before collecting anything individuals looking to donate should
contact an established relief organization for more log on to cidi.org or usad.gov or go to
interaction.org and click on the guide to appropriate giving. I can I tell you as uh oh let me just
reset one second as a helicopter pilot man I wish I could help you know I think I really could I
I'm I'm good at that stuff I'm good at hovering and and getting people out and I know how the
winch works and I can work with the winchmen but I'm sure they don't need my help in that
regard there so I send cash and it seems that everyone around the world is doing that much much more
than governments are actually pointing out it's really the citizens which is beautiful to see
and also asked uh in yesterday's podcast you know for all the god podcasters i said who's god did
this you know what is the point why you know could you please explain that to me which of course
is a question that's unfair to ask but you know it's shit it's my podcast and I did get some
responses to that and the many god i call them godcasters well let's say religious podcasters
have um have commented on this and have made note of it and uh I've linked to some of those
in the production show notes but also uh Rick um from i see him raw um he sent me a
comment well I'll play it for you right now because he did respond well listen up check this out
hey Adam Rick was with it's here for my see him raw you asked the godcasters to comment
on the horrible tragedy that occurred in the Indian Ocean this week and uh I'm not sure why
it occurred but I do want to share a couple of verses job 2 10 it says show me indeed except good
from god and not except adversity and uh job 42 2 says I know that you can do all things and he's
referring to god here and then no purpose of yours can be thwarted 68 thousand lives is uh he's
a lot of lives and I'm not sure why the Lord allowed it but it does say in job 1 21 that the Lord
is given and the Lord takes away blessed be the name of the Lord so I think what it really comes
down to is how are we who are left gonna respond I feel the same thing occurred after the
World Trade Center and uh to those who are uh who have died in Iraq how are we who are left
going to react how are we gonna show love to those who are in mourning and for those who
who are hurt and for those who are uh who are left how are we gonna respond and I think what it
really comes down to is we who are left needs to respond with love love maybe giving money love
maybe consoling a family member who is lost someone how are we gonna show love to those who are
left today and uh I think that's how how the Lord wants us to respond as well with your in the
podcast thanks great Rick Rick requires the way it's uh Weswitz from uh ICM raw podcast um okay I'm
not uh I'm not religious in that regard don't believe in god in the way uh Rick may or uh other people may
who and maybe you listening to this podcast but I do believe that um it is up to us from a
civility standpoint is Tony Khan would say from mourning stories from the podcast is um how do we
respond how are we going to love the people um that are hurt by this uh that is probably a challenge
and there is probably a reason for that most things do happen for a reason I found so there is a reason
for this and maybe it's just a focus all of us and uh to say hey you know uh you think Iraq is bad
maybe this is if if there was a god right and you went are you think this Iraq staff is bad
let me show I can do now pfff the fuckers and maybe we should wake up and say damn you know this
Iraq shit is stupid is it stupid you know and what is it for is it for hundreds of thousands of people
who've been affected by something or is it is it for a handful of people who are looking for
some spoils of something no that's not for me to decide um also a lot of people of um kind of
put out a call to actions saying hey why don't we do like a telephone you know try and raise money
yes I think clearly you know me telling you uh playing these bits from cidid.org
and and pointing on web logs etc to different places we can donate money this is clearly
something that podcasters can help out with I don't think we need to have some kind of like special
podcasse telephone to track it all because we know people are going to give money and we know that
they're going to give as much as they can and I quite honestly I just don't see you know any other reason to
track that through a podcasse and they say oh look at how much we raise with our incredibly powerful
medium I don't think that's necessary because I know how powerful it is we can raise 1500 bucks
amongst a couple of podcasse listeners you know for for Lee and Jenny's dogs I'm sure we're doing
pretty good with with the tsunami relief okay I'm gonna go a little bit long today but I got to
because yesterday I promise I was gonna play this song and I like it so much it is from
Barry Corals Confessions of an indie girl brand new find it Barry Coral dot com but it's an
old ginegoody it's the midnight train to Georgia
it's come to know so it's going back to find it's going back to found
he's going back to find who I sing the place and time here just want to be like mine
and I love you with me all I've been my time to Georgia
um
he got treatment
Oh, I see you stop, but it ain't get fine
Sure, fair out the hallway that dreams
Don't always come true, I'm no, oh
So he just picked up his hopes
Overly in the show, hold his own car
But it won't wait to get back
To the life that he wants to say he would
Just want me like my name
I'll be with you
I'll not spend my train to your job
Over, over, over, over
I'll be with you, over, over
If my...
My wife, he's well
My wife, now he's alone
source code and leaving you now, a little bit longer than normal, but 44 minutes.
And we'll have more tomorrow on the thank god it's Friday edition of the Daily Source code
looking at a great weekend of course where we changed to a new year and on Monday I'm off to the
United States of America on my way to Miami going to hang out with David Ron looking forward to it.
I am very excited.
Have a ball that.
Okay, if you've got an audio comment, best thing to do is email that to me, keep it under five
megabytes.
Email it to Adam at Creole.
Actually, I'm sorry.
You address podcasteratmac.com, podcasteratmac.com, if you've got a private message for me without
an enclosure or an attachment, it's atamacore.com, or of course just leave a comment
on the website www.cure.com.
That I always read so if it's not a real private or anything that's a good place to get my
attention.
All right, that's it.
I'm off the Starbucks to do another iPad or scan and upload this show and we'll see you
tomorrow on the Source code.
Take care.
Drive safe.
Jog safe.
Be safe.
Bye.