Look, here in real life.
Take off and leave.
There aren't many people going in jail.
grup
O
Hey everybody welcome it's the daily source code coming to you from Utrecht you might
say Utrecht in the Netherlands in the low countries this is the podcast from the hotel room
on the left-hand side of the bed which of course is where the power out but it's completely
located alright everybody let's kick it off with some really really really good news my
mom had her operation today they removed her entire lung but she was already off of the
breathing apparatus when she was in intensive care breathing on her own and obviously totally
out of it but doctors say everything went great could not be happy
I want to thank everybody for all the beautiful thoughts prayers, emails, voice messages,
audio comments, everything all the great thoughts that you've been sending along this is
obviously just to be the beginning of a journey from my mom and for her friends and obviously for the
family but we're off to a running start let's put it that way so I'll be in and out of the hospital
for the next couple of days I chose this hotel because it's very near to the hospital so it's not
anywhere really near I'm saying well it's about 20 minute car ride if if you wanted to do it
but it was great because I was looking for a hotel in Utrecht that was you know a nice hotel
this is a word that they call us a four star hotel I guess which is whatever and but my criteria
of course number one top of the list was you know I need Wi-Fi I need really good solid Wi-Fi
and I'd prefer to if it could be a hotel that didn't have the remote control nailed down to the
to the cabinet next to the bed stand and this is great the the Wi-Fi is unbelievable of course
as I already posted on my blog you know when it comes to when it comes to me and and connectivity
I mean Jesus Christ and after four weeks of living on a modem this is almost like you know
taking the first talk off of a off of a join after you haven't smoked for four weeks
which of course I can't really talk about anyway so I got this the beautiful little
personal access code to log into to the Wi-Fi here and it says here this is I love this card
this is a super fast internet hotel ADSL surfing for a fixed price seven euros 50 a day
which well these days is actually a lot of dollars but that's a pretty good price when it comes
down to a star bug let's see what I paid star bug star box I pay 30 pounds a week which is the equivalent
of shoot well that's about forty forty dollars yeah I mean definitely definitely not cheap
so oh by the way thanks to Marcus Mowler for a little bit of the drum cadence the beginning of the
show that was his cousin Tim who was in the blue devils back when he was in high school and of course
as you know by now on the on the production show notes as a link to all of that it's it's amazing you
know I've I've really gotten to this drum cadence stuff all of a sudden people sending
me all these different files and some of the stuff is just outrageously good and there's a whole
industry around drum cadence as people selling CDs and DVDs and I'm actually looking for you know
for some for some hit songs being done by by drum bands because that I'm I'm not a lawyer but I'm
pretty sure that as long as you pay your ask at BMI and you have permission to use the actual recording
and it's okay to do it so maybe that's a way to get you know to play some of those memories we've
been talking about more about that by the way later on in the show just a little idea what the setup here
is I couldn't get one a full size queen or king size bid they only have two singles next to each
other so one will be for sleeping and one will be for podcasting I've got the power book on my lap
I'm I'm I'm so I'm propped up with pillows behind my my back I'm on the on the bed here
on top of the bed with the laptop I've got the headphones on I brought my breakout box the M audio
and I brought the the sure the SMB7 and the stand for this it's a little portable stand that I
use at home oh I'm just going to tighten that there my my father-in-law made this he that guy is
looking amazing you you give him like couple of toothpicks and and Scotch tape and some string and
hillbillgia you know a go-kart he's incredibly talented when it comes to making things and he created
this mic I mean and he's always into the stuff that I'm doing right he's a total techno geek he's
he's a musician he's a recording artist he had a recording studio in fact mumbo italyano that
that I've played on the show the song that Patricia did was recorded in soundhouse which was
her dad's studio which he sold many many years ago so he created this mic stand out of a
a stand that basically holds your music notes and it's perfect it's miniature but I can
extend it with a little tell stop telescopic bit and because it has you know the bass is well if
you know what a music stand looks like you can really extend the bass of the of the stand it's
diameter quite you know quite a way so even though it's just kind of propped on the bed because
the bass is so large now it's just it's there it's not toppling over of course that would be
inviting Murphy in the door here but it's it's pretty good so almost have the identical sound as
as back home back at the cottage where every one of course is having a good time and enjoying the
Christmas shopping but it's going to be interesting the next couple of days because Dave's on the
road Dave Winner he's he has no house he's homeless he's living in hotels I'll be living in hotels
and we'll be in contact and oh god man he had an excellent podcast I listened to on the plane
I'll be talking about that later first I want to bring you some music here on the source code
kind of bending the rules here because it's a mashup you know mashups or smashups or
basically mixes where people are putting two different songs usually one old one new and connecting
together mixing them together you have bands who are doing this live and I got an email here from
Mike Corley obviously it's part of the production show notes and he sends a link to a couple of
MP3s to check out this is the one I thought I'd play for you now because it's it's the time of
year it is the season it's Jenny on the block and Paul McCartney Christmas on the block
from an incoming movie series to on the set the J load of this high-light clips I stayed grounded
as the amounts were an unreal I thought I told you I'm really wrong that's just me
my thin phone he don't hate on me what you get is what you see
I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I know I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I
I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew I knew leaving all your liekir
I'm gonna beat you by the mask that I got
I'm still I'm still taking you back
The heaven and the power held up
I'm gonna be right to another weapon, come on
I don't know what I'm gonna beat now
I think I don't know what I'm gonna beat now
I don't know what they're gonna beat now
It's a bighouse
I think I lie
I love it
I'm the perfect age too
I remember when Paul McCartney came out we're the song
and I remember when J railroad this song
Get I at him. This is Cam and Mick from the Good Day World podcast.
Get I at him. Get I world.
Good day.
Hey, you're doing it.
Get I at him.
We've been doing this podcasting thing for a couple of weeks.
And my way we think it's a lot of fun.
And we want to give you a shout-out.
Say thanks very much for all the boring boys.
You don't want to just miss a shout-out.
You want to promote your damn show, right?
Boying boy.
All the great work you've been doing.
I've been last six months to reinvent this medium.
It's something that's got a big future ahead of it.
We're both sure.
Yeah.
Interesting.
Re-invent this medium.
That was funny.
Because I was just talking to a reporter from Rolling Stone.
Today, she called me.
And she actually had followed my postings of my web blog.
And she was like, oh, you know, I don't want to bond with your mom
and all that, but I have a deadline.
We were talking about this.
We were talking about just about radio.
You know, how it used to be Murray the K.
And that's before my time.
But I like to say, you know, Murray the K was broadcasting.
And people were listening on their transistor radio.
It was little portable things with batteries, sound familiar.
And Ahmed Erdogan was, you know, who's the chairman or founder of Atlantic
Records.
He was selling the shit right out of the back of his car.
You know, we're moving to that space again, people.
It's been good.
So you definitely should get people to come down and check out our podcast.
Because we want to, the few guys in Australia actually doing this at the moment.
And we're getting a lot of really good responses to it.
So get your, get your lyrics and let's just come on down.
Check out Get A World GDAY World dot common.
Hey, Adam, we're running a conference in February, mate.
A blogging slash podcast in conference.
Yeah.
We would love to have you come down there.
I'd be fantastic.
You know, I did a documentary once on a part of Australia.
There were a couple of people.
It was like a rough guide.
BBC does these great documentaries.
And it was, it was awesome.
I had so much fun in Australia.
Started in Sydney when all the way to Perth, you know, stated Cooper
PD, which is, you know, the Opal mines went to the smallest town.
And all the tourist things, right?
But also a spinsters and bachelor's ball.
My God, you guys know how to party damp.
Have a bit of a Jeba?
Come and have a drink with the ruin the pub.
It'll be a route where drink with the ruin the pub is a kangaroo.
Right.
We'll throw.
How about the shaylers?
Where the shaylers?
All the shaylers?
You shrimp on the barby fair.
We might even have a t-shirt for you.
We'll get A World T-shirt.
Yeah, let's go beat up Paul Hook and the kangaroo on it.
Yeah.
So, on you, Adam, thanks for all your hard work, mate.
And we look forward to seeing you on our sunny shores soon.
Right on.
Now, where is matey?
See you later.
That really would be nice to go to Australia again.
It's so nice.
It has what to inhaling.
They have something called gazellechide, something is gazellech,
which the best and the closest translation to that
in English is coziness.
And so, what I found in Australia is they have the gazellechide of the Dutch.
They still have a lot of English properties to them,
which I like, even though they're the pomeas, right?
Prisoners of Mother England is that what it was.
That's what the English call you.
Well, that was a long, long time ago.
And there's also all the convenience, or most of the convenience,
I found of what you find in the States.
Really, really nice.
Australia is okay.
I think it's an undiscovered frontier.
Now, you can't just move there and go live there unless you have
like a whole freaking load of cash and you promise to invest it
certain ways and do certain things.
Or you have to be invited.
You can't just be sponsored.
Remember, friend of mine, Michele, Michael.
He was a programmer, Janbi, and he had been in Australia.
And he wanted to go back to Australia.
And he was a physicist.
He was a professor in physics.
And they said, and the Australian officials said,
well, you can't just come here to live with your family.
Unless you have the proper education and whatever.
And Michael said, yeah, I think I got that.
Until what are you freaking rocket scientists?
And he said, well, that's a matter of fact, yeah.
I don't know what you're in.
You never know.
He might use it.
He might throw it away, but he might use it.
Well, you go.
He uses lots of crap.
He does.
Probably when you use that, we say to use lots of crap.
But yeah, okay.
Did that fit out?
So you reckon that?
That'll be an extra bit of work.
I got a good day.
Well, podcast, excellent.
Excellent.
This is your daily source code.
It is, well, it's already officially Tuesday.
But we're going to call this the podcast for Monday, December 20, 2004.
And I want to talk about, I really, some stuff started to come together.
The minute Dave hit the road, and if you haven't
listened to his morning coffee notes podcast,
in fact, you might, if you haven't on your MP3 player right now,
you might want to stop here, listen to that podcast first,
because I'm not going to play excerpts from it, because it doesn't work
that way with the morning coffee notes.
It's a build-up, it's a story.
I have to listen to the whole thing.
It's short, it's like 23 minutes.
It's well worth it.
Okay, welcome back.
I'm glad you listened to that.
And since you just listened to Dave talk for 23 minutes,
let me play you a bit of a drum cadence, everybody.
Yeah, let's kick it, shall we?
This is from Duncan.
It's the FSU drum line from 1997.
I'm just going to play a little bit because it kicks.
You know, I think we should be a podcast.
It's a drum cadence, you know?
It's like, this is the perfect, if you're just outwalking, you know?
Isn't this pretty motivated?
I think what way you could do if you remix this.
Goddamn, and think about I'd love to hear some songs.
People record songs and use a drum cadence like this.
It's awesome.
Okay, so I'll just let that play in the background a little bit while I tuck and make
so to so talk to you a bit about actually, I think it started to click for me
a couple weeks ago, Dave pointed to an old piece that he had written in 2002
about the monoculture.
I call it dismantling the monoculture and the entire theory.
And I remember reading this piece originally and it just didn't, it didn't kick in.
I'm thinking maybe I should even just read a part of that hold on.
Or is it there?
I got that speedy Wi-Fi here, everybody.
Mm, loving it.
Here it is.
This is the piece that really like, perhaps the centralized system that led to such a
suffocating monoculture was a historic anomaly and artifact.
The technology of the phonograph, radio, and television demanded centralization,
distribution was expensive.
To pay for distribution, we needed financial entities who would be rewarded for risks.
Who would be the next beetles, the band that everyone listened to,
maybe in the future there won't be bands that everyone listens to.
Maybe this wouldn't be so horrible as the philosophers of the centralized systems believe.
Perhaps monoculture has run its course.
Maybe that's what's happening right now, but it's hard to see,
is that each of us is taking more responsibility for getting our own information,
for creating our own entertainment,
and not giving that power to the centralized entertainment and information industries.
Excellent. Excellent.
Written on May 13th, 2002 by Dave Weiner.
So, all of a sudden it just started to click, of course.
You know, if you can record music, you know, if you're like the lascivious bitties,
if you're like a mojoan to record that entire album on a Mac in their attic,
you know, if you can do all that, if we have this wonderful incarnate,
yeah, I got to curse you too now, don't miss Ellie.
If we have this wonderful incarnate, which lets us distribute all this stuff,
then it only makes sense that, you know, we've put this next piece of the puzzle in this podcasting,
where we can act as the intermediaries, the, you know, the way radio guys used to do it,
the way Murray, the K, you know, Murray, the K didn't have some playlists that he was just,
you know, okay, it's time to play this one or the computer spit it out,
you know, and you can even announce that are backing out and sort of say anything about it,
or even mention that he liked it or not, he just, you know, read the next
liner card to promote, you know, the Saturday night dance party or whatever, you know,
no, he was, he was, he was, you know, they were, remember that was smashing record, you know,
it was like, make it or break it, you know, and then people would call up and say, it sucks,
it's, it's, it's smashing, we'll never play it again, and if it was hit or miss, I mean, all these things have gone,
you know, you don't hear those shows anymore. We're coming back to that, we can now do that,
and that's incredibly exciting. Now, yeah, sure, we're not going to be, uh, clear channel,
we're not going to be billionaires, you know, I, I, I've, no thoughts whatsoever, you know,
that, that, it's not even necessary, it's just not necessary, it's okay to have a couple hundred
people checking it out, or couple thousand, and maybe it's a hundred thousand, maybe it is 50 million,
it really doesn't matter. The system is working, that's the thing that's, uh, that's what,
that's what I love so much is that, um, we're rooting around the RIA, although I've got to say
it really, really bothers me that, you know, we can't play these, share these memories, and,
you know, Dave had an interesting idea, you know, that, or it says, he's basically reaching out to the,
to the record companies and saying, you know, why don't you let us use your stuff in some, you know,
uh, low resolution, some low-res manner, so that it really just won't make any difference, if, uh,
it just won't be good enough for recording, and I think personally, uh, and this actually, this used to be,
uh, uh, uh, uh, pre-requisite, and I don't remember if that was Dutch broadcasting rules or US broadcasting rules,
but, um, you were never allowed to play a song beginning to end without, you know, a jingle or talking
over the intro or talking over the outro, and essentially, I guess, you know, with podcasts,
as long as we do that, there were, you know, we should be okay, and people, it doesn't matter,
forget it, it doesn't matter. We have the proof, people buy albums. They've gone out and they've purchased
CDs of those CDs, bitties, because they heard it on this podcast or other podcasts, and they'd like it,
and that's a really big deal. So, you know, it can be done, but if we get about established artists,
I'm so incredibly excited about, um, you know, what we can do with this specifically when it comes to music,
and, uh, of course you did listen to Dave's Morning Coffee notes, and I was listening to that,
I was able to download it off the, I saw that he posted it, um, sometime around mid-afternoon,
my time in, uh, in the UK, and I was just able to download it and slip it on to the iRiver,
didn't even put it on the iPot to put onto the iRiver, because that was closer, as I was running out
the door to, uh, to grab the cab to, uh, you know, to get to the airport, and so I listened to it,
uh, half on the way to the airport and half in the plane, it was like, and just it hit me,
it's like, yeah, we can do this, you know, we can totally get this going, and, you know, we, it's,
we're jelling on it, but, uh, it's just gonna happen, it's so interesting that, you know, we're,
I think, and feel that we're working up towards our January 3rd is when we meet with Ron Bloom in, uh,
in Miami, which shows Miami by the way, because it's warm. And Ron also lives there, so, um,
we got some infrastructure going, but Dave and I are going to stay at, uh, something really cool,
local, you know, like holiday and Ramana in riot, riot, whatever it is, with not with Wi-Fi, but with
great, uh, fixed broadband, uh, Ron actually went and, uh, checked it out, and, um, oops, sorry, the drum
cadence is just keep on coming. You heard, uh, what was it? This is Joel's cadence, drum line,
keep that roll on the back. So I was actually thinking of surprising Dave, I hope that we have rooms,
close by. If not, um, I'll get, maybe we'll just get him when I want to get, uh, an Apple airport
express, just plug it into the wall, you know, and, and hook up the, um, uh, uh, the Ethernet cable,
and we'll have our own little Wi-Fi network. So, and, you know, we're gonna be working together,
and even though we're gonna be talking about, you know, what we want to do on a business level,
and, you know, they're all kinds of businesses. They're also businesses that are not for profit.
Or not necessarily for profit. Or for enormous amounts of profit. There's all kinds of companies,
but we've got something going here, and what, uh, what's happening, and, and Dave and I have,
uh, well, this is something that's, well, I think it used to bother us a little bit more than it does now,
but now we kind of got, they got it figured out that people don't quite understand the story yet.
What happened with podcasting is a story behind all of this, podcasting really came together,
because here was Dave, um, creating podcasts, which is, you know, MP3 files that he was putting up
on his, uh, on scripting news, and he was attached to him to his RSS file, which would be
doing together for years. Uh, but it was like my own personal broadcast that I was receiving,
because I had an aggregator, and I was, uh, that understood in closures, and I was bringing it in,
and I was giving a feedback, and you can look at all the, look at, look at the, uh, around the time
of the Democratic National Convention, and you can see between my weblog and Dave's weblog,
and he was like being the most, I mean, just, he was breaking all the rules of broadcasting,
he was awesome, and shit was, you know, was, wasn't working, and the mic would disconnect,
and it was just, it was an amazing thing to listen to, and I really, really dug it,
and this was around the time that I was, you know, fucking around with programming. So here we are,
I'm, uh, a broadcast or not a programmer, programming something, and then here's Dave, a programmer,
not a broadcast or broadcasting, and it just all, and it was almost like we both had to approach
the same problem from different directions for us to meet in the middle, and that's something
really big and powerful, and, um, and it's gone, and so Dave is now with his voice back, he's,
continue to do his podcasting, and, um, what he's doing is, I mean, you got to subscribe to that
feed, because he tells these incredible stories that build up to something, and, uh, and I'm
really enjoying listening to it, and I'm looking forward to, to, as I said, to seeing him, uh, in,
in Miami, and, uh, and getting some of that energy face to face. Now, I, on the other hand,
work on some programming stuff now, uh, with the open source release of frontier,
and all of these links, of course, everywhere on the production show notes, and I've now, um,
it took me a good portion of the other day, five or six hours, to create a piece of software,
that crawls through the entire ipodder.org directory, because, you know, this is decentralized,
and I'm only maintaining a certain amount of nodes, and then there are all these different nodes
and sub-nodes, which may contain by other people, and, um, basically, I just paste a link into an
outline, and, uh, on the directory, when you click into, like, the music node, you're actually,
pulling an information, uh, from a server, from Holland, and that's rendering in real time,
and below that, there's even, uh, I think the indie music feeds are being maintained by someone
in the states. So, it's completely decentralized, but you have to be able to crawl that entire
directory, so I created a piece of software that does just that, and, um, and, um, and, but now,
also, it parses through the, uh, last 100 podcasts page, which is audio.weblogs.com, because,
not everyone who pings that page to say, hey, you know, my, my show is updated, come and check it out.
It's registered in the directory, so now I'm taking all that information, and that's, uh,
and so, you know, whenever I run this thing, there's, like, 40 new podcasts showing up,
and, uh, of course, there's some checking that has to go on for, um, uh, double, you know, um,
duplicate URLs and, and all that. Um, but the next step is, uh, for me to automatically update the
what's new, um, uh, well, I have to, I want to put a process in between, right? So, uh, I can kind of,
uh, just, you know, see what, what's coming through and make some decisions for the beneficiary
if I can route it to a category or a node that I maintain. Then it should update the what's new,
node, and it'll also, um, through XML RPC, uh, post a new podcast, notice on the homepage by
potter.org. So, I hope to get that part done, uh, sometime during, uh, the next couple of days while
I'm here. Okay, a little bit shorter today, uh, since it is, uh, what's the time here? It's 125,
it's 12, 25 UK times, so I'm not really tired yet, but I really should hit the hay in a couple
minutes. I'm also going to turn out Skype and see if anyone's around before I, I go to bed,
but I cannot leave you before playing this wonderful Christmas message.
Hi, Adam Curry. This is Leanne Westover from the LaCivius Bitties. I just wanted to send you this
quick audio file to say, Merry Christmas. Ever bought it? Boyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoyoying,
everyone goes well with your mother. I hope you get everything on your list.
And I hope you get dispensed on great quality time with your wife and your daughter.
The second thing I wanted to say is haaaa, Man holidays to everybody that listens to your show.
They've been so wonderful about emailing us and buying the CDs. And I can't tell you how thrilled
we are that they enjoy the music so much. So many many thanks to them. The last thing I
wanted to say is that we do still have tons of CDs available. If they're sold out on Amazon
that's just because Amazon is a huge conglomerant and they can't keep track of a little guy.
But we still have CDs available on CDBaby.com. Those ship to Europe anywhere else around the world
just about as well as our own Bennett Studios store that you can link to off our website. So if
you haven't gotten Christmas presents for your grandma or your five-year-old niece or your girlfriend
or your stepdad you can still do it in time. I guess we'll talk to you again after the new year.
Be well, go see some good music and if you're allowed, click as much champagne as you can. Bye bye.
Thank you very much for subscribing to this podcast and check out all the latest podcasts the
last 100 ones at audio.weblogs.com and check out the directory at www.punner.org and of course
curie.com or daily source code.com. So if you want to leave me an audio comment you just
said email it off to at www.punner.com and attach it to us at www.punner.com and attach it to us at www.punner.com.
If it's on the fine page, then shoot me and it won't be sending me to Europe. Send me a link to that
thing. But yeah. All right, I'll be bringing you more news from Los Petales tomorrow and who knows
what else I dream about tonight. Hope you have my streams. Thank you all. Goodbye bye.
This is how I worked out on community work.