Hi everybody, welcome to the Daily Source Code for Monday. It is October 18th, 2004.
Coming to you in my bathrobes, sick as a dog. I'm Adam Curry with your daily source code.
Oh man, it's been just a horrible weekend. I came down with what was supposed to be just a little bit of
the sniffles and a little bit of sore throat and is now a Monday, a Monday afternoon, 10 minutes to three.
I've seen more of my bed in the past three days and I haven't had the past three months of
developing iPod or stuff. But the show must go on. So I've got all my prep that I did over the week
and I've got it lined up for you. I'm just not going to have the same amount of energy as I had as I normally
would have had and would have liked to project. So while I've been lounging around sweating and
visiting the bathroom quite frequently, Patricia continues to dismantle the entire house around me.
I walked upstairs. I was going to get something out of the bathroom upstairs and they're like three
guys there. She's something furniture we don't want. She's getting rid of all kinds of stuff. This is
really a big, a big life change that we're making here. Even the piano we're getting rid of that.
I granted no one has played on it for the past year and a half, but we're just really removing
a lot of the stuff that we don't need anymore. Okay, let's get everything rolling for today. I need
a song to kind of, you know, get the energy up and I figured nothing like the Spencer Davis group
to get your running. Give me some 11 on the daily source. Go!
One time we got a time to come up to the floor. Crazy people walking up the floor to the floor.
I mean, baby, I don't know what you got. Get your power to take it easy. Just run around.
So you have to make it. So you have to make it. You have to make it. You have to make it.
You have to. Give me some more. Give me some more. Give me some more.
Give me some more. Give me some more. Give me some more.
Give me some more. Give me some more. Give me some more. Give me some more.
Is it just me or do I remember that song being longer? There's not even three minutes.
Spencer Davis group. Give me some 11 here on the source code for Monday, October 18th, 2004.
I was just looking through my mail. I got some cool stuff I want you to hear.
And I have about 10 or 12 clips all lined up for you that I prepped over the weekend.
One of the things that I wanted to talk about. But I'm going to talk a little bit less than usual today.
Was about music licensing. That's something that came up that a lot of people have been talking about.
And hopefully we'll get a good discussion going at BloggerCon on November 6.
But of course, what's great about these podcasts is you don't have to use music.
You can use music that is independent music, which you can use royalty free.
There's actually now a indie music node in the directory at ipodder.org, which is just popped up.
What's so cool about that is the music node is already maintained by someone else.
And he's now delegating sub-directories of that.
So we're really rocking on the opml directory at ipodder.org.
But you can always leave it up to our buddy Pete from rasterweb to come up with exactly what you need when you're looking for royalty free music.
Welcome to the rasterweb.
So it's used up for 10-15 late in the evening.
You know, I realized that this podcast thing is pretty cool.
But I don't think there's a theme song yet.
I mean, I run this play in this music that they may or may not have the rights to.
But I got a song here and you can do it too long.
They mash it up, smash it up, delete it, play in the podcast.
I don't care. You're free to do it.
With it, what you will.
So there you go. Enjoy.
Podcast End.
Podcast End, baby.
Yeah. Yeah, baby.
A new entry with a bullet.
Okay, that's the podcast end song by me.
I own the rights and I'm giving it away so you can do it too long.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Rasterweb audio for that generous gift that you've given to the podcast and community.
Something new that we set up is the last 100 podcast.
You can get to it from the from the left hand menu on ipod.org.
And this is really phenomenal.
Anything that's listed in the directory automatically when there's a new podcast available.
It'll show up on this top one on this last 100 list.
And it shows up and they really trick this out.
I mean, it's just the beginning, but already I'm loving it so much.
You can click on it to download the show directly if you want.
You can subscribe the RSS link is there.
And if you mouse over the name of the show, it'll also give you all the comments that were attached to that podcast.
When it was put up on on the podcast feed.
So definitely check that out.
I mean, I've been laying in bed just listening to podcast after podcast.
Sitting here sweating away.
And it's weird, you know, because you drift off into sleep and you wake up again.
And I had my iPod just run in a continuous loop through everything.
So at one point I'm hearing Drew and Dawn and Drew talk about me.
And then I something called replay radio popped up.
I don't know where that came from.
I'm sure I subscribed to it somewhere.
And I could hear the third and final presidential debate.
It was, it was just an amazing experience.
But all these voices running through my head, man, is pretty trippy.
Hey Adam, I just wanted to respond to something you said on Thursday's podcast about Australian radio.
You said you thought Aussie must be starved for good radio,
and that you'd probably only be able to get reception in the cities.
But Australia has one of the coolest radio stations in the world called Triple J,
which is broadcast to about 95% of the country,
which is pretty damn impressive given the isolation of some parts of us.
It's a really excellent nationwide non-commercial music station,
which stays well clear of the top 40 generica.
When I moved to the UK a few years back, the loss of Triple J was seriously one of my major concerns.
It's just such a great station.
You can read all about it at www.abc.net.au slash TRIPLJ.
And you can listen to live streams, or download some archive shows,
including some episodes of the J files, which is a semi-regular biography on a particular band,
or artist, which would make a really cool podcast, actually.
Anyway, just wanted to set the record straight about Aussie radio there.
Something else while I've got you, as a concerned world citizen,
I've been watching the US election cycle with great anticipation,
and downloading the debate videos, but aren't because the broadcast here
was some stupid time in the morning.
I was wondering if you knew about the fact that the Guardian,
which is one of the UK's broadsheet newspapers,
is running a program where they're hooking up UK residents
with the residents of Ohio, one of the crucial undecided states.
So we can write to these guys and let them know all our concerns about Bush.
I'm kind of sketchy about whether you agree with it from a privacy or moral perspective,
sort of trying to influence their election this way,
but very interesting idea anyway.
You can check that one out at www.gardian.co.uk slash Clark County, or one word.
Okay, well, great job with the Daily Source Code.
By the way, what is the verb when you're recording a voice message like this?
I'm not rushing, I'm not emailing or calling.
What is it that I'm doing?
Okay, see ya.
That's a very good question.
What is it?
I thought this morning I was put casting instead of podcasting,
so I'm not sure what this is.
It's audio comment, I guess, that's the closest thing.
Interesting intel, though, about the Guardian's doing,
and also about Aussie radio.
I had no idea, and I apologize,
but still clearly not enough because there's so many podcasts coming out of Australia.
It's unreal.
And I also got something.
I haven't listened to this yet myself,
so we're going to witness this together for the first time.
I have a lot of buddies in the radio business in the States.
And one of my dearest old friends is Dave Fox.
He works for Clear Channel, actually.
And I've used him for a number of radio and television projects,
because he has the greatest voice you can imagine.
And so I sent him a brief note about podcasting,
and I just received an email with seven different files.
I'm only going to play one.
Let's just see what it winds up.
Let's see how this sounds.
Because I asked him to help me dress up the show a little bit with some sweepers and sounds.
podcasting, all's live, Adam Curry.
I hear this rumors on the internet.
Internet, internet.
Internet.
To be the old B.G.Y.A.A.
and as our neighborhood practice there,
they're loved with women all across this country.
Everyone wants to see their exaggerations.
Well Tony Flare were going along.
The truth of the matter is if you listen carefully,
said, I'm a stupid power if you were the President of the United States,
and the world would be a lot better off.
Not Tony Flare.
You cannot leave.
If you send me some messages.
I actually forgot my own.
I'm trying to solve all these bad things.
I'm trying to solve what he means at solving.
If you're a, you're a, you've been given a sovereignty and you're, you're a sovereign entity.
Well, don't you allow or go on along?
My enemies are innovative and resourceful.
And so are we.
They never stop thinking about new ways to harm our country and other people.
And either do we.
Feed people are not allowed to exercise the, the rights as human beings.
I cannot lead.
I, I, you cannot lead.
If you send an excellent, mixed messages.
This word dictates your ship.
It'd be a head of a lot easier.
Just so long as I'm addicted.
I hear this rumors on the, uh,
Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet, Internet.
There's been a whole saying in Tennessee.
I know it's in Texas, probably Tennessee, but there's a fool me wants.
Shame on you.
If fool me, can't get fool again.
Wow.
Another Bushism's, uh, found through the blog digger media feed.
And I have to say, uh, I think that if, uh, if we as a country elects a president,
who speaks of the Internet,
we got a serious problem.
Come on.
I mean, that, that wasn't just a mispronunciation.
He doesn't know what the fuck he's talking about.
All in the Internet.
Damn.
That's really bad.
Vote for John Kerry.
It's Adam Curry.
Adam Curry.
Wow.
And now, another audio comment.
An audio blog posting, a new show.
Out of Deutsch, minor-dumb and heron.
Their podcasting is reaching from country to country.
It is everywhere now.
It is a rage.
They're going crazy.
Come and see it.
I'm my friends.
With an podcast as Deutschlands.
So hello, everybody.
Welcome to my audio blog, uh, or podcast.
Whatever you think it's the right term for it.
This is my first English edition.
Maybe the last, um, just waiting for the feedback.
Um, first of all, the background music.
You hear it.
That's a DJ Machitos.
Uh, the album is called Happy Trends.
And it's from www.magnature.com.
So I just wanted to give you a little, uh, little preview of what's happening overseas.
Because we're not only in Australia.
Now we're podcasting from Germany as well.
If you go to the ipotter.org directory, you can go to languages.
And there's, uh, I think there's German, Italian.
And, uh, we actually have, uh, someone maintaining the German node now.
It's, uh, it's great.
And if you want to hear some really different music for sure, go and check out, uh,
uh, the, uh, the German directory on ipotter.org.
Okay.
I got to let you know that I'm working on something.
And I just, excuse me, I'm just going to check an email here for one second.
Um, here it is.
Let me see.
I deal with this Asian old friend.
So I think I just made it.
Right.
Okay.
It looks like I'm going to get John Stewart on the podcast.
Uh, working on it.
I think it's all kind of like buddy buddy stuff.
So I've put in a couple of calls.
And, and do you think John Stewart could be any hotter at the moment.
Certainly, uh, in the blogosphere.
Everybody's talking about his appearance on CNN.
If you haven't heard it, here's just a little bit where,
it's not funny.
You know, he's not trying to be funny.
And he's, and he's spanking these guys on crossfire.
And he's saying, you know, he's basically like, fuck you.
You guys are not doing your job.
What is wrong with you?
Well, I'm just saying there's no reason for you.
And you have this marvelous opportunity not to be the guy's butt boy.
To go ahead and be his butt boy.
Yes.
No.
I was absolutely his butt boy.
I was so far.
You would not believe what he ate two weeks ago.
You know, the interesting thing that I have.
You have a responsibility to the public discourse.
And you fail.
You fail.
I think.
You need to go to one.
The thing that I want to say is, when you have people on for just knee jerk,
reactionary talk.
Well, I thought you were going to be funny.
Come on.
Be funny.
No.
I'm not going to be your monkey.
What?
I want your show every day.
And it kills me.
I could tell you a lot about that.
It's so, oh, it's so painful to watch.
You know, because we need what you do.
This is such a great opportunity you have here to actually get politicians.
It's really just awesome.
Of their marketing and strategy.
Yeah.
You know, someone who watches your show and cannot take it anymore.
I just can't.
It's like they've dinner with you.
It must be excruciating.
Do you like lecture people like this?
When you come over their house and sit and lecture them.
You know, they're not doing the right thing that they're missing their opportunities
of fading their responsibilities.
If I think they are.
What?
I wouldn't want to eat with you, man.
That's horrible.
I know.
And you won't.
But the thing I want to get to.
You promised naked pictures of this.
Yeah, we did.
Let's get to those.
Why can't we just talk?
Please.
I beg of you guys.
I think you want to touch Crossfire.
We're going to take it quick.
We're going to hold that.
We've got commercials.
Please.
Next.
Stop.
In the rapid fire.
Please.
We hope.
Thank you.
And that.
If you haven't heard or seen the entire appearance of John Stuart,
Nate on CNN's Crossfire, definitely just Google it.
Because everyone has links to the audio and there's bit-torn to the video files.
And he really, really pointed some stuff out.
And the blogger's fear is just on fire.
Everyone's saying, yeah.
This is exactly what someone needed to say.
And maybe it's typical that that comes from a comedian.
Maybe it is.
Anyway, so looking forward to getting him on the source code in the coming week.
I'm going to put my calls in.
You never know.
Hi Adam.
My name is Mark.
And I'm sending in this comment to ask your opinion on something.
During one of your shows, I believe it was one of the trade secrets.
It was said that gosh, we're worried that if Bush were reelected,
North Korea would be the next domino to fall.
And we'd have a war against them that would involve nuclear weapons.
That sounds like a pretty good fear to me.
A pretty reasonable one.
My question is, what happens if Kerry is elected instead?
North Korea is still a threat?
Yes or no?
What do we do about that?
What do you think they'll do?
I'd love to hear your opinion.
Thanks for putting on a great show.
Thank you for your question, Mark.
Actually, he's another person I can get on the source code.
I'm sure he do it.
My uncle Donald Greg, who was a security advisor to Bush Senior when he was a vice president.
And yeah, exactly.
I come from an interesting background.
He is, for a number of years now, has been the chairman of the Korean Society.
I think it's a Korea Society, Korea Society.org.
Oh, let me just move my microphone on a little bit, so I don't sound so muffled.
And I've been talking to him.
I've also seen him on CNN a couple of times talking about North Korea and the talks that, well,
basically, the talks had just, you know, were broken off.
I think if we, when we elect John Kerry, that these talks can resume because really all the North Koreans want is respect.
That's, I think, all that it's about.
Particularly when the access of evil statement came out,
North Korea was listed right there on the access.
You know, that was a bad message.
I think that, and from everything that I've heard from my uncle, we can repair the relations.
It's just a matter of showing respect and showing it pretty damn soon.
So, what are we, man?
We're only like two weeks away from election.
It's heat no.
Okay, let's play a sappy song on the source code.
If you're sick, it'll make you feel better.
Or maybe even groovy.
The central part is Simon and Garfunkel on the source code.
We're only like two weeks away from election.
I, I feel a lower than am.
I got no beats to do, no promises to keep.
I'm devil and just hit, ready to sleep at the morning time.
Drubb js It's Meadows on me.
Life, I love you.
Uh, whoops. What happened there? Okay, let me see, was that the damn I totally sucks.
Oh man. Well, let's play it back up song then. God damn. So what you get from ripping shit off the internet, huh?
Let me buy that. Here's the clash.
Music
Nothing to call back to the faraway towns. Now war is declared.
I back will come down. Nothing to call into the unknown.
Come out of the cupboard. Your boys and girls. Nothing to call in.
Darling, I don't look that out
He beat a maniac, he's beating the task
Let me look, darling, see we ain't got no swing
Except for the rain
And the trenches thing
The ice is coming
The sun's over there
Melted out, expected
The weed is for live
And just stop on it
But I have no fear
Cause I'm done, it's out and I
Live by the river
To the imitation zone
To get it brought up
Because you're going alone
Nothing will call it
To the zombies of death
Quit holding out
And drawing out the breath
Nothing will call it
And I don't want a chance
But why we were talking
I saw you not in hell
Nothing will call it
See we ain't got no hide
Except for that one
But the yellow we are
The ice is coming
The sun's over there
And just stop on it
The weed is for live
But I have no fear
Cause I'm done, it's out and I
Live by the river
The ice is coming
The sun's over there
And just stop on it
The weed is for live
But I have no fear
Cause I'm done, it's out and I live
And I don't want a chance
But I have no fear
Cause I'm done, it's out and I live
And I don't want a chance
Cause I'm not a journalist, I live by the river
I get this, love me call it this, I was there too
And you know what they said, the stomach was too low
And I'm recalling at the top of the dial
And after all this, won't you give me a smile
I've never felt so much that I could like the night
That is curry
Hello, this is Kizzle, I run a site called HectorMedia.net
What this site does is I'm not just purely saying this to promote
My stuff and you don't want to promote their stuff
I've taken roughly 15, 20 shows, I don't know, I'm not really keeping track
They're audio and video that they relate to the hacking, phone freaking and geek scene
So you have all these shows in this one place, so you don't have to keep going to their websites
Now these guys have nothing to do with podcasts and they don't know anything about it
So I know I did this before I knew about podcasts as well
But it still applies to podcasts because what you can do is
You have a few podcasts and shows that kind of fit in your same genre
Let's say you have some people that do a show about fishing, you have three or four shows
Well, I'll come together, one little site have your own little community
Have your own forums and you can all kind of work together
And discuss, oh, you're going to have some so-called on-for-a-gast
Or you can come up with different show topics
And just kind of grow as your own little, have your own little club
Another thing you can do, and this is what I do with hacking media
As soon as I found out about podcasting, I said all my shows
And since when, every time someone posts a new episode on hacker media
It goes into an RSS feed
So I just put the encapsulation thing
And so now the whole entire RSS feed is a podcast
So instead of the hacker media feed being just one show
It's several shows, so it's more like a radio station
So if more people do that, I think it'd be the interesting direction for this to go
Instead of having to find all these individual shows, you find one good station
And I want to tune into the cooking
Exactly, exactly
This is something that Dave and I were talking about just last night
And thanks for the comment
And I think this is probably going to work with OPML files
I've seen, or I'm seeing more and more aggregators working with OPML files
For a reading list or a subscription list
Where you can actually just drag and drop an OPML file
Or import an OPML file to get all your subscriptions that are in an OPML file
And although I think there's only one or two that actually do drag and drop
Probably net news wire and Jager, Jager does a drag and drop
But I've seen lots of different aggregators support that
And I think that this is where we're going to go
You're right with radio stations
I think that we're working on ways to integrate this
Into iPotter.org, but I'm pretty sure that if you have a
Well, if you're maintaining a node, you're maintaining an OPML directory file
Which is an outline when each line in the outline points to a podcast
That indeed could be seen as a station
A station that maybe it's all maybe all the podcasts
Or about one particular topic, but it could also be just people that are talking back and forth
For instance, if I were going to create a station, I'd put morning coffee notes in there
I'd put the dawn and drew show in there
I'd put maybe one or two IT conversations
Maybe the Gilmour gang and that would be deemed as a station
You can subscribe to an entire station instead of just individual shows
And of course you can make your own station by also creating an OPML file
If you want to know more about OPML, go to the iPotter directory at iPotter.org
Go to the Contribute folder
And in there there's information about OPML, how you can create OPML files
And what applications will help you do that
Adam
Brian wanted me to give you some big ups to you for playing my clip of the debate
The other day on daily source code
You don't mad
Yeah, you don't mind
I was actually the AT&T demo we found out later that Brian put on his podcast
I think was his portalette podcast when he did all the
All the synthesized voices
Very cool
Unfortunately, you can't quite put a whole audio book yet into their test form
But it does work and you can select different voices and we're really getting to good places with this audio stuff
With the text the speech synthesis
Hey Adam, how you doing?
I'm doing good, thank you
Name is Jimmy Jet
I wanted to let you know
I've got a podcast up at jimmyjet.com
That's jet with two teas
Also, I kind of stole an idea from Chris Perillo
I'm using Skype, though, to record voicemail
I didn't know if you are aware
But there is a voicemail program that works with Skype
It's called replay telequarter
It's from applying technologies at their website
Applying Technologies.com
It's in beta
But it's not bad
It's got a few bugs
But it works pretty well
So people can Skype, Jimmy Jet
And leave me a voicemail message
And then here it back on the podcast
So there you go, have a great day
And good luck with all the bandwidth problems
Okay, well, thanks Jimmy
Bandwidth problems are more or less solved
Now it's the physical problems that are happening
We're 31 minutes into this show
I think that's just about it
I do want to say that I wish that Skype
And I believe I found out that the development of Skype is being done
I think in India
Or maybe another far east country
I've been trying to get a hold of anyone
who's working on the macOS X version of Skype
Because it's so close to exactly what I need
The only thing that it seems like it should be reasonably trivial
Is we need to be able to select which audio device we want to use
When using Skype on OS on OS 10
Because then I can route the audio around
And I can make phone calls and record those
So if anyone knows anything about
The Skype development team
For Mac, please let me know
Because it's such a small thing that they have to put in
And it's already kind of I think that all these pieces are already available
It works that way with the X10 light phone
It works that way with iChat AV
Just need to get that thing done
And of course I'd love to have the voicemail feature
But that seems like it's Windows only
Alright, I'll tell you what
I'm going to close up the show for today
I'm sure everything will be much better by tomorrow
Certainly I hope to be over this chill
Or flu or bug or whatever it is
And I appreciate your tune
Hey podcasting
All's live
Adam Curry
And that's it
For the source code from Monday
October
Sorry if it was a little less than you might have expected
But damn
I'm still standing
Hey, as always you want to leave a comment
It's Adam and Curry dot com or my weblaw
Live dot curry dot com
And of course all the archives of the source code
On daily source code dot com
Alright, I'm going to go have some tea
And I'm back to bed
I'll see you tomorrow everybody