Hey everybody it's source code for August 19th 2004 I'm out of
today from Korea Castle in Belgium and it's a little bit later than usual. I guess maybe
it's starting to become the norm now. I was late last night as well. It's 10 o'clock
in the evening and I'm telling you until I get to the end of these radio shows, I'm
not going to be able to get this source code up on a daily basis before 8 o'clock in the
morning east coast to US time. Hopefully after that though, we'll be, we'll
be better on the timing. Okay, just switch a few things around here on my screen. A couple
of things I want to talk about today. First of all, you know I've been winding down my
year long 10 year of doing the morning show for Radio Veronica here in the Netherlands.
And so, you know, near the end and last week, well, next week we'll have, it'll be our last
week and then there's Monday and Tuesday because actually my last show is on the 31st.
So we've got all kinds of great guest book and today we have
had the Leofond de Chote, famous disc jockey from Tholm,
30 years ago, he was on the pirate ships,
which were operating on the North Sea.
He ever heard the story behind that, it's great.
Now, I have to look up the history
of the pirate radio broadcast ships,
radio caroline, radio Veronica, radio and what sea
international, it was a crazy time.
And he was one of the pirate disc jockeys
on one of those ships on the international waters
in the North Sea.
And now he is the program director,
or the, yeah, he's the guy that's responsible
for the entire programming on three
of the top commercial television stations.
And it was really, you know, it was very intense
to do a show with, so I've also worked with him.
He directed a live show that I did called Countdown,
which was a new bass show.
We had live guests and we had people performing
and videos and we did that for, you know,
the whole season.
So we worked very intently together
and we've had our ups and downs.
But it's always a really intense,
concentrate when you're doing it to you with someone like that, maybe a little bit more
than normal.
And I wasn't feeling too hot today.
So I was pretty wiped out after the show.
Had to go up to the flat screen factory that I have a stake in called GrandmasterView.
If you, you know, you should look it up, www.GrandmasterView.com.
It's pretty cool that we have humongous flat screens at unbelievably low prices.
So in the, I got home and just slept until like six or six, thirty and had dinner and
now we're just kind of hanging out and about ready to go back to bed.
Such is the life of the morning.
This kajake.
And you can tell I'm a disc jockey because I have all the lore as well.
Now about audio blogging, I picked up a pretty cool post yesterday from Harold Gilchrist.
And once in a second, let me see what the URL of his website is.
I have to find that and put a link to it.
it because radio.weblogs.com website. But if you just Google it Harold Gilchrist, that's
a G-I-L-C-H-R-I-S-T. And he posted some interesting thoughts in his own audio blog about, well,
what he calls the rise of audio enclosure blogging. Of course, that tickled me and I
can just bring my mixer back to the front here. I'm going to play a little bit, a snippet.
Listen to what he's saying. There's a couple of things in there that I like that he said.
Check it out. This is Harold Gilchrist and whereas I call this source code, the daily source code,
if you will. Another audio blogging example, which actually I took example who is Dave Weiner's
morning coffee notes. And Harold calls his audio blogs poolside.
Anyway, but there's a lot of new audio ging.
big out there in a blog as fair. I usually call the blog oddspare. And that's good. That's
good news. So let's back up a second. I said it's the rise of the RSS enclosure audio
blogger. And again, this is just something I'll remember, but it seems that if you look
at the RSS feeds of Adam and Dave, and I believe now Doug Kay is doing it for Callie,
let these audio posts are accompanied by MP3s in the feeds. And developers like Adam Perry
or writing scripts to take advantage of that being there. So follow this as good news. As
an observer of audio blogging, this is very healthy. And I look forward to the, did the
lip in the audio blogging attention, get greater. And I've been seeing it happen now.
Okay.
That's
Some nice words there from Harold
About audio blogging
I don't know what Harold does. I gather from his post maybe he's a consultant or
He said it's his job to pay attention to what's going on in the blogosphere, so
Something that one part that I really like there is that he said that developers like Adam Curry. I'm like oh, yes
Finally I'm starting to graduate into the developer sphere
And I wanted to stop and talk about that for just a second because I've created this thing called iPod
Which more people are using than I then I anticipated
Because now of course I'm getting support questions and all kinds of stuff that comes along with developing something
My intention with iPod was to create something that unfortunately I can only do it for the Mac because that's all I have and that's the only thing I know how to
program or develop on or
integrate systems on
Is
That if you subscribe to an RSS feed that has mp3
closures like Harold explained that it will automatically show up on your iPod, really
making your iPod an aggregate.
And the intent behind it was just to prove the concept, show it says what I want it to
be, this is how I want it to work and hopefully other people will catch on to it and with a
little bit of luck developers will start to make the same functionality hopefully better
in cross-platform development environments.
Steve Garfield who is a video blogger, well he caught me on one of the, probably the Achilles
heel of the iPod or application.
Steve said, hey it's funny, I removed all this content, didn't want from the iPod or
folder and it came back magically.
So there it is, I built an application that doesn't really have a database.
So it dollars I guess it parks the file system and uses that as a database.
enclosures are still in the active RSS feed, it's going to want to suck those in.
So if you have something like, see if you have a feed that doesn't update very often,
take IT conversations for instance.
There's probably 15 shows in their feed and one is added every other day or every three
days.
So if you remove five or six of those files, only one of them or two of them won't come
back.
On the contrary, this is another observation I had.
If you have something like scripting news and Dave posts an MP3 in his enclosure, if
you don't, if your script isn't running often enough, Dave will out post your aggregator
and that posting will actually drop off the edge of the RSS file and you'll miss it.
So all kinds of things to be considered there when it comes to updating.
Of course this is because we're not, we're, we're not using or it's difficult to use
uh, pings effectively because of course
what you want is you want to be notified that something's updated and updated accordingly
and not necessarily pull the whole time.
But that's a whole other discussion.
So anyway, check out SteveBarfield.com.
He blogged the Democratic National Convention.
He's really funny.
I like the way he did it and I can see he's learning his video skills very, very quickly.
I think guess he's doing most of it on Final Cut Pro and the iMovie, but it's good stuff.
And once we figure out how we use enclosures with audio, which I think is a lot easier
to do, I know is a lot easier to develop for just because of the sheer size of the files,
I think we'll be able to apply a lot of this to the video blogging.
Which really, in my mind, if we say blogging in the context of audio or video blogging,
it's audio and video distribution.
And BitTorrent is a major part of that and I hope to start testing with that in the audio
realm pretty soon.
Um
Okay, hope you can still stand this sound of the crappy microphone.
Luckily, when I turn the mic off, it doesn't crap out, and I'm going to do so with a song.
And I've been thinking, I don't really have a theme for what I played the song of the day sounds, you know, it's like so typical.
But maybe today, I'll just be honest about it.
I'm really in the mood for something really hokey, you know, a 70s hokey song of the day,
Because we're For Shout-O-Pro Nelly for Tahoe, Jewel, or...
The 70s. This is Ricky Lee Jones. It's Chuck and Ben Love.
♪ How come you don't come ♪
♪ Yeah, feelin' me ♪
♪ That is a meaner ♪
Come on, come on, you turn it off TV
And head that side on the go away
Come, here we go, come, come, today
Hey, you walk on, make a boy
Hey, you look the way
Yeah, yeah
Later, roll up the line, and then I'll just let me tell
You don't understand what it talks, it's true, it's true
You show it's a quiet, it's gotta be cool
Let's buy some jam, let it go
Well, then you can't get it, look too cute
Hey, you look the way
This is healthy, it's so kinda pinky
Love
Chucky in the love
I don't believe what you say to me
This is solid
I've got that
I look in the pool, how is it here?
I look in the blood stall, what is it here?
No, don't come here no more
No.
I saw you, you silly, you had those down at the fair and say it is Halloween, but it's got uphill, I'm asleep, I hope.
That's it, man. That's it. I'm crazy. I think it's your coldiness, yeah. Is that hurt? What's the name?
♪ I'm gonna be the same as ♪
I'm doing the most of my life.
We're gonna take the most in love.
We're gonna take the most in love,
I'm doing the most of my life.
We're gonna take the most in love.
and get to sleep in Saturday and Sunday. It's gonna be really busy week next week.
Since Patricia and I announced that we're moving to the United Kingdom,
the press of force wants to have the story, so we're doing all kinds of interviews and TV shows next week.
I'm gonna fit some flying in, all kinds of stuff going on.
And of course, early to rise for the radio show.
And I'll be back tomorrow with a wrap up of the week.
Thanks for listening. Oh, I have to remember.
If you have any comments, my email is adam at curry.com, C-U-R-R-Y,
my website, live. curry.com.
And if you're listening to this through your aggregator, thank you very much for subscribing.
And talk to you tomorrow. Bye.