It's Wednesday.
It's the source code and good afternoon.
And as you can tell I still haven't fixed my crappy mic problems
Second or my feedback problems or just a number of technical difficulties
I'm an Amsterdam right now and hold on now. I have five wires intertwined
Hold on headphones and microphone cables
I'm at the Amsterdam house which we affectionately called the bunker because well, it's built like a bunker
I guess in fact these houses in Amsterdam we have one on the canal on the Kuytrosfer which is the emperors canal
When when they catch fire if they catch fire they never burn down
They burn out is what they say what they say in other words the structure always remains just the shit on the inside will
leave these things are built like
bunkers
And I had to stay in Amsterdam because of course have been away for two weeks been on vacation hadn't been here and we have
Patricia's cosmetics company here. I always want to check up on them and my assistant Chris
She keeps her office here. So hung out with the girls.
I just went through the latest stuff, signing stuff, whatever.
And I had dinner with my banker, which is always fun.
If you're in good standing with your bank, that is Thardy is her name.
And if you're looking to invest your money in the Benelux, let me know.
Let me know, here you'll be more than happy to take care of that for you.
And all other private banking services needed.
That was nice. It was a great evening.
It was about 70 degrees.
And it was just the city. It was beautiful.
So nice warm summer evening. Good food.
Nice wine.
Hanging out.
Talkable friends who drop by May or may not know Rodrigo Otazu.
He makes jewelry for great necklaces.
Jennifer Aniston's Wornam.
Beyonce. J-Lo. Madonna.
and my wife. He lives in Amsterdam. I believe he's from Argentina originally. So anyway,
so I'm going to stay here this evening, which is kind of cool because it gives me an extra
hour of sleep since Amsterdam is much closer to the studio than Belgium. So I don't have
to get up until, oh man, 430, can't believe it. Oh, and there was something really nice
that I wanted to talk about. See, maybe five or six weeks ago, a friend of mine called
an acid. You could use the Amsterdam house as a set for, there was something, I don't
know if it was a new gadget show or a commercial or an infomercial. I'm not quite sure what
it was. So I said, yeah, no problem. And so they did the shoot. I wasn't here. Crystal
was, of course, my assistant. And today she said, you know, these guys, they said that
they're going to pick this up, but they haven't picked it up. And I figured it's been long
enough. You might as well just take this upstairs and go play with it. And she clearly knows
me quite well. It is the
Pinnacle Systems Show Center.
And I don't know if you've ever heard of this.
I haven't even looked at the website yet, but essentially it's a box that looks...
Well, it has about the dimensions of a DVD player, really thin new DVD player.
Four lights on the front, that's all.
It's just one brush metal look front, one with a power switch and there's a power light.
A new media light, oh-ho.
And something in the middle that does not have a description, so I'm not quite sure what that does.
But essentially this box has a Wi-Fi card built in and it knows how to listen to a streaming server.
And we'll display that with a nice menuing system on your television.
So this is really something that I'm interested in, well more for the experience than technology.
Because technology is probably crap and we'll find out about that as I get into it probably this weekend.
Just with the experience of having BitTorrent download automatically and
And then I guess the way this works is you can set it up.
So if you drop new content into a specified folder on a PC, which of course needs to be
connected to your home network as well, then this box will recognize it and the new media
light will flash and then you can get into the menuing system.
You can play the new content.
So this would be great for the American TV shows that I record and then just much better
interface.
Although I do have my doubts, first of all, I need a PC to make this work because it needs
to start up a database which manages your content and a streaming server to send the
content from PC over the home network to the show center media player.
So okay, problem one is a PC.
I actually just loaded the software on my virtual PC on my Mac.
It appears to work, but I really have to go to bed pretty soon, so I won't be able to
play with that tonight.
uh...
but I'll have to get a dedicated PC setup for that.
So that's problem one.
And then of course, the streaming server business, you know, what exactly is it?
Is it media streaming?
Is it windows, media, windows, media streaming server?
Is it a proprietary streaming server?
That's all very unclear, but it does play.
Divx, exvid, MPEG 1 and 2 and MP3.
So that should work.
So I'm pretty excited about that.
I'm going to play without this weekend, get it installed.
And I will certainly report back on that.
OK, let me slip the headphones on for a second because every source code
needs an inspirational moment of the day, which means we're going to play some tunes.
And I've got something selected for you from the voice.
Ella Fitzgerald.
Thanks for watching.
♪ I'm not a slave when you fall ♪
But where? One day?
♪ And my life ♪
Not as he passed, but when but more you lose your shit.
Thanks for watching!
Oh
♪ No, I just be a girl ♪
But when you're not wondering...
Go guys, have a good one.
Good way. What's wrong? He missed me.
But when I saw it, it was all about the world, same one you see.
Then run you thinkin'
♪ When you see me ♪
I don't care what you say.
She has one of the classic voices.
Ella Fitzgerald on the source code for today.
And before I go, I just wanted to wrap up by mentioning the audiobook that I've been
listening to, timeline by Michael Priton, the unabridged version, which I bought from
through audible.com.
Fabulous book.
Absolutely amazing.
I'm so enthralled in this thing.
And the audiobook version is just phenomenal.
Speaker is so good.
I've not mentioned it before.
It does the accent so well.
And the story is plausible, man.
I'm not into dragons and dungeons and medieval times, et cetera.
And the story does take you there through quantum travel.
But wow, what an excellent book.
I totally recommend it.
And I was actually wondering about that.
What if I decided, well, I really like this book so much, I'm going to put it on an RSS
feed for distribution.
And here's the question.
Of course you won't be able to...
play it since it's an AAC file that AAC or AAC whatever Apple's DRM stuff is. So you won't be able
to play it but is there an interface that if I give you that file I give you this audio file
that you can then purchase it wouldn't that be great if you fired it up and iTunes and iTunes
said oh I see you want to play this but it's registered to Adam Curry would you like to buy it
and just click yes and the purchase is done. Now that would make a lot of sense. I wonder if
they've got it set up that way I doubt it. Food for thought at least and I'm going to end the source
code today with that thought. Not much blogging time today so I'll have to catch up tomorrow
and look forward to it. So have yourself a great day, what's rest of it or a great evening or wherever
you are. Kindness yeah it's so different everywhere. I'll definitely be on tomorrow so take care
everybody and I'll see you. Bye-bye.