On Pakistani, it's Adam Curry.
Baekhyunan!
Yeah, I want to stimulate you right now I have everybody welcome to the daily store's code
Yeah, Christmas officially over 27th of December 2004 welcome to your daily source code
where users and developers attempt to party together and sometimes we actually do some kind of awkward dance
that looks a little bit like it I guess. How you doing?
I got to say I am doing fantastic today. Everything would be absolutely perfect. I mean we've got
Beautiful sunshine outside here outside the cottage. It's snow just a little bit last night
So everything is blanketed and nice little sheet of white. If only we hadn't lost
20,000 people in Asia with the tsunamis then my day would be absolutely perfect man does that shit suck all what
Mother earth you can't beat her the beots will get you down every single time
And what's perhaps? Of course it's always like that you know if you've ever been to
Junior York and you went to the world trade towers before September 11th
Then you have the same feeling that many many people have all been to
Sri Lanka the Maldees I've been to Thailand did all documentary in fact and was along the entire coastline
Where people just swept away and what what's really quite frightening about and I wasn't even going to talk about this really
But what's what's a frightening about it is
It went from like a couple hundred to a thousand to two thousand to four thousand to six thousand and it seems like this
Just like it's so enormous that we have and it could be 30,000 people for all I know this morning
CNN was reporting 20,000 people dead
Unbelievable
This will lift up your spirits a little bit a little bit of the
University of Southern California marching back a cadence on the source code. Oh my gosh. Who would have thought it?
Actually, this was sent to me by
Aaron Tadas who has lots of questions about podcasting and of course all of the
emails the links
Everything but the actual MP3s themselves to the
The promos into the songs that we play on the daily source code
are all listed in the production show notes which are posted along with the daily source code on
www.curry.com
Working on this stuff though. I've been
emailing back and forth with Dave
We've been talking on the phone
Getting pretty close to actually starting some work on on getting a
podcast production system put together and the way we're doing this. I'm so incredibly excited about because
Basically Dave is is programming just for me and only for me
And then from there we'll go figure out if other people are going to be able to use this or not so I'm really really excited
About the work that we're doing and
Yeah, just to you know getting some stuff moving forward and this is all pre-art January meeting
I mean we still have a whole week before I actually we're before we're scheduled to meet up in Miami. So very cool
So the in-laws are leaving today
They were here for the past 10 days of course a major portion of that. I was in I was in Holland
By the way the opening today I just want to play the
I'll play the the opening bit of that because it was such a beautiful such a beautiful
Song with the power of pure intellect sung and acoustic with the guitar
Just want to let you hear a few words from the from the maker of that wonderful promo
Hi Adam. This is Stefan. I'm sorry to have missed you at the Sarasani coffee shop
All right, so that's
This is a source code listener from Utrecht
Who we tried to hook up at a different coffee shop in in Utrecht, but it just didn't work out with
Traveling to the hospital in my mom and doing other stuff, but
Oh next time I'm sure I left you know it's just in case you were
We're going to be there and
And well then you would at least know that I've been there as well. I left you in my party boy
The owner taught actually thank me a lot for making my compliments to you about this place because it's the oldest oldest coffee shop in the world
Huh, maybe this is the oldest coffee shop in the world
Perhaps the oldest coffee shop that's spelled that sells marijuana in the world
I think I've been to older coffee shops in Iraq
What did you consider part where the and as a thank you
I'd like to give you a demonstration of what this great quality weed here can do for your inspiration
Okay, so this is what the great quality weed at the the oldest coffee shop in the world can do for your inspiration
Actually, thank you very very very very much. Hey Adam. This is Garic Van Geron from the first crack podcast
Garic Van Geron dot com slash first crack
As you can hear in the background we are roasting up some beans for tomorrow's coffee
I wanted to wish you a happy holidays and hope you that you've received the gift of bandwidth
This holiday season
Here's a quick snippet of what some people are saying about the first crack podcast
That's completely not about coffee
That was band-tash from first crack episode number 14 where we talked about his site all right
Wraydard.com
One last thing over at garyconvian.com slash first crack you can pick up your iPod cast buttons and show the world that you've turned your domain
into a radio station in your ear into a voice that's all and
Have a great show and have a great 2005 and we'll talk to you guys later. Bye
Excellent. Thank you, Garic. Garic Van Geron turn your was it turn your domain into a
Radio station and your ear into a voice. Not bad like that
It seems that
The living room in New York City which is a venue
That we first were introduced to on the source code when the lascivious bitties did their show there and I think
For daily source code listener showed up which is I don't have big the living room is I have a feeling it's pretty small
But I'm quite proud of anyone showing about the lascivious bitties show based upon my recommendation
An email from Craig Patchett says hey Adam living room in New York City seems to be the venue for daily source code artists
Barry Correll who we've played on the show before will be performing there on Thursday, January
6 and Craig of course is from the godcast and I don't have a lot of music queueed up for for you today
But I'm sure we've playing some Barry in in the future right here on the daily source code something else that's coming that a couple of people have mentioned
About the sample rate of the shows that I release now. I was pretty sure that I'm doing these recordings on
44 kilohertz sample rates
Apparently the daily source code is coming through in 24 kilohertz sample rates and a number of
Predominantly portable devices like the palm t3 and I've heard
I've heard there was some other device maybe the trio as well not too sure about that
Only supports 22 or 44 and not 24 kilohertz
So I'm gonna have to go through my entire chain in fact
I'm looking at this right now and I hope that you saw the the beautiful work that was done on
Creating the image of of my podcast setup
And I'm looking at this right now if I
I guess I can't look at that yet. I'm recording at 16 bit stereo 44.1 kilohertz
I don't understand how can I be coming through it 24.1 if I'm recording it
At 44.1. Well if anyone out there has any ideas, please let me know because we don't want to leave our
Certainly don't want to leave our our mobile
Daily source code listeners out in the cold
By not being able to receive it because it comes through as 24 kilohertz it could all maybe
Maybe lane brain for some reason that's what I used to post compressed every show because I basically recorded to AIFF
And then I post compressed with a program called lane brain hold on let's take a look and see what the settings of lane brain are right now
Can I do this while I'm while I'm running
Boy, it's getting real slow
You know one of these days I am going to treat myself to a brand new computer maybe a honk in G5 or something
It would just it'll only be a podcast machine wouldn't that be awesome
Okay, I'm just going to open up this this lane brain application hope everything will work
Work okay, and it won't start to skip on the audio. Let me just see what the settings are
Meanwhile is anything I can play for you
oops, I'm on why don't I yeah, well, that's loading up. We'll play this for you
Yeah, I'm it's Patrick Carney from over at
www.pjk.net. I do my own podcast called the pjk podcast
Anyway, I wanted to let you know I just did a show on emergency technology and it was based on my own
Emergency over Christmas Eve where my apartment caught on fire and had to get my daughter out and what kind of tech did I grab and that kind of thing
And it also you know got me thinking especially after seeing this huge earthquake
In the news and all the devastation in
Thousands and thousands of people killed because of that
Started making me think about back up plans and things in the event of a real emergency
Whether it's natural or or man made anyway, so I go through some of those thoughts on my podcast
And just thought I'd point you to it. Anyway, I hope you have a Merry Christmas happy new year and
You know keep on podcast, man. It sounds great. I love your show
Hey Patrick. Thank you very much and I definitely will check that out because man
Think about what kind of an emergency Jesus Christ if you have your apartment caught on fire
Over the over Christmas and you had to get your daughter out and what kind of tech to you actually want to say
Oh shit
That's the stuff nightmares are made of my friend. I'm looking at a
Lame brain and it doesn't seem to have any
Any other preferences for
For the actual recording
Frequency or bit rate. I you know, I can't find it if you have any ideas. Let me know please
Okay, oh, yeah, by the way, looking at today
I really really need to fly. I am just itching to fly. Here's the deal
I haven't flown for what is it six weeks now
Now, it's not true because I flew over here with the Navajo
So it's been five weeks we've been here for five weeks. I need to fly and I'm not even talking about helicopters
I'd love to get in a helicopter and you know fly around for a little bit and I'll probably just schedule something with someone nearby
But what I'm looking for really and if anyone out there is a pilot and I'm sure some of you are
I'm looking for some advice for a great instructor
Someone who can help me with fixed wing because I have my helicopter ppl rating
You know, so
Basically with an FAA private pilot's license. It's an add-on. You have to do a minimum of I don't know what is it?
Well really in all fairness. I should I should do at least 40 or 50 hours on fixed wing before I can
Really do the test although I'm sure that with 10 or 20 hours I'll be able to pass the test of course
I won't know what you know shit about flying airplanes really
So I'm looking for someone who can help me get the FAA
PPL add-on to my license
I'm right near black bush. I'm not too far from farm borough. If anyone has any ideas
Just you know someone who can do
Instruction on either regular basis or maybe will do four days in a row
And I'm looking for at least the Cessna 172 152 is a little bit too small for me
So 172 I just need to get this done and just I need to fly because it's such a you could
The airplanes go over or close by our house all the time and every single time
I'm like oh yeah, I need to fly. I need to fly. I really really need to fly somewhere around
Second week of January. I want to get started on this so if you're if you have any ideas
Any thoughts of great instructors because that's what it comes down to it's not really the flight school
Although I know there's a flight school of black bush airport which does FAA ratings
I just need to fly. I need to learn to fly. I can get my license and in Florida
I need someone to teach me how to fly. Please teach me how to fly and as I was
Sitting on that humongous fat pipe in in Utrecht while I was with my mom who was doing excellent by the way
She's she's walking she walked down to the Christmas tree the other day and I think either tomorrow or the day after
We hear about you know when she potentially can actually leave the hospital and we're very excited about that because things are going so incredibly well
So I was sitting on that big fat pipe and there were a couple of audible
Audio books that I had downloaded previously and then I or that I hadn't
Downloaded that I needed to download because I really wanted to listen to it and I had to had
Downloaded George Carlin's brain droppings previously, but I guess I'd wipe that off my drive and then the great thing about
Autable.com is that you had this entire library so you can just read download anything you've already purchased previously
And I wanted to play this lovely bit. It's it's probably a couple minutes long about three or four minutes
The George car and in this man needs to podcast and he would be the perfect
Person for a weekly or God forbid a daily podcast and it could be short it could be sweet and if I ever run into him
I'm gonna strap him down and make him do one
Here George Carlin talks about the United States not having a present
You know what America lacks a
Present America has no now
We're reluctant to acknowledge the present. I guess it's too embarrassing
Instead we reach into the past our culture is composed of sequels reruns
Remix revivals reissues re-releases recreations reenactments
Adaptations anniversary's memorabilia oldies radio and nostalgia record collections
World war two has been refought on television so many times
The Germans and Japanese are now drawing residuals
Of course being essentially full of shit we sometimes feel the need to dress up this past preoccupation as with
Pathetic references to reruns as on core presentations
Even instant replay is a form of token nostalgia a brief visit to the immediate past for re-examination
Before slapping an onto a highlight video for further review and re-review on into the indefinite future
This yes-termania of ours includes fantasy baseball camps where aging sad-sax paid money to catch baseballs thrown by men who are once their heroes
It's part of the fascination with sports memorabilia a memory industry and it's so lucrative
It is attracted counterfeiters
In this case the age of hyphens
We are truly retro Americans and our television newscasts not only reflect this condition they feed it
Everything they report is twisted into some reference to the past
If there's going to be a summit meeting you'll be told all about the last six summit meetings
If there's a big earthquake they'll do a story about big earthquakes of the past
If there's a mind disaster you'll hear about every mind disaster since the inception of mining
They're obsessed with looking back. I swear. I actually heard this next thing during a newscast
As the anchor man went to a commercial break. He said still ahead a look back
Honest he said it
Hurricane Hugo one year later. Why?
The anniversary of the exonvaldees oil spill for what reason?
The anniversary of the Bay of Pigs pan Amphlite 103 the hostages in Iran the fall of the Berlin wall
V. J. Dave E. Dave yet none who gives a fuck
Bugs bunny's 50th birthday lasties 55th the gold in Jubilee of gone with the wind the start of the Korean war
Barbies celebrates her 35th the 25th anniversary of the New York blackout
Bambi turns 50 should I didn't even like Bambi when I was supposed to how much do I care now
There's really no harm I guess in reviewing the past from time to time knowing where you've been
This part of knowing where you are and all that happy horse shit
But the American media have an absolute fixation on this they rob us of the present by insisting on the past
If they were able I'm sure they would pay equal attention to the future trouble is they don't have any fell on it
And so on television news there is oddly very little emphasis on the present on today's actual news
The present exists only in 30 second stories built around eight second sound bites
Remember sound bite is their phrase that's if they give you just a bite no chewing no digestion no nourishment
Malnutrition
Another way they avoid the present moment is to look ahead on their own schedules
The television news industry seems to revolve around what's coming next
Still to come just ahead up next coming up this half hour more to come stay with us still ahead also later
They even preview what's going to happen as little as one hour later
During the five o'clock news the empty headed prick who does the five o'clock news will suddenly say
Here's a look at what's coming up on the six o'clock news
Then the empty headed prick who does the six o'clock news will appear in shirts leaves in the newsroom to create the illusion of actual work
And tell you about several stories that the empty headed prick who does the five o'clock news should already have told you about if you were really a newsman
And so it goes around the clock
On the five o'clock news to tell you about the six o'clock news at six o'clock they tell you about eleven at eleven
They plug the morning news the morning man promos the noon time lady and sure enough a little later after noon
Here comes that empty headed prick from the five o'clock news to tell you what he's gonna do on the five o'clock news
You know if a guy were paranoid
He might not be blamed for thinking that the people who run things don't want you dwelling too much on the present
Because keep in mind the news media are not independent
They're a sort of bulletin board and public relations firm for the ruling class the people who run things
Those who decide what news you will or will not hear are paid by and tolerated purely at the whim of those who hold
Economic power if the parent corporation doesn't want you to know something it won't be on the news
period
Or at the very least it will be slanted to suit them and then barely followed up
Enjoy your snooze folks
Ha ha ha
George Carlin the man rocks he rocks you rock so
The reason I played that is first of all there must be a lot of recognition in there
Even the stuff that he said about a major earthquake. Oh, we're seeing that right now and take a look at what's happening now
that we've gotten past the initial
Footage we're gonna start doing statistics, but
It's true the media
Is yeah is not giving you the story. It's only giving you the story that they want you to have that the big corporations
Want you to have this is what we're trying to get away from in podcasting. That's why I yeah
I play that for you
What we're trying to get closer to is people helping each other out with a god damn microphones
Tip for anyone looking for a microphone still
There's a deal over at target for a member x m k a three zero one. Oh wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Surely you mean
Tarji
It's old over next to the karaoke equipment
There's also a wireless model available for anyone who needs a little more mobility
Although this one seems to have a very long cord. It's about 10 feet long
Has an XLR jack on the one end and the quarter inch jack on the other end
So you'll probably need the adapter for most PCs which they also conveniently sell
Anyways, I want to also say thanks for the show and
Appreciate all that you're doing and thanks very much
Oh, man, I'm not doing anything. I'm just having a good all-time
Happened some fun. What are we? We're about 21 minutes into the show good because I have a couple more things
I want to play for you. I've received a whole bunch of cool audio comments and and emails over the
Over the Christmas weekend and something that I just reached back to once in a while is the agricast
It's listed on the iPutter.org directory under agriculture
And the agricast is an actual business model. There's a real case here
This is really working. This is a podcast
For the agricultural industry and from time to time I just want to just want to play this because you know that someone is out there thinking
How can you start a business what what what kind of really do with podcasting?
Well, it's just like web logs, man. It's just like it in this case. Now let's listen to the agricast
Welcome to another subject county extension agricast with extension agagent Gary Cramer today
We're going by telephone the Gary's home where he's recuperating from leg surgery. We join Gary now
By the way, that's odd. Hi, this is Gary Cramer an agricast. Here it is. It's December the 23rd
And it is extremely frigid outside and you know it it happens every year
That we've got some acres of wheat ground that don't get planted don't get worked for one raisin or another
And we'll occasionally get questions about how late is too late to plant wheat
So this whole this whole cast
Podcast goes on about planting wheat. Now of course personally I'd like to know
Instead of planting wheat, you know, how should we plant marijuana how could we harvest it? You know what I do
We've already been through that experiment didn't work too well
But I just love hearing the this professional use of of podcasting and
And look so the guys recuperating from leg surgery no problem dilemma get them on the phone
This is what podcasting is is partially at least about this is great. This is disseminating information
We've got the tools that before only the professionals had
Speaking of tools
I've been talking about this OPML
Application which of course is actually the open source
Release of frontier
That's at
What's the link to that
Well, there's a there's a group there's a Yahoo group and that's of course it's all listed in the production show notes for today
What am I thinking
Steve ran into a little bit of trouble Steve Holden as for some reason whenever he tried to open up an OPML file that I'm now
Posting along with the source code it wouldn't open up properly
Actually I saw later that he in the comments that he did fix this just let you know that there's there's something coming with this OPML stuff and if you
if you feel like
downloading the
It may be a little bit early actually to do that, but pretty soon. I think that it's going to be
Really simple to create your podcast using using an outline and also to flow stuff in from other shows
You know you could get stuff from my outline and I don't know
We're still all over the map on this but getting pretty close to some very interesting stuff and
I don't know what I was gonna say
I'm so full of shit sometimes
Tell you what so is this guy?
Hi Adam. This is Quentin's Stafford Fraser and this is coming to you from Cambridge in England. Oh, okay
Clearly just a little bit north and I'm recording this on a little I talk plugged into my iPod here
And these I talk so
Wonderful things but because of a limitation and the iPod the audio quality is is not very high
I have to say this is the first time I've heard an eye talk or one of those is that maybe that's the belkin is that the eye talk
Actually, it doesn't sound too bad. I said, but there's also some funny acoustic here
Yeah, because this is coming to you from my boss
Yes, I'm quite serious because he's splashing oh
Actually, I'm doing can any hear me
Seeing me in my bottle of alcohol is a lot of pretty sight the great thing about audio broadcasts
You could pretend that you know there was something kind of handsome standing lying here, but no, I would not know dude
I don't want to pretend that either
If I pretended that seeing me in my bath was something anyone should afford to
But there was a reason for this and for a casting to you from my boss not the group besides just a gross as all out. Yeah, go ahead
Good one. Oh, bro. You but
I was in hospital briefly just a couple of days ago and I have this dressing which I'm not meant to get wet for a couple of days
So instead of my usual showers
I've been having bath and
It is all sorts of things you can do in a bath, which are different from things you can do in a shower
This I I know we carry my iPod around
The house with me. I have
One of these little Sony travel speaker things and it's battery pad
And I plug in into my iPod and quite often listen to things like BBC feeds or the daily sort code
While I'm shading and so this is something that is this grossing you out. It sure is grossing me
Yeah, I'm talking to you in the bath and then it's okay to me that I could actually record a response to you in the bath as well
And so you are listening to another innovation from Cambridge, which is I think of the first ever bath
bath cast
If you're from almost anywhere in the world other than the Southern England
Now, you know, there are various I think merchandising opportunities here because
This is my iPod in the bath and iPods are not really designed to go with baths very well and
If I drop this it would not be a very happy iPod. So I think all those manufacturers out there who are making
Interesting sort of cases and add-ons on the southern friday pots should
A lot of speakers kind of rubber duck or one of those little yellow ducks you could even bid your iPod in so that it would be
safe in the bath or something like that
Anyway, I feel you're not going to get very many more bath cast from Cambridge because where's the first female bath cast then from Cambridge?
I was uh, I normally are kind of sharing guy and you know
I got to say I'm also normally a showing kind of guy myself. You know, I run a weblog her status
You know, you don't run a weblog my friend. You want to wet log dog
But I think shellocasting well that would just be silly, wouldn't it?
Hmm
Okay, actually this this is a part of a larger question that Dave actually posted on
iPod.org
The question that he posted is what's wrong with the iPod? By the way a lot of you probably got an iPod for Christmas
I gave Christina an iPod MIDI for Christmas, which she didn't even know she was getting she didn't even think she would get it because she knows how expensive
They are
Which made the surprise all that much nicer, obviously
But there's a lot wrong with it. If you look at the postings again a link
To the iPod.org posting from the production show notes for today
There's a lot. There's a lot of things that can be improved obviously and add on for a rubber duckie so that
Good old quentin can
Can play with his iPod in the bath is one thing, but the fact you know the idea of listening to a podcast
And then hitting a button to automatically record a response and have that handled somehow
I think it's pretty cool. That would be nice. You know from listen to a to a
To a podcast and I say hi. I want to respond and then just hit it and it could you know it could mark what I was responding to?
What point in the in the podcast record that and then send it off appropriately if all the data was all there and we knew where to send it
etc. They could happen. They could happen. So if you have any thoughts about
What's wrong with the iPod or maybe a little or positive is what can we do to make the iPod better or to make a better iPod?
Which doesn't even have to be called an iPad iPod?
Nor does it have to be made by Apple necessarily
You know post the post a comment there. What do you say a little bit of music? I'm ready for some music not too much though
Just about a minute or so because I don't know if you can handle this. It's a mashup
Which I received from Ian Robbins
I came across this mashup today thought I might find entertaining. It's called just lose the accordion
And if you're
an M fan you'll think oh my god here comes and indeed
Oh
Every one of my boy to the dance floor to the dance floor to the dance floor
I'm an M on the accordion there if you want to hear the whole song I don't know if you could actually handle
Well, I guess you could skip through it. Okay. I'll be honest with you
The download broke after 55 seconds and I'm still on a modem dial-up so I don't have more than that
But of course, I have the original link to that
MP3 in the production show notes M and M in the accordion mix
Definitely different. That's for sure. See something else I posted the last night about
Creating an iPodter for my GSM cell phone lots of responses to that although it seems that apparently and I and I actually tested this
I have the what do I have? I have my Sony Ericsson. I don't get this because
The Sony Ericsson I can I can Bluetooth from one phone to the next and resend and receive no problem
I can send to my Mac but however when I want to transfer something from my Mac back to the Sony Ericsson
I try Bluetooth file browser and I try
Yeah, basically the file browser and I try to direct upload and I'll try the browser device and in both cases it cuts off the connection
And apparently it's not that easy to send stuff to your Bluetooth phone from
From a Mac or there's lots of hiccups and handy caps and work around that you need to
Need to put in place
So if you have any more information on that I'd love to know about it because the idea is
I mean if you already have your iPodter running right and your iPodter basically writes all your new podcast out to your
iTunes your Windows
Media player and that eventually onto your MP3 player. Why couldn't you just add a little extra process?
That said, okay my favorite favorite favorite podcast the one that I need to have every single day and I want it with me
Can be transferred
From the iPodter itself through Bluetooth onto my cell phone, which is basically sitting next to the computer anyway being charged
And since I can only fit I think was it I have a 40-meg
Storage space on it. It would have to put one on and it removed the one from the day before essentially, but it could be
It could be something that's very useful not maybe not for
Source code or dawn and drew, but maybe for some
You know partner information that you just need to have and then the great thing about it is you're the iPodter could be running anywhere
Right because you only just need to basically authenticate that this is the the cell phone that the podcast has to go to and I think it will kind of just work
And as I was thinking about that, I thought Jesus Christ you know my Audi actually had some iPodter technology or at least philosophy built into it
It has the traffic monitoring system, which I think we've played on the show before and
What that does is it monitors you know, there's there's all kinds of
Montering systems throughout Europe and it knows where the traffic jams are if it's if it's
Still standing traffic or if it's slow moving traffic the length of the traffic jam, et cetera
It also often knows you know what the cause is road works or accident
Something else though, you've probably heard the BBC
Road reports cut into my studio a8 as I'm driving you know as I'm not driving as I'm recording in the Audi
So those reports are actually recorded in and and I geez I'm not in the obviously I'm not in the car
But next time I'm in the car I'll let you hear him it records up to like 30 different or 30
Previous reports so in the morning when you get in the car the past 30 reports that have been broadcast
Even though the car was off, you know, it's been locked the alarms on it's out
It's sitting there recording these road reports so you can you know go back
It depends on how often they do them, but in the morning sometimes every five or 10 minutes and you can hear those reports
That is basic iPodter technology and
And to think that you know, they still can't
Just send me an Excel sheet from or some spreadsheet directly from the car at the end of the month, which says
Okay, here's the trip she took here's what the mileage was here's who you went to see and it should just email it to me from its built in
GSM phone
Now of course, that'll be way too smart. It would be exactly what we wanted and that would be I guess wrong
Okay, let's see
I got this thing about the the Gilmore gang that I picked up
I don't know if I want to play that right now because it's about four minutes it basically was it's a great piece of
The Gilmore gang where Mitch Kurtzman who I guess is a venture capital
Venture capitalist talks about you know, let's let's play let's play a little piece of it
What the hell let's play just a bit of the Gilmore gang from the 24th yeah
It'll be about four minutes, but worth it to listen to a venture capitalist who
Well, who knows what he's about and and knows about what's happening right now and I think there are some exciting times if you happen to be looking for money for a start-up company
You know Larry Elson saying that there's going to be a consolidation and then going out and buying
bunch of companies
Self-prefetic
What's the fundamental
It's leading the Alson to do this if if customers are going to have less choice
Isn't that going to make their job of being in control a little bit more difficult rather than the other way around?
Well, that's this probably falls into for customers to be careful what you wish for
category
Because it you know my guess is that the customers will always make sure that there are alternatives
And if they're on any you know the alternatives will be created just because everybody's going to want at least two or three competitors in the major market spaces
You know, I'm sorry. I had to witness someone talking about market spaces
Predictions are mixed because Larry Larry's effectively said two things one as he said they'll be consolidation
But the other thing he said that I I really disagree with is he's also predicted that innovation isn't going to matter any more
And it's kind of the end of it end of innovation and the you know the
Software industry the technology business is going to look a lot like a you know like the car business or something where there aren't
You see those comments echoed and
You know and someone silly manners and articles and everything's in the New York Times with a Wall Street Journal
So what is you know if you look up and down the valley. I was talking to some of the folks who you know
Including John silly Brown who was saying he's never seen more innovation. They invalid today than any time in the last 10 years
So what things do you think are going to be innovative coming out in the next you know
Two to five years of whatever window you want to pick well. I wish I knew I mean
As venture capitalists you mean you don't know we we tell well
I I Dan Gilmour told me any promise he's warning me to secrecy
Yeah, so
A point blind blind for stay
As venture investors I think we we see only a little bit into the future, but
You know everything that we feel rise if we were really that smart we'd probably be back wanting companies instead
Don't you love it one venture capitalists recognize that does great major investing like we are
So instead what I I would agree that we're seeing a phenomenal amount of innovation
I think part of it is there was a tenth we've been through a period if you look at the last
You know decade or so we went through I think some innovation at the beginning of the internet and then the internet bubble and craze
Was not really a lot about innovation it was about business models and distribution and
Financing and going public and we didn't see a lot of innovation during that period. I mean we can come up with instances and exceptions
But venture capitalists for funding business models not technologies. Then we went through the recovery from the bubble
And this
Dirth of innovation because everybody had their heads down people weren't investing in anything
If you had a job you were keeping it you weren't risking
All by leaving your your paying job and going starting the new company and so it's only been I think in the last
year or two that
That really talented entrepreneurs are starting to pick up their heads and go to go out and get funding for some great ideas
And now it's not about business models. It's all about innovation and technology
So it's I completely agree with the observation that it's the most innovative time I've seen in a long time
And that is in I think in a major part
Thanks to stuff like podcasting. I haven't finished the entire show because they go on to talk about okay
So what is them of this great innovation and like hmm got really boring
Because I didn't hear any podcasting mentioned, but I'm sure if I listen to the whole things
Steve Gilmore probably slipped it is somewhere in a world gone mad
Where everything you know is wrong
One man
He's quiet and a quest to find a softer toilet paper
It will shake the very foundation of what is right
If you only listen to one podcast this holiday season you owe it to the world to listen to the daily download
The poop report
Paul's Chris Rockwell's performance
Solid
Play Akin gives the daily download two thumbs up the butthole and Oprah Winfrey says with an ass like mine
I'm so glad I have the support I need that's only available from the daily down
The daily download starring the Reverend Chris Rockwell as Bill and the Americans standard toilet
As his side kick plans
Red and directed by Chris Rockwell a jury brought high in production
This podcast is not yet been raped
Hotcast is not guaranteed to improve
Check out eight boy monkey girl dot com. I gotta tell you there's something about talking about poop
Doesn't for me the daily download something you definitely don't want to check out
Yes, it's the podcast you need to listen to if you want to be just plain old regular
You
All right, everybody that's it for the source code for the 20% of the summer
Just about to wind out the year will have the more podcast pleasure coming up this week more about the
Developments that's a David and I are working on his he's in Arizona, and I
The lovely hills of Sarah in the UK. I didn't get to talk about the delay at about fire Fox today, but there's always tomorrow
When I will return with more daily source code
Please send me a comment promo for your own show by the way if you've seen the iPod on order directly ever since I wrote the
iPod or directory scanner
We've had more podcast being added on a day basis than ever before it's just explaining
So we'll talk about that tomorrow about to fire Fox about you
I put a directory scanner and about delays while recording using all these breakout boxes in garage band and virtual sound
Interface and second. I'll see you tomorrow take everybody have a great start of your week bye bye
You