Thank you for watching.
Well good afternoon from Curry Castle in Belgium or good evening or good morning.
Monday, September 13th, 2004, I'm Adam Curry and great to have you aboard.
We've got a lot of cool stuff to talk about today on the source code.
Of course, iPodder also want to talk about programs.
I'm thinking of a new program myself that I want to put together, stuff that we need
to make these programs doable on our computers.
Of course, I've got a song of the day, a little bit of geek talk, and I also have
a comedy clip that I want to play for you today, so lots to get to.
This is the place where users and developers party together.
At least we try to.
In fact, I was thinking about this.
Imagine if we could actually harness the power of all the developers in the world.
And so many people are actually developers by scripting applications,
putting stuff together.
And I've seen in the past couple of days just looking at conversations going
back and forth between iPodder developers that we really seem to get along
on common ground.
Imagine if we could have a campaign like developers for carry.
or developers against Bush.
You know, there's a lot of power in what developers could do.
Of course, we'd have to be incentivized as developers,
and, you know, so there'd have to be some campaign promises.
Like, well, actually, I set up a conversation I had
with Dave Weiner this morning.
Free pizza might be, or free beer might even be enough incentive
for us to get us to vote.
Unfortunately, that apparently is illegal.
So I want to talk about iPod a bit.
We got a mailing list set up.
I did that at Yahoo Groups,
and I pointed it out on my web blog on live.curry.com.
There's one thing I'm going to be hammering on the mail list.
And, of course, I want to see how everything starts up
and what people are talking about.
Everyone's starting to introduce themselves now on the list.
It's installers.
We need to really work on our installers.
We've got all these different versions of iPod
that work with Windows and iPods and other MP3 devices
that can sync up to Windows Media Player.
So we've got everything going.
It's just that there's still too much work for users.
It should just be double-click.
There's a screen.
screen that says, going to install this, you know, here's how you get rid of it if you
want to.
And maybe one or two questions about some default feeds.
And that should be it.
It should be no more.
And boom, it's gone.
They can forget it.
We got it.
Cron jobs are running.
Everything happens instantly.
That's something we really got to work on.
I've also noticed that running iPodder, and I know I talked about this before on
source code, that I'm really using my iTunes almost like an email client now, where, you
know, a couple of times a day, I have my email client sent to pick up mail every 15 minutes
because I quite frankly, I just don't want to be bothered any more frequently than that.
I used to have it set to one minute, you know, when I was thinking of ideas or public
company that I co-founded.
And that was crazy.
You have no life.
And even though I know that the iPodder runs only four times in a 24-hour period, I've kind
of deprogrammed those times.
I don't exactly remember when.
So that...
I'm surprised.
It's the serendipity that I'm looking for where I just pop up iTunes and look at the
top of the library list.
Oh, yep, there it is.
There's something new and click on it.
And usually it's a blog digger media file which is hilarious and I've picked up some
great things in the past couple of days over the weekend.
So just interesting to see that I'm really using iTunes a lot more than I ever did
and that's really, it's a joyous experience every single time.
You know, is there something new?
Is there maybe a new Morning Coffee Nodes or is there a new Gilmore Gang?
By the way, I gotta tell you, I actually started to debug my iPodder because I
didn't get a new Gilmore Gang on Saturday.
Usually I get Friday show, sometimes Saturday morning when I get up and it's
already sitting there for me and I was like, oh shit, something must have gone wrong.
So I'm checking the log files and I'm looking at all kinds of places and
seeing if something went wrong with the iTunes transfer and then I went to the site
and I saw that, well, there actually was no update, no Gilmore Gang and I'm bummed.
You know, this is...
Actually, I should say, and I hope Doug Kay listens, or that he does listen once in a while
to the source code, is that, man, you got to let us know.
That's like death for radio and audio programming, skipping a show without a reason.
Especially in this space, the iPod platform space, IPS, is deadly because you have no way
to promote.
It's television if an episode is preempted.
then you can promote that continuously and people know about it but there's no way to tell people.
And if you don't have it on the weblog, just see this as a complaint.
I'm bummed. I like that Gilmore Gang.
There's an excellent format for what we're doing here with iPods and other MP3 devices.
And we'll also have to start looking at publishing tools fairly soon
because we're going to get bored of the same shows over and over again
even though there's new stuff.
We need some variation and we need to help people enable their RSS feeds
or just get RSS feeds out there so that they can start publishing stuff.
And we have to make it the exact same simplicity that we've done on the receiving end with iPod
so we need to figure out ways that people really have to do nothing
to get their RSS feed with enclosures out there
so that any iPod or enabled device can grab it, download it automatically by subscription.
I've been talking to a couple people about this on email and phone conversations.
Something came in which I thought was pretty cool was a Python screen scraper script.
I'm going to have to link to that where if you basically publish an HTML page with links
to MP3 files, it'll create an RSS 2.0 with enclosures file of that page.
But of course that's not really, you know, I don't think it's a very elegant way of
doing things because I'd rather have stuff that's archived properly and hold on
a second, sounds like my wife is coming home. One sec, let me just see.
Someone's certainly coming home.
Okay.
The dogs go crazy.
Alright, let me get back here.
Now Andrew Groomit. Is that the way you pronounce it, Andrew?
He sent me an email about something he just posted which is a small Python script
called DER 2 RSS.
So basically you drop this into a directory somewhere on your hard drive, which is in
your web server's documents path, which means you can access it on your local drive, but
it is also accessible through a web browser.
And you fire up that script, and in the folder it creates a little file called rss.xml, and
in that is the contents of that folder with some information that you said that you preset.
Like the name of your channel and the number of entries you want to contain.
And it will maintain that file.
So every single time you add something to it, if it's a watch folder that script
should run automatically or you just run the script and you've got it, and
then any web server can access that file.
Now you'd really want to run that on a server somewhere, and
I think then we get into some complicated territory where it should be just
an application that is as simple as give me an address of either your web
log so we can hopefully take care of it through a web log.
the blogger API or even better the meta web blog API or give me an FTP server and
I'll drop the file there and then of course after I've dropped that file there
I'm going to ping web blogs comm or something like that to let the world
know that the feed is has updated and I was talking to Dave this morning as it
was how it's actually interesting was this morning for me last night for him
because he's in Seattle now and he said that I had actually come up with a
solution or figured it out and as he said that I was thinking did I think of
that or I couldn't remember but anyway what he said was right it's exactly the
opposite of what we're doing with the RSS files creating playlists from the
channel information oh hold on hi hon yeah
yeah these both that was her who came home
right so about so that's on the receiving end where we basically on the iPod or
unpa...
the RSS feed and from that information that's in there creates folders to store the files,
creates a playlist, etc. What you want to do is you want to make it so simple that if someone
creates an mp3 file, all they need to do is really edit the ID3 tags because that'll give you
all the information you need to create an RSS file out of that. And there's many ways it
can be done. There's even a command line tool that I've seen for changing ID3 tags that you
can attach to a watch folder. I mean I think somewhere in there is the way to do it. And
people who are interested in publishing something will certainly already be familiar with the
concept of ID3 tags and editing those. So this will just be a little button next to it which
says publish and then it's going to FTP your RSS file to an FTP server that a web server can
access and also FTP your mp3 file up and that should be it. It should work.
as simple as that and I'm going to of course try and bake up one of my own versions.
Alright, that's enough for iPod. Let's talk about programs, shows like this for a second.
I've gotten quite a bit of email questions about the legality of me playing music on
the source.
which is, you know, all right, sue me.
You know, who's losing in this game
and how much of a thief am I in this particular case?
And of course I'd be more than happy
if I were to make money on any kind of program,
just like all broadcast radio stations do,
you give a percentage, usually between two and 6%,
to ASCAP, VMI, and a couple of other foreign agencies.
They'll be happy to do business with us,
but right now, you know, we're not really stealing anything,
just enjoying some old tunes now and again.
And what's interesting about it is that everyone talks about,
oh, well, you're playing this song, you're playing that song,
but not once has someone said, well,
how about that tune that you played?
code which is the Rachmaninoff Burris remix here I'll play it for you for a second.
This one.
You know why?
It's because we're not conditioned to think that way and if playing Kiss I was made for
loving you was stealing then this is stealing just the same.
This is probably already a remix of someone who took stuff from someone else that was
originally composed by Rachmaninoff.
There's a whole bunch of aspects to look at and I think this is sounding pretty loud here.
Oh
One, two, three, four.
Okay, well...
Another big note to self.
Gotta check the batteries before each show. This is the second time this has happened to me. This drives me crazy.
You know what? I have another battery. So why don't you bear with me here?
I'll have to feed back now. If you want to then you can just fast forward this piece of the
program.
I took the old battery out. It's on the receiving end of the wireless set that I have.
So I like about doing this on a Mac, because this is all like hot swappable.
You can do this on the fly.
And now I should be able to switch back to the...
There we go.
To the better microphone.
Okay.
Now of course you know that my mic battery is going to go.
Or what I'll do is when I get to the song of the day, I'll change that one just to
make sure.
Okay.
So we already mentioned the thing about, you know, no one thinking about the tunes
and there's all kinds of copyrighted material all over the place.
And there's a way to solve it if we're doing programs like this and we're making money on
it.
And that way it's just to hand off a percentage of your growth revenue.
It's done in broadcast all over the world.
I think the only thing that's different is the actual percentages themselves.
Could we just adjust this here?
Mic is good.
Okay.
So now we talk about programs and there was a nice post by Steve Kirk's.
which now I want to get to. My computer screensaver just kicked in.
His post is called Have a Take, Don't Suck.
And in there he says, well first of all he's very nice and compliments me
and calls me the gold standard of audio web blogging.
You know, the whole essence of this piece is that he's recognizing
how these programs fit together and how there's a format.
He actually speaks of a format and that, you know, there's not
not every one or everybody is going to be appropriate for doing this type of stuff.
You know, and there's a lot of prior art to look to.
I posted a link to Steve's posting.
So just have a read on that little plug.
Now some stuff that came in through the iPodder,
some interesting programming thoughts.
This of course came through BlogDigger.
It's a class of speech.
by William S. Burroughs, who I hadn't heard of before.
The speech is about something called the wishing machine.
And from this, if you do a Google search
on William S. Burroughs and a wishing machine,
you'll run into all kinds of really interesting stuff.
He's passed on.
He died in 1997.
And this is an hour-long speech
that he did on the topic of the technology of wishing.
And there's two things I want to play this clip for you.
Two reasons why.
One is just so you can hear his brief introduction of his speech.
And the second one is listen to,
and this is dated from 1985 or 87, I think,
listen to how this technology now can be used.
Here's someone who's just going to walk in,
is going to put down a recorder.
guy's speech and here it is still living years and years and years later and
totally distributable and you could make an archive of these and there you go
you could distribute them through the iPod platform. Anyway so listen to
this I'm gonna let you hear the piece where the guy is who recorded this is
actually setting up the microphone for the speech by William S. Burroughs.
June 24th, 1986.
June 25th, 1986, William Burroughs of Gamble Sigma,
Norwey Institute's Emeriting Program.
Now you hear there between his introduction and William S. Burroughs actually talking,
it sounds a lot like the source code, lots of dead air, and microphone noises.
Okay.
Good.
The subject I will address, first subject I will address, is of interest to young and
old, man and beast to everyone without exception.
It's the subject, it's the technology of wishing.
How to formulate your wish in such a way that it has some chance of being real?
And a consideration with last popular appeal, the responsibilities involved in wishing,
you might say the ethic to wishing.
Okay, so that's just a little piece there of William S. Burroughs and you can see how this
can be pretty enthralling, you know, it's just like another audiobook as long as the
audio is actually decent.
In this case I think it was, they must have plugged directly into the microphone.
Something else that I came across from, oh it's Free Reads from Jim Kelly.net.
Jim Kelly is a writer and he actually introduces exactly what he's doing and why he's doing
these things.
introduction before each book. So I'm going to play that introduction for you. It's a
little on the soft side, so you might have to crank up the volume. But it's interesting
to hear how he's going to use the iPod platform and also his motivation behind it. Here's
Jim Kelly from JimKelly.net with an introduction and then I'll let you hear the first couple
paragraphs from his story, The Best Christmas Ever.
Hi, this is Jim Kelly. Welcome to Pre-Reads.
I'm releasing the story you're about to hear under a Creative Commons license.
Basically, it means it's free.
Copy it as much as you want, send it to your cousin in Kalamazoo, or your pal in Poland.
All I ask is that you don't alter the file, or delete this intro, or the app to follow.
If you like what you hear, you might consider clicking over to my website,
www.jimkelly.net, and putting a little something in my PayPal account
to cover my costs of studio production.
How much? That's entirely up to you.
I'm no actor, but I am the author of the stories in the Free Read series,
and I've tried to perform them, more or less as I heard them in my head when I was writing them.
As the contributions roll in, if they roll in,
I hope to return to the studio to record more of my work.
In any event, I'm glad to have you as a listener. Enjoy!
The best Christmas app.
Okay, a couple of observations here about Jim Kelly.
First of all, I think it's really cool what he's doing by putting this together.
The thing that really hurts me here is that he is having to go to a studio and sounds like it because the quality is really good of his read.
That he has to go to a studio and pay someone money to get this kind of quality where you can easily get this kind of quality on your PC.
There should be no problem at all. There's enough processing power in there, enough digital signal processing chips.
It all should be possible. Users and developers are a huge crevice between us there on what we really need.
The biggest problem is that users don't know what to ask for as usual because we don't really...
know what the capabilities are. I mean I'm slowly turning my power book here into a
portable studio but something different than all the applications have been made
for. Something that creates a sound file on the computer and that can mix
everything together all virtually. That's really what's happening here. And of
course it would be nice if we could match up the right readers with the
right story writers because you know although Jim does an excellent read I
think you really there's a lot more as an advantage to have that you can gain if
you have someone who has the right type of talent for doing a read of an
audiobook. So a lot of matching up to do if possible. And I've been talking to
lots of people and been thinking about doing an additional show. So you know the
daily source code of course stays and thinking about something weekly perhaps.
And as a part of that or maybe a whole show hold a for show all together if anyone
out there.
is feeling good about it, we need an audio book review program definitely.
And it should be so simple.
I've even thought about this.
We could modify iPodder so that if you're listening to, let's say there's a feed, an
audio book review feed, which of course is great if you have time to listen to it, which
is where you're going to listen to audio books anyway.
And it's a show and it comes in every single day and there's a review of maybe one book
with an excerpt.
And if you want it, then you just hold down the play button on your iPod.
It marks it to a special playlist.
When you reconnect, boom, it goes out and talks to Audible or BarnesandNoble.com
or whoever you're going to buy, Amazon, wherever you're going to buy this from,
and pops it up.
It already knows that it came through the audiobookreview.com show.
And there's a transaction all over the place.
There's a market there.
And I'm so certain that audiobooks are just going to grow and grow and grow as
more iPods and MP3 devices.
are out in the marketplace. So, yeah hon? Yeah come on. Come on. Yeah I'm still busy.
Yeah. Give me a hand please. Yeah, okay.
Is your hand sharp enough? No man. That's over your feather.
Oh you're...
This is Patricia who brought me a nice bowl of chicken soup.
Because it's rainy? Mmhmm.
I'm gonna catch, wanna go out, and not allowed to. Thank you hon.
Bye.
very nice. So I've been thinking about a show with a co-host. Actually, I've been talking
to someone about a show as a co-host. And, you know, we're not quite there yet. But
just from a technology standpoint, now I'm thinking, how can we do this? And I wrote
it, I tried to explain this on my web blog today by writing about it, found it kind
of difficult, or I don't think anyone will understand what I'm saying.
In the broadcast world, when you have, I'll say, a radio show and you want to talk
to someone else who is somewhere in a different country or different world or
different state or around the corner, just not in the studio, what you need to do is
either lease a line, you can do connections through ISDN, that's how it's
done often, so you get a nice clear quality, or you immediately downgrade to
a telephone, which of course is the easiest, cheapest way and almost
anybody can use it and has access to one. And part of the big promise of the
internet.
of course especially for broadcasters is hey you know we can connect to anyone
And I think the CNET television used to do that once in a while that have a bit where
you could call in with your net meeting, video chat software, and oh, I suck, that never looked
good.
And it probably still wouldn't today.
But that was years ago until for its time, or for the period of time, way ahead of its
time.
But now I think that if I'm going to do a radio show with someone else, there should
be no reason for us to both be in the same room at the same time, yet we should be
able to capture an equal fidelity quality of us talking.
And we should be able to have a real time conversation just like we're talking on
the phone.
And of course, I've already been interested in voice over IP and I thought,
wow, you know, what we need to do is we need to hook up either Skype or some
type of chat program so that we can basically hear each other and then
record the output of both.
And as I thought it through, give up with some issues.
One is the way I have it set up now so that I can record my microphone and
and any other sound that I make on my Mac,
I'm basically recording through a program called WireTap,
which just anything that'll come through the speakers,
WireTap is going to record.
Now, my microphone, if I just plug the mic in
and there's no application talking to it,
it's not gonna do anything, you won't hear it.
Therefore, WireTap can't record it.
So I use Apple's GarageBand kind of as an amplifier
and I turn the monitoring on in GarageBand.
I can set some effects and some EQs
and because I can hear it through the speakers,
it will be recorded by WireTap.
Now, if I want to use Apple's iChat AV for instance,
to talk to someone else to have them on the show,
I could certainly record what they're saying
because I can hear it through the speakers,
therefore this WireTap program will record it.
But my microphone is already being used by another application,
so how am I gonna make sure
that the person on the other end hears me?
So anyway, I figured it out.
which is very interesting is that for some reason with these two applications probably
because they are both Apple programs and use the core audio, my microphone can actually
be accessed by these two programs at once.
So now I'll be able to record my voice.
I'll be able to record whoever's on the other end of the iChat AV and of course when they
get audio conferencing I'll be able to do it with a whole bunch of people which will
be fascinating.
I can also at the same time any sound effect or any song or anything I play on any media
player, any sound that I make with my Mac even like turning up the volume.
Hold on, did you get that?
There you go.
Any sound that comes out of the speakers will be recorded by wire tap.
But then there's one problem there is that when I play a clip, the person on the other
end won't be able to hear that clip because then I basically have to hold a microphone
up to the speaker and that's not the way it should be done.
So I've toyed around with a couple of different programs that let you route audio from one
program to the other.
I'm just having a little bit of this chicken soup here.
Yeah, it's good.
And I couldn't really get those to work the way I wanted to, so I haven't quite solved
that problem yet.
But this is going to be so huge when we all figure this out and we start to want to make
these type of programs.
This is going to be such a market for software to do this stuff.
It's going to be awesome.
So anyway, that's on the horizon.
I'll update you as everything unfolds.
Okay.
Song of the day.
It's a classic one.
This is really a song that is perfect for the weather here today in Belgium.
It was raining all weekend.
It's been dark and musty and wet and just continuing to drizzle and then rain off and
on again.
So there's no other song more perfect for a day like today than the Mamas and the
Pappas.
Of course it's Monday.
so good to me
It just turns out to be all
Monday Monday
And trust that day
Monday Monday and just think if Karen Carpenter and Deaton Mama Cassis ham sandwich we would
have still had two great singers with us today.
And I apologize I'm not quite sure what happened during the song but for some reason the whole
computer froze up once or twice and I'm sure that was reflected in the recording but everything
seems to be running so I just let it go.
I figured this whole program has been crappy enough.
And I might as well add that to the mix.
Quick bit of geek talk.
I've been noticing that Google is doing some stuff that I'm not seeing a lot written about
but I have picked up on a couple of links I'm not quite sure I understand it.
Excuse me.
Oh great chicken soup.
One of them is Google FS or maybe it's Gmail FS it seems that somehow there's an API
or there's some way to address Google specifically Gmail.
I think it was Google FS which stands for the file system.
away from Linux for you to mount your Gmail Drive space, which of course is one gigabyte.
And along with that, there's another application, a little program, which is also something
you have to download and work on Unix.
But that's where all the, you know, a lot of the fun stuff does seem to start.
It's called Galina.
And what that does is whenever you send an email to your Gmail account, it automatically
generates a blog post on a web blog page.
So, you know, it seems to me like there's something really interesting going on there.
And are people just finding these APIs or is there active development going on?
Or, you know, what the hell is it?
And while you ponder that, I want to play something that I discussed when I was
talking to Dave, Dave Weiner, who was temporarily at least has moved to Seattle.
He's going to be there at least through the November 6th BloggerCon conference,
which I'll, I'm attending and I'll be leaving.
a discussion on, gee, shall we do it about this?
So that's a lot of fun to look forward to.
So we're talking about that and talking about our upcoming move to the UK.
And there's a lot of exciting stuff and just stuff you run across when you're moving,
your financial stuff and changes of addresses and letting everyone know what's going on
and then your stuff.
And Dave said, well, you know, I'm to the point where my stuff fits in one car.
And I'm like, yeah, you know, I have a wife and a 14 year old daughter and our stuff just
doesn't fit in one car.
It's just no way.
And we've got lots of stuff.
And I said, have you ever heard the George Carlin bit about stuff?
And he says, no.
I said, well, I'm going to play that for you on the source code.
So I looked at my iTunes library.
I know I had it at one point.
Couldn't find it.
And so you got to love the internet one quick trip to Lime Wire.
And I guess this came off a bear share client.
It is the.
original piece that George Carlin does about stuff. I'm going to play a little bit more
than just the stuff. There's a commercial and advertisement which comes after it, which I
might as well just leave on since it's Carlin to the max. So enjoy this bit from George
Carlin. It's called A Place for My Stuff.
That's my job thinking up goofy shit.
Come around every now and then letting you know what it is.
Or reminding you of things you already knew but forgot to laugh at the first time.
This is my office over here.
Let's face it, if this is my job, this must be my office.
Looks like an office to me.
Got me a little desk here.
Kind of nice desk.
And a chair.
Chair goes with the desk, of course.
You could sit on the chair at the desk, if you like, making them a set.
Or you can use the chair as an occasional piece.
Which is nice to have in the office, I always say.
Actually this is just a place for my stuff, you know?
That's all a little place for my stuff.
That's all I want, that's all you need in life is a little place for your stuff, you know?
I can see it on your table, everybody's got a little place for their stuff.
This is my stuff, that's your stuff, that'll be his stuff over there.
That's all you need in life, a little place for your stuff.
That's all your house is, a place to keep your stuff.
If you didn't have so much stuff, you wouldn't need a house.
You could just walk around all the time.
The house is just a pile of stuff with a cover on it.
You can see that when you're taking off in an airplane.
You look down, you see everybody's got a little pile of stuff.
All the little piles of stuff.
And when you leave your house, you gotta lock it up.
Wouldn't want somebody to come by and take some of your stuff.
They always take the good stuff.
They've never bothered with that crap you're saving.
All they want is the shiniest stuff.
Put your house is a place to keep your stuff while you go out and get more stuff.
Sometimes you gotta move, gotta get a bigger house. Why? No room for your stuff in here.
Notice when you go to somebody else's house, you never quite feel 100% at home.
You know why?
No room for your stuff.
Somebody else's stuff is all over the goddamn place.
And if you stay overnight, unexpectedly, to give you a little bedroom to sleep in, bedroom
they haven't used in about 11 years, someone died in it 11 years, and they haven't moved
any of his stuff.
Right next to the bed is usually a dresser or a bureau of some kind and there's no room
for your stuff on it.
Somebody else's shit is on the dresser.
Have you noticed that their stuff is shit and your shit is stuff?
Say that shit off of there and let me put my stuff down.
Sometimes you leave your house to go on vacation
and you gotta take some of your stuff with you.
You gotta take about two big suitcases full of stuff.
When you go on vacation you gotta take a smaller version of your house.
It's the second version of your stuff.
You're gonna fly all the way to Honolulu. You're gonna go across the continent,
across half an ocean to Honolulu. You get down to the hotel room in Honolulu
and you open up your suitcase and you put away all your stuff. There's lots of places in the hotel room to put your stuff.
Here's a place to put a little bit of stuff there. Put some stuff here. Put some stuff here.
You put your stuff there. Put some stuff here. There's another place for stuff.
Look at this. I put some stuff here.
Even though you're far away from home, you start to get used to it.
You start to feel okay because after all, you do have some of your stuff with you.
That's when your friend calls up from Maui and says,
hey, why don't you come over to Maui for the weekend and spend a couple of nights over here?
Oh, no.
Now what do I pack?
Right. You've got to pack an even smaller version of your stuff.
The third version of your house.
Just enough stuff to take to Maui for a couple of days.
Get over to Maui. I mean, you're really getting extended now.
When you think about it, you've got stuff all the way back on the mainland.
You've got stuff on another island. You've got stuff on this island.
I mean, supply lines are getting longer and harder to maintain.
You get over to your friend's house on Maui and he gives you a little place to sleep,
a little bed right next to it, there's a windowsill or something. You put some of your stuff up there,
you put your stuff up there, you got your vising, you got your nail clippers, and you put everything up.
About an hour and a half, but after a while you finally feel okay, say,
all right, I got my nail clippers, I must be okay. That's when your friend says,
hey, I think tonight we'll go over the other side of the island, visit a pal of mine, and maybe stay over.
Oh no. Now what do you pack?
Right. You gotta pack an even smaller version of your stuff.
The fourth version of your house. Only the stuff you know you're gonna need.
Money, keys, comb, wallet, lighter, hanky, pen, smoke, rubber, and change.
Well, only the stuff you hope you're gonna need.
We'll be back to the album in just a moment. First, these messages.
Say, why not become a schmuck? A licensed, practicing schmuck?
Or if you qualify, a CPS. That's right, a certified public schmuck.
You know, it may not seem like it when you look around, but there is a shortage of schmucks in today's society.
And there's big money in schmuckdom. The average schmuck today earns over $34,000 a year.
And there are openings for schmucks in virtually every field.
The government is run by schmucks, big businesses run by schmucks,
and more and more people are becoming schmucks on their own.
You know, some guys can only manage to be schmucks on New Year's Eve.
But here's your opportunity to become a full-time year-round schmuck.
Give us a call. Don't be a schmuck. Be a schmuck.
That's George Carlin. And of course you heard a bit from his very famous, A Place For My Stuff,
which I just love it, man.
Here's a guy when he's doing some of this stuff, doing a show like...
this. Wouldn't it be great to wake up every morning to a little look on life from George
Carlin or from John Stuart for that reason? There's a lot of people I'd love to hear.
Just a little, just a little bit about the day. That's it for the source code for today.
A little bit, a little messy here and there and I'm going to run out and get some more
batteries for tomorrow's show. As always, if you want to respond, you can send me
email adam at curry.com or leave a comment on my web blog live.curry.com.
You can always find a new source code at DailySourceCode.com where you can subscribe to the Daily Feed with iPodder.
That's DailySourceCode.com slash RSS dot XML.
And you can get the iPodder at iPodder.org.
We'll see you tomorrow for another source code.
Take care!
The power of your new thoughts.
The Power of Your New Thoughts