scree
When I'm in the kitchen
all taken up, didn't connect
on English and Rezyli Slim
Takeout at the show
monarch or naked
Now just wander around
Come on and do it
in the Netherlands, I'm Adam Curry, welcome to the really big show. How y'all doing? It's been okay
here, it's almost time for me to go back home. Back to Jolly Ode England, I got to tell you, I am pretty
much ready.
But of course, I'm celebrating my last night here in, uh, with all my friends from the source code.
We're going to go for my life.
We can't start the show without, at least not a show at home without a fight.
Okay, and this is being a severe issue.
Okay, so I'll have to figure out where the lighter went. Luckily, lots of music
planned for this evening or this morning, or this afternoon, depending on when you're listening
to this podcast. For some reason, I've been really inspired by being here to play more music
on the source code. Part of it is, of course, because, you know, I've been talking about it,
talking about fighting the next, the next Beatles, and that we could actually find and support the
next Beatles through podcast. It is completely possible. And also, there's a lot going on in the
music scene here. There really is, and people have been sending me all kinds of links to mashups,
mashups, but also some just great independent music that, uh, it totally has been just blowing me
away in its quality and, uh, and just, you know, there's a, there's a lot of, a lot of community
stuff happening here. Um, so, uh, today, and maybe, you know, also because we're kind of into the, uh,
the, uh, the end of the year and, uh, shit, you know, you've already heard my news. I have the best
Christmas present ever. Um, so goodbye to my mom. I can go back home tomorrow to be with Patricia
Christina and the in-laws, of course, will be with us for the holidays. Um, and my mom is doing great.
And, um, yeah, I, I think, uh, she's on a very good start to a, to a, yeah, a road of recovery,
which is going to still take quite a while. But, uh, anyway, lots of good vibes, uh, everything's been
received, feeling good, ready to go back home. And, uh, oh, my, what, I got some, uh, uh, a cadence.
I got some more cowbell for everybody. Actually, this is from, uh, Jim Davis, and when I first heard this
like, I recognized this. I think this was done by a friend of mine. His name is Ben Libron. He's a pretty
well-known remixer. This is basically pieces of full metal jacket, remixed. Well, you'll get the
idea. But it's just where those things are kind of. It's a bit militaristic, but yeah.
Me, my look for my, uh, lighter. That's enough of samples in a local culture.
I don't want no G-D-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D. I don't
want do have life? I don't want each other. I don't want no G-D. I don't want to be here. I don't want no G-D. I don't want no G-D.
I don't want to wait, I don't want to be bad
I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad,
I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I don't want to be bad, I just want to be bad, I just want to be worse anymore, I just want to be worse, I say i don't want to be worse, I just want to be worse, I just want to be worse, I just want to be worse, I just want to be worse, I just want to be worse, I just want to be worse, I just want to be worse, I just want to be worse, I just want to be worse,
I'm going to use a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
All right, we'll close the gates, we'll come at now Those are the hardcore champions and make sure the lines stop only Stella SuperHooksets, Captain Don't miss those who don't has the same size. Yeah, I don't know
I know about you, but I just can't sit still when I hear stuff like that.
I'm 99% sure this is a Bentley Brom Mix of Fomeral Jacket and whatever stuff.
I think this is something that was from the 80s and one of the radio shows we used to
do back then.
That's probably why someone sent it to me.
He said, love you, show newbie, hope to be a podcast or some day.
I'm so sure that this is, whoops, that was weird, haven't had that happen, yeah, did
you hear that?
Oh boy, hopefully everything's going to keep working here.
But I wanted to actually, I did something productive today.
Do you remember I was in Hilversum a couple weeks back and I was there just overnight and
I'd also gotten a super fast internet hotel.
This hotel is better by the way than that one, comparable in price, but that doesn't
really matter.
I was there to help a couple of friends out.
They were recording a television pilot to talk show with two of the guys that I worked
with on my morning radio show.
So today, I went to the headhonshow with the TV network, SBS, who I sold, the Adderous Family
Reality Show to, had a nice chat and I think we pretty much sold this show into one
of their TV networks, which is really great, we're really all pretty fucking excited.
Because it was a long shot and everyone just kind of came together and everyone chipped
in and barely no money on the table.
And now everyone will have a job if we're lucky, which is going to be very, very
cool.
And so I'm excited about that.
So that was a productive bit of the day, let's see what else I do.
I actually, I got the, I don't know if I told you that I had an MG and Amsterdam and the
second night I was here or the next day that I was here after I arrived Monday night.
At the end of the day, I went to go get the MG and Amsterdam and drive it back to Utrecht
because I thought it would be handy to have a car, but it's been crappy weather and
I'm six foot three or six four and I just can't fold up into this freaking MG and then
it's a manual transmission, which I have no problem with, but I'm, you know, I use my right
hand for other things now while I'm driving, you know, now I'm used to automatic transmission.
I know what you're thinking, hey, you know what, let's, let me, I think the mine cords
long enough.
I'm just going to be a quick little sample here of the night air and Utrecht, I have
a beautiful balcony and I got this great mic, so let me see if we can catch some sounds
here.
There's some people biking.
Going home.
I wonder how that sounds.
Okay.
That's enough.
Too much fresh air for you guys.
As I said, lots of music lined up for the show and by the way, it is evening for me.
It's a quarter to ten.
I'm sorry.
It's a quarter to eleven here.
It's a quarter to ten in the UK, so I'm, I'm trying to kind of live on UK time again.
And I've been just receiving so many beautiful voice comments, audio comments, and actually
my mailbox overflowed a bit recently, I had to delete some email because there was so much
coming in.
I can't possibly play them all, and I really try to stay within some reasonable time limits
on the show.
40 minutes max, and today may even be just a little bit shorter depends, you know, how
much, I don't know, just depends.
I did want to play this one though, because this was just too cute, just wonderful.
Hi, Adam.
It's Lance from the Digital Experience podcast, and with me is my wife Pam.
Hello.
And my son Isaac?
And my son Stephen, can you say Stephen?
Yes.
And we all wanted to say hi to you and to send our best get well wishes to your mom
after recovering very nicely from her surgery.
Can you say get well?
Wow.
Get well.
And Merry Christmas to everybody.
Can you say podcast, Stephen?
Yes.
Podcast.
Case.
Prince of Pod.
There you go.
So Adam, even though it sounds like you got one of the best Christmas presents
around, we all wanted to wish you happy holidays to you and yours and a very best new year.
All right.
Thank you.
Same to you and everybody.
And everybody's families out there.
Oh, man, there's just so much.
There's so much to get through.
You know, this is really what I need.
I need, you know, people to help me produce the show and produce more shows.
I could do 15 shows if I had people to help me keep track everything and keep everything
together.
I'm not a manager.
It's like they, you know, he needs some programmers to get some, to get some software done.
That's going to help us, you know, create this, I think, even better infrastructure for podcasts.
We talked the other day.
He actually called me from the road, man.
He does his brain work when he's driving holy crap.
And we just, you know, connected on so many different, so many different things.
And it's just, yeah, you know, he's like he's already on his way to, you know, to getting into shape.
And he already feels much better.
And I just saw a web blog post that, you know, he's getting ready to start doing some programming.
And he's, he's include me in.
I think I understand it.
And I'm extremely excited about it.
So there's some cool stuff on the horizon.
The really is.
I also got a very nice email from Daniel.
I think he works for, for or with American Heartbreak.
Of course, we know, American Heartbreak.
Michael Butler from Rock and Roll Geek Show.
I'm one of the first, one of the first podcasts.
And they heard me talking about American Heartbreak playing in Europe.
And he said, they really hope to see me in Berlin with Butler at,
what is it?
Well, wild the heart.
Wild the heart, maybe.
On the seventh of January.
And check this.
This is the part that I like.
As Michael said, you're on the guest list of every European concert of American Heartbreak.
I mean, that's, that is like the ultimate.
That's like Elvis.
You know, how many bands have Elvis on the guest list?
You know, in case he shows up and he wants to,
wants to be in this show.
And I was like, I'm on the, every single show.
I'm on the guest list.
That is, I, you know, I've made it now.
I feel totally, totally honored.
Unfortunately, that's not going to work.
Cause I'm going to be in the States until the 10th of January.
But I have to check out the website.
See if I can see if there's some other days.
Maybe that can catch American Heartbreak on tour because that would be cool to catch up.
And also, make sure to check out the podcast, the production show notes.
Now, the HTML version has been kind of messed up.
I don't have that nice, you know, that pretty little rendering that I did before.
That's kind of a part of the server transition.
I just want to get off of the other servers.
Get off of the way I was producing that before.
This is kind of like a placeholder.
Because I think that what what Dave and I discussed and what's coming soon will be much more smart about how that's rendered and how you can access that and what you can do with that information.
So, I think, you know, just bear with me on that.
You can still, of course, in the show notes.
There's also the, one of my colleagues here, the show details.
I'm so professional.
Where it tells you, you know, like the date, the location has the direct download link.
And also, a download to the bit torn version, because we're going to have to start figuring that stuff out pretty soon.
So, even though it's not in the RSS feed, I'm already putting it into the show notes, which you can get in OPML version.
And as I said, kind of the messed up funky, what the fuck is this HTML version?
Something else that is, is just in the show notes that I kind of left in there is an email from Charles Kellin, Charles Kellin,
from the Guilford songwriters.
And you should check this out, because basically, he's inviting me to come to New Year's Eve party at a bar in Guilford,
which, of course, is my hometown now, featuring live music from some top quality local musicians,
which probably ends up in a drunken sing-along, which sounds just perfect.
And, you know, he, I guess, basically, he records this, and this sounds like a perfect podcast.
So, I want to see if I can get in touch with him and see if, see if I can work something out.
So, that'll be very cool.
Anyone else who's, who's in Guilford, I encourage you to check out the message and come on by if you feel like it.
See what else, you know, I've been, actually, I've been, I've been carrying this one over from several podcasts,
some more about the hacking of the, the I River, the IFP-799, that's the MP3 player that I bought,
and I was so appalled that it actually uses its own proprietary digital rights management software
to get the MP3s on and off or not, if it's protected in their proprietary format.
And basically, I just been collecting emails and comments and some links, which,
finally, just put pasted right into the, into the production show notes, so you can get a good idea of what can be done about that.
Because there is a firmware update you can run, and you can just basically use this thing like, like a USB external drive.
There is one comment in here in audio comment that I've kept all that time.
So, I don't remember what this is.
Let's listen to it. This is from Lee.
Hi, Adam. My name's Lee.
I'd love to show the listening for a couple of weeks.
I just thought I'd leave you a comment about your IR River device.
I heard you've got an IFP-799 or something like that, which got me thinking,
because I've got an IFP-180, which I got about a year and a half ago.
I didn't know there was still making new versions of that series.
Anyway, it looks like your device is much cooler than mine, but I had the same issue with the IR River music manager
when I was fully expecting the device to just plug the device in and have it show up.
As a normal removable drive, turns out you can make it do that.
If you check out IR River's downloads, they actually have two versions of the firmware for the IFP devices.
If you actually flash your device with the other downloaded firmware,
when you then reboot it, I think.
You lost me there. I'll listen a little bit longer.
You lost me with the flash of the reboot.
When you plug it in, one possibility you might have is that I think for your device,
it's still listed as beta or beta or have you pronounced that.
Oh, man, did you read that whole Mary Harder thread about what beta is or not or beta?
Did they say beta in the UK as a beta?
Hey, beta this, baby.
Beta?
Yeah, beta.
Should you sell it if it's beta?
Could you charge for it if it's beta?
I don't know.
So your mileage may vary.
Good work conditions.
Just depends on how much you like trying experimental stuff.
Well, I've been a user for years, so I pretty much love being a beta tester and paying for it.
Check it out.
Hope it's useful.
Thank you.
Love to show you.
Thanks, buddy. I really appreciate it.
So actually, I have the links in there to the firmware hacking page.
And there was one other quick comment I got from Mike Massey.
He says I was listening to the source code December 16th.
I heard you talking about the I River Cheese Stick.
All right, I said it looked kind of like a cheese stick.
He says, I have one of those.
I agree with you.
It sucks.
It's not for the camera.
It's such a piece of crap.
I got rid of it now.
I have an iPod.
Oh, you know, apparently there is a fixed word, Mike.
So if you have it, you know, maybe you want to pick it up and play around with it.
Ed Alcoma.
I've been in touch with him.
He's been around the scene for a while.
He sent me a link.
I want it comes to mashups and I'm sort of going to look closer to the Mike.
It comes to mashups and smashups.
Now people are sending me links to all kinds of amazing stuff, which of course could never
ever be released.
But I'm sure it's okay to listen to in the context of the podcast.
And I left these links.
Of course, this is from a site that features a series of mixes by a fiction, fiction area,
a fiction area, a fiction area, a fiction area band.
The Beastals is what they're called.
So essentially what we're talking about here is mashups of the Beastie Boys and the Beatles.
I don't know if I want to play one whole song.
I'll play some snippets of a couple of songs.
This one's titled What You Want Lady, The Beastals.
So please don't leave until after they finish playing the band.
Right now it's by a great, great pleasure to introduce artists and musicians.
Help us.
Let me listen to that.
Press the bell.
Okay, so that's one example, right?
Let me give you something else.
It's weird.
It's really trippy because sometimes I like it and sometimes I really hate it.
It's hard to say.
Hold on.
Why is my system not firing here?
There we go.
This is titled Hold It Together Now.
Here's a piece of tape for us in England by Ringo Star.
John Lennon.
George Harrison.
Let's go.
We're gonna start the channel.
That's different, eh?
I party with the Beasties in Montro, baby.
Yeah.
They're old now, like me.
Okay, we're more.
I feel fine right now.
Let's play some more body music.
I don't know how this is turning out at all.
I'm just tired.
I want to go home.
I want to be back where there's no bandwidth.
It's coming though.
Actually, it's coming when I'm not there.
When I'm going to be in the States, that's when the bandwidth is coming.
Which of course has me worried that I'm not going to be there for the install that it may not be entirely perfect.
But it is indeed coming.
And this is Paul Eastman.
He has a bunch of friends.
They got together.
They recorded this song for their own enjoyment.
He's what he says actually.
I know a whole bunch of people that have had the creativity stifled because of a record company in radio station politics.
A person's career can be in the hand of person that chooses a radio station playlist.
Well, we've gone over there.
That's how it works.
If they don't like your song, it simply doesn't get heard.
Hope podcasting will finally break them in a lot of the monopoly that broadcasters and record companies have enjoyed for so long.
By the way, I'm not drunk or overly stoned.
If you hear me kind of tripping over my words, that's a damn hijack.
For some reason, sometimes it trips up and it gives me a delay.
So I'm hearing my voice delay just a little bit in the headphones.
I know that some of you out there who use GarageBan know this problem.
Stuff we got to work on.
Anyway, so as Paul says, here's a little tune that I did with a few friends of mine.
It's a cover of an old song written by Holland Dozier Holland.
Well, we heard of those guys, right?
We have permission from their publishers to cover the song.
We own the sound recording and we'd love to hear it on the daily source code if you like it.
It's a mere 4.1 mags.
Hey, everybody, get a mere 4.1 mags.
Here's come see about me.
It's a song, watch your way, don't feel it.
That's what I never told you.
It's easy for you to feel it.
I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, it keeps me crying.
I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you.
I'm trying to tell you I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell all I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to told you, I'm trying to tell you, I'm trying to tell you,ー
Keeps me crying, ever for you
So what you hide, can I avoid and see you happy?
I say we've got a way to know
Say we've got a way to know
I'm not a baby, I don't believe
But my heart says you're happy
No matter what you want to say,
I'm not a baby, I don't believe
I'm crying, ever for you
So what you hide, can I avoid and see you happy?
Say we've got a way to know
I'm not a baby, I don't believe
But my heart says you're happy
I'm crying, ever for you
So what you hide, can I avoid and see you happy?
It makes everything more different
So we'll play
My love
My Love
Yeah, kick-and-women, I need that when you might have to have the Incranette
King going on the pitch.
Yeah!
Oh, take it up there.
There you go.
I've got a lot of news and we're easy listening.
Look at that.
Oh, make it easy.
Morning, midnight.
Good night.
Incranette.
It's all right.
It's just right.
Yeah, that's it for the Daily Source Code for today, a little bit on the short side.
Three minutes.
But...
It's all right.
So, I've got, I'm feeling good.
I'm going to pack up, get the show ready to go, most of it, I'm going to pack my bags and tomorrow
I'm out of here after some quick Christmas shopping which of course I have not done yet.
It's typical if I have the most of the day to take care of it.
And remember the word is OPML, go home, spread the word, make babies.
All right, everybody, some time tomorrow or perhaps Saturday, because I'll be traveling.
They will be in our source code.
If I don't talk to you before Saturday and you celebrate Christmas, I'm happy Christmas.
Otherwise, you just enjoy it great weekend, I'm going to talk to you guys soon.
It's all right for the Daily Source Code for the Daily Source Code for today.