I'm casting all's life at a curry.
Just power all the glory of your life.
How do everybody? Good?
Afternoon, good evening, or almost good morning is just a little bit before midnight here on Wednesday, October 27th, 2004,
coming to you from the bunker in Sin City, home of the coffee shop,
and stood down the nettle that's the source curve.
Power all the glory of your life.
Oh boy, one of those days,
didn't get to my email until about 10-15 years ago.
And it's full of all kinds of particular due to an interview that I did today,
on WNYC.
Without a doubt, New York's premiere,
and I think only public witness to it,
not be only one in the Tri-State area, mind you.
But yeah, it was really, really good.
So I'm going to play some of that.
We're going to review the launch of Apple's new iPods.
And of course there is some audio comments and some RIA for you.
Power all the glory of your life.
And I think I talked about this the other day that WNYC
released a CD with what I call pod tunes or a music that is free to be used and copied as you wish.
Some well-known names on there, a Beastie Boys, a David Bern by now, of course,
this thing is circulating around the net.
And if you're hey, if WNYC is going to quit so much push behind these bands,
they've chosen and they've gone through the trouble of doing this,
then we might as well participate in everywhere we can.
So on the podcast today, a couple of songs that come off of that CD,
this is one big holiday.
My morning on the source code.
So I'm going to play some of that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Was a bad man, man
Can't find him
Telling I was starting to eat me
All the way
No, no
Baby
We'll stay
Oh, oh, oh
Make a way
We'll be alright
So we'll let it start
Up the river
And it's going all around
We'll stay
Oh, oh, oh
Make a way
We'll stay
Oh, oh, oh
Make a way
We'll stay
Oh, oh, oh
Make a way
We'll stay
Oh, oh, oh
Make a way
We'll stay
Oh, oh, oh
Make a way
We'll stay
Oh, oh, oh
Make a way
We'll stay
Oh, oh, oh
Make a way
We'll stay
Oh, oh, oh
One big holiday, my morning
From the wire to open source music CD
It has a name
Oh, I was second
That CD had a name, didn't it?
I couldn't say that
Hold on, let me see
I'll look at iTunes right now
The wire CD volume one, alright
I could have come up with one myself
This is the source code
It's now officially Thursday
But we're still going to say this is Wednesday
October 27, 2004
It's been on a bit of an emotional rollercoaster the past few days
Get really excited about what's happening with everything
All things podcasting
And then my mom's still still going through some tests
I think I might have some reasonably good news to report by tomorrow
I'm getting up at six and we're going to the hospital
We have a 930 appointment
One final test that has to be done
Just to make sure that we can indeed go the surgery route
Which would be fabulous
And that is relative to what fabulous really is of course
So, so it's been kind of up and down
But today
Now, I think this was set up through DocSurles
He got an email
From someone I believe it was a producer from WNYC
Public Radio in New York
Asking him to come on the show
On the Brian Lera Show
Which is a morning radio show in New York
Which apparently a lot of people listen to
And talk about podcasting
And very graciously
Doc said, well, you should talk to Dave and Adam
And I got to be honest that I didn't really follow all the email threads
The email is fucking exploding out of control
I can't wait to get on a 14 hour plane ride to San Francisco
Just to sort out my email
What I'm basically doing now is I'm trying to get all the directory stuff
For new entries to the directory and get those in
That has priority you know besides
Whatever shit comes in from tax attorneys and lawyers
That just I'm forced to look at
With fucking office attachments
Excel sheets and word documents I hate him
So, this was really amazing to be on the show
I think I was on for almost like 20 minutes
And there were playing bits from podcast
From the source code, the Don and Drew show
And just to give an impression
And really went into detail and they really done their work
And this producer had indeed done really done his job
It was funny because
And this had never happened before
I've been lots of radio interviews in the states
All over the world
And for the first time I was given like the legal disclaimer on the phone
And I have to actually ask questions
Do you agree to have your voice with broadcast on radio and AM and whatever
Do you agree that this can be archived on the internet
For webcast and on CDs for distribution
Yeah, so you agree it's like signing your waiver
And it was great and he
Brian there opened up the phones for calls
This is a New York-based radio station
And it was as if we had set it up
But we hadn't
And in came to me a very familiar voice
This is 93.9 and AMA 20 WNYC
We're speaking with Adam Curry
We developed a software that allows so-called podcasting
Which is broadcasting or just moving audio around
via MP3 on the web or to your iPod
And here is Brian in Durham, North Carolina
Who says he's a podcast
Brian, you want to go to your NYC?
Hi, how are you?
Okay.
For my podcast is audioactivism.org
Hey Adam, I really appreciate all you've been doing
It's really a great outlet
To a lot of creative people
All right.
And what do you do?
Go ahead and plug away
Sure, my podcast
So I was going to comment on that
I was like I was so amazed
Here's Brian from audioactivism.org
I just been listening to his podcast
The night before my way back
From Amsterdam to Belgium
And it was like that's when he said
Hey, it's really great
And for a split second
For a split second
And you can actually I'm going to read
I'm going to wind this
I'm going to rewind this
I'm going to say what I was thinking of saying
At the moment, Brian came in
Okay, so you'll get the full effect
I didn't want to do it because it's like public radio
It was a really big deal to do this in New York
But I'm going to kind of give you that effect
Hey, it's just fine
Okay, we go to this part
All right, and what do you do?
All right, okay
All right, and what?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Basically, you're saying this is so great
Thank you Adam for this
I really appreciate all you've been doing
It's really a good, great outlet
To a lot of creative people
Boy, boy, boy, boy, boy
All right, and what do you do?
Got it?
Sure, my podcast is basically about
called three or else
And a uniform resource locator
Basically, like web address
That has something to do with activism online
It's another thing that blogs do really well
It's a type of social software that allows people to connect
And obviously during this sub-political season
A lot of people have been using it for different types of activism
But it's not just about president
It takes other things as well
But you can see the show so much political
And that sense, and it allows me to reach
You know, a huge audience, a group of people
We're hosted by a Biblio.org
Which is real famous for hosting all kinds of things
Like free software, that sort of stuff
But that's what I've been doing
And what's amazing is I'm listening to your show
As a streaming in V3 with iTunes
On my PC at work
And I heard about this show
On Docs, Girls' Blog
So the viral nature of how we hear about
You know, what's going on, what items up to
And what different people are doing
Is, you know, a really fantastic
And I'm talking about John Stewart there
Yeah, that's great.
Brian, thanks a lot for calling
And that's,
I think it's been good rather than competition
So then the interview goes on
I put a link up to a recording of the stream
That Rick from WGBH
Put up for us and he said I could point to it
So the audio skips here and there in a couple of spots
But you'll get a general idea
And I think this is another win for the good guys
This was great
And I also, since it was so much time
You know, it was so nice to talk for such
For such a long, it's like three segments
And 20, 20 minutes total
I got to talk about, you know,
Users and developers being together
Also, a lot of Dave Winner came out of my mouth
During that interview
Particularly, you'll hear a bit about
The blogger's fear getting closer to
You know, what CNN is showing on television
So I just wanted to give credit there
Because I was listening to the interview again
I was like, wow, you know, I sometimes
To open my mouth and Dave comes out
You know, that could, that could be dangerous
Sometimes, got to watch that
Okay, let me see
Yeah, I got a lot of stuff to talk about
Still, back to the music for a second
In my previous show
I solicited blatantly
For folks to come up with a show
And if you're willing to listen through some stuff
And cue some MP3s up
Maybe you can produce something
And I've already seen it in my mail
I've gotten quite a few responses
I can't respond to all of them
And I'm, you know, basically going to sit through everything
It was kind of cool to receive an audio comment
Though from Andy Affleck
Adam, hi, this is Andy Affleck
Coming to you from the Washington DC area
In the US of A
And I'm, I'm responding to your call
For help, looking for a producer
From the latest podcast
Almost forgot all about it
Because the story from your wife
After it was so hysterical
I'm sitting listening to this on
The bus ride home from work
Laughing my ass off
And people in the bus are looking at me like
I am some sort of strange person
You can see the looks and the faces like
Must be one of them carry people
Anyway, which I am
It must show
He's not like us, he's one of them carry people
So anyway, I'm intrigued
By the notion of
Uniting a producer
Meaning someone sort of
Gather up
Scoured in that for some music
And he also might be useful for the show
This is an intriguing, intriguing proposition
For me because I have been wanting to do a podcast
Since I first discovered this
Sometime in early September
I think it was
I've been listening to shows
Since just before early September
And
You know, and trying to do it
My own show
I just can't imagine pulling it again
I just can't, with a four year old kid
Finding a place to record
Alone
Is almost impossible
Right now I've got my wife corraling
Another part of the house so I can do this
But I
The idea of helping out though
In that capacity
Is sort of the side of it that really interests me
I think I've got interesting things to say
But you know, I could put that on hold
Or I could still do my own thing
But to be able to sort of help you out
In some of the things you're looking at
Finding music
Trying to come up with some new ideas
Hack, I used to be a frontier developer
Many years ago
Met Dave once too even
Daddy remembers me
But in your rate
You'd be frontier developer
Many years ago
Did a lot of work up at Dartmouth College building
Systems for them
So even on the 10th bus side
I even might be able to help out
I haven't done anything in front here
Since
Four point something or other
But
I doubt the language itself has changed all that much
Anyway, I am
Basically saying
If you're interested
I'm interested
Maybe we should
Talk and see what we can
Figure out
If you got a million of the responses
And people who've said a lot more
That's fine too
Figure out give it a shot
And that's it
Signing off
From Northern Virginia
Bye
Isn't that amazing?
I mean
The kind of people that are out there
You know, interested in music
Frontier developer
This is great
This is
I really really dig in this
And I got
Also received just like
Andy mentioned
I got a lot of comments about
Patricia's
David Bowie's story
Which lasted a lot longer than I expected
I thoroughly enjoyed it
We talked about that
A couple of times
Yesterday
I had a lot of fun interviewing
You know
I even got more out of
The interview
The David Bowie's story
Then I heard
The first four times
I squeezed it out
I was like
Tell me about David Bowie
Come on
Tell me that story
And
I even got some requests
People saying
Hey
Can't you give
Patricia like your own
Hipy story
Channel or something like that
She does have a couple more
And she says that she enjoyed
herself
And that she's looking forward to
Another episode
We got to go
Careflon
I can't stretch it too much
You know otherwise
She'll get out
You know she'll be onto us
They'll really dig in this too much
So
And you know
Don't you'll make me a slave
Even more so than I am already
So
We'll get more hippy stories
I promise you that
Hit in the email here for a second
Some came in from Toaster
Toaster says
He's been enjoying
Daily source code
And kind of made a mix
You know a lot of these bush mixes
That I've played
Well, he kind of made a mix
From the source code
Along those along that vein
And he mentioned something
That we definitely have to talk about
I do want to
Just say that we lost a great
He's a broadcaster
But he totally was a podcaster
John Peel
British DJ
Who I used
They used to air him over in the Netherlands
I mean he has to show what's
Indicated across country lines
I mean this guy was big in Europe
He used to die very young
65 to years old
Of a heart attack
He was in Lima, Peru
I don't know what he was doing there
And Toaster was also obviously a big fan
Said you know
Can you play the mighty wall
Or the Smiths
Unfortunately you know
Can't do that
Because we're trying to stay away
From many problems with the RIAA
Which sucks you know
Because I know what he's talking about
With these songs
And those are memories
You know it's important stuff
So unfortunately I can't do that
But I do want to play your mix
Because it's really really good
Back in La Blom Blom
No one's buying anything
Two weeks ago on the highway
Hard in the side holster
La Blom
Be perfect right here
Hold me right caught up
La Blom
No one's buying anything
Two weeks ago on the highway
Hard in the side holster
La Blom
Be perfect right here
Hold me right caught up
La Blom
She doesn't want my wand
I hate it
No one's buying anything
They must have had their ears on
They're blind
Look at what people are doing
What links for women to go
I hope you hear us
Back in La Blom
La Blom
The next side holster
No one's buying anything
Now shut me down
Look what's going on
La Blom
Flame
Bring back much of it
Desperate
Black Ferrari's Good Thoughts
And prayers
See you tomorrow
Ohhh
Eat all the heat off
Great Energy Boost
It's a full-surdest planet.
A lot of energy.
And it's a full-surdest planet.
love that. And I tell you that at the end of the day, a buddy of mine came over, friend of
mine came over. We had some dinner. Well, that means we're like, we're not got some pizza
came back and hung out here. And we're just talking about, you know, life and stuff and
getting older and smoke the couple joints. And then listen to this mix. It's very, very
cool. Ray, thank you very much. Looking forward to coming over your way. And who knows? I'm
sorry, toaster. Ray is from London. That's who I was going to talk about. Oh, man. See,
smoke too much. All right. Let's get it straight here. This was a, yeah, this is about the
director. He said, this is about OPML. We've been talking about this and Ray, who's
going to welcome me from London and look forward to becoming. Has some some interesting
comments and suggestions about XML, RSS, and particularly OPML and our iPodder.org
directory. Hey, Adam. This is Ray Boison here, recording from London and the UK. Looking
forward to having you here. Oh, how do I know that? It's going to be an interesting
experience for you. I have a suggestion for the podcast directly though. I'm the editor
of the technology directly. And I've noticed a lot of people are having some problems with
the XML OPML, ML files that they send me as links. A large percentage of them are not valid
in XML terms. I spend most of my iPodder time dedicated to helping the users getting
the XML files to validate properly. My suggestion would be a link on Apple.org that allows
the podcast to validate his or her's feed file. I'm not sure how to support it, but maybe
we could get Dave Warren involved to help out. Well, that's all from cold London. No, enjoy
the rest of your day. Oh, man, cold London. Thanks. That makes me feel real good. We're
moving in less than it was like three weeks now. So I am living in the midst of boxes
of my friends. I'm pretty sure that there are some validators that I don't want to, you
know, point to them without knowing if that's okay. So I know that Dave's going to hear
this and he's going to probably point me to a tutorial and a validator. I know there's
an RSS validator. There's a couple of them. And there's probably an OPML validator. There
should be. So that's that is good because I agree. I also spend a lot of my time helping out
folks who want to maintain nodes within a directory. And if you go to iPod.org and if you're
new to the podcast, this is a distributed directory. So no one owns it. No one's the boss of me.
Anyone can contribute, maintain a node. You can add sub-nodes to that. And it's completely
distributed across the web. And if you think that you want to start your top node, then you can
do that. What's cool about this now is that it's also flowing into the new iPod or software.
iPod or X. I'm using currently a beta version which is importing the entire directory. It's
actually following all the links and crawling it and parsing it and bringing it information.
And they are doing some really cool stuff. Stuff we've done in the weblog world, which is going
to give us more information about what's happening in the podcast. God, I want to say it space.
Okay, in the podcast world, let's leave it at that. And also I got a screenshot from Andrew
from the iPod or Lemon Edition team. And they're also incorporating the directory into their
next release. So exciting stuff coming up on all things iPod. Check out iPod.org if you don't
already, if you're not already using the software or just for the latest updates podcast. And of course
for the podcast directory. And now something about MP3 voice mail to email. Adam, thank you for
dare I say inventing podcasting. Oh boy, I love the daily source code. And boy, almost cut up on all
your podcast. Great stuff, very informative, very entertaining. A few podcasts back you mentioned,
it is IR for receiving MP3s in your email. I don't quite have that set up, but I have been using
J2.com's free fax voice mail email service. Basically, you get a US phone number that accepts voice
emails and faxes and then emails into you. The voice emails are limited to five minutes and the
quality is low, but it isn't too bad for a quick update or an observation. I use the voice mail
box to send myself quick reminders when I'm driving. The voice mail attachments come as GSM files.
And on my Mac, they play right in the mail program using QuickTime. They also play on Windows
with QuickTime. I think the service could be a pretty cool way to call in short podcast, like
maybe from a trade show. You can have the voice mail as forward to Danny Box, so I can imagine
a mailbox script that takes the attachments, converts them to MP3 and then posted to your blog.
I don't have the skills to make this happen, but perhaps with your vast daily source code
influence, you could encourage one or two of your listeners to look for a solution.
Another way you might benefit from these MP3 voice emails or GSM voice emails would be for
listener calling people going to call into the number, leave a voice mail and you can play
it back to your show. Since it's free pretty much anyone who's podcasting can probably afford
to now have a call in number for their podcast show. I'm really liking that idea, and I think I
had a J2 account, but when it was still called J fax, I don't know, and I actually had a local
Amsterdam number, and something happened in one away. I remember the problem is that they only
would send wave files. They wouldn't make MP3s, and they got pretty big, and I should definitely
look into that. I wish I had God, I can't really say this. I wish I had the Windows version of Skype,
or at least the Windows functionality, because you can get this cool voice mail program to add on,
and apparently it records voice mail when people Skype you. That would be really cool, you know,
to kind of route around the whole telephone company dance there, but also a call number would be
cool, but, you know, kind of think of it. Is that what I really need, you know, more things to
check, more voice mail boxes, more email boxes, I'm really drowning here folks. Let me see,
looking at the YEP external recorder, we are 20, what are we 28 minutes into this? I don't want
to make it longer than 40 minutes. I do like that as a length for a show. So what I was going
to do, I was going to review two parts of the Apple iPod presentation. I also want to play
another song from the wire to the, okay, I'm going to drop the second part of the Apple iPod
presentation, which is just you too. And I'll just, I'll sum up you two's appearance, presenting
the new YouTube iPod with what my daughter Christina said, who was 14, and she's a punk rocker,
and she said, you know, did you two ever not like suck? What do you mean? They're pretentious
and they are, and they're cell outs and go look at it on Apple's website, you can look at
the presentation, you know, and it's just sickening, man. See these guys, like pretend like this,
oh, you know, Steve Jobs is saving the music industry. This is the future of, you know,
iTunes music store is it, but meanwhile they're saying, you know, as long as we get paid, literally
the edge is saying, hey, as long as we get, you know, I love Napster, and I love it, as long as we get paid,
it just wasn't all, it was all the wrong things to say. It really was. Anyway, I was very disappointed
by the presentation of the new iPod. I know I'm a fan, you know, I got an iPod. I'm a Mac fan,
I'm an Apple fan. I love Steve Jobs's presentations. I love the way he does him. He's much thinner
by the way, of course, he's been sick, he was operated on for cancer, and it was, it wasn't taken
in back, I was like, whoa, man, he really got a lot thinner, and he looked, he just looked a little
more frail, you know, which is totally understandable, of course, but if you haven't seen him,
just trying to give you an image. And so he goes through blah, blah, blah, on some socks, you know,
we have socks for your iPod for 25 bucks for three socks, fuck that, colored socks, I'm not kidding.
And then, you know, the big moment, it's time to look at what's next.
It was a nice stage. It was a nice stage. With iPod.
All right, so that was the socks, the joke about socks. We get asked a lot. What's, what's podcasting?
Next. Oh, what's next? You know, what's next? For the iPod. You know,
at this moment, I'm going, oh man, I hope he says there's some people out there on the internet,
and I hear their podcast then. No such luck. Everybody loves music, and iPod will always be
a music device. Whoa, this is where I started to get worried. It will always be a music device, okay.
It's about listening to music, but you see what I'm saying? We've got this great device. It's got
a screen. It's got this amazing user interface with the click wheel. What else can we do with it?
What else can we add to the music? And our competitors are saying,
oh, shit. That's Dave. It's answer to the phone. You're on the source code. Good afternoon.
I'm curious. Hey, Dave. You know what? Let me see in the next episode. No, I'm, I'm, you're on the source
code right now. You have breaking news. You read the Times article?
Better with everything. It is a K-A-S article. Yeah, a podcasting is defined and accepted. It doesn't
even appear as its name. What are those? This is our previous review. Well, hold on Dave. Hold on
home. You're breaking up. I want to be able to hear you. Come again on that last bit?
It, they used the word podcasting like it was in the English language. Really?
Yes. It's not a little piece. It's a, it's a welcome to the wonderful world in it. I piece of
for the New York Times. It's, you know, they've been very sort of unwilling to accept. I mean,
yes. They really defined the camera. They play up Don and Drew. Hold on Dave. I'm going to call
you back because I want to hear this and it's just shitty. I know if I call you back a little bit of
two seconds. God damn. So this is Dave calling in with the New York Times article that we've all been
waiting for. Let's see if we get a little better connection. Yeah, I'm much better. Okay. Okay. So
sorry. Yeah. Yeah. It has a picture of, um, um, uh, the net rock skies. Oh, really? Yeah. And it has some
really great quotes for you. Um, it's just all around. We'll be able to ask these. And
the nice thing about it is sort of like what, what is really not even said is that they just use
the word podcast. Let's throw a word. Excellent. And, you know, the head of mine is, um, I mean,
we, you know, it's to have all of this stuff feel, you forget how, I'll get, if they, I'll get it.
But they say, you do food for our, uh, honest, on it, I subscription. So, you know, it's like,
I'm, uh, it's food for your iPod. Absolutely. Right, but which, you know, who's feeling your
iPod? Yeah, you know, uh, you know, so it's, it's a very, very, very adorable way, um, uh, I think we'll
look back on this moment. Yeah, you know, it's, you know, it's a very, really important just to
be different from the way that they handle. Well, I think it was, you know, now that I'm on the
head, it's pretty, it's pretty, it's best. Uh, most of the time that we'd say there's no business
model on the, or it's just like, to be radiates the fan. Right. Yeah, exactly. It's the hype of the day.
This is not like that at all. This is not, I got it right. And I think that, uh, you, you're,
like, you, to close the piece. Your quote is that, um, so we, you say, we, it is a nice,
you can receive, I guess, with, uh, be it to any, and that's the thing here's to administer.
Well, I wish I could have understood that. I hope, I hope no one who reads that article
listens to this podcast. The, uh, because, you know, you, yeah, they don't see, as he took the
off his body. Oh, that's too bad. They didn't do any fact checking there at the New York Times.
Actually, actually, this was written by, uh, Sirus, uh, was his name Dave Fabiar?
Caramel, are you? Caramel, are you? Caramel, are you? And he, you know,
I have to say that he emailed me about five or six times after, uh, we spoke on the, we actually
spoke on a Skype call, and he checked a whole bunch of facts. Yeah. He, he was very, very thorough.
And I think he's a freelance writer. I think this might have been his first big piece for,
is it, I mean, how many words is it? It's not one piece. And, um, I don't know how many words it is,
maybe 1000 words. But, um, it's a great piece for podcast. And it's, uh, it's a, it's a piece
for RSS, by the way. I mean, it's, it might be the first article that's part of RSS for a long time.
They've been supporting it. But it was, it was really nice about it. It was an interview with, um,
big K, and the variety of tick conversations. Yeah. Yeah. Actually, this is that, you know,
the reason why we'd use three users. Yeah. And so it's not, you know, we don't focus to be on
the, you know, or the wiring in the plug and stuff like that. We want to do this with some of
what people are doing with it. And that's that. We just want users and developers to party together.
Yeah. But, you know, when it comes time to the story is users, the developers,
perfades in the background, the developer, he can get possible for the users to put on a
don't on true show, you know. Yeah. Absolutely. There's a, yeah.
Cool. Now, if you pointed to this from scripting news,
bottom of scripting news, and I'll still, but then I bought it. Or two excellent. Excellent.
Yeah. Yeah. This is good. This is a validation of the ice piece and, you know, thanks
here at your time. Really. Yeah. Well, thanks everybody, because everyone's been a part of this.
This has been great. Thanks everybody. Thanks, everyone. All right, Dave, I'll, I'll check
you later, man. I'm going to play some tunes. Thanks to the news, buddy. Hi. Sorry about the
quality there of Skype, but I don't know why I decided to sound like shit. It doesn't matter.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Yeah. The Kors foralec. Yeah. Mmm, yeah. Yeah. I don't know what influenced me. Yeah? ese yeah. Yeah. That's the hardest I can know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Happy in the show. They got one but they like you. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Good. Yeah, it's actually this Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Do better for me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
This is a good day, and there's some other important things in there that I'm happy
to see.
I'm seeing recognition as Mr. Winner of the inventor of RSS. It is indeed nice that the
New York Times is writing that.
Okay, let's, you know, it's 40 minutes, a little bit longer into this, what are we now?
This is a very small display, 41 minutes.
Okay, can't do a show without something nutty from Pete, from Raster Web Audio.
He's so into this podcasting thing, and this is the latest episode of Crack Me Up.
Hope you don't mind if I play it in its entirety.
This is Draster Web Audio, 4024, and 26.
What we're going to do here is, you know, I'm preparing for the data to slash dot, add some sort
audio commentary thing where you can provide your comments in audio.
So I thought in preparation for that, I kind of do some of the more popular ones, the
ones you're going to see anyway, so that way they'll be done, you won't need to do them.
So here we go.
Yeah, but does it run Linux?
Natalie Bartman, imagine a bail wolf cluster of those things.
Microsoft sucks, but it's not open source.
Did you even read the article?
This isn't new.
I've been doing this for 10 years.
Cowboy Neil, BSD sucks.
First post, BSD is better than Linux.
I have poured hot grits down my pants.
Thank you.
The site is already slashed at it.
Apple sucks.
That's it.
Thank you for tonight.
I love you.
That was awesome.
I was cracking up here in that for the third time now, fabulous.
All right, everybody.
And that's going to do it for the source code for today.
I will do the Apple stuff another time.
Yeah, I want to be positive.
Now that we've got some good, good energy flow in the New York Times article, I was going
to say in the closet about the iPod presentation, and I know Steve Jobs is going to read
New York Times.
He's going to read this and he's going to hear about our podcast and maybe he'll
start singing.
And again, maybe he will.
This yet is still pretty attractive.
But I think that brush metal look would have been more of a brush.
There.
Look at my good.
A metal tampon.
Two strings coming out.
One for head four, one for the line out jack.
And I'll be back tomorrow.
I'm going to hospital my mom.
So it'll probably be there.
I like post on the show, but I'll have some music out there.
And thank you very much for tuning in.
And take care.
Adam Curry, Adam Curry.com, live.kirt.com, and DailySourceco.com, see ya.