I'm not gonna have to do it in the evening, good morning, wherever you happen to be listening to this more rather than the source code.
Let's go to the list.
home as a framist of my web world. Even though it's been really crazy.
to record a source code. And in this case, I'm joined by a guest, although he'll only
be a minor participant in the story. His name is Taxi Eric. He's my regular wheelman.
And besides being good buddy, he's also kind of like a gypsy ring, wherever I'm stuck.
Whatever problem I'm in, I give McCall and he'll come and bail me out if necessary.
So let me just explain what...
from the car right now we're doing about what are we doing Eric 150 kilometers now we're coming
from the northern part of the Netherlands in the province of Croningen which is near the city of
Croningen which is a big college town and what else they do there yeah they suck natural gas out
of mother earth that's what they do in Croningen and it's quite a drive from my house it's actually
yeah oh boy what is 175 miles and I drove halfway up to
So, how are we going?
I go home and drive over.
He jumped in my car, left his cab waiting with the meter running.
With the meter running.
Because I had some business to do today as you probably remember.
Yes, there was my last morning radio show for Radio Veronica.
It was crazy.
a lot of driving in between.
And today is the start of my new life, new life day one,
everybody.
And that means that we're starting to wind things down
and get things prepared for our move, our pending move
to the UK.
So the good news is there's the House of Belgium
is sold.
That happened just last week.
So we're all pretty pumped about that.
So now we're going to start looking for something in the UK,
probably in the Surrey or Kent region, which is South of London.
And so one of the things I promised myself, let's see,
about four years ago, I noticed in Amsterdam
that the trauma helicopters, which are here, they're yellow,
which some bad happens.
You're going to be real happy to see one of these guys
to pick up and take you to the hospital.
That they were operating in a very difficult rooftop situation
on top of the hospital.
And that they were actually doing all the servicing
and their fueling at Svipol Airport, which
are equivalent of JFK or any major league airport.
It's a really big hub for...
for the rest of Europe.
Which is very costly because it doesn't matter if you're a trauma helicopter or your
to pay the same amount of money.
about I think two hundred.
they can carry more people in the...
said, hey, that's not not right.
And being in the aviation myself, I said, well, why don't we get a heliport where they
can land nearby and we'll operate that.
We'll let these guys fuel up and we'll make it $40 instead of $200.
Now you have to know that the Netherlands doesn't have a large aviation history when it comes
to local aviation.
And it was very difficult.
Many people have tried to get a heliport known as ever succeeded.
It took me almost four years of going through city councils, different versions of them,
you know, people leave after a while.
And finally I got all the paperwork.
self-appartner, Helle Holland, which is probably the only real helicopter coming to talk to.
And they'll start exploring the heliport probably before the end of this year.
So they've been to visit me several times their main offices.
It's all done with fitting that for this particular case nightclub see their facility
and hang out.
7.25 pm, by the way, this is Monday, September 1st.
And we're on our way back.
Eric is going to drop me off around the middle of the Netherlands in Aden.
Wednesday today. What did I say? Monday. Okay, so maybe I should not smoke any more this joint.
Okay, it's Wednesday, September 1st. Thank you very much.
So just briefly about the radio show yesterday because it was kind of fun and I posted a link,
certainly NSFW to what happened during the last show, the management. No, not my colleagues,
but the actual management of the station felt that after a year because it was just a year that I promised
to do the show of basically being silly and giggling about women all morning long, it was time to send
me a really good stripper and that was jeweled parrots. What do you think? She was very good looking.
So and despite the fact that it was radio, it kind of worked. She came in as she said,
she was the cleaner and then oh boy, it's warm in here. I never seen a cleaner with high white
boots though. That was kind of a giveaway.
I want to talk to you about a couple other things.
There's so much that I need to discuss, but I just haven't had the time.
There's so many different audio bits I want to let you listen to.
I've been picking up blog posts.
I've been picking up people who are starting to enclose their posts in RS2.0 feeds within
closures.
I got a beautiful long email from Dave Slusher from evilgeniuskronicles.org, which I really haven't
had a chance to parse properly.
But it was definitely a hey neighbor.
How you doing?
Why don't we get acquainted note?
I'm really happy about that.
Because this is source code where users and developers party together.
That's my entire mission.
And currently we're working on the iPod platform.
Anyone I don't know if Dave Slusher is a user or a developer, and I think it's fine to be
both.
way heavier on one side or the other. I'm trying to beef up my developer or I guess
system integration competency so I can do more modeling and developing and prototyping
of what I want my computer to do and the different bits that are already in there that we
just need to connect to each other. So the iPod platform which we've been talking about
for quite a while is picked up some steam rather quickly thanks to an article from the
inquire inquire not the inquire but the inquire which is publication owned by the register.
And the piece was written I don't have it with me actually here but it was written by
Doug Moni and it was it was a title of the piece it was great MP3 fodder with iPodder
and it was a very very flattering piece basically saying hey here's something new and I think
what Doug did was really important he put into plain well written English words.
what we're trying to achieve with this and I've pointed to it on my web blog.
Please check it out so you can find the link at live.curry.com
and you can see if you're not quite sure what we're talking about here or
where this should go, Doug explains it perfectly.
And I do know Doug from many years ago
and only opportunity to let you know about that now
since he's writing about me. There's some history between us
because back in 1983 I was working at
I'm sorry, not A3, 93, 92, 93. I was working at MTV
had already been doing a lot of online stuff with America online.
Then before then it was what was it? It was Vienna,
Vienna online or Quanto. Anyways, all the online services had finally gotten myself
in Panics.net in New York was distributing my,
what I then called, cyberslees, which was kind of gossip news
through my .pland file, which meant you had to finger
my Panics account and upper pop the day's news
in the form of a .pland file.
This was before Web, but in fact we only had something
called Go for them, which is very much hyperlinked
like Structron, it was all text based,
and basically worked best on a Unix terminal
with your arrow keys to follow a link to the next server,
but it certainly was nothing quite like
the worldwide web that we know today.
And so I got in trouble, apparently,
that was my first experience with terms of use
and Panics shut me off, you know,
and like, who did I think I was?
Of course I was this commercial dude trying to turn the internet
into a,
and no more access for you, and certainly not for doing this kind of stuff, because it
overtaxed their servers.
And then I keep quite remember how I met the guys at digx.net, which were in Reston, Virginia.
I think it was Reston.
It was in Virginia, definitely.
Bolt or more, oh shit, well, Doug will kill me that I don't, and there's two dogs who will kill me that I don't know, and RS as well, and several people.
Because these guys were just a bunch of, really a bunch of data...
If you are a bokeh, you are a bokeh.
Ah, okay, that's...
um...
it's starting out to be pretty strange show
uh... so anyway we got into it i think i saw an ad for the uh... somewhere that
you could uh... buy a uh... server space
for tea i think it was uh...
it was. And so I got a sun three card with maybe it was 40 or 50 megs of this space at
the time. Just go crazy on and that's actually when we registered MTV.com. They said,
you know, you can have an IP address or you could register it to something.
That's, I don't think that's that important anymore, but at the time,
certainly for brand like MTV, you know.
too and of course that was all done.
That's why I hooked up with DJX and these guys were there along along
And Doug, I think, I don't believe he was there in the beginning and he was already doing
PR stuff.
But these guys were a hoot.
They were originally boogah, boogah.
they are that they, um,
Florida outfit, man, I'm horrible at this.
Anyway, I think they all did okay,
didn't they made some money and we all like each other still.
So it was nice that the duck picked up on that,
but he's always been falling what I've been doing
so that it's really...
And tomorrow we have a photo shoot.
My wife is doing a photo shoot at the castle,
but I'm going to be home all day, which will be nice.
I get to sleep in a little bit, which I try to do this morning,
but still a work at six.
Still in the rhythm of the 330 wake up call.
And I'll be able to do some proper preparations on the source
code, because there's so much happening,
and there's so many ideas.
And it was great to hear the duck K of IT conversations
platform thing and I'm now getting more questions from people like Taxi Eric. I just want to plug in their MP3 device. I don't know when iPod is my dumb
something that she plays music on and she hooks it up to the computer and I said,
well, you know, I explained that now we could make it so you just hook it up to
the computer for it to charge and we pick up in the morning you've got all your
new shows. Which would be what shows would you like to hear Eric if you had to
listen to anything and it could be produced anywhere it could be anything you
wanted or kind of...
Do me music or just also anything you want if you want to be talk or music or in the morning
I want to have some information I want to hear some news about last night. I want to have some news
to happen today and I want to know something about the traffic, I want to know something
about the weather.
What kind of things, you know?
So, that's really, you can hear now immediately how community-based a radio show is.
He really wants to know what's going on in his world and he's a cab driver, so what does
he want to do?
like it's that simple.
You just have to find your community.
It's just like web logs.
Only it does.
learning curve, but maybe not even.
If you look at a lot of weblog software,
there's sometimes there's a learning curve
you're for that.
And with audio blogging, it'll be the same.
And I'm definitely going to delve back into what kind
of software we need to do this kind of audio blogging
on the desktop, which has infinitely more capabilities
and possibilities right now for what you can do with audio
versus an audio blogging service where you call up
the phone or where you drop a, you know,
where it takes over your your internal microphone
and records it for you.
There's a lot to be said for that.
But the feature said that you can do on the desktop
is infinitely more rich, I think.
All right, quick break now because I got a couple more things
to say after I'm done.
This is something I picked up.
um, the came from and see what feed it is.
the blog digger.
from their NP3 feeds.
I'll link to the original source from this, although it was kind of funny how they start
off and start ragging on the fact that you're not doubtful on to get from the original source
but you're hearing it somewhere.
It's a nice, it's a fine tune that I like because it speaks to both sides of our party
to the users and the developers.
Check out every OS sucks.
Well, hi there.
Thank you for downloading another fine quality comedy product from 3Dedrals and a Peggy
and your friends at MP3.com.
Good for you.
Of course, if you've downloaded this from Napster, screw you.
You know what, free isn't good enough for you?
You gotta rip us off.
That's okay.
I will find you and I will kill you.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
You see, I come from a time in the 1970s when computers were used for two things.
play pong. Nothing in between, you see. You didn't need a fancy operating system to play
pong, and the men who went to the Moon God bless him did it with no mouse, and a plain text
only black and white screen and 32 kilobytes of brown. But then around both the late 70s
home computers started to do a little more than play pong. Very little horn.
Why computer started to play games? Balance checkbooks? Why you could play a saxon on your Apple
2 or write a book all with a computer that had 32 kilobytes of RAM. Was enough to go to the Moon?
It was enough for you. It was a golden time. A time before windows. A time before mouses. A time
before the internet and bloatware and a time before every OS sucked.
Oh man.
the olden times make them.
I'd laugh and play all night and day on Sork 1, 2 and 3.
The Amiga Vic 20 in the Sinclair 2, the TRS 80 and the Apple 2.
it was a much, but it was enough. But then Xerox made a prototype. Steve Jobs came on the scene,
red of mice and menus, windows, icons, a trash and a bit...
TV said to Xerox, boys turn your heads and cough.
When no one was looking to rip their interfaces up, stole every feature they had seen put
it in a cute box with a tiny little screen.
Mac OS 1 ran that machine, only cost 5,000 bucks.
But it was slow, it was buggy, so they wrote it again, and now they're up to OS 10, they'll
charge it for the base...
Every OS waste your time, you're the best top to the lap.
Everything since Apple does, just a bunch of crap.
From Microsoft and Macintosh to LinLine and Linux.
Every computer crashes, because every OS sucks.
Well then Microsoft jumped in the game, copied Apple's interface with an OS named Windows.
rose and rose. Then Windows 95, then 98, man, solitaire never ran so great and every single
version came out late, but I guess that's the way it goes. But that bloatware will crash
and delete your work in TME, man. None of them work, but gates may be Richard and Captain
Kirk. But the Windows OS blows and sucks at that same time. I've treated in here right for
what? It's top of the line from the CompuHut, the fridge stove and toaster, never crash on
me. I should be able to get on live without a Ph.D. My phone doesn't take a week to
glue it, but TV doesn't crash when I'm muted. A mishasket text in my floppy drive, I wish
that it was still alive. But it ain't the hardware, man. It's just that every OS.
Now there's Lennox or Lennox, I don't know how you say it or how you install it or use it or play it or
where you download it or what programs run, but Lennox or Lennox don't...
Before you say it, it's getting great press though, how it survives if anyone's gas
in me asked me to great big mess for a leotist nerdy schmucks.
It's free they say if you can get it to run, the geek say hey, that's half the fun yeah,
but I got a girlfriend and things to get done.
The Linux OS sucks.
I'm sorry to say it, but it dies.
Every OS waste your time from the desktop to the laptop.
Everything since the abacus, just a bunch of crap.
Cause every OS sucks, every computer crashes it
Cause every OS...
beautiful every OS sucks and that drives right to the heart of what we're talking about
That's something that both users and developers know but explain both from a different vantage point
users know that every OS sucks because
Every OS crashes even XP. Oh even OS 10 something always will suck eventually
Every developer knows that every OS sucks because well they deal with it every single day
And there's always bits that suck in there and something I've heard Dave went what Dave Winer say
probably read him say hey
That all software sucks all software is buggy and it's absolutely true now that I've been putting my own stuff together
I know what the mistakes are in in iPodder. I know what's wrong
I know it should be working differently and until you really dig into the code you won't know
But you'll encounter it you'll find say hey that's strange. Why's it doing that?
It may not come back. He might trip over it something might replicate but there's bugs in there
Shit, we were just booting up the in-cart navigation. I might Audi A8
But you think I paid enough fucking mula for it to
For it all work the same thing is just it was rebooting and then finally caught and everything worked
So I'm gonna wind up a source code for today. Just one do a little plug for taxi Eric because
Well, that's part of how this kind of stuff works
You know, we've got a little individual part of deals happening. I'm getting a discount on this ride right baby
So if you're if you ever come to Amsterdam and you need
Someone to wheel you around town at a good price and comfortable car. He's got a Mercedes
CD elegance okay, 800 the from the elegant series
And he's very clean and very he's very sweet boy
But actually
Just fun to just talk about taxes for a second in Amsterdam
Many many years ago there was basically a monopoly the taxi you get a correct correct me if I'm wrong
Eric on this the TCA the the taxi central
I'm so they they basically had all the medallions and
You couldn't really compete with them, but there were some guys
Because you had to buy a medallion because what a medallion cost back the day
These days was 100,000
Guilders for only one-third of but one-third of a medallion so three guys
Together would pay 300,000 guilders at the time was about a hundred and fifty thousand dollars
Okay, so for one medallion to be split up by three guys
So you could do that you could because the monopoly
And but of course it was
And they had the radio transmitting system and could dispatch cars etc and
So some guys said you know screw it will just be independence and you could they could wait by a could you wait by a phone?
By a call phone or you had your own clients or own clients mobile phone
Telephone everything you know, okay and
But that of course took a major investment on these guys' part, you know,
going with about 40 or 50 thousand dollars, basically by your one-third mind you of a medallion.
So these cars, of course, were... it would always be on one car. Eric? No, it could just be three cars.
It was three guys, so it was all the way 24 hours a day. Okay, so then yeah, three guys running on
one medallion. So we had little micro pockets that started to pop up. And what really,
boom for these guys was really the introduction of GSM mobile telephony. Because now you had
these groups of guys who each had their own customers, you know, once you wind up with someone,
they hand you a business card and hey, can I call you again here? It's my cell phone number,
call me. And they started connecting these networks together. So if you're in a town like Amsterdam
and you know, you don't just know your two other colleagues on the medallion, you know, maybe 50
guys and all kinds of other groups. So what they do is if they could...
make a client run themselves they call up one of their buddies uh... because
you know that's not just spoke to uh... to keep
and people's over its triple airport so maybe he's done all call him up so
they have this all mapped out in their head and they have all these
really appreciate it when you see it and the phone calls just keep flying all the time.
And he calls someone else and he pick it up and then they'd hook him up later on.
So it was a total barter system.
And some guys got a little bit smarter and we're charged guys to give them work.
So that kind of coupled along for a while.
But then the city of Amsterdam did something very interesting.
And this day don't know why.
They said, you know what, we're going to change the rules.
No longer is there a limited amount of medallions.
We can start a taxi company.
All you have to do is pass the test.
Well, you could only imagine that this brought in a lot of really bad drivers.
What?
Bad cars also.
Everything, bad drivers, bad cars.
They didn't know the way.
They didn't know how to speak.
They didn't know how to open the door, open the truck.
What's just shit?
Now besides that, you had a whole bunch of guys sitting around who would invest at $50,000.
And you know, within the day before two, a couple of years before, who were going to...
pay that off probably for the rest of their professional career just as a part of the
cost of doing. And these guys, yeah they got fucked basically.
So if you're lucky you can still get for the same, but you did pay 40,000 euros, I say
you're rose. Yeah. Now maybe you get, if you're lucky you get two, maybe two and a half
tasks. For that same medallion. For the same number.
Okay, so, and that really stirred up a whole bunch of shit in the cab world. And so now
the free, actually I think, although it sounds really shitty, I think it's, I think it's
actually very good because the free market at work, you see what's happening. You see
the people who have hooked up with someone that they like and they appreciate and they're
willing to pay for a courtesy and service and a clean car. Now they pay a little bit more
and they, and they get a really good deal.
to our, uh, yeah.
again it's not just for a cat.
yeah i'm gonna drive away as fast as possible
all right so if you're coming to Amsterdam
let me know send me an email out of it career dot com
all the up with the taxi Eric
this is the source code we still have, what do we have?
But we've got 45 minutes until we hit, until we hit Hillversome.
You know what we'll do?
We'll try and upload this at a hotspot at a Wi-Fi point.
We get to Hillversome, so we can get it up to the server then.
And then by the time I get home, I already have responses to it.
It's a wonderful thing.
And tomorrow, of course, we'll go in depth a little bit more about the iPod platform and
the latest updates and recent happenings around iPodder.
And hopefully some more cool bits from stuff that we've been thinking up around the
net because we are definitely making some stuff happen here.
Until then, I'm Adam Curry.
If again, if you want to react, Adam and Curry.
Oh my God