I'm counting casting with Adam Curry.
The power of the Lord is coming.
Yeah.
Howdy.
Thursday, November 11th, 2004,
coming to you from Curry Castle and Flanches Belgium.
Flanches.
And to the Belgium.
It's your daily source code.
I'm Adam Curry here in the barn.
Studio in the complex.
The power of the Lord is coming.
Okay.
So, how you doing everybody?
So, in kind of a stay at home day,
Christina didn't have to go to school.
What was the deal for Christina?
How come we didn't have to go to school today?
What?
Back at the school.
Oh, it's a Belgian holiday.
And so, the international school has a holiday.
Even though it's a Belgian holiday.
Really.
How many Belgian teachers work at the international school?
Huh?
Another teacher.
Right.
Okay.
So, what is Vapa Stilston?
What is that about?
What's that holiday about?
The end of the war.
Something about the end of the second world.
The first world war is not it.
And I think it's the first world war.
Okay.
You got to stay home.
As long as you got to stay home, right?
Well, howdy.
Y'all.
This is the source code.
Patricia is in Amsterdam.
She's working with Movers over the next two days.
Getting stuff packed up there.
Now, at the same time, on Monday, moving into the bunker in Amsterdam is the Dutch version of the apprentice,
the Trump reality show.
Or, I should say, it's not really the Dutch version because they pretty much just stole the format and of twisted around
that it's kind of the same thing.
Only don't have to pay any format rights.
So, a famous lawyer named, but on Moscow, he will be the guy that needs to eventually have an apprentice to replace him.
And he's actually a pretty funny guy.
He's a kind of like a celebrity lawyer.
He does a lot of high profile cases.
He's been doing more and more.
Really showbiz, like celebrity related stuff recently.
Which is okay.
You know, it's the courts.
It's all show business.
So, there'll be, I think, to start off with 10 candidates, that gets little down to eight pretty quickly,
who will all be living at the bunker, working at the bunker, and trying to get that coveted spot of being the next,
Brom Moskovitz, entertainment lawyer at large.
So, that will last for about three and a half months.
So, you know, also, we have to get all this stuff moving in and out.
I'm really happy about that because, you know, you make a killing on renting out the TV production, believe me.
And on Monday, the movers come here.
We're there also packing Tuesday, then Wednesday, Patricia's in England, getting all the stuff set,
then on Thursday, Christina's when you and I go over, so we have to stay in the castle.
All there's going to be is one bed here.
Yeah.
One bed.
How about a TV?
Do we get to keep one TV set?
Or we just keep the internet connection.
And we just laptop it.
Yeah.
Right.
Oh, let me guess a good shot at DVD.
The one that I picked up for you with Don and Drew.
Okay.
Tomorrow, which is Friday, the BBC are dropping by to see the frickin' mess that this place is.
They insisted they wanted to see how a podcast is made.
Well, they're going to get it.
That's for sure.
Everything around me is pretty much boxes and stuff is piled up highs.
I've been keeping up to speed on that.
And the name of this BBC show, it's BBC 2 television,
is the culture show.
Tonight, actually, is the first episode.
It's coming on.
I think it's on right now.
But there seem to be archives of it coming up on the BBC TV 2 website.
BBC 2 website.
So hopefully we can watch that over the internet as well.
And I guess they just want to know what podcasting is about more or less.
I got a mouse finger.
Or just a trackpad finger.
Yes, they talked about having iPod or ears.
And actually, I'm now wearing Altic Lansing headset, which is...
It's a real bitch to put on.
It's kind of a plastic headset with the headphone parts.
Kind of...
I guess you're...
You kind of hang them on your...
A little bit half on your ears.
And then there's the plastic bar that goes through the back of the head.
So it's kind of like a foldable headset that you really don't put on the top of your head.
But more in the back here in the neck.
It takes a while to figure out how to put it on.
And then it may still be just wearing it some foolish feedback words away.
But it seems to work and the quality is good.
The sound level is also good.
And there's nothing sticking in my ear because
I said it's kind of irritated from having all these...
These ear buds stuck in them for hours on end recording and listening to podcasts.
And now my finger...
...that I use the Mac power book to record everything with.
I use it for everything.
And I've been mousing so much on a track pad lately that now my index finger my right hand hurts.
And whatever I need to exert any power with it.
So there's this...
What is this?
There's a Bluetooth mouse that I got, which is pretty awesome.
And just click it once and it kind of hooks up to the power book.
And then you can take over all track commands with this Bluetooth mouse.
What's nice about it is it has a right click and a left click.
So it's a two button mouse and it has a scroll wheel on top,
which is something sorely missing from most Mac mice these days.
So I've been using that to alleviate the mouse finger.
Getting back here in Holland.
Situation post-dalephone hospital murder is not good, my friends.
Free speech is under attack.
People are burning up each other's churches, mosques, schools.
Now in the media it may come across a little bit bigger than it all actually is.
But there are actually schools being burnt down.
And people are lighting fire to churches and mosques.
Everyone's trying to calm the situation down.
Politicians are freaking out.
What's crazy is that there's two politicians who have also been quite vocal about muslim culture
and integration into the Dutch culture.
One of the Mackehid builders.
And the other one is Ion here she is,
who actually made that movie with Teo von Hoch.
The movie that probably ultimately was one of the direct reasons
that he was assassinated, murdered, brutally.
Not that that should be any reason whatsoever for any type of art or free expression.
But all the papers now and I don't understand how you can do this.
If you're in a governmental leading role,
sure you should have all the protection you need and you should get all kinds of protection
and it should be known that you have protection.
And you should have really amazingly good personal security and protection.
But what they do here is they say, well, you know,
well, the literal word is umlahtoku,
which means they've dived under or they're in hiding.
So they're saying that, oh, I'm hiding and I wake up one morning in this house
and I have lunch at a different place and I go to bed in that place
and I haven't seen my home in two weeks.
I'm like, what the hell is that?
I mean, how bad is the situation that these politicians are actually going into hiding?
That makes no sense to me as a leadership role to say,
we're in hiding, that seems like chicken shit.
So it's not good.
And the media, of course, is flipping out on this.
They love it.
They have some fear to play on and they're using everything they can.
And everyone's jumping in.
It's like a big, you know, pile jump of people trying to calm down the nation
and get stuff, you know,
people just going for whatever they can.
It's really, it's kind of nasty.
And everyone's confused and people are frightened.
And I'd have to say the thing that you hear the most now is folks saying,
well, you know, we think we're just going to leave the country.
And, you know, was it like 20, 30,000 people ready to go at this moment?
So it's not good.
And of course, this all just coincidentally coincides with our leaving,
moving to the UK next week.
That wasn't planned, but boy, I'm not sorry about it.
I'm not sorry about it right now.
How about you, Christina?
What?
How do you feel about leaving right now?
Hey, you don't want to go?
Why not?
You want to stay at school?
You'd like all your friends at school?
Well, that sucks.
Two months ago, it was no problem.
Yeah, I knew it to myself.
Yeah, we needed a question, did.
What about your health?
Oh, you didn't know the kids at school?
Yeah.
Well, you're going to meet new kids from new lands.
You sound really enthusiastic.
Okay.
What are you on your MSN?
No.
Okay.
Alrighty.
Well, onto a couple of podcasts, then.
Some stuff that I've picked up and stuff that I want to share.
We also got some music to play.
Actually, a couple of songs that are all non-R-I-A-A music for you on the daily source code.
There's a new, or there actually has been a note in the podcast directory entitled Religion.
And there's been more podcasts coming out.
And that note of the iPod.org directory is growing quite slowly.
And just going to play a little bit of a new, what I call a Godcast, a God podcast that came in.
Not so much is to listen to the message.
But I'm always happy when religious broadcasts are show up.
Because if there's one thing those guys know, it's how to make money.
It's not begins, begins kind of a journey for us as a church.
As we're going to begin to kind of explore what community is through the voices of our community.
And in preparation for this, I wrote a little something here.
It says that there's no need.
I don't know if they're actively soliciting donations.
But they're not about four or five different religious broadcasts.
And that's a really good thing.
You know, this is a great avenue, a great outlet for people to share their church sermons,
or temple gatherings, or whatever it is.
It's totally appropriate.
And yes, indeed.
You can also probably do quite well at getting some real donations.
And thank we encourage that, too.
I was perusing through my latest subscriptions.
And all the shows that I am subscribed to with my iPod.
I mean, I listened to a lot of podcasts that come through an audio.weblogs.com, which is
a really great place to sample them.
But I'm subscribed to the show Coverville.
Have been ever since the Abba Coverville show, which just totally killed me.
And today, there was a referral to the Daily Source Code in Coverville.
And that was about the David Bowie story that Patricia told.
By the way, still to come as she's not here tonight, but hopefully tomorrow night Patricia
will tell the Stevie Nick story.
Don of Don Andrew has been bugging me to get her to tell this.
It's a short story and it's just gross.
So, you know, I know you're all going to love it.
But right now, here that little bit and actually a song that goes along with it from a coverville
from the episode from two days ago.
I'm going to go ahead and get to a song that kind of got inspired to play here by.
Wow, I guess it's Adam Curry again.
I'm going to mention him a couple of times on my show.
But his wife apparently had a trist with David Bowie around the time that space oddity
was becoming popular.
So I decided, well, I'll dig up a cover version of space oddity.
So here it is. Enjoy.
Come on.
Start the mission and make us look new.
Come, Come on.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Where am I sitting in a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent
and going to get a tent and going to get a tent and going to get a tent
Your circumstance, there's something wrong, can you hear me, make your tongue, can you hear me, make your tongue, can you hear me, make your tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you
hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can you hear my tongue, can
Coming to you via satellite, it's Coverville, featuring space audity there performed by
the Flying Pickets, a former kind of a theater troupe out of London back in the 80s
that had Occupella and one of their productions, and during the show, realized that they
enjoyed doing the Occupella a lot more than doing the theater group.
Okay, there you go, courtesy of Coverville, podcast, you should check out, actually a podcast
which I've made a part of what I'm just calling the pod squad, and people asked me
all the time, particularly journalists asked me, you know, so what do you listen to?
Can you mention some other podcasts, and of course I send them off to the directorie,
I send them off to audio.weblogs.com to check out stuff there.
So finally, I've just gotten so tired of people asking me the same question over and over again.
I put together a list, and I link to it today from iPod.org, so you can find it there.
And it's basically just, well, what it really is, the underlying files and OPML file, I actually
link to it in the posting of RSS feeds that I'm currently subscribed to, I took a couple
out that, you know, that I don't want you to know that I subscribe to.
But the other ones are just kind of the things that I definitely always have streaming into
my iPod.
So you can check that out, and what actually, what I'm hoping that some of the iPod or folks
might look at is since this is also an OPML file, it's kind of like a reading list,
so maybe you could compare it to programming, like a network, or maybe this is my personal
station or something, I don't know.
But what would be cool is if you could drag that OPML file into iPod or have it subscribed
to all of those programs and, you know, give you an option, you know, subscribe to all
of them or make them all as one feed so that there's only basically one channel, so
it would be, you know, in this case, it would be the pod squad and anything that's new
on the pod squad would come into one playlist.
The most important thing, of course, is if you take that whole OPML file out, is then
it needs to unsubscribe and all of those different feeds.
So anyway, just some stuff to work with, and I gotta tell you, I've been so swamped with
doing stuff here.
Got the contracts finally sorted out by the way for the UK House and what we transferred
to our down payments and everything seems to be on track if banking traffic will hopefully
get money from 0.8 a.m. be in time.
Anyway, what was I saying, yeah, because of all the, all the, just all the craziness around
here, I haven't really had time to check out the iPod or developers list, I've got to
dive back into that.
Hopefully this weekend, after I take care of filling up a couple of boxes with stuff that
were definitely not taking with us.
Remember the George Carlin stuff piece?
Well, you know, that's what I'm doing, trying to cut down on all the stuff.
A podcast that I, that is also, by the way, on my pod squad list, is Aldo Castineda.
He presented himself pretty early on in the podcasting days, looking and do some stuff
with the, actually, he was immediately looking for business models and trying to figure out
how to get some money flowing through these podcasts.
And he has his own podcast called the Biter 2 of Business News.
It's really interesting because, well, the whole thing is actually, I'll play the intro
to it.
It's kind of soft, but I'll shut up in a minute and you can hear it.
It's a format and it's very short.
It's based on Julia Child, actually, so listen to just a bit here, but Biter 2 of Business
News.
Well, I was great.
Do it yourself, first.
So I have a whole chicken carcass here, and I'm just gonna whack it up with my fever, and
I have a pumice rubber hammer, and that makes it what she's doing to do things.
This is a Megabyte or two of Business Legal and Financial News, served in one or two minute
bite-sized chunks inspired by Julia Child, welcome to my kitchen.
Super fast, a Biter 2 of Business Legal and Financial News.
I'm the guy who manages the law finance and Business Sections on iPodder.org.
So I just wanted to update everybody to two new entries in the law category.
The first is a weekly policy update from the Center for Democracy and Technology.
That'll be listed under law, and then the other one is WLF, Williams Law Firm, WebLug,
of legal news and observations, including a quote, the day and daily updates.
Both of them, I think, well, actually know the Center for Technology and Democracy is quite
a long podcast.
It's the audio section from a video rolling, they do weekly and put on by one of their analysts.
The way you hear here is Aldo, who is clearly maintaining a node in the directory, talking
a little bit about the new shows that are coming in on the business front there.
So make sure you subscribe to his podcast, always bringing you the latest stuff in the
business news.
That's kind of the way we got it.
I guess kind of got to work together to figure out what you want to listen to and what, you
know, how are you going to fit all these great shows into your day, right?
You've got to find some guide.
So check out Aldo if you're looking for business stuff.
Palisine and leader, if that has died or he is not a liver failure, a mysterious blood disease
or a poisoning plot, like Schrodinger's cat, he may be half dead and have a live while
crying.
Visitors fighting to take his place, connive, flora the voters who backed carry off seeking
therapy.
Deepest notice, because they're wary and staring at walls when there's nothing to see.
It's called post-delections, election, trauma, sufferers want to move to Canada or back
home with mama and the Scott Kiererson.
Hold on a second.
You noticed that there's no tap dancing.
Sounds like she didn't realize that her tap dance shoes were either not on or maybe
the track wasn't recording.
Well, I'll just try and help out there.
Priority, no durer or has been dismissed for doing research on her own.
If she was holding out for Nagyoti, there would be a fewer or Scott gets the chair and
Derek also screaming as well.
This bulletin, just in era, that's condition is worse.
He's in a coma or he's speaking or heading for Palisine in a verse.
That biggest news since Osama and Lawrence voters took up for books and provided the
post that turns Republicans from the losers and the voters stay tuned for like breaking
up to that tap dance and podcasting news.
All right, little help from your friends and you'll get by, right?
So coming through on openpodcast.org, haven't been able to get the tap dance and podcast
news, their own feed yet, but working on it, my friends, working on it.
Now time for some ass knocking on the daily source code.
If you know the words feel free to sing along, please buy all means.
Bob Schneider, this feels good right here, this is nice.
All right, let's do this now, people, let's do it, here we go.
Let's party like some better cake, don't drop it to ground, like it's no good thing.
Bob, this is something like a sack of a pair, pretty little peery night, it's actually
a new fan.
But the match is a good match, it's a new vibe, but the people come back up pretty, blue,
I got to teach the world to sing the song, so we can now get together now and get the
bow.
Let's shake it together now.
I wanna do this by this mama, fucking wrong now, yeah, this time to crack it down, yeah.
And it's not a team can't move on, it's not a problem with the goodies together now.
And it's not a team can't move on, it's not a problem.
You can't even come, go, you're not because they're not all too bad, it's not too much.
But I'm still getting play, max relaxing the booty group, do all the crazy for this shit,
I'm supposed to do it, I got nothing else, that was a ton of men,
while I took care of all the fans when I was a little kid.
People coming up and asking me how to go up against the land like you got to be such a bad motherfucker,
moment in my sea, I said, show me shit, it just came naturally, yeah, yeah.
It's just you guys, here we go, one, two, one, two, one, two, one, two, one,
three, let me in.
I'll go with the goodies together,
cut down, let's do this by this mama, to go round and round,
Man, stop to a crackdown!
Yeah, so I can't even count on one stop
But we're with the goodies and get it all
I'm snare, live, morons, canals
From November 6th, as knocking
On your day in the source code
Hope you sang along there on that audience participation bit
Ooh, nice awesome fade there on that MP3
But it's cool, you know, there's a lot of this stuff flowing into
My iTunes, I guess a lot of from the blog digger media feeds on it from the indie feeds that are out there
And also part of my personal pod squad is always the Koma 1000 news updates
And once again, our consumer guy, her wise mom is coming to you at the rescue to your rescue
If you're looking for anything electronics for the Christmas shopping season
The marketplace is flooded with electronics
In fact, these days there aren't too many places where you can't buy electronic products
I mean Walmart is selling plasma TVs
So where's the best place to shop for electronics?
It all depends on what you want
Price, service, or selection
That's the conclusion of a just release survey by consumer reports
The magazines Amanda Walker says they pulled more than 10,000 readers
And found that no brick and mortar store earned top marks across the board
No matter where they went, they really couldn't get that trifecta
The best service, the best price and the best selection at one spot
The consumer reports survey shows the best prices can be found at amazon.com
And Costco
4 selection and service at a big retailer
Ritz cameras and circuit city came out on top
For best service, including the fastest checkout
Consumer reports readers chose Ritz camera and radio shack
By the way, the number one complaint of those surveyed was
I can't find anyone to answer my questions
A complaint most common when shopping for electronics at price club stores
I'm her wife's mom, the consumer man
Looking out for you on comal 1000 news
Excellent, thank you very much
Her radio shack, I told you that's the blogger's store
Man, that's where people still help you
What's this slogan?
You got questions?
We've got answers?
My daddy, my now making an announcement
Hi, this is Dan class
Former comedian actor, stay at home dad, shut in
And when I'm not changing my daughter's poopy butt
Or checking out the babes at the PTA
I like to do a little podcast that I call
The bitterest pill
Here's a little taste of the latest dose
Alright, here comes the promo of your balda
My first, when I first moved out here
I got a job as a production assistant for David Chase
You know who that is?
He was working on a show that I didn't like very much
That he created that
And I kind of wrote the guy off
Like, oh, this show is his boring and son
And I wanted to be acting and I was really bitter
I hated the actors because I wanted to be one of them
You know what I mean?
I had a very bad attitude
David Chase of course, the guy that I thought
Made a tea bad TV show, turned out to eventually
Create and produce a show called The Supranos
I don't know if you've heard of it
It's on HBO, it's brilliant
It's awesome, every episode is genius
So that's how good a judge of character
I've been in the past but when I was doing that
I had to run on these errands
And one day I was in a pharmacy just outside of Beverly Hills
On Sunset Boulevard
Picking up something or I don't know why
I don't even remember why I was there
But I realized that Louis Anderson is in there
Who was the big, large guy who eventually
Would host the family feud
But he was really big comic at the time
He was really famous
Oh my god, my first celebrity sighting
It's Louis Anderson
And I realized that Rod Stewart is in there too
Oh my god, this is the greatest Rod Stewart
And Louis Anderson in the same celebrity sighting
Okay, this is getting really good
And I tell you, you've got to listen to this
You've got to subscribe to this podcast
This is awesome
So you're ready, you got Louis Anderson and Rod Stewart
In the store, what's going to happen next
Well, I'm not going to spoil that here it comes
And then I realize
Louis Anderson is staring at Rod Stewart's ass
Just staring at it
But he is never stared at an ass before
It was awesome
And then about three weeks later
I was on a lot of Universal
Which is where I was working Universal Studios
And I was coming out of an elevator
And Tracy Lords was going in the...
Okay, you're really going to listen to the podcast
To check that out
What were you saying Christina?
I have to wait to watch a new video
From the show, it says
From the footage on there
How long you show on that side?
Because you can't watch it
Because I'm recording, is that why?
What do you have it cut out?
Do you have it ready to go?
Yeah
Well, let me come over there and check it out for a second
Hold on
Let me see what you got going
Hmm
Hold on, I'll just turn this off
I'll just keep this recording
Just for one second
Okay, let's see what you got
There's just a little short little thing
What is this?
From their side, see it starting
Okay, so it's a piece of video
From Halloween
Okay, play it
See what it is
They made it really scary
It's pretty warm
What?
But I gotta stay shut up
It's always nice
Is this their track?
No, they're really impolving
This is basically what I'm going to be in this side
This is just going to be for real
A home movie
No, it's just going to be too far
It's just going to be too far
It's Halloween
So they made this themselves
With the Halloween is the only normal day of the year
For me
I got it, cool
All right, so
This christina's favorite band Good Charlotte
They seem to be putting together some pretty cool videos
From the road
With just journalists that guy who makes all their videos
Cool
Okay
Hey, and I found something online that you might want to listen to
This is from garageband.com
Check it out today
This was the number one
Or the top rated
Excuse me, top rated song
In the pop rock category
It's round two
Plenty of the song is she
And I like it
Check it out
It's just going to be for real
When I look at you, it's just my way, you do
That might as well make it happen
She's all the flavours that I like to taste
As you watch it, it's in any way
She will try to push it up this same
Now we'll read them all
Anything
All the flavours that I like to eat
When I look at you, it's just my way, you do
That might as well make it happen
She will try to push it up this same
Now we'll read them all
Anything
All the flavours that I like to eat
She will try to push it up this same
Now we'll read them all
Anything
Check it out on garageband.com
That is round two
The name of the band title the song is Shee
Are you going to let the dog out?
Sorry
Please, yeah
Don't let all your eyes
Okay
See, this is what happened
Mom's away, mom's staying at the bunker in Amsterdam
I'm in charge and what do I get?
No cooperation
Zero
I don't even get anything
No love, I get no love
Okay
There you go
That's how this is going out
Everyone's hearing it, you're giving your dad no love
Give a second to the silencer
The little brook died
Who's that?
I've never thought about the little brook
I don't know my friend's name
My wife's to come over here and tell the story
But this was in
So that's in Belgium
Really?
How old was she?
She was kidnapped
How long were this happened
I didn't hear about it on the news
I didn't see anything about that
There's so a local thing
Not many people there actually
Shit
People never said no
They were changing things like
Rest in peace at older ones
Yeah
That's horrible
It's a name that's old in there
What are you going?
Colleship
Okay
I'm going to finish up the show
I got two more things
What's that?
I'm going to go rock in the room
Well that's what's 14 year olds are supposed to do
You're supposed to go rock in your room
Okay
Close the door
Thank you very much
Let's say hi to an old buddy
Who I saw out in Palo Alto
It's a blogger con
Our friend from real reviews
Hey Adam, it's Michael Gohagan
Hey it was great to meet you last week
And I had a blast at blogger con
Sounds like you did as well
You know I really enjoyed the opportunity
You and I and Steve Gilmore and some others got
To just have a really good conversation
Over drinks on Friday night
Trader Vicks was a lot of fun
I did want to let you know
I think this is the first of its kind
But I've been asked to do a podcasting 101 presentation
At this coming weekends
Southern California Mac fair
There's a once a year fair they hold
And I'm actually presenting both Saturday and Sunday
Just spreading the podcasting word so to speak
After talking with promoter
He's rearranged the schedule
And he has us in the main auditorium
Right in the middle of the day
Both days so we'll have great turnout
We're going to go over everything
From what podcasting is for the uninitiated
All the way through how to do it
Package it and podcast it out to the world
So I'm sending this to you just hopefully you've got some listeners
In the Southern California area that are just sitting on the fence
Not quite ready to pull the trigger
And I'd like to suggest they come on by
I never know where my next favorite podcast is going to come from
And hopefully it'll be somebody in the audience
This is coming weekend
So just trying to get some more podcasters in the coming weeks
You know the best part is the promoter called me the other day
And one is to know if it would be all right if I had somebody
From Apple there
Introducing the new photo iPod
For the first four or five minutes of my presentation
I said sure to that I figured it'd increase the people in the audience
But better yet we get to segue right from the new photo iPod
I can segue into another you've seen that
Let me show you how that things really supposed to be used
Should be a great weekend if
They can stop by my blog at mwgblog.com
Look for the podcasting 101 link
And it'll give you all the details how to get their times and locations
Also I don't want to forget to mention that August and Ray over at iPod
Rex have been kind enough to donate two licensed copies of their iPod
Rex software for us to raffle off one on Saturday and one on Sunday
So this is a real deal man. We are going to be spreading the podcasting word
Adam you keep up the good work and we'll talk to you soon
I'm Michael that's so excellent
And it was cool to meet Michael because I I had no idea what he did in real life
I shouldn't I shouldn't tell you if real life
There's another side to Michael that you don't know about it
Would you get him to talk about that and other
Either an audio comment maybe he'll do it on on real reviews
But it's nothing like the great movie reviews that he does
So yeah sounds like some cool stuff happening
And you know giving away some goodies helping people to get into podcasting
Excellent and yeah, of course, always happy to promote that
Okay, we're you know just about
Yeah, actually 40 minutes so I'm at the a lot of time that I'd like to keep it, you know, keep the show tight at
This is one last bit of some audio from a piece of video that has been circulating around the net
I had heard about it from my friend Ron Bloom who now actually has a weblog
And he's pointed to it on this weblog
It is a piece of video from CNN where John Ashcroft
Break seemed to song and I mean not just you know just any old song
He sings the song let the eagle sore and he's got his vibrato going and he's
You got to listen to a little bit of it now. So the whole song it's different pieces cut together
But then this is you know we didn't know he had these hidden talents
Let the eagle song listen to that vibrato
Like she's never saw before from a rocky coast
To golden shore
Listen
And he's doing this I just want those regular conference bikes on the days
You know
Okay, so you got to see that video if you ever chance it's linked from the production notes
For today's daily source code and that will do it for the show tomorrow
We're gonna do some podcasting with the baby
So I think I think the name of the host is Santa or Nana next
We're gonna accidentally in there
So she'll probably just preconceived she'll probably one of those two bubbly English girls that'll be hosting the show
Look forward to that
Again, I could be completely wrong and totally off the mark
But we will know tomorrow my friends so we'll be taking the sort of report in the source code
At the messy castle which we've almost moved and we're out of here
Addition of today resource code
As always comment through at number 3 dot com of course you can leave anything on the web log live dot 3 dot com
And for all the archives and the most recent shows daily source code dot com we can also find
RSS 2.0 podcast feed
Take it easy everybody
Talk to you tomorrow
Bye bye