Hi podcasting daddy, Sunday class comes up to you this year and asks you Master of Artic.
Then you know what the answer will be and how many presents you will get.
Goethings from a German speaking luciant.
Fantastic with Adam Curry.
Ah, boy.
Everybody, how you doing? Welcome to the daily source code coming from the fastest internet hotel in the world.
That's the way they build themselves.
This is your daily source code for Wednesday at December 22nd, 2004.
I'm Adam Curry in Uthman.
How's it in the afternoon, it's 4.15.
I slept a major portion of the day.
I was so completely white after yesterday.
I just, I know I slept for 13.14 hours.
So I'm a little bit discombobulated, but I really wanted to get a source code done because
even when I went to bed last night, I had enough material and enough stuff to save.
I could put you on your pack yesterday's day in the three source codes.
But a lot of stuff to do outside of what's been going on here in Holland,
it is really cold here, by the way.
Yesterday it was minus 3 degrees and I decided after I visited my mom.
By the way, medicine is amazing.
What they can do is it just boggles the mind.
And I don't know how to explain it.
I'll tell you the scariest thing that happened to me yesterday.
Because there was actually a hole.
Let me get a little bit of Christmas vibe to hear all of that.
Let me get rid of the rock mining out there.
Here we go.
Can you remember where I found all this stuff?
I did a little bit of show prep this morning when I woke up before I went back to bed.
I found all kinds of Christmasy tunes.
I got to get into the holiday spirit, right?
Links to all of the stuff of course in the production show.
Anyway, my mom is doing great.
All things considered considering they removed an entire lung.
She has not changed.
Her eyes are just as clear.
Her face.
Everything is over speech.
Yeah, I think that today she was actually going to get out of bed or sit up.
Otherwise, just nothing changed.
Except for one thing that I told her I was going to talk about this in the podcast.
She said, yes, she wouldn't put it pastly.
But the scariest thing for me, the scariest thing was in the morning yesterday when I went to go see her.
She was still in intensive care.
She was just about to be taken out.
She spent the night there.
And we walked.
I met today before this.
And Bob and I, her husband I walked in.
And she was there and she was, you know, it was my mom.
But it wasn't.
And I was like, oh my god, it's just looks horrible.
And I realized that, of course, because of the operation,
she's normal is that they still not given her her teeth back.
Let me tell you, if you've never seen that, you've never seen your mom without her teeth.
It's like, man, it's just, it does not compute.
And it was, at that moment, I was just, I was floored.
And I'm in intensive care.
It's like, she looked okay, but she didn't look okay.
And whoa, it, that just totally, totally freaked me out.
And if that was the only thing that had freaked me out,
I think we're doing pretty damn good.
Hey, we fit it just perfectly in that beautiful little bit of Christmas music.
Hello, Pete. Hello, Pete.
This is Rask Web Audio, of course, 2014.
Well, 18.
Well, folks, today we're going to talk about podcasting.
Yeah.
I'm going to tell you the rules of podcasting.
And there are rules.
You need to follow this.
Rule number one.
Always.
No, no, wait, sorry.
Never talk about podcasting.
Wait, hold on.
Hold on, hold on.
I've got Russell Beatty's list of rules.
I want to find my list.
Okay.
Number one.
Keep it short.
Number two.
Make sure the background music is not too loud.
Otherwise, you can't really talk.
Maybe keep the background music, not too loud.
That's very important.
And, of course, number three, the most important.
Always.
Leave people wanting more.
Pete, good old Pete Pardell.
We'll be hearing more about him from him later on in the podcast.
You can tell I got a little bit of the sniffles now again because of this weather here.
And now, actually, the temperature just shot up to plus seven degrees.
So it's all over the map.
I have no idea what's going on, but they were talking about a white Christmas here yesterday.
And obviously, they're not anymore.
They also have this crazy thing in Holland, which it's called the Elf State of Tocht.
The 11 city skating competition.
And it can only take place after the canals of frozen throughout the entire country for, you know,
X amount of days and they measured the ice.
And this is, this is really like Hans Brinker in the Silver Skates time.
Okay.
And it's more or less like a marathon.
It's a, I should look it up.
It's several hundred kilometers.
And you skate on natural ice on canals, which means you have to either go under bridges or you have to do what's called
Cluna, which is a certain type of crawling around the bridges.
So you get off the ice and so it's not to dull your blades.
And you know, they do it on racing skates or the old fashioned wooden skates,
which are literally you strap these slats of wood to your shoes.
What's that noise?
I have the window open.
You strap these slats of wood to your shoes.
And they have a blade embedded in them.
And the last people who are hardcore and go, you know, like the old way.
Old school with the old fashioned skates, which is pretty amazing.
I think the last time it happened was,
oh man, that must have been, I don't know, mate, was it 10 years ago?
Or I mean, it really doesn't happen very frequently, particularly not with, you know, global warming, et cetera.
But whenever it gets cold like this, people start talking about that again.
So anyway, I'm here for a couple more days.
In fact, I'm right after I record the podcast,
I'm going to immediately drive off to the hospital.
My sister will always in from Italy.
And she's in.
She was actually already planning to come over for the holidays with her husband, Alessandro,
and her, their two kids and my other sister Tiffany.
So they're at, they're going to meet me at the hospital.
Then we're going back when we have dinner, all the siblings.
Wow, it's like a real family affair.
And, and it's so the season for it as well.
Let's see what happened yesterday.
I found a great coffee shop here in Utrecht called Vietstock.
So of course, that's a takeoff on Woodstock.
But it's Viet, W-I-E-T-S-T-O-K stock.
So it's like a stick of wheat.
Real nice guys.
And it's apparently, it was voted the best coffee shop in the world,
or in in all of Holland by some American magazine, High Life, or High Times,
or then again, maybe it was boy's life.
Can everybody remember?
Time to learn.
Good morning and welcome to today's podcast for December 22nd, 2004.
This is a brief daily podcast offering words for the wise and the otherwise.
Yesterday's word got me thinking and reading about word creation
and where new words come from.
This of course led me to a new word, neologism.
NEO, L-O-G-I-S-M.
It is word that has two meanings.
The first is a new word or term.
It can refer to a meaningful word like podcasting,
or it can be a nonsense utterance of an insane person.
The second meaning for neologism is the act of inventing a new word.
For example, the NBA types frequently use the word learnings
to describe observations or conclusions.
Since learnings isn't a dictionary word,
they're unknowingly engaging in neologism.
Any neologists out there?
Send me your new words.
If you'd like more information on today's podcast,
please visit todayspotcast.com.
Questions and comments can be sent to Scottat todayspotcast.com,
or you can leave me a voicemail at 435-514-435-435-435.
Please tell your friends about podcasting.
Hi, it's Scott.
Excellent.
I love this podcast, by the way.
You can find it in the other part of our directory,
or in all the different ways that Scott just told you there.
Neologism, neologism.
Participating in neologism.
It's one to add to the list of sila liquies.
Music for you today.
And I'm really concentrating on getting more pod safe music
on the show, getting more people involved in scouting out good
songs.
And there's been some recent, some press recently.
I think that is getting other people excited in that as well.
And of course, if you heard the morning coffee notes that we discussed,
the Dave did about us finding the next beetles.
You know, the beetles are pod casting.
Well, and maybe we should, this is the last time.
Hold on.
It's very difficult.
I found to put your glasses on if you had headphones on.
Because they kind of, let me go.
That's better.
We're never going to talk about the next beetle of pod casting ever again.
Because that's just kind of, let's just find some superstars.
Okay.
I got some candidates lined up for you in this particular show.
Let's start with American Heartbreak.
I was reading through Michael Butler's Weblog.
And there was a blur about an American Heartbreak song that they were
releasing pod safe RIA free.
And it's, you know, it's hard to get new Christmas songs.
They just don't make enough of them.
Go, American Heartbreak.
Do you remember that in down my Christmas tree?
Don't remember anything.
But made it for my phone to make.
Wake up and I'm freezing.
Drink it doesn't kill my thing.
Children spinning at my window must be Christmas time again.
Don't start with American Heartbreak.
No wish I could meet.
I was dreaming never again.
Every year the same.
But those night, I'm gonna be.
I'm gonna be by myself with Christmas.
I'm gonna be.
Live my life and nothing.
To face another year.
You can be a fool compared to a night.
Be dead by Christmas anyway.
Be with Christmas party.
You're the the other way.
And wish I was never born.
See another Christmas day.
Just go and remember.
No wish I could meet.
I was dreaming never again.
Every year the same.
But those night, I'm gonna be.
I'm gonna be by myself with Christmas.
I'm gonna be.
I'm gonna be by myself with Christmas again.
I'm gonna be by myself with Christmas.
I'm gonna be.
I'm gonna be never born.
No wish I could meet.
Wake up in a recent.
Take it doesn't kill my pain.
Tell me if you didn't have my window.
Must be Christmas time again.
See another Christmas party.
But yeah it's over the year.
I wish I was never born.
See another Christmas year.
Just go and remember.
No wish I could meet.
I was dreaming never again.
Every year the same.
But those night, I'm gonna be.
I'm gonna be by myself with Christmas.
I'm gonna be.
I'm gonna be by myself with Christmas again.
I'm gonna be by myself with Christmas.
I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be alone
and I'm gonna miss the same
I'm gotta be alone
No more Christmas day
And I'm gonna be alone
Lying on Christ my stares
Yeah, it's a nice uplifting, a little holiday cheer to the African-American heartbreak,
Christmas song, a new daily source code, excellent, excellent, you know, and it's hard
to get good new Christmas songs, you know, it really is, it's just difficult because everyone
always plays the standards and the traditional's over and over and over again and then it's
good.
We need one for our generation.
Thank you very much, American heartbreak for that, perfect, absolutely perfect, and I
got to take, I like Christmas, I really do, not for any religious reasons, I'm
sorry, I do have some flammage in my throat, just the light, you know, so let's just call
the Festival of Lights or whatever, because it's a whole bunch of holidays and religious
lights, things going on around this time of year, but it's kind of nice, and here in New
Threat, the National Top 40 Radio Station, so that's a public radio, public broadcast, they
have, it's called 3 FM, so they have a 24 hour radio station, which is kind of like BBC's
radio one, they're doing a big thing for Darfur, and they've caged three of their top
DJs, one of them girl Claudia, in this glass studio on the kind of the Nuda, which is a
central square here in New Threat, and they're broadcasted from their live 24 hours a day,
and it's all lit, you know, so you can basically see the whole studio, and they have guests,
the trick is that they're basically playing all requests all the time, but you have to, you
have to donate money to Darfur, so people are calling up, it's like, oh, it's a tell-out
though, on a radio, a radio thorn, I guess, but to give it an extra twist, they are, you
know, I guess, in all of the field of the world, and identify the hunger vibe, they're not
eating for five days, so they went in Monday morning, and they don't come out and tell Friday
afternoon, I think, or six p.m., and they will not have eaten anything for the entire week,
they drink water, food juices, they're, I mean, they're drinking tea, they're drinking coffee,
the drinking Coca-Cola for crisis, which is not, not very good, and even worse than that,
is they're smoking, they're, I mean, they're all smokers, so of course they're substituting
the hunger with a drag on a cigarette, man, I told them, you guys got stuff, and say,
now they have doctors on site, and they have a, you know, a whole medical program worked
out, but yeah, the doctors had mentioned that we shouldn't smoke so much with it, anyway,
so I, I just happened to walk by, and they, they call me in, and so it was on the air,
and it was, it was kind of interesting, it was, especially because I just come from the
coffee shop, you know, then to be live on the radio, I was like, well, you know, I got
it, I don't know, I don't know, that's exactly what I thought, I don't know, but I told
him, I said, look, try this out, why don't you, for a week, give your dog a bowl of Coca-Cola,
and a couple cigarettes every day, and let's see how, how he looks at the end of the
week.
Well, I tried to tell him what, you know, Don always says, but this was kind of like the
clean radio version of it, right?
Hey, there's no, it's a new movie podcast that I thought was kind of interesting.
Howdy listeners, welcome to Family Reviews, the podcast where our family gets together and discusses
movies available at your local centerplex, for rental or on television, or on the web at
familyreviews.blogspot.com, stop by, give us some comments.
I want to say about Oceans 12, except that it's up there.
So here's the deal, so they, they, oh my, once I only reset my mic, okay, back, that's better.
Here's the deal, the family reviews a movie.
You get the, you get the, just, just listen to it for a second, listen to the different
family.
There's a movie where somewhere, somebody along the production area, so taking a look
to the script and said, I'm sorry, we can't make this and do a motion picture to
that.
They shot that thing in Amsterdam, by the way, which is so typical that we, all of Holland
was so incredibly excited about Oceans 12 being done in the Netherlands and, you know,
George Clooney and Brad Pitt all staying at, you know, at the Amstel Hotel for weeks
on end and all the celebs.
And of course, this is going to be the movie that sucks, right?
This is going to be the ishtar of, of, of, of these actors career, and this is the big
moment for Holland to shine.
If you ignore the critics and go see this movie, you're doing it at your own peril because
it is just a bad film.
The movie is a sequel to, both in the 11, which I thought was, no, this is the movie.
Wait, was there a deal at the Amstel, for, for good will, didn't?
What the hell is that?
I want to hear the other people review and comment.
No, no.
Okay, anyway, listen to the family reviews, because it's, I think it's the first, review, podcast
that I've heard.
Of course, we have real, real reviews, which is Michael Gohagan, hey, got it right
the first time, like, but he doesn't necessarily do new movies, so anyway, and he's not
just reviewing.
He's going in depth about the movies.
It's a totally different vibe.
There was a comment that came in on, on the website at curie.com, Mike wanted to know,
Mike says he's actually moving from PC to a Mac, specifically for podcasting, makes
sense, busy at looking what to buy, he says, can you spare a few valuable podcast minutes?
He'd really be interested to hear what hardware I'm, and software I'm running my podcast
on.
Actually, we haven't talked about this in a while, how I record these, so I'll give you
this set up real briefly.
There's a hardware and a software part to it, so I'm just, I have regular power book
G4, he said, Blase, a regular power book G4.
Although this one has been around the block, it's chipped, it's broken, the hinges are
a bit cramogeney, you know, pretty soon, it'll be time for a new one.
What I do is I run audio hijack pro, and I have attached through Firewire, an M audio,
Firewire 410 breakout box.
Basically, I just use that as an audio input for my SureSM7 microphone, which is a professional
broadcast microphone, but you could use any mic, but this is about what I'm using.
So that's plugged into the M audio, and so basically that comes up as an audio device,
which you can capture in audio hijack pro.
I send the output of the hijack to the headphones, because I want to have a good volume,
so I can hear everything.
I use audio hijack pro now to record in AFF to direct to the hard disk, and that works
because AFF, well first of all, it doesn't have to compress anything on the fly, so it's
basically writing raw data out to the hard drive, so it won't skip if some heavy processes
hit my computer for some reason, and also should the computer crash, the file will still
be there, and I can always start recording again, and just add the two bits together,
whereas with an MP3 recording direct to disk, you might lose all that information, in fact,
you probably will lose it, and so I always compress my files after the fact.
The M audio has a button on it, which basically switches the input from a mic to a line,
and I use that just to turn off my microphone when, for instance, the song is playing or something
out, so I'll demonstrate, so that's just me pressing that button on and off.
Then I've got a couple of effects, you can put effects into your audio channel in audio hijack
pro, so essentially I'm processing my voice with the first with a monomizer, which because I'm
only using one channel of the M audio, it makes one channel, so basically it takes one channel
and makes it into a mono to two channels, then I have a compressor running light compression,
there's a 10 band EQ that I used to equalize the voice a little bit, and then of course,
I have very little bit of reverb, it's there, it's hardly noticeable, but it's there, and it makes
a difference, and then I have the spectrifier, which just gives me a visual representation, so I know
that something's going through the whole audio, that's at the end of the chain, so I know that
if it's made it through there, then it's probably being recorded to disk, but in between there,
I've inserted the voice over module, and what's cool about that is I'm not using, see what I was
trying before, I was trying to capture quick time, and then use the voice over module to insert my
microphone, so now basically I'm concentrating completely on the mic, that's running through the whole main chain,
and then I just add sound flower, this is my sound like gobbledy group to so many people,
I'll shut up in a second, I add sound flower 16 in the voice over module, and I basically,
here it comes, I gotta document this differently, then I use detour, audio detour, this is crazy,
I use detour to send quick time output to sound flower 16, okay, you get it, you got it,
good, because I'm not sure I understand any more either, hello Adam, this is Murlaferty with my podcast
geek food action grip, and I'm here to answer a call that you had for short podcast, and answer a
call that Dave Slusher from Evil Genius Chronicles had for Southern women podcasts, so I'm here with my
short Southern female podcast called geek food action grip, and I'm using the podcast to read my
essays that have been some published, some unpublished, but most of them hopefully humorous,
and I promise to keep the podcast under 10 minutes, you can find my blog and my podcast at
essentialmath.com slash geek food, that's one word, thanks a lot, you know, this is once again
demand making its own supply, and that's great, I mean so I asked for something, Dave Slusher
asks for something, and all of a sudden it appears, and I suggest you check that podcast out,
lots of podcasts by the way being added to the ipodder.org directory, as I'm starting to get some
technical bits together, and I have different ways of bringing all this information in to make sure
that wherever a new podcast pops up on any directory or any, any node of our directory that
it basically can float to the top, and that you can be alerted about it on ipodder.org, so it's kind of a
throwback, I guess, to the NCSA, what's new page, remember that? Back in the day, so, you know,
if you want to know what the podcasts and what the new ones are, and of course there's the
audio.weblogs.com page. If you're new to podcasting, this is a great place to let people know about
your podcasts as well, but you have to basically tell this service that you have a podcast that's
updated. There's instructions there on ipodder.org, how to create a feed, how to ping
audio.weblogs.com, and it's worth it, because that's a good place to, it's just like,
if you go to look at weblogs.com, the whole world is pinging that as well, and even Microsoft stuff
pingsweblogs.com, so that's just a good central place that I wouldn't know, hey, you know,
I've got an update happening here. Something to go on in secret for many weeks now, it shouldn't
have taken many weeks, but that was probably mainly my fault. The 12 days of podcasting projects
set up by Pete Pradele of Raster Web with Don and Drew of the Don and Drew Show, and they selected
a whole bunch of podcasts. I'm not that I'm allowed to tell you, but I don't really remember who they all
were. A lot of pioneers, I think, and early, early podcasters, and they came up with lyrics,
and everyone had to do their, you know, day of podcasting, and they're putting this all together.
What I really didn't realize though, I thought, of course, I didn't read the instructions properly,
and I was busy with all kinds of other things. I thought, I was just supposed to do,
I'm doing the first day of podcasting, and I thought I just had to do one line, and I did a
couple different reads of it, and I sent the whole file off to Drew. I didn't know that these files
were being put out verbatim, unedited, because I listened to it. I was like, oh, and I thought
they were going to be put into the music immediately, but I guess what's happening now is
every day, we're going to release a day of podcasting, and then at the end, we'll
be January 1st, there will be a whole entire mix of the 12 days of podcasting. Check out
Donandru.com for information on it. I'm also posting a link in the show notes, of course, for today's show.
I'm not going to play you mine, because I'm not a singer, it's horrible, and I hate doing this,
but I didn't want to be a party pooper. I will, of course, play you a bit of Donandru
who pick up the second day of podcasting. I'll tell you at least what my, what my lyric is,
my lyric is, on the first day of podcasting, Dave Winer gave to me an enclosure in an XML tree.
Okay, ready?
Mm-hmm.
Kind of three, one, two, three.
On the second day of podcasting, I'm a part of it.
Okay, I'm the second day of podcasting, I'm a part of it to me.
See, Donandru, punk's a cousin.
All right, no, let's do the punk's a cousin.
Okay, ready?
Mm-hmm.
On the second day of podcasting, I'm a part of it to me, to punk's a cousin.
And you guys should have done harmonies. Come on, huh?
And so anyway, they're putting this together.
And my secret hope is that other people, you know, who like messing around with audio on their
computer will, you know, take these daily files and perhaps create an alternative mix to
whatever this is supposed to be. So stay tuned for that.
And of course, I'll be playing you these little days of podcasting snippets as they come along.
Now, the Donandru show, they picked up a sponsor, not too long ago.
I think it's MSMobles.com and they, I think that's the, that's the person who's sponsoring them,
but it's about Mike, it's basically a whole website or a project about Microsoft mobile devices.
And so I went to the website, MSMobles.com, I suggested, and there's a podcast there as well.
And this is just confusing to me. I want to know more about MSMobles now.
And I know this guy is, as email me, we've, we've come back and forth before, but
I mean, is this a Microsoft company or a Microsoft consultancy or
one thing for sure, the podcast is interesting.
Do not listen to this eyes closed process while striving or operating machinery, only listen
when you can safely relax completely.
Well, come to MSMobles.com.
That sounds like, um, what's the name of that's, uh, the dog on Conan O'Brien?
What is the, uh, insult coming dog? Is that it?
Do you understand?
That's iPhone's are important.
In this podcast, I would be. Could it be that Microsoft actually understands what we're doing
already that they actually get, this is great. I mean, this is a Microsoft commercial that I'm
interested in listening to about latest news from the area.
If you would only put on that was.
Enjoy. Okay.
Okay. And then what was, all right. Well, go listen to that podcast too, because
it's trippy. So, um, I'm not quite sure what's going on there.
I hopefully will get some audio information about MSMobles and the sponsorship and how that's
working. I'm delighted for Donna Drew that they've got a sponsorship, um, but I think that
what I'm hearing is this podcast is better than the commercial that, you know, or the mentions they
do on the show. Maybe they should get this guy on and get him to do some, do some of that wacky stuff.
I don't know. Just different ways of looking at commercialization, eh?
Hello. I'm Ken Strugian. I'm here to tell you about our brand new Ken N.
Squip show holiday extravaganza. The festivities include me pushing Squip over the edge with my new
Pupu Santa and then going completely bonkers for bosoms. For some reason, the thing that popped
up to the top was this great big huge breasts. I mean, big boobs, big melons, big hawkers.
Ken? Yeah. Sounds more like a popped breast implant. Ken, what the hell is with you in the breasts?
Are you suddenly breast crazy? Well, I thought you were going to say I had to send my
Pupu Santa to Dave Kendall. Oh, for God's sake, human and stupid bull. And there was like a
disclaimer, my long about how use of this product could cause sudden uncontrollable liquid bowel
movements. Ken? Yeah. You are preoccupied with poop, and now it's this breast thing. What the hell
is wrong? Take your pick, which is worse. Squip serves up a new recipe for a delightful holiday
Mexican man killed his lover in a drunken fight, then cooked the man's body in tomato and
uninsuas. And ate it over three days. Oh, my. The victim, a young man, arrived at his cardboard hut.
His cardboard hut. That's right. Well, the corpse, which had it to back, ripped open and it's
inner. It's called a very important story. Go with that. And then explains how you can use your cell
phone as a marital aid. Who made six toys.com offers instructions for using your cell phone as a
vibrator. It also provides practical tips such as using a condom if you plan to put the phone
inside you or if you want to talk on the phone later. What do they mean? Could you talk on the
phone with an opio? That's this week only on the Kenan Squip Show. Available at www.dustingmybrain.com
slash KASS. Podcasting may never be the same. And I believe I've mentioned that the
Kenan Squip Show consists of two of my dear friends who have jumped on to the podcast in
craze. Ken was my personal assistant for years before that he worked at MTV's The Talent
Coordinator and VP of Talent Pupu and later he ran entire divisions at Think New Ideas. He's
been in my life for many, many years and he's completely nuts. Cindy was one of my first employees
at my company on ramp and she's a beautiful, wonderful human being and the only employee who's
ever thrown up on me in a drunken stupor and I love them both dearly. Hey dudes, I'm going to go
off to the hear me. Hey dudes, how you doing? I'm going to go off and meet my sisters at the hospital.
I'm going to hang out with my mom so that'll be the kids and mom all together. I got another great
podsafe song for you. This is a guy named Roger. He has a band called Intwin. I&TWI&E
Intwin and I've played this song probably in one of the first daily source codes or maybe
it was pre-sourced code I think that I probably put an MP3 up on my weblog when I was doing the
radio show for Radio Veronica the morning radio show. So yeah it predates my podcasts.
Roger was, he basically has this band and he put together his own little marketing
play at the band in the Netherlands. Although I think he I can't remember he lived in Canada
or the states for a couple years. His English is excellent. He's just you know good looking
kid very talented got the voice you know he could have been from you know California who knows.
So he's kind of like stuck in Holland. What what his plan was is he went on pop idol or
yeah the Dutch version of American Idol and went through the audition process and he was selected
to go into the you know the semifinals or whatever and he said you know I'm not going to do it
because I don't want to sign the contract you gave me and so the you know there was this big
there was the first the first series of the show. So of course the media got onto it and it
was all a marketing play because he had no intention of actually going through with with the entire
contest he just wanted people to hear about his his band and of course he got a record deal out of it
and they released a song which was very successful in Holland and it just it didn't go anywhere
and that can be timing that can be a number of factors but it doesn't have to do it doesn't necessarily
have anything to do with the quality of the song and this is a song that I've permissioned to play
on the podcast and it would be you know awesome if other people other podcasts pick this up and
played the song. I think you like it it's a shoot now you could hear this on any radio station anywhere
shoot strange the stars don't shine the rock is now soon to go and try to happen
isn't it strange that we can't love back and seeing and just what went wrong I want to know now
when we are should I pretend in a little thing you know when what you've done could you
come face to your face with me isn't it strange that you told me one thing suddenly change your mind
isn't it strange that you come out for me turn away and leave me behind now if he's like I'm drowning
he's like I'm drowning in a way without you I know the feeling because I felt it's all before
I hope you don't feel just like me I hope you don't feel just like me I hope you don't feel just like me
I hope you don't I be
isn't it strange that the world seems to turn away when I try and explain what's all strange
then two can be as one yet another same and if he's like I'm drowning
feel like I'm drowning in a way without you I know the feeling because I felt it's all before
and if he's like I'm drowning in a way without you I hope you don't feel just like me
I hope you don't feel just like me I hope you don't feel just like me I hope you I'll be
don't feel just like me I hope you don't feel just like me I hope you don't feel just like me
We'll be with just like that, man
I hope you don't feel just like that
But I hope that was real much and wasn't that bad
Maybe not to love it
Not to love it, yeah
Not to love it
We'll go to my way
Not to love it, yeah
Is that kick or what?
In twine, featuring Roger and happy on the daily source code
Winding it up for Wednesday, December 27
All right, that's it tomorrow
I promise I'll be a little bit more together
It's just a sleeping for 13, 14 hours
Really threw me off a little bit
But I got through everything I wanted to get through today
And I'm just going to enjoy the bandwidth
Enjoy some good foods tonight
We've got the family and we've got to do this
That's kind of what you want to try to do
During this time of the years, hang out with me
Maybe hang out with some people you don't like
And see if there's something about it
Yeah, you're right
I'll see you tomorrow
We'll be back here with more source code
But Thursday, take it easy
We'll be back with more source code