Welcome once again to your daily source code. Today is Tuesday. It's, uh, man, December 7th, 2004
come to you from Curry College of the United Kingdom of Great Britain, of that island
off the mainland. It's your source code. This is of course being the official place
where users and developers attempt to party together, although it's getting harder to do.
That's right. There's less drugs available here than in Belgium and
getting much much harder. Oh, man. Boy, if we've been through a lot in the past 24 hours,
it's, uh, I woke up this morning and the first thing I thought was right. Let's go find some
bandwidth. It's one of those things, you know. I like don't you wake up in the morning and think
bandwidth. So I immediately ran down my list as I was still in my bathroom,
but actually we got up a little bit late as usual. About 930, Patricia was already up and cooking, cooking
stuff in the kitchen, which was nice, especially that really unhealthy, really thick,
sliced English bacon. So I started calling, called over to Pipex to inquire about WDSL.
Well, it looks like the service has been discontinued.
Then I called the Bulldog DSL. Guys got a real good wrap for providing 8 megabits per second.
Also, according to their availability checker, also available at the Guilford Exchange,
unfortunately, they're still running on British telecom equipment. And after, you know,
searching through my email and just looking at the latest stuff that had come in overnight,
I was turned on to easy net. Actually, I'd received a couple emails about it earlier,
and they only do business accounts. Luckily, I have a business, so I was able to set one up,
but really friendly. And all of a sudden, once I posted about easy net, and that's
easy net.co.uk. It's probably easy net.net. Then, you know, just everyone's spranging to action,
co-founders, XCTO systems engineers, everyone started emailing me, and everyone's going to, you know,
trying to help out is really, really cool. And so, you know, now I'm committed. I know that these
guys, they who have their own equipment at the Guilford Exchange, I know that they'll be able to hook
me up. Of course, it's still going to take an X amount of time for British telecom to basically
perform three keystrokes to relinquish my line over to easy net, so that they can then subsequently
hook up my DSL connection. Now, I had a couple of choices. And the top of the line choice,
which I can actually get here from easy net, you're going to love this, is an eight megabit down 725k
up DSL connection. I was like, oh, man, that could be my own fucking ISP. I could be every podcast
there's ISP with that kind of pipe. Actually, of course, it's, you know, that's the downlink,
that's really, that's really got all the pipe. And that was, after thinking about it, that's
really ridiculous. There's no need for that. And they have a second option, which is somewhat
less expensive. I'm still going to wind up paying £199 a month, but I will get four megabit
down 725k up, which is pretty astounding. You don't get that kind of speed up almost DSL connections.
So, it'll be great for posting podcasts and getting stuff out there. Five static IP addresses,
the whole thing. So, we'll still have to wait until BT switches over the line, so they can then
take care of it. But at least those guys got ports and everyone's working on it. And I want to thank
you so much. It's so cool that everyone jumped in. And even if I have to wait two more weeks,
you know, I already feel good knowing that it's going to be great. And I'm going to have a great
bandwidth. And I'm using my various iPoders. I'm actually, this has been a great opportunity
for me to test out different iPod or software, since iPod or X, which I've been using,
doesn't have what I call the vacation switch, basically. There comes a point where you don't
have bandwidth. You've got to catch up on your podcasts. And it's a pain if you have to,
you know, if you're downloading three podcasts per channel. It's just only so much time in the
day if you have only a few moments to connect to a pipe. This is all content management stuff
that we're going to have to start figuring out with iPoders eventually. I probably just have
the first person to really bump into it. Actually, as you'll hear later on on the show, I'm not the
first person to run into trouble with bandwidth on the receiving end and missing a couple of
shows and then basically trying to catch up. There are more people who've had the problem and more
who are coming up with the different solutions. And I just haven't had enough time to check out
all my email. I did see that my boyfriend drew, no, and from the dawn and drew show, sent me an email,
and it turns out that he's, he's into drums as much as I am. I've only discovered that I kind of
like, you know, drums, the drum cadence. So this is the Michigan drum cadence, by the way,
that I'm playing as a repeat. I just, I don't know, it kind of does it for me. I like it. You know,
and now, of course, people are sending me drum cadences from all over the country, which probably
would warrant a podcast all by itself. Any takers? I've been not played too much of that because,
you know, drums can get, get all jealous and shit. You can't have that. Also, wasn't touched with
Lee Wilkins, of course, we know Lee and his girlfriend, Jenny, they're two cute little doggies are
locked up in jail in Atlanta, and I had reached out to the source code listening community and
asked for you guys to help out. As of this morning, when, when he called me,
guess what? Already $1,200. So I, the clearly, they're going to make the 1,500, and thank you again
for, yeah, for helping them out, because that's, that's very cool. Just the fact that we could do it,
blows me away. It's, it's, you know, it really just shows what, something's going on here. There's
something working with his podcast. Okay, so that's enough drum cadence there. That was,
that was especially for, for Drew from Don Drew. And you know, it's, it's starting to itch.
I'm, I'm getting a real itch now, you know. I still have to wait for the bandwidth, excuse me.
I still have to wait for the bandwidth to come in, because I've kind of promised myself that was
going to be the focus. But after that boy, I got to start flying. I am itching to fly. I hear
these helicopters going by by the house. Not that I necessarily want to, I mean, I should do an hour
to, in a helicopter just to, you know, just to keep the feel going and, and find a flying buddy,
basically. But I really want to get my fixed wing license so that it'll be much easier to fly over to
the mainland, basically go anywhere I want. And quite honestly, I've gotten the airplane flying bug.
I thought I would never want to fly anything other than helicopters. But after, what have I
done about 12, 15 hours in a, in a Session of 172? And as you know, I've done an hour or two in,
in a mooney, you know, all of a sudden, it's like, whoa, you know, this is, this is cool, because
in an airplane when you take off, first of all, the thing wants to fucking fly. I mean, all you
have to do, you know, metal to metal, you're pushing the throttle all the way against the dashboard,
basically. And then you wait for the airspeed indicator to hit the right, the right number,
you just ease back and things up and flying. Helicopters like, no way. It wants to tip over immediately
and thrash about. It doesn't want to fly. So that's beautiful, you know, and you, you pull these things
up, you're in the air and then depending on what you got, you know, autopilot, you know, you
drink your morning coffee, you know, just kick back and navigate your way through. I am, of course,
oversimplifying it. Please don't get all pissed off. If you happen to be a pilot, because of course,
they know that simple. But it is, you definitely have more limbs free than when flying a helicopter,
and that's quite a luxury. I look forward to it. So there's black bush airport, which is only
15 minutes away from here. Black bush is spelled in the, the old English spelling, bush,
BU, S-H-E. And I think it's a cab air aviation that I'm going to go talk to. They do F-F-A-A.
F-A, sounds like an R-I-A thing. Federal aviation administration licenses. So basically I have a
US helicopter pilot's license, and they can help me get the out on for the fixed wing.
Because it isn't, you don't have to go through all of the motions that you have to go through
for your initial PPL. You know, you have your theoretical part. And that basically you don't have
to do over. In fact, the theory for helicopter is the exact same theory ends the same test for
for airplanes. So you already have all the, all the basic theory. But when it comes down to it,
it's all about experience. There's no substitute for experience. And I've been checking out a
couple of podcasts. You know that I'm a big proponent of short podcasts. And then I'm looking
for, like the, you know, we've got the skinny on sports. You've got the sports pod. You've got
ICM, real reviews. Raster web audio, of course, always good for a short podcast. And you know
that I'm a follower of religious broadcasters. I love watching religious broadcasters on television.
And I love listening to them on the radio. They have a message they want. And by the way,
I'm a spiritual guy. So I'm not knocking any of this. I have a different way of believing in
something else that I may believe in. But it's irrelevant. We're all communicating a message here.
And if you look at the religion node in the ipodder.org directory, it's got some, some good podcast
in there. And some new came in that I don't know if I've talked about this before or not.
But it's from, it's the godcast, basically godcast.org. And they bring you the living word. And
basically it's a passage from the Bible every day. And what I do as I figure, you know, it won't
hurt to listen to a little bit of a little bit of the Bible here. Listen, this is actually a
Matthew 22. What I'll do is I'll spice it up a bit with the, with the Michigan drum cadence.
Hi, this is Rachel Patrick from godcast.org. The little more from Monday December,
August 2004. Our verses for today are Matthew chapter 22, verses 37 to 40. And the translation
is the NIV. This is Jesus speaking to the teachers of the law.
Jesus replied, love the Lord you're God with all your heart and with all your soul and with all your
mind. This is the first and greatest human in the second is like it. Love your neighbor at your
son. All the law on the prophets and on these two remains. Matthew chapter 22, verses 37 to 40.
Thanks for listening to the living word. Currents and verse requests are always welcome.
I feed back at godcast.org. This is Rachel Patrick hoping that God would truly bless and so
I was in a cute hole. Let me see that last bit. That was beautiful. Hold on, listen to the last bit
of her. Oh, that was really nice. I just don't want to play the drums through that. Check it out.
Godcast.org. This is Rachel Patrick hoping that God would truly bless and so your day. See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, Rachel. In a cute, that's beautiful. It really is. A little sappy on the music,
but very, very powerful way of communicating with kids. It works every time.
Okay, an email that came in. Hey, Adam, just finished a new intro from my weekly show podcast.
And I've paid, well, he says, human, but I'm sure he meets homage to you and your
point on annoying. I hope you approve. A lot of people last me, people are just tuning into podcast.
Where's this Boeing thing coming from? And it was Christina, who reminded me that it
actually came from watching the simple life with the Paris Hilton Nicole Richie because even though
it's a reality show, it's not really a reality show because it's edited together and everything's
kind of set up, but it doesn't matter. But whenever they do something weird that have sound effects
going point, be repeat. And then, you know, whenever Paris inevitably had to shove her hand up
a cow's ass, you know, you'd hear boy, boy, boy, boy, boy, boy, boy, boy.
Hi, everybody. Okay, up there is.
Help, up here, here, here are what you ready to ask!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, you just a horn in joy without enzyme acid, or more than ㅡ, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You're retritzing me when you hope you're really life.
What you should just walk in and chill.
It was a promo.
It will send me promos to their own podcasts.
What are you doing?
Come on to my microphone, baby.
Do you know where the other microphone is?
No.
I can't find it.
I have the wire of everything because I want you to...
If you walk in or anyone walks in, I want you to have a mic.
Oh yeah, you say have that one.
It's the grey one.
It's the 421.
It's a classic microphone.
What did I use to sing through?
I haven't washed it.
Really?
Since you were seven.
It's a lipstick.
Hmm.
Okay, so Patricia's walked in and showed me her arms which are black and blue.
Yeah.
What happened?
My upper arms.
Your upper arms.
Have you been...
As your husband been being you.
Are your boyfriend?
No.
Nobody's beating me.
Your boyfriend's pretty cool though.
He's hanging up paintings and mirrors and he's...
Is he?
And he's drilling holes in the rental house
that we're not supposed to be drilling holes in.
He's pretty handy, isn't he?
Pretty handy.
You should give him sex once you lie.
I knew that, but you just always...
What?
But you always say I can do that.
I pay people to do that.
Yeah, I used to.
But you know...
Before we downshift.
Now I notice that you can.
You're actually pretty...
Don't tell anyone.
Because then Donald makes me fix up her crappy house.
Oh, no.
Oh, don't do that.
What's happened?
This house is in 1930's house.
And it has silly doors.
With very high handles.
Door handles.
And I walk into them all the time.
But you...
I'm a tiny little girl.
Yeah.
But how can we...
Walk into door handles before?
I know.
The doors are narrow.
Not that I'm fat or anything, you know.
Well, you didn't put on a way honey.
No, nothing.
I'm very skinny, actually.
Yeah, the doors are strange.
I don't know what it is.
But...
Can you stop walking in the doors?
And I'm tired.
So I'm wobbling a little bit.
Yeah, you're tired.
From one side to another.
And I...
I'm bumping into them.
I don't know what it is.
But it looks horrible.
Both arms are black and blue.
Like you're...
You're nipping your bump.
Oh, you're hitting me all the time.
It's like a white Tina Turner.
Oh, I got it.
I'm going to finish up the show.
Hold on a sec.
There we go.
A little reset.
Thanks, son.
See you later.
Love you.
Me neither.
Yeah, love you too.
I don't know if we talked about this.
But there was a lovely woman from audible.com
who was at BloggerCon.
And Dave and I met with her after BloggerCon.
And we probably talked to her for about...
A good hour and a half or so about what podcast
and can do for audible.
And then we're both customers of audible.
And we talked about what we liked and we disliked about audible.
And we're...
You know, I was saying where the fuck is the Oprah Book Club podcast?
That's what I'm looking for, you know?
And shit, you know, I was basically saying,
hire me to do it.
I wasn't really saying that, but, you know,
I was as a figure of speech.
I was like, so clear that this is what they need to do.
And it's just not easy moving organizations around.
They're located in Wayne, New Jersey, which I know Wayne very well, by the way.
Is that any of the Willowbrook Mall?
Think, Wayne?
Regardless of that.
It's interesting that today I should receive a...
Actually, it's the full podcast.
I'll just play a little bit of the beginning.
It's from audible in Germany, audible.de.
And guess what?
They're doing a podcast.
audible, clever lesen.
The time.
From 1411 to 2004.
Yeah, coming with the guy.
The time.
All man.
I hope no one understands German.
Listen to this show.
Okay.
So that's the audible.de podcast.
Isn't that cool?
So one of two things will happen.
Either A.
This will catch on.
And audible will start doing book clubs and podcasts all over the place.
Or B.
It probably just is likely to happen.
Headquarters is going to fucking freak out and tell them to stop immediately because this was not sanctioned.
This is not how we do business.
And now an audio comment from Ben.
Which I haven't listened to yet.
So God knows.
Hi there Adam.
It's a fun time Ben over from tracks of the tree.
Hey, fun time with my first audio comment to your website.
I just want to say as it is customary to say.
Yeah.
I really enjoy the podcast.
And I'm listening since show 10.
And I can't go a day.
I'm just, you know, it's a figurative thing.
When you go a day or can't you go a day without?
I was listening to your podcast from November 30th.
And then reminded again on the first of December podcast.
When you said that you wish that I potter or I potter acts or whatever program had a button that you could press,
which you would only download that the podcasts that you want after going on vacation.
Actually, I want to update that situation.
I found what I find.
I found a new program called Play Pod.
It's for OS 10.
Actually, some Apple site.
Was that next to Potom feeder?
I mean, I'm finding all these new OS X.
I pot variance.
The play pod actually has some of the features that I was looking for.
And I've been, I've been testing it.
Or whatnot.
Well, I can't give you that right away.
What I can offer you is a way to do the same thing without buying or changing any software.
You have everything you need right in front of you.
Are you ready?
Oh, my goodness.
Down a business.
So what you need is iTunes.
Got it.
Pretty.
It's actually pretty simple.
What you do is you open up your new podcast dynamic playlist.
Do you remember the new podcast dynamic playlist?
We set up way back when in the early days of podcast.
Oh, I'm going to think way back.
Yeah, I remember.
Basically, the rules for the new podcast or anyone who doesn't have a new podcast.
Okay.
I was like running now.
I was like, Ben's got it wrong.
That's only if you can download everything.
Then, of course, it's different, you know, different challenge.
And then you can indeed use iTunes.
What you're explaining basically is content management.
And that's the thing that we don't have running quite yet in any of the iPodders that
I've seen.
Let's just, and I, and Ron Bloom, who Dave and I have been talking to as a, he's a, he's a great business guy.
I got to tell you a story about Ron.
Not today.
I got to another time.
Actually, I have to tell the story when I'm with Ron.
Otherwise, he can't provide any role model, but doesn't matter.
It's, for a business standpoint, if you say anything is like the TV of anything.
It's not really a good idea because TV, although a big hit with consumers has not been
in the success that, that was thought, that it might, that the potential was projected to be.
Let's put it that way.
And of course, the reason is because the content is limited.
The content is limited to the people who own the fucking products, which is basically the television networks.
But the TV of podcasts and the TV of radio, when it comes to the actual functionality,
is so right on, you know, and what does TV do very well.
It does content management.
It makes decisions for you.
And it looks at the size of your hard drive.
And it looks at all kinds of things.
And, and it starts to fill itself up based upon a rule set or a matrix.
And I think it's not simple, you know.
It's, it's a, basically, there's a, there's a lot that has to be done before, before you get that right.
And the number one thing is just when this shit get deleted.
I've been hovering around three gigabytes on my hard drive for the past, you know, month and a half.
Just, you know, deleting stuff and getting, you know, I've been the basic content management manager.
And that's what my computer should be doing for me.
I should, you know, I have a pretty simple set of rules.
You know, I rarely want to save anything.
If I do, I put it in a special place and save that.
And otherwise, get rid of shit when I have to.
And, or it's, make sure I've played it.
If I haven't, you know, alert me to it.
I mean, it's a real simple rule set.
But that's where a lot of the iPod or stuff is going to go eventually, I think.
So, so it's not, it's a, it's a different person.
What was the other thing the other day?
You know, just have a slider that basically, well, fuck it, that won't work either.
Yeah, you got to, you got to be able to make some, some really good content management decisions.
One that I made was to subscribe to the Willis effect.
Oliver Willis, I met at the first blogger con.
And, great guy.
Very, very outspoken on his blog.
I forget what his day job is.
But man, once he discovered podcasting and he pinged me and he sent me a, he sent me a quick email saying,
Well, I don't know if you have bandwidth or time, but, you know, check out the podcast.
I've been listening to him podcast number three at this point.
And he takes on the media and it's, it's fun to listen to the Willis effect.
And that felt, it feeds into the, you know, the story that came out, that's coming out Monday morning,
about Pat Delman, you know, God bless the sacrifice to the country.
But the media, once again, has a lot itself to be played by the military.
The military is tweaked the story of Pat Delman's death in Afghanistan in order to serve their purpose.
And it's a matter of media being manipulated by the military, by the government, by whatever,
because media doesn't actually, they don't do any work anymore.
They get pre-fed personal uses.
That's why they're open to pressure from outside of groups, because if you craft a story and a simple,
back to the simplicity argument in a simple way that the media can handle,
then you can get play for your story.
You can get your, your point of view out there.
Oh boy, is that true?
That is so true.
But he's going to go on.
He's going to say that the media is stupid.
Then I have to disagree with it.
But it's true what he's saying.
It's once you've got something focused.
And it's in a nice, bite-sized chunk, the media will eat that shit out.
Because the media is, it's like a drum.
You know, if you can hit them right, you can play.
Boring.
So it's a matter of, you know, from the Telman story in Afghanistan to the never-ending stream of stories
that comes out from the military's PR department that writes pre, you know, stories ahead of time for the media.
And it says, you know, how great things are going in Iraq.
That's sort of what they do.
And the media just follows, hey boy, and how's that dollar doing everybody?
Huh?
How's that dollar?
You're paying for something America?
Wait a minute.
That's my tax dollars, too.
Got a damn it.
It's along like the laptops that there are.
I'm not saying that the media doesn't necessarily has a conservative agenda.
I don't think the media necessarily has any sort of agenda other than a bias towards the stupid in the simple.
I don't think the necessarily, you know, are in the pocket of the Republicans,
even though a lot of the corporations that, you know, own the media are in favor of Republicans because I think the media is just dumb.
I think the media just does what the easy thing is.
If the easy thing is to report that the war's going bad, that's what they do.
If the easy thing is to report, you know, that the war's going awesome, that's what they do.
And I have to agree with all over here because, and that's not just because it's the easiest thing.
It's the most efficient use of time.
Basically, and I've seen this happen time and time and time again, particularly with news media, anything.
And particularly with television news, you know, you got to get the story, got to get the shot, got to run, got to move to that, you know,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
So sometimes the reporter comes out predetermined, knows exactly the story he or she wants to get.
Sometimes there's, you know, an investigation and then boom, this is it.
And I'm going to get that.
I'm going to focus on that and it's based upon ratings.
And the lead up to where we had no investigation of the war's claims.
Look at the New York Times, supposedly liberal New York Times.
The New York Times devoted more space on its pages to explaining Jason Blair than to explaining the poor reporting of its own war of its own correspondence.
All right, okay.
So check out the Willis Effect, Oliver Willis.com.
Another podcast that you actually can't receive yet is the Ken and Squip Show.
I think I've talked about this before.
Ken Kencer J. Living in, well, fuck does he live?
Oregon. Oregon, I think. Yeah, Oregon.
Used to be my personal assistant, basically lived at my house.
And Cindy, the squip, squipper, who was one of my first employees at the thinking of ideas, actually when it was still called on ramp.
They've caught the podcasting vibe and they put up one show.
I talked about it, pointed to it.
And of course the inevitable happened.
Good line.
Pre thanks, giving digital stampede,
ties up internet traffic for hours on East Coast.
The apparent culprit seems it was something called the Ken and Squip Show.
An internet audio talk show also referred to as a podcast.
An instant hit with geeks.
I take a fence to that personally, around the globe.
Yeah, hold on. I just want to play that bit.
What was it? The geeks.
There we go.
With a web geeks.
I take a fence to that personally, around the globe.
And after a plug by internet pioneer, Adam Curry,
very most of the Ken and Squip holiday extravaganza special,
exceeded all bandwidth limitations causing the eventual debacle.
And the untimely demise of our broadcasting empire as it turned out.
So we got basically our plug-pulled.
We were on the very eve of Thanksgiving.
While we were busy stuffing our birds,
we got bent over the coffee table and stuffed ourselves.
Yeah, right on.
All right.
So you can find it at audio.weblogs.com.
The show was listed on today's top-hundred podcasts.
So definitely give that, you know, check it out.
I'll put up a link in the podcast production show notes for today.
Because I actually, what I did as I hooked him up,
and I gave him a little bit of bandwidth off of one of our servers.
I think that, you know, listen to the show.
Let me know what you think about it.
I think we're a little bit of coaching and a little bit of technical help.
We could have a definite, you know, pod squad membership coming up here.
Because they're pretty funny.
And I'm not quite sure.
I don't know if this has done all on Skype
if they're recording separately from their individual locations.
But it sounds great.
And I just love these two to death. They're funny.
Bantrax.
Bantrax podcasts.
Attention on Bantrax.net.
Hey Adam, this is Candace Lupus from Bantrax.net.
First, we wanted to thank you and all the others
that have made podcasting happen.
And our wives will also like to curse you
for taking up what little free time we did have for them.
We'd also like to tell you about our podcast at Bantrax.net.
What we do is we focus on independent artists, authors and comedians.
But with one difference, we also give them the place to sell their art on our website.
We take care of the hassle for a minimal $2 fee
and they get to make what they want from their work.
Again, a big thanks for podcasting.
And we hope to see you around Bantrax.net.
That's B-A-N-D-T-R-A-X.net.
And by the way, we heard Patricia's story the other day
about Stevie Nix's stinky butt.
Well, we have our own celebrity brush with stink.
Oh, yeah.
One time we were doing a news interview with Weird Alienca Vic in Australia.
And let me tell you that guy can stink up a stall.
Bantrax.
Bantrax podcast.
Attention.
On Bantrax.net.
Everybody.
All right.
Excellent.
Excellent guy.
I see you on demand.
Okay.
Let's see.
And we're doing pretty good here.
We're going to make it in the 40-minute time window.
Good, good, good.
It's what I was looking for.
Winding it up with some more British culture.
And this is something I have to look at yourself through the podcast show notes.
An email that I got from Craig Morgan and Craig said,
and you just caught up with the last few daily source codes,
thought in your quest to understand the UK,
you might get some kick out of this.
It's the passport to the pub.
And this is actually a really big deal in the United Kingdom.
It's the pub.
And we're still kind of looking for our local pub and where it is,
and we're supposed to go.
And of course, once we're there,
how we're supposed to act and kind of fitting with the locals.
So it's this whole, and it's really,
it's a social issues research center that is published this.
It's what the pub is about,
the background, choosing your pub,
how to make contact.
What, you know, pub talk, when to treat,
when it's your round.
And then, of course, the opposite sex,
and it turns out, and guys, check this out.
Where is it?
Until about 20 years ago,
it was pretty much a macho thing,
but now women, women, women,
make up more than half of the pub going audience.
Wow.
I can't.
You know, English women, man.
I haven't really studied them yet.
Patricia pointed some cute women out to me,
what we're doing grocery shopping today.
And I don't know if she did that.
I don't know why she did that actually.
I was on the phone talking to Alessandro,
Italian journalist, who was interviewed me
for a magazine about podcasting clearly,
because there are a couple of Italian podcasts.
So maybe she just tried to distract me from that,
or, I don't know, but I gotta, I gotta figure,
well, you know what?
It's time for a pub cast.
That's what we're gonna do.
A pub cast, definitely.
Looking forward to doing that.
Oh, I gotta wind it up for today.
Let's see.
Oh, I love playing promos that I haven't heard before.
This is a wizard's holiday promo from Mr. Mark
and Digital Bill.
Well, what the hell?
Let's check it out.
Hey, this is Digital Bill,
and this is Mr. Mark.
From the Wizards of Technology,
and we're just here to tell you
about our special holiday technology edition podcast.
Very cool, huh?
Absolutely.
We're both giving our top five favorite holiday
geeky technology gifts.
And not all of them are expensive.
We have a very double-corned,
a copy of goodies up there.
Boy, it's a range of things all over the place.
So come on down to the website,
pick up the podcast for our special holiday technology
edition of,
go ahead.
The Wizards of Technology.
Is it up?
You know, whenever someone tells you
is a veritable plethora of anything.
You know that you got to go check it out, right?
The Wizards holiday promo.
That's going to do it for the source code for today.
Tomorrow I am off to London to the big city.
To big smoke as we call it.
I'll be there meeting with the banksters.
So I haven't quite decided yet
if I'm going to do a podcast.
I'm going to take the train by the way.
If I'm going to take do it on the way up
or on the way coming back.
Or if I'm going to find a spot
and London to sit down,
maybe in and do the show.
I'm just having lunch.
So I will have plenty of time to figure out
how to do the cast of the pie.
And that's it for your source code for today.
Tuesday, December 7.
Thanks so much for tuning in everybody.
Of course, comments are welcome.
Please send the audio comments now
as an attachment in emails.
Don't you can keep it under five megs.
It should be okay.
Because I'm just leaving the email on during the night
to suck it all up and cash it.
Have it ready for me in the morning.
Like an email.
I thought it was kind of, you know, something like that.
It's adamantcurry.com.
Of course, you can leave a comment on the webinar.
You can find it.
Curry.com.
And of course, the latest episode
will be archived today
with the source code of daily source code.com.
And if you haven't heard it yet,
check out Dave Winner's Christmas story
on scriptingnews.com.
You got kids definitely play.
It's a good one.
I'll check you tomorrow, everybody.
Take care.