It's Adam Curry!
What's this?
Take a PC and a microphone into the bathroom?
Not read.
The shower of pure intellect.
Do you have good light Adam and drink the show?
Cheers.
The shower.
Yeah.
Hey everybody, welcome to your daily source code.
It's coming to you once again from Surrey.
Surrey.
Adam Curry and Surrey never in a hurry.
It's from the Curry Cottage in the United Kingdom.
Today is Wednesday, December 29th, 2004.
Once again a full full show for you at the time of recording.
Although I don't know if I should tell you that every single time.
But it's kind of midday.
It's 11.30.
We have some friends dropping by.
Actually, they should have been here about half an hour ago.
So I said, fuck, I'm going to start the show.
And if they show up, they'll just actually hear the dogs barking now.
You know that when I start the show, that's when they come.
Right?
Screw it.
They're going to have to wait for 40 minutes.
As will you because for the next 40 minutes, the source code is
Chock Full with new podcast, pod save music and general diarrhea of the mouth from me.
I've been actually had a great sleep last night.
We went to bed on time.
Well, it was 11.30.
That was real early for us.
We've been going to bed so late, of course, to Christine.
That still doesn't start school until next week, mid next week.
So I was up real early this morning, up around.
See, I woke at six o'clock and kind of slumbered around until seven.
Got up, let the dogs out, let the cats out and set down.
And watch the sun rise over the downs.
I've posted a link to a picture of the downs before on my weblog.
It's just beautiful.
Just beautiful.
But then, of course, all the shit sets in, right?
Because wow, you hear that?
I've had this problem with maybe if I just quit my email application.
It seems like that is somehow screwing up the recording sometimes.
In fact, you should probably quit all applications when recording a podcast.
Directed this.
So the day start off great.
It was beautiful.
I was drinking my tea.
I could see the animals, frolicing in the back.
You know, looking at other people on the downs through the gate.
And then, of course, I read the news that we are now up to a death toll of almost 70,000 people.
This is, this just boggles my brain.
It's hard to fit this in 70,000 people.
You know, when we thought that 9-11 was bad or the great Chicago fire or, you know,
Tiananmen Square or, I mean, God, it's so hard to imagine.
And you know what's going to climb?
You know, I'm not sure exactly how they count this or how they do that.
But you know what's going to go up to 100,000.
And I'm dumbfounded.
I don't know what to do.
I mean, of course, immediately I gave money to Red Cross.
I'm sure that you've probably done that as well.
It's a reputable organization.
You know that your money is going to be spent well.
But it's got to be a drop in the fucking bucket.
And how many people are affected?
You know, how many people will you know that lost someone in this great tragedy?
I bet you it's going to be more than you can imagine.
I got an email from Lou Josephs, who's been a weblogger for quite a while.
He's also a broadcast guy.
I think he still lives in DC or in the Virginia area.
He says, Jonathan, I have a great friend on the island.
I don't know which island that.
A Sri Lanka.
Sorry.
He's also a ham radio operator.
Old technology.
But it works when the podcast doesn't details on his blog and on Mark's blog.
So they've actually had some contact.
And I've obviously put a link in to, to lose weblog from the production show notes.
Something about the show notes.
If you don't mind me just skipping over the 70,000 dead.
Jesus Christ.
I don't know what to do yet.
Something about the show notes briefly though.
I was talking to Dave last night.
And we've had some great conversations in the past couple days.
It's almost every single day and he'll call up.
You know, I kind of know where he is because I try to follow along with scripting news.
In fact, I've learned that it's best to make sure I've read scripting news before I talk to him.
Because, you know, he presumes sometimes that I've read that.
And vice versa by the way.
Come on in.
They're here.
No.
Oh.
I'm doing my podcast.
I thought they were here.
Come in.
What?
You just had your coffee, right?
Oh, but are you offering me another one?
Yes.
And I have chocolate sponge cake.
And I have an offer of...
What do you have on sale today, Pat?
Yeah.
Chocolate sponge cake and cheesecake.
Strawberry cheesecake.
Oh, you don't want to leave the cheesecake whole until the guests come.
We first going to taste it.
Okay.
Could you please bring me some cheesecake?
How it is.
Why don't you?
Yeah.
We'll check it to see if it's good.
I'd love some cheesecake.
It's a chocolate cake.
It's wonderful.
Now the cheesecake will be gone.
Yeah.
And I'd love...
Yeah, thank you.
What is this?
What?
This is lovely service.
Is this always here in the cottage?
Yes.
Really?
What do I have to do for that?
You know?
No.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
I was just talking about the 70,000 people.
Oh, yeah.
The fuck are we going to do about this shit?
And why?
Why?
Okay.
Thanks.
I don't deserve it.
No, of course I don't deserve that.
The fuck is that?
It's horrible.
Who's God?
Can you close the door, huh?
Thanks.
Who's God?
Did that?
That's what I'd like.
I'd like George Bush to stand up and say...
This was not our God who did this.
I'd like the Buddhists to stand up and say...
This is not our God.
Or maybe some God will take responsibility for it.
Please.
And the God casters, which, you know, I have great respect for the God casters, pod casters, who
are doing religious podcasts.
We have quite a bit of them in the iPodod.org directory.
Where's the explanations?
Where's Reverend Tim and tell me why?
Why, why, why?
I'd like to know why.
If there ever was a time for religion,
to make a statement, good or bad, this is the time.
This is the time.
I wonder if that's going to happen.
Hold on.
Let me just reset my audio hijack pro here.
I told you this is such a weird problem to have this latency.
And everyone has it one way or the other.
If you're doing digital broadcasts and you've got stuff...
Chained together, you're going to run into that.
So, I hope you hook up with the guys from...
What is it, amoeba?
Rogue amoeba software?
Wait, who makes audio hijack pro?
Is that Rogue amoeba?
Yeah.
Rogue amoeba.
Okay.
Anyway.
So, I'm just dumbfounded.
I don't know what to say.
I really don't.
I wish there was something that podcasting could do to...
To make it better.
To make the hurt go away, to help these people.
I don't think there is.
I think the easiest, simplest form that we've come up with...
Of ways to help people is to send money.
And...
You know, I don't think that an early warning system putting that in...
And by the way, you know, this could happen in the North Atlantic.
This could happen in the Pacific.
It could happen in the North Sea.
You know, what's the Star Wars plan for that?
You know, and will we have enough money to implement that?
I say we, because...
I figure I'm pretty much living on American soil in the UK.
By the way, I've noticed that...
People in the UK actually like youngs.
It's changed a little bit.
I think in the past that used to be...
There were some apprehension.
I think that there's...
I don't know what it is.
I don't know.
Maybe it's just American culture has steeped in.
Or maybe we've come to terms.
Or maybe because we're fighting side by side in Iraq.
I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
But...
I feel very welcome here in the United Kingdom.
I seriously...
I really, really do.
And it's so nice to have so many people sending me free little emails.
You know, about the corkiness of the UK, helping me out with learning the culture.
Man, it's...
It's really...
It's a great thing.
It's appreciated.
Right.
Your source code.
Always looking at what's going on.
Where users and developers party together.
One of our big users...
Are the lascivious bitties.
I got a beautiful email from Leon from the bitties.
I thought I'd send you a message of solidarity.
On vacation for Christmas, first in Omaha,
then in Brooksville, Florida.
In Omaha, I had a kinko's with Timo Wawireless,
but here in Brooksville, no rental car.
No wireless opportunity and only dial up.
Thirsty for podcasts.
Can't wait to get home to hear what you've been talking about over the holidays.
Just a message of solidarity, at least we have cable and pound cake.
Be well.
Leon, thank you very much, Leon.
We got cheesecake here.
And actually, I've been learning to live.
This Wi-Fi thing is getting us much closer to ubiquity of broadband.
Because yesterday, you know, that I rushed off after I finished the source code
to go pick up Christina's friend at the airport.
And I just grabbed the laptop with me, had it encoding on the back seat.
We'll talk about that in a second.
And when I got to the airport, I had to go to the departures level
because there was no Wi-Fi available on the arrivals level.
Go figure.
That's where everybody is sitting and waiting the most, you know,
beautiful opportunity.
And was able to just hop right onto the, onto the T-Mobile wireless.
In fact, it's a, I should have taken a picture of it.
It's a huge sign at Heathrow, a terminal 1, 2 and 3.
That says, you know, T-Mobile, the world's largest W-Lan network,
which is a big statement to make, but you know what?
They are out there.
And it's getting to the point.
Just look at what Dave, what Dave Winner is witnessing.
He bought a truck stop.
Wireless subscription.
This is great.
And he says that only in a couple of months since the last time he drove coast to coast
has he seen, you know, the ubiquity really, really pop up.
There's almost, you can get a Wi-Fi almost anywhere.
So getting pretty damn good.
And of course, because you can get Wi-Fi almost anywhere,
you can get some excellent dropcated since this time.
It's a hit.
Remember this one.
There's a University of Michigan, I believe.
You remember I'd asked for some hits?
Remember I'd asked for some hits.
That was the, oh shit, I messed up the last bit home on shit.
That was the widest version of Slupia, I've ever heard of.
Oh, this very squinger.
It's very square.
Patricia just walked back in where the great announcement here.
No, no, no.
I was just thinking, I was downstairs, the whole house is nice.
I cleaned up everything.
All right.
Because we wanted to show the new cottage and the house smells nice.
I have candles on and you know, a little bit of papery here.
Oh, curry, everybody.
And you know what?
Because we're ready for them.
Yeah.
And always, and I know people who have cats know this.
Mm-hmm.
They go to the kitty's house.
Just before you guess.
They pooped.
Yeah.
They go on the kitty's box.
Because they don't like the smell.
They don't like our smell.
They don't like papery.
They don't like all your candles.
They have their own papery.
All right.
Isn't it always the same?
Han, you know what?
Yeah.
You can come in here anytime to talk about poop.
I want you to know that.
I'm so happy.
Anything poop related is good in my book.
I'm a vegetable.
Okay.
Love you, Han.
Let me know when they're here.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, lovely.
Thank you very much by the way for the wonderful drum cadence.
More hits, more hits, please.
More hits.
Yesterday, I mentioned that I thought that I had solved the entire encoding issue of not being able to play this show on certain palm devices.
And I disabled the filter selection on the lame brain MP3 encoder.
If you don't know what I'm talking about, skip ahead one minute or listen to yesterday's podcast.
So I set it now.
I deselected all of the filters and set it at 44.1 kilohertz.
And I got a lot of comments.
Mainly people saying, please change it back to whatever it was because we could hear all this warmably noise.
Because I guess lame brain does have a lot of really cool filters in there that that really processes the sound.
So today I've tried it differently.
I'm setting it to 22.050, which should that's a sample rate for the audio, which should work on the palms.
And it should also sound good.
Because I've left the filters in.
Well, let me know because I agree yesterday sounded really warbly.
And yeah, it wasn't, it wasn't quite what I was looking for.
New podcast.
Finally, I'm able to create a book category on ipod.org because we have the brand new bound cast.
Fitting a new revolutionary medium like podcasting.
We'd like our first book to be about a revolution in itself.
So our first book is Revolution in the Valley, which is Andy Hertzfeld's book about the development of the Macintosh.
From all the way from when he was first hired at Apple.
Through the development of Macintosh itself.
And then all the way into the Scully crew of that ended John's first term.
And it's a great start-up story.
It's got lots of light hours and pizza by the ton.
And you know, strange characters and weird happenings and things like that.
And it's organized into a hundred short stories.
And they're all well-written and quick to read.
I read the whole book, kind of covered a cover in about three hours.
You know, that's why you could freak with the sort of stuff.
I'd love this story.
The development of the Macintosh for me is the ultimate, you know, expression of passion.
Where the people who worked on it were all just brilliant.
And it's kind of a story that inspired my whole career.
And I think that applies for a lot of us.
What's interesting, I think, about the book, is that it shows that the development wasn't anything unusual.
You think about how Revolutionary the outcome wasn't, you think, wow, you know, to be involved in that,
was just been insane.
But because the model of the development with the late hours and that dot-com insanity has been reused so many times,
a lot of what they went through is very similar to what we went through today.
And it's inspiring in a way.
It's inspiring to see that at the end, all of that, you can do something revolutionary and change the world.
And this was one of the very first times when that happened in the computer industry.
And Andy's really captured that feel in this book.
So for me, this is a five out of five star book, of course.
And I think that if you're going to return some books or return some gifts,
that you got, you might want to go and take this book out as an exchange.
So there you have it, our first book review.
Five out of five stars for Andy Hertzfeld's Revolution in the Valley.
Oh, dude, most excellent.
The bound cast, a little bit soft on the audio there.
I tried to crank it up as much as possible.
Great mic sound.
And God, I love having a book review that lasts two minutes and 30 seconds.
That is perfect.
And I guarantee you that eventually will sell some books.
And I bought it out or directory.
You can go to the books node brand new node.
And just select that.
I guarantee you will not regret it.
Hello.
Hi, Mr. Curry.
Well, hold on.
Let's agree on one thing, everybody.
Let's agree.
We don't call me Mr. Curry.
Um, that makes me feel the 40 years I am.
Vote podcasting.
I just got my 40 gig about.
I pod for my 21st birthday on the 9th of December.
Okay.
Now I see why you're calling me Mr. Curry.
21.
Okay.
Higher time from then until about the 20th getting my library organized.
Then I heard about podcasts.
Sorry.
I was a little slow on the news, but once I did get iPodter, I took to it like a fake.
And let me tell you something about the iPods.
I bought an iPod mini for Christina.
And configuring these things on Windows is not snap, you know, snap crackle pop easy
123.
No way.
You know, it's got a reformat itself.
You've got to actually it has to be a little bit charged before you can connect it.
And then you have to disconnect it from from the install process, plug it into the firewire
plug that plugs into the wall outlet or to the adapter so that it can reboot its firmware.
It's a fucking horrible process.
And in the Netherlands, and I have received multiple calls about this.
There is no Dutch user guide.
You don't even give you a fucking English user guide.
Now, they're dumping these iPod mini from either Germany and or France because that's the only two
user guides user manuals that it comes with is with a French one and a German one.
And it's complicated.
You know, if you don't have a Mac, we just plug it in and the shit works.
You've got to figure it out by yourself.
And if there's no Dutch user manual or even an English one for that matter,
sure, you can download it from Apple.com.
Sure.
That's not the point.
Not when you pay that kind of money for an iPod mini.
I've been helping so many people doing a basic phone support trying to help them
rig up their iPod mini.
It's wacky.
It's not an easy install process.
In fact, it reminded me a lot of the first iPodders.
Jesus Christ is so hard.
So, of course, what we'd want in the future would be obviously to have the iPod
or built into the iPod.
And do I have that list?
I was going to talk about that today, wasn't I?
About, yeah, I'm going to talk about iPodzilla, of course.
I have your show, Dawn and Drew Show, Leo LePortz, Pack Report, really learned Spanish
and a whole bunch of others.
So, I'm always listening to the podcast.
Either way, I really want to start my own.
I'm kind of used to the blog thing because I do a mobile blog on textamerica.com
and I have the link in my email.
But sorry to bore you with the introduction.
I don't know how to explain where I'm coming from.
Basically, I want some pointers from, you know,
the father of podcasts and passmaskers.
Okay, if you go to iPod.org,
hold on a second.
I'm getting that frickin' delay again.
If you go to iPod.org in the directory,
there's a documentation node.
You can find all the links you need right there.
It really is the resource for,
what they've put on that, the resource for the iPod platform.
By the way, they've also father of,
the podcast, please.
The internet.
Don Maselli.
Mother of the internet.
Could please.
On how I can get started.
Okay, no problem at all.
Just go to iPod.org.
That's where all the resources are that you need.
I guarantee that's exactly where you're going to find it.
Glad to see, by the way, that Dave got his audio fixed.
That crapping out was apparently caused by,
how shoot, what was that thing that automatically
records radio broadcast for him?
That was apparently what was causing all the hiccups
in his recordings.
So I'm glad he got that fixed.
And he put up a test podcast.
Hopefully we'll get some more from the road
from him today or tomorrow.
My God, what are we 20 minutes in this?
I have no idea how I'm going to finish the entire show today.
Let's see.
We have another first recording here.
You know, Adam, JT here, soon to be podcaster.
Just trying to test out my rig here and send you a little note.
I heard that Carlin thing you played the other day
and just laughing hysterically.
But just wanted to voice a little support.
Let you know you're doing a fantastic job pushing this.
And I buy into your vision completely.
In fact, I plan on starting two podcasts.
One kind of dedicated towards technology for the business user.
And that's kind of like my business slant, so to speak.
And second one being geared towards frankly beer and wine.
Yeah.
All right, screw the technology.
All right, finally another beer podcast beer and wine.
Got a little bit lesser expensive wines for the masses.
And doing a bit of beer brewing and sharing those experiences online.
It's unbelievable.
There are at least four beer podcasts.
This is big, big stuff.
This, this almost as big as religion.
I'm telling you, large circles of friends and all that.
And they're all totally hyped about what's going on with podcasting.
So keep up the great work.
I won't keep this short.
So you won't have all kinds of bad download times.
You know what's nice about about the bandwidth when you send something through email.
Excuse me, as long as I don't have my mailbox full up, fill up.
Over night, everything comes in.
If you send it the end of the day in the States,
I'm going to have it the next morning.
It'll be already down.
It's kind of like an email iPodder.
It's really, it's quite incredible.
So anyway, great can't wait to see you come along with with yet another beer podcast.
I love beer podcast as much as I love coffee.
I was talking about the sense sale the other day.
Wondering if that was for sale in the States.
A couple of comments.
Of course, all of these listed on the on the show notes.
From Jennifer.
A sense sale machine is on sale in the States.
In fact, she says, my mom got me one for Christmas.
Love it, love it, love it.
And Joan sent me an email, which was actually almost even cooler.
She says it Christmas, my parents came over.
A lot of talk about geeky and geek and tech stuff.
They talk about her internet business.
And she says, check this out.
My dad happens to be the developer of the electronics and processing unit of the sense sale.
And he retired just a couple of weeks ago.
And was actually received a highly tweaked sense sale completely made of aluminium.
We need a picture of that, Joan.
I want to see the the pimped out sense sale machine.
And by the way, I've learned here in the UK it is aluminium.
Not aluminum, as we say in the States, aluminium.
I've been corrected on my.
In fact, the English are great at correcting.
Well, at correcting English.
Another excellent email here from Jim Davis, who says that he just received his February 5th
Mac addict.
It's the magazine.
It has in there a nine step procedure.
I didn't know it was nine steps.
I think it could be shorter than that.
A nine step procedure on podcasting.
And the disk, they always send a companion disk has all the software that you need to start
to podcast.
So of course, I haven't seen this yet the Mac addict.
I will pick up a copy as soon as I can get my hands on it.
So in there is BB edit.
I'm not sure.
Well, I guess BB edit too.
Maybe to create your RSS file.
Does BB edit 8.0.2 have a template for RSS files?
That's probably it.
I'll have to look.
I potter X2.2, excellent guys.
Line in, which is from Rogumi, this software.
It's a free way to basically get the mic going on your computer, on your Mac and record it.
Soundflower and transmit, which is I think an FTP client.
I don't know if you necessarily need that.
I mean, basically you can use some blog software and it will get you to the same place.
But kudos to the iPod or X guys for getting that kind of distribution.
That's freaking awesome.
So great to see podcasting being propagated once again.
And speaking of Mac, Phil Terone says that he's been using a media center PC 2005.
And an Xbox media center extender kind of as an iPodter.
And he's posted a link about it on in gadget.com.
So I put that link in the show notes as well for you to check out if you're interested.
Something about the show notes that Dave and I discussed in our talk yesterday.
I said, how many times do you check out the production show notes?
He says zero, never checked him ever.
So why is that?
He says well because if I wanted to check the notes, then I would have to be there at that moment.
So I would be talking about something he should be able to pick up the iPod and somehow get to that.
Which I think we're totally be a function of OPML.
But then he said something that kind of scared me.
Because he says, I don't know where, well, he was, of course he knows where the show notes live.
But he says, you know, when I do my aggregator scan, the show notes don't pop up.
He says, what he would want and this is what kind of freaking out is a way to scan the show notes to make a decision on whether he wants to listen to the show or not.
This is a very frightening thing for a broadcast or a podcaster for that matter.
Makes no difference for any communicator.
Because it's like judging a book by its cover, which means that not only do I have to now make a great podcast,
but I have to make a great show notes as well in order to make sure that people check it out.
So actually, I've decided, I don't want people checking out my show notes.
I want them to listen to the podcast.
The podcast will have a theme, will have a title, maybe one or two notes in the ID3 tags.
Of course, you should be able to get to the show notes to go back and check that if you really need something like the next song I'm going to play.
You want some information on Barry Coral.
You need to figure out where to get it.
But I don't like this idea of checking it before the podcast.
In fact, that freaks me out.
And I know because it's like the TV guide.
If you knew it was on the news, of course you know what's going to be on the news.
But if you really knew it's going to be on the news and they promoted that and they gave you the whole rundown,
not just the highlights, would you watch the news or would you scout around or would you look at the competition?
I think you would.
So I'm not too sure about putting all the topics of a show into the show notes.
I like it from production from a production standpoint.
So for instance, Michael Butler played a song that he received on CD the other day.
Podsafe music. He actually built it as Podsafe music in a rock and roll geek show.
And he played it.
And what I'd like is I'd like to be able to get that song.
In fact, I'd like my, you know, to be able to just click something and get his production notes and click on that song and be able to take the entire song and put it into my podcast without.
It will be beautiful.
I didn't even have to download it if it was kind of just all there.
But it doesn't matter.
If I could just drag and drop that into my, into my production console, that would be enough for me.
But I'm definitely freaked out about, you know, this is what's on the show because you do get the judge book by its cover.
And maybe we'll get there anyway, so maybe we have to learn how to write better show notes.
That could be possibly, you know, just the way it is.
In fact, have you ever noticed that if you, it's almost impossible to get the rundown of Letterman and Leno at the same time.
Because you'll start, I think I used to do it.
I'd start out with Letterman and, you know, and then switch after the first two names of Letterman because those will be his top guess switch over to Leno in the intro to see if you can see who's going to be on Leno show.
And it's very hard because they, they promote everything almost at exactly the same second.
So you kind of got to make a decision beforehand.
And maybe people do make decisions, maybe it's based upon the decisions of the promos.
I don't know.
Anyway, just in the mail.
What are we at?
Geez, only 10 more minutes.
I'm never going to make it.
Okay.
In the mail today, I finally got the brand new CD by Barry Coral.
We actually played something, what do we play, aspiring angel a couple days ago.
Beautiful note, Adam, hope you're well.
I've gotten some really nice emails from your listeners.
Thanks for all your support.
We'll smiley face from Barry Coral.
Confessions of an indie girl is the title of the CD.
One of the songs I liked a lot was midnight trained at Georgia, her rendition.
I'm not going to play that because I want to play something that she wrote herself.
This is a song I like from her CD.
This is the world you call home.
I guess it's a planetary premiere everybody on the Daily Source Code, Barry Coral.
Well, they got your down in your home town.
They tell you when.
They tell you how.
They find solutions and institutions and things.
To keep your back.
Yeah, I'm not going to hit them.
Someone here has been in your shoes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like the don't.
They're buying some comfort from your blue.
Have your listen to your radio.
And pull it off a stereo.
I hear it on your own.
All out of the world you call home.
Well, she broke your heart in a million parts.
And there's no ceremony for the venue.
So now you just move in the talk where the light can catch you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just want to hear from someone who's been in your shoes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like the don't.
They're buying some comfort from your blue.
And you listen to your radio.
And pull it off a stereo.
I hear it on your own.
All out of the world you call home.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know you found someone who's shrink up for you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you listen to your mv3 player.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
and V3 player. The world you call home, Barry Coral, from a brand new CD,
conversions of an indie girl, check it out and find out where you actually buy this CD. I'd
say Barry Coral.com, B-A-R-I-K-O-R-A-L. Or as we say in the aviation world,
so do it. Bravo Alpha Romeo, India, Kilo, Oscar Romeo, AlphaLima.com. Tomorrow I'll play some more
from Barry Coral. Really digging that CD. It's some of it's downbeat, some of it's slow,
but there's some real good uptempo tunes, and I think tomorrow I'll play the midnight train to Georgia.
I love her rendition of that. It's really cool. Okay, got a little more time that I've budgeted at
least because I don't want to keep you wait and longer than you have to on finishing up the goddamn
show. Podzilla. Talk about this yesterday about loading Linux on your iPod, and once I got back
and after I'd picked up Christina's friend, I did it. I installed Linux on my iPod. It was really
easy. You know, download of the application, click it, select it my iPod, it installed. It's a dual boot
if you can believe it. So when I crank up the iPod, I can choose whether to boot into Linux,
or I can choose if I want to go into the regular iPod system. I said like 10 gigs left or the
40 gigs. So basically when you boot into Linux, there's 10 gigs sitting there. Just waiting to be used.
All the executable files are in there. It's amazing. I think this is just the beginning. I think a
lot has to be done, but this is the first time actually the ship was working. I could scroll through
songs that were already on there by the way. In the other memory space that I guess it's
somehow knows how to see that. And I could play them. Of course, a lot of the stuff that you've
come to know and love about the iPod like power management, it turned off automatically. It doesn't
do that in Linux mode, but damn, we've got some really smart people working on this stuff developing.
And I'm going to follow it. I'm going to keep all the updates going. I'm very excited about this,
because if you can get an operating system on to an MP3 player, we could maybe route around
everybody and just make what we like. And please check out iPod.org where Dave started a conversation
about, you know, what's wrong with the iPod? What can we do to make it better? And there's lots
of people sending in all kinds of smart ideas. And now we actually might be able to to bring those
ideas to life. One of them, of course, is recording on the iPod. Not in this crappy eight
kilohertz sample bitrate that the built in and I'm Mike and whatever, you know, that they produce
standard out of the box with the iPod. But now you can go up to 96 kilohertz sample rate.
And the guy that turned me on to this is Ford Bailey. And Ford was nice enough to send
executive done it myself, but he sent me a recording that he made on his iPod. Listen to the quality.
Hey Adam, Ford Bailey here. And I'm recording on my iPod at 44.1 kilohertz. 44.1, but you do.
You know, it's unlocked the potential of the iPod for recording this iPod Linux has,
because Apple won't let you record it. I think it's eight kilohertz, which is fucked up.
And, you know, where the artists now, we need to be able to record our shit, right?
Yeah, going. Try iPod Linux out and try the recording. It'll record Mike or
line in beautiful. So you can use it as a recording device from from your power book or whatever.
And it's not invasive install. You can install it alongside your original iPods operating system.
So it's, uh, it's pretty easy.
Give it up. You're warranty may be void. And no, we're prohibited by law.
And, uh, it's put the word so that we can get, you know, development to speed up on this project,
because that will, you know, we have open source software on iPod. We'll be probably be better off.
Thank you. No kidding. And then how far off is?
Okay. Thanks buddy. And how far off is, uh, is the eye river from there? You know, or any other
MP3 player? I mean, is it? I don't know. I don't know why you can, maybe the iPod can do this,
because it has, you know, a disconnect. So it has a discontroller and all kinds of stuff. I don't
know anything about this, but totally, totally exciting to it. Even just to boot up and see your boot up
sequence, you know, if, if you've ever seen Linux boot up, uh, or if you, um, if you boot up your
Mac and you press, uh, Apple key V for verbose, it'll give you the same start up. You see all the
BSD stuff, and it's real geeky, right? But I love seeing that on my iPod.
Yeah, it's exactly. It's time for what is a day number nine of our 12 days of podcasting.
Eight review movies, seven torrent seating, a six pack of hanging,
three goofy coke, two punks of cousin and closures in an XML tree. Yeah, okay. If that doesn't do it for you,
then maybe tomorrow's installment will. Musicians, we're not all musicians. That's for sure.
All right, everybody in the kitchen, sing on now. Take it up back. Take your hat for new
music. Take your hat. All making me laugh. Yeah, everybody. Morning, noon, and night.
Good night, internet.
Who are my kids just now? That's it for the source code for today for Thursday, December 29th.
So I didn't get to everything I wanted to talk about today, but that's good because I had some
stuff left over for tomorrow, uh, which we're talking about, and that will make it, uh, Thursday,
the 30th almost the end of the year, and only five more days away from absolute total mega
bandwidth at the cottage. As always, comments are more than welcome at adamantcurry.com.
If you want to send an audio comment or song or anything, if it's under five meg, it's just a
touch it, send it off tonight, and it'll be there waiting for me in the morning. I'm off to Starbucks
to shoot this one up to the bird. As we used to say in the radio biz, and of course,
the download all the latest stuff, because so many new podcasts every single day between 10 and 20
new ones listed on ipodder.org, which is populating throughout the entire net, got to love it.
All right, everybody. Take care. See you tomorrow. Bye, bye.