This hit shut out of your Texas Ranger's final score last night and I'm really screwed on
635 OVJ.
It's Adam Curry.
It is the last day of the year.
Hey everybody, welcome to the source code 4.
Friday, December 31st, 2004, the last day of 2004 and the last cast for the year with the same number
2004.
There we go.
All right.
Lots to do with the source code today.
I mean, lots of power, lots of power, lots of power, lots of power, lots of power.
Man, actually, it's probably too much and I just want to get all the stuff out.
You don't want to keep anything more to start fresh in the new year with a new podcast.
There we got all going on.
Wait a minute, you know, there's absolutely no podcast that can start without a little
bit of drum cadence.
I'm sorry for the abrupt rock mine off break off there, but we just got a kick some cadence.
Hit hit, yeah, I'm telling you that this is one of my presolutions for the new year.
I got to start a cadence cast.
It's just too many people who are so totally innocent.
God, I love that.
Hi Adam.
This is The Noir Man from TheNoirMan.com.
I just wanted to say hi.
I love the show.
And I've noticed that you're on this drum cadence kick.
No, you don't say it lately.
So I wanted to share a little something with you.
As it happens, yours truly was a snare drum or back in school.
I happened to have some old tapes of my line doing stuff.
So this is an MP3 of my drum line, the Yuma High School marching criminals.
That's right.
My high school mascot was a criminal.
And this is us circa 1994, I think.
I believe this was the fall of 1994.
And I hope you enjoy it.
And once again, I love the show, best wishes to you and everyone in your life for a prosperous
new year.
Right out.
And keep up the good work.
Unfortunately, it's not one of the better recordings.
But of course, it is nine years old.
The criminals.
Yeah, we need to, I'm telling you, I'm going to do a cadence cast in the new year.
It just has to happen.
I'm receiving so many different drum cadences from people.
Let me see, I think I have what I had the blue doubles here.
I mean, I don't even have enough time in the source code to play all of this stuff.
Check this one out, this is pretty good, too.
This is from 1986, the new devils taking first place.
All of these, of course, are appropriately linked in the podcast production show notes.
Also got an email from Dorothy from Westalay, or is it Dorothy West?
No, no, it's Dorothy from Westalay.
She says that this cadence stuff sounds a lot like tyco drumming.
And now, of course, I can't find the tyco drumming bit that I had queued up.
I'm almost over here somewhere.
Shoot, I'll have to find this.
Lots of emails, lots of different cadences all in the production show notes for today's source code.
It's really, it's amazing how many people are into this.
This is a big community.
I'm just looking for more hits.
Looking for more hits done by really swinging bands.
It doesn't just have to be drums.
It can be, it can be with other, the fact, preferably with other instruments.
So, in today's source code, we have a lot of stuff to talk about.
In fact, I'm already going to skip right over the first two or the second and third items that I had queued up for today's show, because I know we're not going to be able to get to them.
It's 330 in the afternoon on the last day of 2004 here at the Curry Cottage in Lovely Gilford in the UK.
So this morning, I knew that I had to, or that I was going to go out with Patricia, I'm going to do lots of grocery shopping, get all kinds of stuff for tonight.
Of course, it's the three of us and then Christina's friend Isha, who was visiting from Holland.
She's British and she goes to the British school and that's where they met in Amsterdam.
She's been friends for a couple of years, so she's celebrating with us.
So we got all the food and stuff to burn in the fireplace, which of course can't be wood, right?
No, no, no.
Unfortunately, I'm not allowed to burn wood in this fireplace here.
It's just, the room is a little bit too small, so I have to resort to duraflame fire logs.
I know, it's not very manly, no chopping of wood, no splitting stuff, and no tough time lighting it.
This is just, you know, extend the two ends of paper, which light and go.
So I said to Patricia, I said, you know, yesterday, I actually tried to find a different spot than Starbucks to go,
you know, to get some connectivity, and I know that there are several other Wi-Fi providers,
just not necessarily with a, you know, a caffeination bar and baristas, standing by for my every back and call.
And it wasn't too successful, actually yesterday.
I also had a kind of a date with Lloyd, if you saw the weblog yesterday, he dropped by just to say hi.
So yeah, I kind of want to hook up with him, didn't want to, you know, just blow him off.
I was looking at other places to go, and I said, well, you know, what I'm going to do this morning is I'm going to load up the car.
I get my 12 volt adapter, so that it adapts to 110 volts right into the laptop.
I got everything else set, laptop on the front seat, got my I Stomler software running, which basically it scans,
frequencies to find Wi-Fi, and then it'll tell you if it's an open Wi-Fi or if it's closed.
Actually, I can't get it to, to make a sound when it finds something.
I thought that there was a way to make go blip or blowing or boiling, boiling would be appropriate, of course.
So I kind of magnified the screen, it's really easy on a Mac on OSX, there's a way you can zoom in on the screen.
So I zoomed in on the application itself, made it really big, so I knew that when I was driving out of the corner of my eye,
if it caught a Wi-Fi link, I'd see that happen, and I'd know to, you know, stop, we're trying to figure out if that was something that I could tap into.
So back out of the driveway, roll down like 15 yards and blink, there it is, I see it, this fucking net gear pops up on my screen,
which was not there before, the last time I checked was about four weeks ago, and it's an open Wi-Fi access point, and one of my neighbors has,
and I'm not quite sure which one, I try to locate it, it's, it must be bouncing off something because I can't really say,
okay, it's this house sorts that house, and it wasn't there before I know, because I checked the neighborhood quite thoroughly with
the same setup. So here's my theory, because I found that the previous people who were renting this home,
when they left, and they did something which wasn't really nice, although, perhaps understandable,
they basically transferred every single service and utility to their new house, and the real estate agent has no idea.
What's, I mean, the real estate agent actually told me there was already broadband in this house,
and we moved in and it turned out there wasn't. So here's my theory, I think this is what happened,
because also gas electricity, you know, the provider was contacted by the Revestate agent,
you know, who takes care of all the rental stuff, and they sent me a letter saying, sorry,
you know, we'd love to put it in your name, but you have a different provider, and we don't know who's
not going to find out who is sending, who is giving me electricity and gas, and how can I pay for it,
because if I don't pay for it, eventually it will turn off. So I think that the previous
tenant transferred everything, including broadband, which means that one of my neighbors was
probably on the on the waiting list, popped to the top of the queue, just as I was supposed to get
that port from British telecom, and probably they got my port, something like that, I guess,
doesn't make that much difference, because at this point, well, there's only three more days
until the fine folks that had easy net come into install my four megabit link. Of course,
I won't be here, so I'm working with Christina to instruct her exactly where it's supposed to go,
what's supposed to happen, and hopefully even get her up on the broadband while I'm in the states,
because I'll be gone until the 10th or the 11th. I think I come back on the 11th. So it's going to be
it's kind of like the stewardess landing the 747 with controls coming from
air traffic control on the ground. We'll see how it goes. She's pretty smart kid, she can figure
a lot of this stuff out. So anyway, so I found a spot right outside the door. Now, it doesn't,
I tried to to receive the same signal from inside. I walked around the whole neighborhood, it's almost
impossible to figure out who's it is. I know who's it isn't, because a couple of neighbors,
drove by or were getting ready walking into their house and I said, hey, I'm picking up a Wi-Fi,
is it yours? No, not mine. So I'm trying to figure it. Anyway, I'm happy it's there, and I will be using
it right after I finish this source code. I'll drive my car 15 feet into the road and I'm
be uploading from the A8 Studio. Think about it. I almost have a mobile studio that is, well,
that's completely mobile and has the Wi-Fi ready to roll as well. So anyway, so
after that, we went shopping and I took some time to buy a couple of newspapers, big newspaper
country here. Not what I'm used to at all compared to the Netherlands. There's so many papers,
tabloids, broad cheats, different types of information. But all the pictures, and of course, I've
seen most of these pictures on web logs, which is really, I think, web logs once again, or once
disaster strikes, web logs eventually bring you the best news, or the most complete news,
let's put it that way, because none of the news is really good at all. And I'm sure this has
happened to you. It happened to me this morning again when you look at these pictures, a picture,
which takes up the front page of the newspaper and you say, well, it's like all this rubbish in
the water. What is that? Is that crops? Until you look at the picture and I'm sure that this
happened to you, you say, oh, God, it's people. Thousands of people. It's very hard to be, it's very hard
to be upbeat, happy, it's very hard to understand. It hasn't quite hit the two girls who are here
Christina and her friend. They haven't really been exposed too much to it, I guess. They haven't
been watching that much television. But I know that the questions are going to come and I know
that it's going to be hard for them to fathom it. Once they truly understand what kind of devastation
this has been, what are we up to now? 125,000 on the death toll. So as I played that bit yesterday
from the CIDI, the best thing you can do is give cash. I'm giving cash left and right wherever I can,
I'm seeking out organizations. I figure if I give cash to several different organizations,
it'll help in different ways. At the shopping center, there's people outside, collecting money,
red cross, and in our own communities, of course, this is happening as well. I've got an email
from August. August is a part of the iPodorex team. He and Ray were talking about the horror
of course in Indian and Asia. What they're doing is, since they say that this point, they're probably
the only podcasting iPodore client that charges money for the full version, they're going to donate
all income of iPodorex's sale for the next days. Let's see, through January 8th for the next week
to the disaster relief. So when you buy iPodorex, use the word help in the coupon code
help HELP, and all of your money will go directly to the disaster relief. And you'll have a cool
iPodore client as well, which was also nice, by the way, when I was outside in front of the
Audi, I did an iPodore scan. It was great. It's just so nice that just have stuff come through.
I put out a call to the godcasters, podcasters listed under the religion node in the iPodore.org
directory. Because, you know, it's this god, is this mother earth, is this nature? What is it?
You know, I have questions, and I put some stuff out there. And what I'd like to do now is I'd
like to play a bit of this podcast, which is it's very new. It's brand new. I really like the podcast
for a number of different reasons. Production value extremely high. I'll stop it midway as we get into
this podcasters answer to my questions about the disaster. Please welcome to the podcast community,
Reverend Tim. Incoming subs-based. We have Tim, podcasters.
We're not giving them applause. What do I look like to hear?
We have Tim. She don't move much, but she makes one heck of a scarecrow.
Okay. Unbelievable. Unbelievable. Here we are again. This is Rev Tim, and it's great to be here
with you today. By the way, Rev Tim got some reverb and cowbell happening there. Greetings.
And welcome to the whole world. And this podcast is all about bringing hope to people around the
world and just kind of inspire you. So at this point Patricia was listening and says,
he's got kind of a sexy voice. It's kind of the message of God to your life in a
bringer. And at this point she said, I'm getting like a thornbirds kind of vibe from Rev Tim.
Look on life to you. I'm a pastor in the San Francisco Bay area and actually really I'm more of a friend
to a lot of people. And I get to speak open to their lives very often.
Now if you want to show notes, you can just point your browser over to podcast.rev.com,
podcast.rev.com or if you want to contact me by email, just go ahead and send podcast at
revtim.com. And that's how you can get a hold of me. You know, I wanted to come to you today and just
kind of talk a little bit about the tragedy of the tsunami that hits the Asian area.
And we were challenged yesterday. The Godcast community was actually challenged yesterday
by Adam Curry and he was kind of wondering out loud what could have caused all this or
or kind of his there are bigger picture involved. And let me just play a little clip from his
his podcast that happened yesterday. And I think you can get a little bit of an idea of what I'm
talking about with that. So check out what Adam Curry had to say and then I'm going to give you some
response to that. Who's God did that? That's what I'd like. I'd like George Bush to stand up and say,
this was not our God who did this. I'd like Osama bin Laden to stand up and say, this is not our God
did this. I'd like the Buddhist to stand up and say, this is not our God or maybe some God will take
responsibility for it. Please. And the Godcasters, which you know, I have great respect for the
Godcasters, podcasters who are doing religious podcasts. We have quite quite a bit of them in the
iPodot org directory. Where's the explanations? Where's Reverend Tim and tell me why? Why, why, why?
I'd like to know why here. If there ever was a time for religion, how cool is that? We're talking
to each other long distance, revenue to make a statement. Good or bad, this is the time.
This is the time. I wonder if that's going to happen. So you can see, I was really amazed because I just
had one podcast so far. This is only my second one. And I appreciate Adam talking and bringing that
up because I think that is a question that a lot of people have around the world. One thing that I
know is when you are trying to find out things about life that I know that God has a plan and
a purpose for everyone. And the thing that I have is as far as a life's birth as it's in the Bible
in Jeremiah 29 and 11 where it says, I know the plans that I have for you. They are plans for good
and not disaster to give you a future and a hope. And I think that's something that really kind of
drives us long-term and a philosophy through our life and gives us strength through the difficult times.
So what I'd like you to do is I'd like you to take 12 minutes out of your day and check out the
Revitim podcast. It's only about 12 minutes. You know I love the shorter podcast. And actually,
I'm a fan of Revitim, whether we agree or see either I or not. And my feeling after,
um, hold on. Hello. This is the man who rocks my boat. Yes, this is, in fact, I don't know. It's
both men because I, I just played Revitim the Revitim. I want you to talk about Revitim.
Talk about, no, no, I have to go because the shops are closing. But we just went shopping. We just came back.
I mean, for Christina, she wants pick up a shoes. I'm just so people know I'm not lining.
What did, what did I, what did you say about Revitim?
That he sounded very sexy. Thank you. Good.
That's right. He's married. Yes, he is. Yes, of course. Of course. Okay. Are you taking the car?
Are you taking a good news? And we're safe. Are you taking the car?
Cab? Okay. Okay.
Okay. This is probably the email close at four. Yeah. I think so.
Love you. Bye. Of course, Christina needed one final pair of something to end the year.
Hold on, to end the entire year.
Reventim. Okay. Anyway, I like your podcast, dude. It's good. It's very inspiring. We will not agree
on a lot of things. But what I like about Reventim, the Revitim podcast, is it inspiring? He's got
great production values. He has a great voice. I love the reverb. Need more cowbell. But the
reverb is good. And he's playing bits. He's playing clips. Very, very modern. I'm totally
digging it. And you're inspiring, dude. It's a good podcast. You can find it under the
religion node on iPod.org, which by the way is now being maintained by our buddy Rick from ICM
Raw, the independent Christian music podcast. And he's got it all split up now with different
religions. And so the node is really expanded into its own little mini tree. So check it out if you
want. I like it. You know, I actually, not a lot of people know, but I am a reverend. I am the reverend
curry. I became, I was ordained in politics. I'm going to say 1989 or 1990. And I have performed,
I basically to perform wedding ceremonies. It was one of those wacky DJ things, you know,
where on Valentine's Day I married 70 couples in Austin. But I was pretty serious about it. And
I have done some, I've performed some weddings for friends and another family and other people I know
and some really weird mixed marriages where they couldn't figure out who should do the service.
And I've always kind of enjoyed doing it. Because I take it seriously when two people
want to be together. And I'm not necessarily proponent of marriage. You can live together or
be you want. You know, just if you want to have a different kind of ceremony. I was your guy. I'm retired
now. And thank you, Rev Tim, for responding. He goes into in a whole bunch of detail. But with most
of the, the God castes, I've found that there's no real concise answer. And I don't think it's fair
to expect that from, from anyone. But they do refer to multiple passages in Scripture. And it's
always interesting to hear what people have to say. So talk about Rick, who is now maintaining the
religion node. I've been sitting on something that he sent me. He started sending me a couple of
recordings that he did with Rick Daringer. Rick Daringer, you probably know from Rock
and Roll Huchiku, probably one of his biggest hits. So Rick Wesowitz, he recorded a couple of
live sessions with Rick Daringer. I have one here live at Cheney Hall, actually have two songs.
And he sent me a version of Hang On Slopey, which of course he sent after I played that drum
cadence, the incredibly white drum cadence of Hang On Slopey. And, you know, immediately I said,
dude, can I play this on the source code? And he said, well hold on a second, you know, it's
it's iTunes safe for now. So put it in your iTunes. And he got in touch with Rick Daringer and Rick said,
yeah, hell, play it on a damn source code. Go for it. Hang On Slopey. So that's exactly what we're going to do.
Hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey
Won Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On, Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On, Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang on, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang On Slopey, hang on Slopey, hang
Hang on, slew that slew that slew that high out.
All the sick and way down low, now boys.
You know, back at 1965 when I first recorded this song,
the very first thing our hot shot New York City producers did was,
they went and they edited out the second verse.
What about the cowbell?
So what that means is, every single time you guys have heard this song
throughout your whole life, you've been cheated out of the second verse.
So I come here tonight to write along standing in justice.
I come here tonight to set the record straight once and for all.
You know why?
Because the buck stops right here.
So tonight we're going to play for you guys the missing.
The second verse.
So beware's a red dress, yeah.
This is all that's a hills.
But my slew beware's that red dress, Lord.
You know it gives me the chills.
Yeah, yeah.
What slew and when I see you walking, walking down that street.
I say you know slew big girl.
You know the one for me.
So where's the hell?
Hang on.
Stupid.
Is that being hang on?
Yeah.
I almost heard you sing at the last song.
Hang on.
Stupid.
Yeah.
Let's give it to him right now.
Okay boys, let's see if we can win!
Because now we're going to find out how a low you can go!
Let's see if we can win!
Imagine there's no heaven in it!
It's easy if they try!
No hell below us, above us, only sky!
Imagine all people living for today, the color of girls city!
One, two, three, four, imagine there's no countries!
Now imagine all people living life and peace, the color of girls city!
Let's see if we can win!
Let's see!