Before we get started, let me remind you of the following.
The results of events predicted in these things
may be very materialistic from actual results.
Doctors that could cause actual events
results to differ from expectations included,
lack of growth, intense competition in our industry,
integration failures, changes in government regulations,
operational failures, or looking to England's representatives.
All right, so with volumes of today,
it should not be relied upon as representing our nation
and the depth of any subsequent case.
While we name the lights up, they call it,
let me tell you the truth of the future.
We need to, not to be so even for an interesting thing.
Augustine, all's live!
Adam Curry!
Our honor to all of you.
Howdy everybody, and good evening!
From the bunker in Amsterdam, being head of the lens,
it's your daily source code for Wednesday, November 3, 2004.
Post-delection and post-exceptance speech
of our president George Dembibber.
The power of the Lord is strong!
Well, I'm here in the bunker, since I'm staying overnight here.
I want to be on time at the airport.
My flight leaves at five minutes as well,
and I've had to come out and come from Belgium.
I would like to leave around the shoot for 7 a.m.
to make sure that I, uh, we get stuck in traffic on my way to the airport.
So much easier to stay here, while we still have the place.
Yeah, like it's selling really fast. I think not.
And by the way, if you're really rich, and you want a cool place
to rent an Amsterdam, let me know.
It's like a really cool pad, okay?
I mean, like a chick magnet pad.
Oh, yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
All right, let's get this podcast going for today.
Just watch President Bush,
except for that of course I'll have a little bit of John Kerry's
speech as well well there you have it that's the ball game I was you know I
got a kind of a weird feeling watching the popular boat which of course is
also very interesting and there was a definite 3 million margin there there's
no dispute and apparently the first time since George H. Walker Bush was a
president that they not only the electoral votes were one but also the
popular vote and there was that you know that minute or so that I'm saying wow you
know I'm in the minority not used to that but oh sorry but as I was just
talking to Christina my daughter my 14 year old daughter on the father said well
you know the way the way we do it in America is if our you know if your guy
isn't chosen as president then you you got to support the guy that was chosen
and respect the majority in the vote but you know I see it as a great
opportunity for keeping our eye on the ball and getting ready for the next
election as as I heard Dave say on a mini podcast on his way to San Francisco
in the car you know one thing we know for sure in four years Bush will definitely
be out of the White House so plenty of opportunity and you know wouldn't be
nice if we got a blogger in the White House in in 2008 now Christina is
really angry she's pissed off and she's particularly pissed off she came up with
some statistic and I think she put it on her weblog she has a weblog that is
pretty much a good Charlotte weblog for the band good Charlotte it's called the
land of the young in the hopeless calm which points actually to Christina
dot menilla sites dot com now she's a vanilla user from way back when that
service was first native available for free and of course it's still
supported by the good folks at user land and she was really pissed about
this statistic that only one out of ten americans under the age of twenty
four voted and she said you know she's saying you know what the hell was all
those rock against Bush CDs you know they sold so many CDs but where are
these people they didn't go and vote they just couldn't be bothered to get up
off of their ass and I was really impressed you know with the with the
just with the fire that the girl has you know so she's just super
disappointed I said well you know we've got all the tools we've got our web
blogs we've got our podcasts and you know we can keep an eye on these guys and I
like buddies from Morocco when I went when I was over there after Taylor from
Hulk was murdered at the coffee shop so there was an old's a proverb in in Morocco
that was and of course it loses something in the translation he kind of
translated it from Arabic to French slash Dutch and I'm gonna translate it
from that into English but basically the same says that there's no way that you
can gain a better new friend by dropping an old friend even if you hate him
because you never know enough about a new friend there is no such thing as a
new best friend and as I said it loses a little bit in the translation but I
think I think what you know the point here is and maybe this is a point that
Republicans had all along and maybe they have a point that maybe this is not
the time to switch you know we know this guy I know he's up to no good a lot of
other people know he's up to no good I think we can certainly stump that out we
should be able to and it you know it might have taken four years anyway to to
rid all of the you know the horrible connections that are and you know the
relationships and all the stuff that's that's going on in big business and
big government and et cetera et cetera so what better way for everyone who
voted for Kerry who's a little bit bummed out now and of course you know we've
got some attitude and judgment to do there's no better way to just kind of
shake it all out of your system by sharing it with the homosexuals for
me I guess that's why they call it the blues Elton John on your daddy's
source code don't wish it away don't look at it like it's forever
between you and me I could almost accept the things I don't get better
and while I'm away just don't feel on the inside and I want to belong
before you and they're wrong please stay at our hearts we'll we're high
and I guess that's why they call it the blues John on my hands
we'll be tough man with you let me look like children let them like lovers
rolling like fatter all over common I guess that's why they call it the blues
just hearing the space picture my face in your hands
new for each second without hesitation but never forget on your mind
without your girl cry in the night of the hell tomorrow I'll share a little
of you more than I love life itself and I guess that's why they call it the blues
John on my hands we'll be tough man with you let them like children let them like lovers
rolling like fatter all over common I guess that's why they call it the blues
we'll be tough man with you let me look like children let them like lovers
I'll share a little of you more than I love life itself
and I guess that's why they call it the blues John on my hands we'll be tough man with you
let them like children let them like lovers rolling like fatter all over common
I guess that's why they call it the blues