Once again, it's the source code and we're on a Monday 23rd of August 2004.
Hi everybody, it's Adam Curry coming to you from Curry Castle in Belgium.
I am exhausted.
It's been an incredibly long day which of course started with the alarm clock kicking in at 3.30
to go off to the radio show which went well.
I had to come home pretty quickly because the people I told you about who come to see the
house twice already, well they wanted to come today for the third and final time and so
it looks like they're all just about set to make an offer.
So hopefully stuff will move along and we can move on with our plans.
So today is going to be a little bit of a short.
version of source code because after I got home, remember this is about an hour and a half drive,
and there was also an accident on the highway, so it took about two hours to get home. Then we had
to go check out Christina's new school, which is in Antwerp, the international school or the Antwerp
International School, which will be going to at least for the next couple of months. Excuse me?
No. Batteries? Van lights? Christina, how are you? It's medium open, how much car? It's real. Okay.
Okay.
I'm not going to do it.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
I'm not going to do it.
Sorry.
This cracks me up. That was my wife Patricia who just walked in. She knows what I'm doing.
She knows I'm recording and still she'll insist to come in and try and just mess me
up, which is really part of the theme I wanted to talk about today. I found the interesting
blog post from Dave Slusher from the Evil Genius Chronicles at evilgeniuscronicles.org.
And I know that he had tried out my iPod or script and he sent me a note. I think he
dropped me a comment on my web blog and he said that he had created a Pearl script version
that does the same thing. Only his was somewhat more complete where you just throw a text
file in with the URLs to the feeds that you subscribe to you want to subscribe to and
get the MP3s from. So you can configure that kind of manually. And his already runs automatically
through a Cron script.
because he's running it on a Mac.
So his pro script is called get underscore enclosures.pl.
And I'm writing up a whole kind of an essay about
what Steve Gilmore calls the iPod platform.
And so now that we also have the IPHP,
IPH Potter, which is built in a PHP.
So I got to build a little directory to all of that.
But as I said, it took us a long time
to get back through traffic from the school,
from our meeting with the principal
and some of the staff and faculty there.
So then I got back and I found that Dave Slosher's script
was done, I downloaded it, it works,
it's extremely cool and I will post about that.
But maybe even more funny is how,
he's audio blogging his evil genius chronicles.
And I'm gonna play a little excerpt from that.
where, well, you listen to it and then you'll see what I mean.
Hold on.
Interestingly enough, my wife, who tends to be a skeptic about these kinds of things,
when I said something about the audio blog, made the statement,
what are you saying that's so important you need to do this audio blog?
Which actually, you know, is a reasonable question to ask and a reasonable thing to examine.
Ultimately, I think the deal is that there's no real need that's an orthogonal access to the real question.
The question is not what's so important.
You know, we're not audio blogging because it's so important.
We're audio blogging because it's another tool in the toolkit.
It's another different, you know, interesting kind of novel way of interacting with people.
And one of the things that gets lost in a lot of online communication,
textual communication is nuance in people's voice.
and you lose a lot of humor of stuff because you don't hear people laugh and you don't kind of hear the sarcastic tone of voice.
And so this is just a different interesting way to form connections between people.
So there's actually a gap in here that's missing where my wife came by and rolled her eyes at me as I'm doing this.
And so you know she generally tends to think that most of the stuff is kind of dumb.
And I can't necessarily say that that's wrong.
It's important to remember that you know for as self-important as bloggers tend to be about the blogosphere,
99% of anyone you will ever meet think that you're full of shit.
So that's an important kind of grounding thing that we need to keep that we think we're bringing about the Infatopia
and everyone else thinks we're a jack-off.
So, you know, gotta keep the perspective.
I actually made notes for this one because I wanted to do it.
Okay, so it was interesting that I actually pulled that excerpt from his blog post from
yesterday from the 22nd, because he has exactly the same thing at home, whereas wife walks
in, rolls her eyes, like, you know, you're fucking crazy.
What are you doing talking to yourself?
Who are you talking to and how are you going to make money on this?
Is this what you're going to do with the rest of your life?
Well, clearly, if we both had the same situation, we found each other so quickly in the game,
there's gotta be more of us and there's stuff to be done, I presume.
So right, oh yes, I wanted to give you a song of the day.
This is from Dutch band, jazz rock, a whole bunch of different things.
They did play at the Nord Sea Jazz Festival.
I think it was not this year, not this past show, but the year before that.
And this is from... I think the only album released.
And I've linked to it before on my blog.
This one's called How the Wind Bluffs.
Check it out.
And we're coming blue in the house.
I see a little girl.
She won the stool world.
But something's wrong with her.
She walks barefoot with a turd.
A young child without a home.
Sniffs go to carry on.
Why should we cry for him?
We just... a j-woke.
And I talk about the wind move.
I don't know if this is bad or no.
This is so sad.
How the wind blows.
I don't know.
This is Batchoo, this is so sad too
There is this little boy, he's just a living time
No mane on holiday
Pays my, it's okay
How the wind blows, and I don't know
This is Batchoo, this is so sad too
And I don't know
Start moving and keep me Somewhere I am a few Ten thousand bodies, cut by the enemy.
So cold but...
I am a few Ten thousand bodies, cut by the enemy.
How the wind blows, I don't know this is bad, you know this is so sad, you know how the wind blows, I don't know this is sad, you know this is so bad, you know
So sad to know
Look in the industry...
chat Mia
It's a sad thing, but you're welcome.
mode Jones how the wind blows
yeah man never bother
that their entire album by the way was recorded all on a Macintosh using Pro Tools did at
their house in their attic these guys really are starving musicians had them on the radio
show a couple times and they're great and power to them I think they make some really
great tunes oh by the way hope you've noticed that my audio is no longer crackling the quality
should be a little bit higher I'm using a combination of two programs that basically give me what
I want one of them is a wiretap which allows me to record the audio from any application
there are a couple of different programs that do that like audio hijack and there's a program
that I found. It's not perfect, but it points out to me
through a comment on my blog post about better software for audio blogs. It's called Live
L-I-V-E is for the Macintosh and it does give me the ability to input my microphone
and makes tracks. I can even actually assign keys to different clips to play. Yeah, I
mean, there's a few, it's definitely an overly complicated interface for someone who's just
doing simple blogging stuff. But if you could switch between a real simple version of this
interface with what's running underneath and then this more vast expanded one that would
be perfect. Now, of course, the drawback to this is it only works with AIFF files and
not with MP3s. So first you have to convert any MP3s who want to play to AIFF and then
you have to import them. So it gets to be a little bit of an ordeal, but we're getting
closer. And with that, I'd say we're going to wrap up this version of the daily source
code. Again, there's an essay coming about the iPod or
Or the iPod platform and the different versions of iPod are there now out there and
You know hopefully how we're getting close to creating something so I will talk to you tomorrow as we
But what is tomorrow is tomorrow be Wednesday hump day? I'll see you then
The power of the sword is not.
I