Good afternoon friends, family, world leaders, welcome to the Daily Source Code for Wednesday.
Oh boy, I got a couple of songs to play for you.
Lots of examples of new podcasts and little bits I want to...
That's Jesse, my dog, giving me a little message there.
I don't know how long the show is going to be until I'm actually done with it, but hold
on a second.
Come on, Jesse.
Come outside.
Come here.
Just in time.
I'm only starting the show.
That's our dog Jesse now.
Ouch.
Okay.
So I was thinking, just looking at the amount of time I spent on the preparation for
today's show.
I'll just leave the door open, you guys can do that all yourself like it.
Okay, so I was thinking about the amount of time that goes into preparing a source code.
Today about an hour and a half I'd have to say, and that's, you know, during the day
I save stuff, I save emails, I save files that I find.
I have a special playlist and iTunes, the stuff that comes in through iPod or in iTunes,
I drag into a source code playlist so that I can kind of remember where I have,
where I've stashed everything. Do you hear these dogs they're going nuts today?
Well, anyway. So I thought, you know, this has to be compensated somehow.
So today's daily source code is brought to you by Grandmaster View.
And let me tell you about Grandmaster View and let me put a disclaimer in.
I own a part of the company. I'm a minority shareholder.
Grandmaster View, it's a new way of watching. It's brand new flat screens.
Flat screen TV technology that is so smart, it'll blow.
you away. And you can also buy them in the United States. So I'll talk about that in
a sec. But just briefly about these flat screens. Some of you may know that I made an investment
in this company a while back. What happened is these, and I didn't invent this. This is
a Dutch invention made in the Netherlands. And also, currently, the production line is
in the Netherlands. You know, with the advent of plasma screens and LCD screens and all
this technology that's made television.
And granted with plasma, there's a lot of disadvantages.
It's about, what is it?
Over 100 pounds that you have to hang on your wall.
There's always an ugly wire coming down.
The screens are, they only have a certain lifespan.
And it's very expensive to replace those.
The cost of a screen, like a plasma screen,
is very expensive.
The size is limited.
They just don't get as big as you might want
for your home cinema if you were using as a home cinema.
And I hooked up with these guys, Grandmaster View.
And they showed me a flat screen that was 2 meters 20
diagonally.
So that's about seven feet.
And it looked to me like a plasma screen.
I couldn't understand it.
And there were no wires.
It was hanging up.
They even had a nice little ambient light behind it.
It was against the wall, but just a little bit
set off from the wall with a light.
And it's.
just looks so cool and the price tag was something like 2,000 euros so say two
and a half thousand dollars I said now you know clearly a zero dropped off it
should be 25,000 for this size and even that may not be enough. So here's the
trick about Gram MasterView and why I like it so much. In the past at least
the past eight or nine years there's been a lot of development going on in
projectors. Projector technology has gotten really good we're outputting
you know a standard projector that you just buy or you know anywhere at any almost
at any appliance store is going to give you probably more than a thousand ANSI
lumens of light and that's an enormous amount just a couple years ago was you
know you barely get 500 and you can get a lot more than that and people do buy
much higher intensity projectors because the screens have barely changed so you
probably catching on to me by now that what these guys did is they developed
a better screen they came up with a special coating which of course is you
know that
the secret sauce of the company and they produce this beautiful flat, it's a, I call it wood,
it's not of course, but it's just a flat screen, they put a beautiful edge around it so it
has that plasma screen look and the reflection that you get from this, you can watch these
screens during the day with the
They're perfect for business, but I have one at home.
I've had one for over a year now.
And I love it.
I love it so much that I bought a piece of the company.
So Grand Master View, grandmasterview.com, if you're in the Netherlands, we have an
American affiliate now, very proud of that, and you can read everything about Grand
Master View.
florida.grammasterview.com.
All right, that's it for the commercial portion of the show.
Now let's get on to some religion, everybody.
Put your hands on your iPod and seal the power.
Oh Lord, won't you buy me a Mercedes-Benz?
My friends all have horses.
I must make amends.
Worked hard on my lifetime.
No help from my friends.
Oh Lord, won't you buy me a Mercedes-Benz?
Oh Lord, won't you buy me a Color TV?
Because dialing $4 is trying to find me.
I wait for delivery each day until three.
Oh Lord, won't you buy me a Color TV?
Oh Lord, won't you buy me a night on the town?
Because I'm counting on.
you lord please don't let me down
read that you love me and buy the next round
oh lord won't you buy me a night on the town everybody
oh
me. Hey Mercedes Benz, my friends all have horses. I must make amends. Worked hard all
my lifetime. No help from my friends. Oh Lord, hold your body. Hey Mercedes Benz.
my iTunes this morning. That's where I got everything for today's show, by the way, except
for one song which is a request, which, oh gee, I had to go all the way to LimeWire. I
went to our podcast library and was able to download it in seconds. That later on, after
a double shot of prayer then, man, I hope Lord buys me a Mercedes Benz. All my friends
have Porsches. Look at the mailbag. I got an email from Tom Pole, that's P-O-H-L,
and then we had all those Mac problems. He sent me a brief note and said,
it could be that your hard drive is failing. Very possible. It always seems
when you're using big files and doing all this kind of stuff that your hard
drive does. It's the first thing that has moving bits, so I guess that's where
it's why it's prone to breaking first. It says there's a great utility called
Smart Reporter that will check the physical health of your hard drive. You
can find it on version trackers. Smart Reporter. I'm definitely going to check
it out and see what it is. I figured I cut the source code first for today
before I go fucking with my art.
drive, which is probably a smart idea. And this is also stuff that not only will I point
to all of these links along with the posting of the source code, but also a lot of them
are listed on iPodder.org.
on that. The directory of shows is current. You can add your own show. There's a link.
Just click on that, fill out the details and all I basically have to do is just make sure it's added,
make sure it's what everyone really says it is.
Clearly we have an intruder in the house.
Uh...
Yeah.
That would be our handyman.
Let's see what he's doing.
Hey Luke!
Can I get help, eh?
Eh?
Oh boy, hold on a second. This is Belgian.
What?
A sponge?
I don't know what sponge it is.
Did you look at the garage?
Or at the stairs to the basement?
Okay, close the door, Lucas.
I'm just recording, don't laugh.
Thank you.
Okay.
Well, he was looking for a sponge.
And I'm happy to interrupt the show for that.
So, another link I'm pointing to is from Mark van de Vettering.
His site is brainwagon.org.
We've had Hugo show us how to set up our Macs to do a podcast.
And he's got a whole rundown of ways you can do this on Windows.
We've been waiting for this.
So, that's also an iPod.org.
Again, as I said, I'm getting that together.
Now, what we really need is a different look for iPod.org.
It looks kind of lame, actually.
Um...
Let me see.
How did I have all of this set up?
Here we go.
I want...
I wanted to play a little bit, oh wait a minute,
there's another thing that I had here.
And remember we were talking about,
about all how settings podcasts up
and how do we route audio and geez,
not like we haven't been talking this for quite a bit.
Got an email from Tim Ayello,
spelled like the actor's name I guess.
Adam, been a while, listen to your podcasts.
He says, when it comes to the voice applications,
he says you may want to look at the gaming world.
I hadn't thought about this.
He says, for instance, voice apps,
TeamSpeak and then Trillo might be used
for being able to get a bunch of people in
and talking all at once with very good quality.
Cause this is what the gamers are doing.
The gamers are playing online and,
you know, they're, so they're using high CPU
intensity applications and they're talking to each other.
So it seems like,
like there's some stuff out there,
it's just that we have to,
we have to connect these worlds together.
And I'm glad I got this, this email from Tim.
So hopefully if you can help us out,
here's some information on Tim.
TeamSpeak has a client recording facility, I believe it only pumps out a dot wave.
Well, okay, we can always convert that.
It has both Windows and Linux clients and servers are available for Windows, Linux,
Solaris, FreeBSD, NetBSD, Mac OS X.
It hasn't tried Ventrilo yet, but I think that's really interesting.
And I'm glad that we're going to try and incorporate some of these
complete different communities and also have some GeekSpeak coming up
from the board game GeekGuys, a little bit of their show that I wanted to play for you.
And something else that showed up on the iPod this morning, thanks to the iPodder.
It's another political song, it's another mix.
It's the trigger-happy single mix.
We're going to give you a dictatorship.
In the name of freedom, we're going to take yours away.
In the name of liberty, we are going to give you the Royal Chef.
Give up this offer, do it on your own Don't kill me anymore baby, baby, you're not
hiding my hope
I like to think that the mind you left them must take hello
You turn to your barrel on yourself baby.
Right wing, left wing.
I like chicken wing.
Die for the world.
Die for your country.
I'll make a generous gift to your...
Thanks for nothing.
How can you leave yourself?
I'll have a pabbler on the raise that is worth my un-call.
Well,
I will change my hands.
Through time,
I will change my mind.
I will change my hands.
Through time,
I will change my mind.
I will change my hands.
Through time,
I will change my mind.
Don't forget your hat!
No one's coming for you though!
Why back the camera guy?
Oh, it's your cousin's hat!
What happened to them, baby?
You ain't been over the phone!
This is kinda like day-shot over phone.
No one's been having that good of a while, come on.
You from the Post Office?
I'm getting out of here.
Yeah.
Trigger Happy. Too bad about the quality.
While I was playing I checked it out.
It's a sample that's 48 kilohertz, which is just not enough.
And I think it sounds really muddled and you're not able to hear all the world.
with Iraq I recupation you know you gotta appreciate that so hopefully we can find out who did
that get a better quality mp3 of the song that would be most awesome great song I really like
the good tune could have used a little bit more cowbell and you remember just the other
day maybe you don't maybe didn't hear Dave and I were talking about song
And I said, you know, Beatles, man, you just don't hear enough Beatles.
And I don't know if this is just what's out in the air,
or if it's, you know, if it's buzzing around,
but I listened to Geek Speak,
trying podcasts about gaming,
and lo and behold, here's how it started off.
She's got a ticket to ride She's got a ticket to ride
Hey, welcome to GeekSpeak.
We're up to episode three.
Episode three.
Cool.
Yeah.
All right.
What are we talking to this week, maybe?
Oh, well, I'm Scott Alden.
Yeah, that's true.
And I'm Dirk.
Actually, I'm Aldi.
I'm Aldi on the show.
Yeah.
All right.
You say so.
That's interesting.
In Europe, we have two supermarket chains.
One is called Dirk for Dirk von der Brug, but we call it Dirk.
And the other one, which is a German one, is called, You Got It.
Aldi.
So, this episode, we have Mark Kaufman and Eric Hauptmann from Days of Wonder, the publishing
company that has recently come out with a couple of winner games from the German game
of the year, the Spieldizar.
Yeah.
Take it to ride.
And also Memoir 44, which just won the two-player IGA award.
So, if you want to hear more about that, definitely check out GeekSpeak.
It's a great podcast.
You can get to it from the iPod.org show's directory.
GeekSpeak is the name of the show.
the show.
And so there you go.
There's a new game coming out or just came out called Ticket to Ride.
But I love this podcast.
You might not understand Jack all about what they're talking about because they're in their
industry.
They are in the gaming industry.
They're talking about the new games.
They know what you should see.
Their website.
It's amazing, by the way, geekspeak.com.
So this is just complimentary to what they were already doing.
But now they're interviewing the game designers.
And I'm just tickled by that.
I think it's great.
The thing I played for you a while ago was Northwest Noise.
And I just want to recap that this was three days before the big media caught on about Mount
St. Helens.
He reported that Northwest Noise is only about the Washington and Oregon region.
That's Northwest Noise.
That's what Northwest Noise is chosen as their audience.
Although if you have any affinity with it, it could be interesting to have a family
there.
But he said, you know, there's some word about some rumblings going on deep in St. Helens.
And he had this big spiel about how the previous eruption happened before.
She was born and really had only had concerns about that.
50 or 60 people died during that eruption.
This was three days before big media started reporting on the fact that it could erupt,
and lo and behold, it did.
I didn't listen to all of Northwest Noyes.
I don't know if there's a report later on about what they're expecting.
He kind of had me going for a second because we have a reporter on the scene at Mount St.
Helens and well clearly that caught my interest.
I do do on the air reporting from location.
So let's let's queue up his latest escapades up there in Mount St. Helens.
So I hate Tim. How you doing?
Hey there!
I'm in the crater again.
He's bastard.
He's stoned me.
Take a second look.
See how it's doing down here.
you get the picture. But if you want to know anything about the northwestern
region of the United States, North with no
to pronounce, but a great podcast.
Something else I've been keeping track of is a podcast called Career Opportunities.
Again, you can get to...
career opportunities is really about just what it is.
Your career, how you can advance your career, stuff to watch out for in a corporate environment.
And I ran a public company.
Certainly, well, let's say I ran the New York office of a public company and was one
of the co-founders of it.
And there's a lot you got to think about.
Certainly in the States.
And there was a bit that he had on the...
I think this is an archive of something he's done before, but it came through on my
iPod today.
The title of this is Keep It To Yourself.
And you'll probably recognize some of these situations.
Despite the fact that companies are trying to become more like a family and less like
a cold corporation, it's always best to remember that there are certain aspects of your life
that you shouldn't share with your coworkers or your managers.
The stories you tell now may come back to haunt your career in the future.
For the years, I've been on the receiving end of many stories I would have rather not
known.
These include graphic descriptions of...
drunken nights on the town, sexual adventures, and quasi-legal activities.
While you might want to share your adventures, your coworkers probably aren't the best audience.
It's a simple truth in any industry that you are never sure who you might end up working
for down the road.
Today's intern might end up running a hot new startup, or you could be laid off and
end up following a coworker to a new company.
The entertainment industry describes it in this way.
Whoever you stepped on getting to the top will be kicking you all the way down.
As you can imagine, people can be reluctant to hire someone who has a history of heavy
drinking or drug use.
Except in the podcast industry.
That it's too risky to their professional reputation to bring you into their company.
They might be afraid that your actions would reflect badly on them.
Okay, you gotta listen to it.
You can listen to it two ways.
It's great sound advice, but it's also funny when you...
scenarios that you can run into.
And haven't we all run to them at one point or another?
We're about 23 minutes into this daily source code for Wednesday, October 6, 2004.
And Dave Weiner finally posted a morning coffee notes.
It's been, I think, about a week and I understand why because he's been busy.
He's been doing trade secrets with me.
We've been talking a lot about iPod and podcasting and he was up at the Microsoft conference.
I think there was a Web 2.0 conference, but he also went to this.
I believe there were some get together that Microsoft invited a number of bloggers to come
look at something they were presenting.
And of course, it's all under NDA, so I have no idea what it is.
And Dave made reference to David Weinberger in his morning coffee notes.
And something really interesting.
Dave makes a real good point about privacy and the fact that we really are just kind
of getting used to what we have.
And if we ever really want to make the internet work the way...
we all dream it works, we have to figure out some of this privacy stuff.
And it's certainly interesting to hear Dave champion Microsoft a little bit, or maybe more
than a little bit in these thoughts that he has about privacy.
Now actually the Morning Coffee Notes is about a whole bunch of things.
He also goes through the history of desktop publishing, to web logs, to podcasts, which
is really, it's a good listen.
So check that out.
The show is about 45 minutes.
But I want to play this one bit where he talks about privacy.
It's about four minutes.
And he hooked up with David Weinberger, who you've probably heard from, or heard of,
at Microsoft.
And they had this conversation.
And here's Dave's version of the conversation and his conclusions.
Weinberger and I, it's funny because at a philosophical level, I've said this
to him before that.
We are in total agreement on the philosophy of the web and we're actually gonna have a session on this at blogger con called the core
Values of the web the idea there has to be led by Mary hotter
From Berkeley, and I think she's now at Technorati also
and
It's an academic subject. It's question of well. What is at one point? I was when I went to Amsterdam
I went to the W3C meeting in Amsterdam. I think was in it was in
2000 yeah, I was in 2000 and I I wrote about that saying I was looking for the heart of the web and didn't find it
That's okay. I mean at one point that was the heart of the web
But the but the web had moved on and was a lot more than that at that time
And it of course is today even more than that
but the web does have a heart and it does have a philosophy and
And we're sort of like the blind men and the elephant and elephant
We're all sort of looking at different parts of it and Weinberger is one of those people and he's written some great books
you know, small pieces loosely joined is one of his books and of course the Clutrain Manifesto,
which I think is one side of the coin and the other side of the coin is blogs.
And we seem to be, you know, I was a math major and in math, very theoretical type of math, not,
you know, and in math the great thing about math, the reason why people love who do math,
love math is because there's this sort of, you can approach a theorem from five different approaches,
you can always end up at the same place. And it shows you that something that it's very hard to
describe in words, other than to say that this is what beauty is. Beauty is where you discover
the underlying law that explains the nature of something that one wouldn't necessarily think
has an underlying law that and the web is like that.
The web, the essential element of the web is the link.
And it goes all the way from the deepest technology,
all the way up to the simplest user interface,
that where you link, you're like the web.
Where you are exclusive, when you don't link,
you are not like the web.
So, Weinberger and I agree on everything,
but today, or actually it was yesterday,
we found something that we don't agree on,
and I think I'm right, and I think he's wrong.
So I thought, wow, this is a momentous occasion.
Let's celebrate it.
Of course, I think I'm right, and I think that if,
in a short while, he will agree with me,
because I once was where he is.
He asked a question, he said,
will this require the use of passport?
And the Microsoft person said yes.
And he said, well, then I won't use it.
And that's certainly a place where I...
was once and and no I don't have a passport. On the other hand I'm probably
going to give in and get one and there's a reason for that because the world has
changed. First of all when we were against it there was this idea that we
would all work together and we would create something that was open and
democratic and not controlled by a major monolithic antitrust violating you
know convicted company that couldn't be trusted you know and all that's very
valid and it's still valid and this is how Microsoft screwed not just
themselves but all of us do because they should have been much more careful
about earning and keeping our trust or not just our trust but deserving of
trust and no we would be wrong to trust them but on the other hand we would be
even wronger not to do something about identity theft do something about it
take some step to protect yourself.
In another conversation I said to one of the people
at the conference, I said, you know,
let's create a hardened laptop.
Let's create one where if I lose the laptop or it's stolen,
they don't automatically get all my sensitive information
off there.
Why is this a concern?
Because more and more our financial affairs
are moving on to the internet.
It's just too convenient and there are too many incentives
for us to do it.
Businesses, you know, will give us a few points off
if we are willing to move all of our business
on the internet because it's cheaper for them
to not have to print out and mail out invoices.
And they're willing to share the savings on that.
At some point, you're not even gonna have
the option of getting paper.
You're gonna have to do it electronically.
And at that point we're all gonna be very vulnerable.
And mass, mass hijackings of identity.
will be taking place.
I think we're going to record a show today.
And I just saw that he's no longer idling in Seattle
through iChat.
So that means he's awake.
So after this show, we'll probably
record trade secrets.
But that is true.
And wow.
And you know what?
In the Netherlands, as of January 2005, all
It's mandatory for all tax returns to be done electronically.
And this, of course, has become a big deal because not everyone can file their tax returns
electronically.
So of course, now there's companies that will do that for you that kind of sit in the middle,
but that's a big, that's a giant step.
And the government did it.
Excuse me.
government did it, as they say themselves, to reduce cost.
But yeah, so it's a tax return.
That's a little different than a bank account.
But is it really?
What kind of information are you sending over the wire that can just be picked up by anybody?
Now I see that we're already 30 minutes into the show and I still have a number of things
I want to do.
I'm going to skip over a bit.
I was going to play a bit from the Audio Activism podcast, but I'll save that for tomorrow's
show because it's kind of a whole different topic, but it's really a podcast about political
issues.
And then I just wanted to skip on to a request that I received as Dave and I continue to
find out what do we want to do with these podcasts and what kind of music do we want
to play?
So Dave should just do a print show.
It should be the Dave and Print Show, the Dave and Print podcast.
But he also mentioned another group who were probably...
just as important as the Beatles or the Stones or the Kinks.
I even put the Bee Gees in there.
If you think back to Bee Gees in late 60s,
they had some different songs than Saturday Night Fever.
So I'm going to, first of all, turn the big podcast antenna
pointed out to Seattle.
Here's one.
I love the colorful cliché
And the way the sunlight plays upon her head
I like being the sound of a gentle mood
Also wear a bat with super-pun through the air
I'm taking a look at the vibrations
Good luck, Rachel.
Today's our day's run.
Softly smile, I know she must be fine
In her eyes, she goes with the two of us
I'm picking up her pet missions
Goodbye, Rachel
...
That was in the days when did those quick fadeouts beach boys good vibration
hump in your hump day for Wednesday October 6 2004. Okay, gotta talk a little bit about
iPod. I know that people are getting tired of
bit to play about that very topic in a couple minutes. Also some comedy on the
way in the very first Engadget podcast. But hey, this is the place where users and
developers party together, right? And we still got some work to do. And I got an
email which was copied to a number of other people from Ray Slakinski. Now I've
spoken about Ray before. I'm pretty sure he did the nucleus bit torn client
that I'm using to grab American TV shows. And as soon as he saw the iPod
or script that I created, the original Apple script, he started making pipe.
And that script was then used by August to create iPodder X, which I love.
I think it's the definitive Mac iPodder client.
And it just works great in all the new versions.
And Ray goes on to say, you know, so I helped August all the way up to 2.0 with patches.
And at the time he was working on iPodder, which is this great cross-platform effort going on,
which is coming out pretty soon.
And this is going to work on Mac and Windows and presumably Linux and other platforms.
But this is what's really beautiful about what's going on in this community we have.
And you can become a member just by subscribing to the iPodder developers list.
There's users and developers on there alike.
I actually tally that and see how many people on the list think they're users
and how many think they're developers or how many think they're both.
Here's what Ray says, what I realized, I still really want to
And that means I have to work on the iPodrx side of things.
So he's basically saying goodbye to the iPodr team, wishing them well.
He says, I wish you guys all the best.
Think you're doing a great job and what's going to be the best cross-platform iPodr program.
And so what we're seeing here is that, and this is the beautiful, this is the beauty
of it, is that Ray just wants to work with August.
It's not about having the most successful iPodr.
It's not about, I don't think it's about money.
It's about wanting to work with someone.
And that's just beautiful when that stuff happens.
So wish Ray and August good luck on the iPodrx.
And I got a mail from Michael.
Now this is not an easy name to pronounce.
I'm going to say, Joaghan, Joagun, Joagun, well it's G-E-O-G-H-E-G-A-N.
Michael, you really have to record an MP3 with the pronunciation of your name.
I had been working just kind of on the side with a couple of developers.
kicking back and forth the idea of, you know, what kind of genre do these podcasts fit into
and can you just put into the, when you're doing ID3 tags, so basically that's the metadata,
the information that you package into your MP3 file so that, you know, the name of your
show appears in the playlist.
Well there's also a genre tag in the ID3 spec.
I'm not going to go through the whole thing here, but Michael did a little bit of research.
He says that there, let me see, what is it?
There is an organization, TCON, I think, who have basically come up with all these different
content types and so I've been just using speech which I think is content type 101.
And Michael gets into this and explains it technologically how apparently we can use
the category and then put a podcast category behind that.
I'm not quite sure how it's...
to work yet, but the important thing is that we want to be able to categorize, first of all,
just so that you can say podcast and every other MP3 player will understand, oh, a genre podcast.
And if possible, it would be nice to say genre podcast sports, or music, or finance, or gardening,
or whatever. And that'll just make it a lot easier for us to categorize stuff and find stuff
on the user end, on the receiving end. So you can say, just give me all the,
I want to make a playlist, a smart playlist is what we use in iTunes. I'm sure Windows Media has some.
Just give me all the gardening shows followed by a financial show.
Somewhere in there is some beauty to be found.
We just got to figure out how we work with, and it's interesting, isn't it, that someone
or somebody took the time to categorize and say, okay, here's the 200 categories that
are possible and no one thought about a podcast.
So we got to figure that one out.
Quick bit here from Evil Genius Chronicles.
You know our friend Dave Slusher sitting in South Carolina.
He's running into some of the same issues that I am on my podcast, so I think I'm doing a
little bit better today by mixing it up.
Here's his podcast, Evil Genius Chronicles from yesterday.
I got a big long list of stuff to talk about.
An important point, and we're going to come back to this because it really does actually
matter, is I'm in Conway, South Carolina.
We're near Myrtle Beach, but it's a little town near Myrtle Beach.
We'll get back to that.
That's like check off with the gun over the map.
piece it will be fired before
I've got some feedback I need to play and this should catch me up on all feedback.
If you've emailed me audio feedback and you haven't heard it as of today,
it means I screwed up and forgot to play it. So feel free to send me a message reminding me I never played your feedback.
You don't have to send the file, it's entirely my bookkeeping.
It's just I forgot where I left off.
And in honor of a new mic configuration, all feedback will be from guys named Mike.
Here we go.
Hi Dave, Michael Gohagen here.
Recently on your show you've mentioned that you feel you might be discussing podcasting and
the whole iPod platform phenomenon almost too much.
And frankly, I don't know how you talk about anything but podcasts.
I mean you have a unique and kind of special situation where you're at the center of something
that is exploding all around you.
And as it continues to grow, the quality work, the guys like you and Adam and some others are doing,
I just think is so important.
You know, I really think a kind of a critical juncture is coming up here where the podcast
podcasting community is going to start to get some attention from the outside, from some
non-technical oriented people.
When those first looks come from the media and other sources, I think that it's important
that quality shows like yours and others, some of the other things being produced, are
kind of at the center and the forefront so that it doesn't get dismissed as some sort
of amateurish thing going on on the internet.
As more people get involved in this whole podcasting thing, and it's growing every
day, I really think that kind of the watch words are going to be that quality is respected,
and participation appreciates.
And I don't know where we're going to be a year from now, but I really think you're
paving the way.
I know that I am the consummate podcasting consumer.
I'm downloading these things in the middle of the night, loading them on my
iPod, listening to them in my car, or when and where I choose on my own schedule.
I'm not a computer guy.
I'm not in the technical business, but I get it.
All right, that's beautiful.
So a couple things about that.
One, I really like the idea of sending a recorded feedback into a podcast.
and playing that back. Great idea and I encourage you to send that to the daily source code as
well. And indeed, now that we're moving a little bit beyond the testing one, two, three, is my
trend.
We've got to start defining what we're doing and what these podcasts are about.
Now, it may very well be that Dave Slusher wants to continue talking about podcasting.
I think that's great because I'd love to say, hey, if you want to know what's going on
with the latest podcast developments, here's the show you want to check out.
Personally, what I want to try and do as I move a little bit away from all the podcasting
stuff and I still want to try and make it as friendly as possible so that when I talk
about genres in your playlist, I'm hoping that the non-technical listeners are
saying, oh yeah, that would be good if I could sort it that way.
So there's always going to be some of that.
But I'm going to try and do what I've always done.
Shit, I've always introduced videos, records, whatever.
So I can do a mix of that and now add it to the mix is podcasts.
And just give you an idea of what's out there.
And of course, I want to point you to where you can subscribe to these.
And then instead of getting out the URLs, and there's been a lot of discussion there,
what's the best way to talk about URLs in an audience?
show and a podcast or radio show, well that really is... excuse me. So the best way is
just to... anything I talk about, any shows I talk about will be in the podcast directory
on iPodder.org. Something I came across that was a nice complimentary podcast to an existing
blog is from...
photo blog and I've gotten a little bit into photo blogs. I'm not talking about a
mobile blog where you send stuff from your camera. I'm talking about real, you
know, the digital photography, beautiful pictures, settings and if you're into that
you'll know that with most modern-day cameras when they take a picture a lot
of information is encoded into that picture about what camera was used, what
shutter speed, what setting and so you know this so you don't have to write
all this down it just it's captured right into the picture and so there's a
great number of communities that are sharing this type of information and
just a quick bit from his podcast it was titled Monty Woods and it has to do
with a particular picture that he took.
Hello and welcome to my photo blog.
Today I'm going to do something different.
I'm going to post a picture and make some comments on it.
And attach this audio file to it and see if this generates some interest.
Of course this could also be deep thoughts with Jack Handy.
Or have some value for the viewers of my photo blog.
The photo is titled, Double Rainbow over Monty's Woods.
This picture was taken a couple weeks ago.
So you clearly understand how the community can benefit from this type of podcast.
And also if you're just into yoga and want to relax, it's a great podcast to check out.
I was really pleased to see the first Engadget podcast up here on the scene.
The Engadget guys not only did they put their first podcast together, but they also did yet
another setup and explanation very detailed with all the right links.
Engadget.com that's E-N-G-A-D-G-E-T dot com of course.
from this post from iPodder. And Gadget is already by itself just a great web log. These
guys basically have all the latest stuff on the latest gadgets and they've got secret
insight information. Sometimes they even get in trouble with these companies because
the traditional way of reviewing new gadgets is you leak something to your favorite reporter
and then maybe they'll get a picture about
And the trade shows, they're taking pictures behind with little camera phones.
They're getting intel from the Far East.
And this really pisses off a lot of companies.
get enough of this stuff. So they've already got a very established community going on.
They're now, as a part of the gadgetry, they decided to set up a podcast system, do it with
as much open source of free software as possible. And even that took them well over three hours
and they had some good examples there from the stuff that Hugo Schochmann has done.
talking about. They got it all together with an interesting new way of connecting all the
bits by the way. So I might try that out on a show soon because they basically did a show
together through iChat. Quality isn't quite perfect yet but I think that has more to
do with the microphones than the setup. It's like at least one of the mics with the internal
mic because I think I can hear the fan noise which is, that's kind of the way it works
with the, I love the power book. So you have two speakers built into the power book
and the internal mic is actually in the left speaker and so of course if you're
doing an iChat and someone's talking then if you're using the internal mic it's
gonna you know it's gonna hear that speaker and it's gonna send that person's
voice right back and that wouldn't have been very good so Apple came up with a
brilliant solution and what you first think of is oh this voice filtering.
What they did is when you're doing an iChat the left speaker is disabled and
this person comes through the right speaker. It's very...
typical bootstrap fix there.
So of course I listened to their first podcast
and these guys are all over, they're smart,
they know what's going on,
they know that there's business to be done with podcasting
and they were talking about it.
And with like the FCC even coming down on Howard Stern,
why not just ride around that and offer subscriptions
or figure out ways.
And I guess that'll be the next thing
is how to make money on this.
Yeah, I'm sure we'll see some of that coming out.
You can, like you said, I mean,
the FCC's involvement in actually being proactive
about monitoring and censoring content,
it actually changes the game here
kind of like how satellite radio did
with letting people pay for what they wanna hear.
And in some ways this goes a step further
unless people create what they wanna hear.
I mean, if you listen to some of the broadcasts
for being created, whether it's Doc Searle's Linux show
or Adam's broadcast with the Daily Source Code,
I mean, Adam, it's really interesting.
This is a guy who's a professional broadcaster, right?
He was on TV and...
I think he's enjoying this sense of freedom to be able to go say what he wants and do what
he wants.
In fact, the other day I was listening to it, I don't know if you've noticed this, do
you listen to his show?
Yeah, I've listened to three of them since I started poking around on this.
Okay.
So I've been listening to them all and the amazing thing is Adam actually smells mad
weed on the air.
And so the really funny thing is you're sitting there and all of a sudden you hear
a lighter flick and a bull start or a bong start going in the background and Adam's
sitting there taking hits on the air.
He's talking about whatever he wants.
He's swearing, he's doing all this crazy stuff.
And you know, you just think about what he's doing.
He's running his own media and his listeners.
So it's kind of busted him out into his own thing.
Yeah, I can't imagine having to pitch that as a show idea to someone.
So here's the thing.
It's atmosphere, city, and house.
Smoke and weed, talking about technology.
And he gives away the content at the end of the show.
People are downloading it.
They can do it right.
What do you think?
I can see them going to the programming director.
So we're going to do this show where I call up Dave Winer
and we smoke weed on the phone and talk about technology
and whatever else.
No, no.
It's the graduate meets easy riders.
And then we play songs in weird remixes and mash-ups
of George Bush.
Exactly.
So I have some technology stories
that I kind of bookmarked for this broadcast.
If you want to talk about a couple fun things,
a couple of interesting things.
One of them is it's just a prediction.
I think speaking of iPods and this.
broadcasting thing. There's some rumors about whether there's going to be a flash
base iPod and flash bases and non hard drive.
So there you go already straight into some good news and some tidbits there.
iPod and I think that's actually confirmed but listen to the Engadget podcast for more information on that and just a few notes about that
Now first of all you have to know I was raised in the Netherlands born in the States who moved here when I was seven and I remember quite well
Just to give you an idea of the culture of Europe and how that differs immediately media from the States
I'll never forget there was a show on the television in 1972
Television in Netherlands consisted of two channels two national channels
They started at 7 p.m. With the news on both channels identical news was very much like Russia and
It ended around 11 30 with a clock, you know and then it went over to the
To the test pattern that was it time to go to bed make babies whatever come on good people of the lowlands go to bed
And I'll never forget that like 7 30 there was the show on once or twice a week called chef on ukul's
Thing was disco show or whatever, but it was it was a wacky show
It was kind of like Benny Hill
In a way like yeah a bit of Benny Hill except the girl
that are running around are naked.
I'll never forget my parents.
Here we are, this all-American family.
And 730, I'm sitting there with my sister going,
dude, check this out.
What is going on?
I thought this was going to suck this movie.
This is a great country.
So the human body is considered something that can be shown.
Another part of the culture, in the Netherlands at least, not all over Europe, is that
people have their curtains wide open during the day.
Please look into my house.
I want you to feel welcome.
When they're closed means you're not welcome, of course.
And obviously, when it comes to drug policy, who are we kidding?
Who are we kidding?
So I am totally enjoying this freedom.
I'm used to a lot of this freedom.
I'm used to being able to...
What swear words am I really using?
I'm used to being myself.
That's the morning radio show I did.
I think part of the success of that.
for a year was because I was just being myself, just shooting the breeze.
Howard Stern is the same.
It may be one part of Howard Stern, but he's just being himself and he's saying what he's
thinking and he's saying hey, nice boobies, you know, because he means it.
And I think that's what people like, is honesty.
We're so fucking tired of, you know, television screaming at us and editing in effects, particularly
editing, you know, concealing the real truth behind what happened.
All the reality shit.
from hours of tape and sound effects are put in and voiceovers, all to position you and
help your brain understand the story that they're trying to tell.
And people I think, that's why people go back to theater.
That's why actors go back to theater.
They want to have something real that's live and it's just not exciting after a while.
And I think that's what's happened with radio and I think that's why we're here
with podcasts.
The only freedom I haven't enjoyed, mind you, even in the very liberal United States
of Europe, which still doesn't have a constitution, is freedom of choice of music.
Now at MTV in the beginning we could say a lot more, but at a certain point it was you
can't rag on any artists.
You can't say Alana Miles, yeah, she's Miss Doug Morris who works for Atlantic Records.
You couldn't say that.
That was a big no-no.
You know, in fact we had to say Michael Jackson, the king of pop.
Did I ever tell you that story?
That MTV has always been pre-recorded except for some of the live events.
And on Thursday we record for Saturday and Sunday.
On Friday we record for months.
So it was a double shift on Thursday.
We had to do two shows worth.
So a lot of the VJs are there.
It's one after another.
We're taping these segments.
We didn't ever see the videos while we were taping, right?
Those were in.
Long Island.
And so it was Michael Jackson weekend, all a part of the big Michael Jackson will only
appear on the Video Music Awards if we make Michael Jackson.
And we all had to come back on Friday and do three shifts.
So including Mondays, we had to do Saturday and Sunday over again because part of the deal
that was negotiated between MTV and Michael Jackson is that every single time we would
use his name, you would have to comma, pause and say the king of pot.
So it had to be Michael Jackson, the king of pot.
That freedom wasn't there to say Michael Jackson, who is still probably a really good musician
but looks so fucking freaky.
And even on the radio, the radio stations need to have some kind of automation.
They need to have some kind of playlist so that it's the way radio works in today's
commercial environment.
If you're talking top 40 stations, they're really only playing 100 records, if even that.
And they just repeat them over and over and over again because the top 40 station, your
average listening time is 15 minutes, if that.
And it better be a number one hit song playing when you tune in or a big hit from a recurrent
about 8 to 10 years ago.
Now other types of stations have a much like an easy listening or a mix, the best of
the 70s, 80s and 90s.
They'll have a little broader playlist but still you can't have the disc jockeys or the
air talent choosing the records all the time because you may get some weird doubles.
And of course all about control.
know, there's business behind the records that are played.
So I've never been in control of what I wanted to play.
Yeah, you can always do one yourself.
You can always switch stuff around the playlist if you want to.
If you know the music directly.
But you never had that freedom.
And now not only do I have the freedom to do that,
but I have a library at my disposal
that is so humongous.
I've got everything, the Beach Boys.
I want to get some Beach Boys.
I had good vibrations, but it was like a shitty MP3.
Only one minute of it.
Went to LimeWire, downloaded it, ready to go.
But it's not just for that.
There's podcasts will be archived
and will be stored on peer-to-peer networks.
It's a beautiful thing.
So back to the words, the cuss words, et cetera.
I think the only real thing I said is fuck.
I tried it, my daughter who's 14 also is trying to grok this whole concept of, why is this
word not good?
Why is this finger not good?
And there's no one who can explain the difference better than our friend, George Carlin, here
to give you the seven words you can't say on TV or radio for that matter, but in a podcast,
it's okay.
I love words.
I thank you for hearing my words.
I want to tell you something about words that I think is important.
I love, as I say, they're my work, they're my play, they're my passion.
Words are all we have really.
We have thoughts, but thoughts are fluid, you know.
And then we assign a word to a thought.
And we're stuck with that word for that thought.
So be careful with words.
I like to think, yeah, the same words, you know, that hurt can heal.
It's a matter of how you pick them.
There are some people that aren't into all the words.
There are some people that would have you not use certain words.
Yeah, there are 400,000 words in the...
language and there are seven of them you can't say on television. What a ratio that is. 399,993 to 7.
They must really be bad.
They'd have to be outrageous
to be separated from a group that large.
All of you over here, you seven.
Bad words.
That's what they told us they were, remember? That's a bad word.
No bad words. Bad thoughts. Bad intentions. And words.
You know the seven, don't you, that you can't say on television?
Shit, piss, fuck, cunt, cock, sucka, motherfucker, and tits.
Those are the heavy sevens.
Those are the ones that'll infect your soul,
curve your spine,
and keep the country from winning the war.
Shit piss fuck cunt cock fuck a motherfucker and tits, wow.
And tits doesn't even belong on the list, you know?
Such a friendly sounding word. Sounds like a nickname, right?
Hey, tits, come here!
Right, tits meet tuts, tuts tits, tuts tuts, man.
Sounds like a snack, doesn't it, man?
Yes, I know, it is, right.
And I don't mean your sexist snack.
I mean new Nabisco tits!
New cheese tits
Corn tits and pizza tits and sesame tits onion tits
Tater tits
Bet you can't eat just one!
I usually switch off
But I mean, that word does not belong on the list.
Actually, none of the words belong on the list, but you can understand why some of them are there.
I'm not completely insensitive to people's feelings, you know, I can dig why some of those words got on the list.
Like, cocksucker and motherfucker, those are...
heavyweight words. There's a lot going on there.
Besides the literal translation and the emotional feeling, I mean, they're just busy words.
There's a lot of syllables to contend with.
And those K's, those regressive sounds, they jump out at you, man.
Cuckaboo, the fucker!
like an assault on you, you know?
I can dig, then.
Now, we mentioned shit earlier, of course, and, uh,
two of the other four-letter Anglo-Saxon words are piss and cunt,
which go together, of course, but forget about it.
Little accidental humor, I further.
The reason the piss and cunt are on the list is that a long time ago
I don't mind fucking shit, but PNC are a-
P and C are...
glad to such stupid sentences is okay you fuckers I'm going to take them now
Of course, the word fuck.
Fuck I don't really love his some more accidental humor. I don't really want to get into that now
because I think it takes too long but I do mean that I mean I think the word fuck
is a very important word it's beginning of life and yet it's a word we use to
hurt one another quite often and people much wiser than I have said I'd rather
have my son watch a film with two people
people trying to kill one another and I of course can agree it's a great sentiment
I wish I know who said it first and I agree with that but
I'd like to substitute the word fuck for the word kill
in all those movie cliches we grew up with, right?
Okay, Sheriff, we're gonna fuck you now!
But we're gonna fuck you slow!
So maybe next year I'll have a whole fucking rap on that word and I hope so.
There are two way words, those are the seven you can never say on television under any circumstances.
Forget those seven, they're out.
But there are some two-way words, those double meaning words.
Remember the ones you giggled at in sixth grade?
And the cockroach three times!
Say the cockroach three times!
It's in the Bible!
There are some two-way words like it's okay for Kurt Gowdy to say Roberto Canetti has two balls on him!
I can't say I think he heard his balls on that play, Tony.
Please don't even... He must have hurt them by now.
And the other two-way word that goes with that one is prick.
It's okay if it goes to your finger.
Yes, you can prick your finger, but don't finger your prick, no, no.
The always amazing George Carlin with a classic, classic routine, the seven dirty words you
can't say, some words you can't say on television.
And I think that really sums it up, you know.
We just go on a little bit overboard with the word usage in English language at least.
And which reminds me, I really should cue up some Eddie Murphy for you next time.
You know, I've played a couple of George Carlin bits.
Eddie Murphy would be good too.
He's got some classic bits.
And podcasts are great for comedy because, you know, we still have the freedom to do
what we want on them.
So if you, you know, you comedians, give us the joke of the day.
Give us the Italian pickup line of the day.
Give us anything.
We're looking forward to it.
And that's it for the source code for today.
I tried to keep it to an hour, but George Carlin ran just a little bit long.
We're about to...
And I want to thank you very much for checking the show out.
Of course, the Daily Source Code is recorded live in front of a K9 studio audience from Flanders.
If you want to respond, email me at www.cury.com
See you tomorrow everybody, bye!