This is my casting. It's Adam Curry.
The power of the door.
Hump day. It is...
The Davies Westcode. We're using the developers party together.
Welcome to everybody coming to you from Curry Castle and Flanders Belgium for the very last time.
Once again, it is your Davies source code.
For Wednesday, November 17th, 2004.
Well, everybody. This is it. The final one from the castle.
We are so ready to get out of here.
It's just so totally fricking boring.
There's nothing to do. Nothing here.
It's just taking care of business.
There was a lot of business to take care of today.
Let's see. I felt like I was living on two sides.
Two different dimensions of the same moment and time.
We're on one hand. I'm trying to finalize the contract with these guys that are renting the bunker and Amsterdam for the reality show for the Trump-like apprentice type show with a famous Dutch lawyer.
I'm trying to close the contract on that.
You can imagine when you have a television production crew.
You want to really shore up a whole bunch of stuff because you know they're going to wreck the house.
That's just the way it works. That's where television works.
So no problem as long as they take care of it.
So you know working with bank guarantees and all this shit.
So I'm kind of like in the cat bird seed because they have to start shooting on Sunday.
They just as typical TV production goes.
They took too long to get all this shit together.
So I'm sitting pretty and I'm really no rush.
Conversely, at the same moment Patricia is over in the UK trying to, you know,
get our home.
And I told you that we're going to be renting for at least a year just to get our bearings and see if we want to live where
we know what we've selected.
And you know, and we also were thinking of downsizing somewhat in just in general, in life in general.
So while she's over there trying to, so we're doing, I'm trying to, you know,
get these guys to, you know, finish up the contract on my terms.
The wire transfer, which we sent initiated last Thursday had as of this morning still not arrived.
And of course, you don't get a key if you haven't paid your deposit.
You know, so it's a sizable amount of money.
And well, you know, so I'm still going to figure out where it is, which is,
it's just fucking ridiculous, you know, with these banks to, you know, under the, under the
concept of, or the term of, you know, we're clearing your funds.
Fuck that.
I can send an email in three seconds, you know, they're clearly using the money.
But, you know, what does it take, you know, I'll pay extra just to get my fucking money there on the
same day, same minute, same hour, same second, it's ridiculous.
So of course Patricia wound up having to go to a, to a Barclays bank nearby the home.
And using her credit cards to get the required funds, which is a big number.
So it was pretty funny.
But there was a Dutch girl or woman who worked at the bank.
And she recognized Patricia and said, oh, no problem.
We'll hook you up.
So that worked out.
But you can see where I felt that I was kind of on two different dimensions of the same equation.
So it felt very, very surreal.
So I spent a lot of time working on that and just getting the move all set up, you know,
financial moving, tax moving, all this stuff.
It all kind of comes down to the same moment, excuse me.
Okay, nice cup of cup of tea.
I'm getting into the mood here.
Let me see.
Oh, man, the BBC want to come and reshoot on Friday.
I got a voicemail message and normally I would have said, yeah, that's a definite,
but I think we're going to have a big problem here.
Houston, because I spoke to Patricia.
She called about half an hour ago.
It was a quarter to eleven here.
So a quarter to ten you, UK time.
And the moving guys had just finished bringing everything into the house.
They haven't even started unpacking.
So they're going to do that tomorrow.
But Patricia said, you know, you're not going to believe it,
but we still have too much stuff.
And she said, I'm sending stuff back.
I told you that we wanted to downsize.
Because we had like three houses worth of stuff.
And I don't know.
I think Patricia had totally mapped it out in her head, which she wanted.
And then all this other stuff, all just figure a place for it.
But you know, there's just no physical place for some stuff.
And so we'd already paired down so much.
And we thought that, you know, we were doing pretty good,
but it turns out we could do even better.
And we come to think of it.
This is shit that we never missed.
I didn't even know we fucking had this stuff.
You know, it's just stuff.
And it's furniture stuff.
And so she's sending some back.
That's great.
So tomorrow Christina and I,
we fly over.
And so tomorrow afternoon we should be in.
I don't know if we can be able to do a source code.
I do certainly not be with clips and stuff like that, because I won't have any real
connectivity to to connectivity to speak of.
So it will be a bit rough for the next couple of days.
But you know, me, I'll find a Wi-Fi nearby or I'll just drive in a town or whatever.
And looking forward to the adventure.
Patricia sounded really upbeat and really happy even though she's dead,
dead, dead, dead fucking tired.
And when I say dead with a heart patient, you know,
you got to be careful what you say because she's,
she's really been pushing herself to the limits and it's almost been over doing it.
She sounded really happy, and her sister's there helping her.
And so tomorrow, you know, they're going to work on work on unpacking some stuff.
And she said the kitchen is great.
She loves the way the kitchen is turning out.
So it's cool.
And you know what?
We are so ready to be gone.
We're ready to be out of here and start.
New fun and new stuff in the land of make believe.
Now before you listen any further to this show about five minutes into it,
you want to alert you to find service that comes from Nick Star.
And he is doing something rather interesting.
He's creating and providing a mini daily source code,
which is kind of his abbreviated version of this podcast.
For people who just don't have the 40 45 minutes to an hour depending on,
you know, how good, you know, how important or excited I am about something,
how important something seems to be.
But you know, 40 minutes, you don't have time for that on your commute.
You can always listen to the abbreviated source code.
You can find them at Nickstar.com.
And now in the production knows I'm doing a better job of getting the podcast feeds,
the website, and email information all into one single outline.
So let's listen to a little bit here of the mini source code.
From my Nickstar.
It's cool.
It's very flattering.
That's right.
I got a little bit of RIA for music.
This band is the plain white teas.
Band, I'm actually a personal friend with their great.
They're out touring right now.
Plainwhite teas.com.
Check that out.
This is a great song by them.
They said I could totally use this song.
So everything's cool.
All right.
This is the mini source code for Tuesday, November 16th.
This is the wrap up of what Adam Curry's daily source code is all about.
So you're running on the hallway.
You don't have the extra time.
Grab your mini iPod.
Throw on the mini source code.
So all that's left in the curry castle right now is just two cats, two dogs,
Christine, one bed, one small TV, and two laptops.
That's it.
There's a little fire going on the fireplace.
Christine is on a windows laptop and break in her dad's heart.
And we all know that.
So Patricia's up in Ireland.
And there's a funny Adam walking around the house.
And he's walking to do, to do, to do, to do.
So okay.
You can check out the mini source code.
You can subscribe to the podcast feed.
You can do a straight from the production notes for this show.
A daily source code.com or you can just go to Nickstar.com.
And it's funny how all kinds of mistakes come into this.
Patricia's definitely not an island.
It's Christina and not Christine.
So it's kind of like the game of telephone.
So it gets interesting.
But I certainly appreciate the effort.
And it really made me laugh to hear in fact how trivial these podcasts can be.
But yet so somehow disturbingly exciting.
You know what I'm saying?
Just like the interaction that we get in audio comments.
You probably remember yesterday I plugged a great way to learn Spanish.
A new podcast that is going to, I think blows the doors off of any type of self-help,
you know, self-learned language course.
And that's in the iPod.org directory.
Now listen to Victor Von Reesling's real podcast on how to really learn Spanish.
What's in girls is that?
He Von Reesling radio show coming from studio city, California.
Welcome.
Hey, show.
I have no idea.
But we've got things for you to listen to.
And maybe even a couple of guests.
The very first thing probably.
I'm Von Reesling of the Thamaturgic Cartographers.
I had to look it up.
So, you know, there's a dictionary online.
Thamaturgic.
THA nevermind.
Here, let's just set the tone and let me give you a little bit of education up front
if you're not familiar with the Spanish language.
Each shit and die.
Go and let me hear that email at the.
See, now I took two years of Spanish in high school, public school.
And I didn't learn any of the useful Spanish.
The first thing you learned when you're learning other languages.
How to cuss, right?
But we had to look it up in the dictionary.
So, kiss my ass was like, best of me as no.
Which turns out isn't right.
That's like the dictionary definition.
Kiss my ass.
Bessa Mikulu.
Yeah, right on.
So, that's Victor Von Reesling.
Uh, of course, links to his feed and his site in the.
In the show notes for today's daily source code.
It's already the 17th of November, 2004 tomorrow.
The 18th were finally moving.
We're out of here.
I've been really happy with the.
Suggestions that I've been getting for my.
Uh, my, um, I potter year problem.
I'm wearing the headphones as soon as they're wearing the.
The Mac alley headphones.
I like them a lot.
Got some.
Uh, so now the.
Yes, I talked about how the earrings were.
Uh, digging into the side of my head.
Uh, Doug.
Uh, Welch says take a pair of side cutters to the earring.
Stood trim and down to size.
Then file a sand off the newly trimmed point.
Uh, are you a power tools kind of guy?
No.
Uh, no.
And I need my workbench.
I need my black and thicker workbench to adjust my earring.
So it doesn't hurt while I'm podcasting.
Uh, uh, Cindy's script had a suggestion as well.
Yeah.
It's quick.
It responds to your free for earring help.
I have a solution.
Walk through.
Hit me.
Something about relief you have seen.
Um, first.
This is what you have to.
You're here.
Get yourself to cotton balls.
Oh, that sounds like shit.
What is it?
This came in as a wave file.
And I transferred it to MP3, but it sounds crappy.
Let's see if we can get through it because she's actually got some real advice that
I don't understand.
And, um, put one cotton ball through the post.
Put it ear in your ear.
Put it in another cotton ball and put it through the back of the post.
And then put the ear touch or post.
Um, actually they're ear nuts.
Watch his or screws.
We can not.
Um, expertise that holds the earring onto your ear.
Put that on.
And see if that helps.
Um, if not, your only other option is to take hearing loss.
Take care of completely because no matter what you do, um, just a combo.
Don't work.
It's going to hurt your ears.
And, um, you have a small zip rock pad.
You can put the hearing in.
See your podcast and then put that in your ear.
Okay.
That's the solution for today.
Hi.
Yeah.
Thanks, uh, script.
You know, that's, um, taking the earring out freaks me out.
I have to understand that Patricia came up with this great idea of a pierced ear.
Oh, they look so hot, honey.
Um, now I'm talking 10.
Yeah.
And I was more than 10 years ago.
Maybe it was 13 for me.
It was 15 years ago.
Yeah.
16, 14 or 15 years ago.
Um, and I said, well, you know, I just freaks me out.
I don't want it.
I'm like needles and I'm weird about that.
And, uh, and I said, well, tell you what, you know, I'm going to go get this ear pierced.
But then I'm taking back one of the diamond earrings that I've given you in the past.
And I'll take that one that nice, big fat one.
So you'll have one and I'll have one.
Um, and so that was cool.
And, you know, I really put it in and, you know, after you get like a training earring.
And I'm just just a fucking worst.
I don't take them out.
It freaks me out to have to take it out and then put it back in.
Just the whole idea of inserting the earring into this hole in my ear.
It freaks me out.
So that's not an option as far as I'm concerned.
And then Christina, who, of course, is not here right now, which has been listening along
the source codes for the past couple of weeks.
We've been in close quarters here in the bar in the past couple of days.
Um, and she says, well, you know, dad, the solution is you got to, um, you know,
put the headphones on like this and put the, uh, the strap nut at the top of your head,
but either at the back or in the front.
And I said, oh my God, that's like the gay Abba look.
Now, if anyone remembers, uh, you know, Agueta and Frida from Abba, um, they were,
they were, they were, I think it was like, either all their songs or most of them.
They'd be sitting at the, when there was a studio, uh, shot of Abba, uh,
then they would be singing with their headphones, not on the top of their head.
Probably not so as to ruin their hair, which is what I always thought.
Um, but more with the, uh, the head piece that connects the two speaker shell things
that go over your ear, uh, over their forehead or, uh,
at the back underneath at the back of their neck.
And now I'm understanding it.
You know, I'm understanding this whole Abba vibe.
It could have been because of the, um, because they're earrings, because it hurts.
And you know that it's fucking trouble when you start to understand what Abba is all about.
Damn.
I'm, um, Baron Sachea sent me an email, uh, and he sent me a link to an MP2 file,
which I never even heard of.
Of course, I turned it into an MP3 file.
Uh, and he also has a link to a pretty cool website, um,
that, uh, has all kinds of binoral recordings, which basically means having fun with audio
in stereo.
So here's, uh, a nice stereo track of some dogs, uh, that you want to crank up your, uh,
your MP3 player right now, because it really just reminds you how beautiful audio can be.
Oh, hey.
Come out.
Let me jump.
Come.
Come on.
Dude, I don't know if, if, if you like to drink, or, uh, or if it's, uh, weed, or if it's, uh,
whatever it is you do, whatever your poison, you know, if it's just pure oxygen you get high on.
Man, take a hit off of whatever it is and listen to that recording again.
That dog was in my brain.
That was awesome.
Um, we've just forgotten, I think, about how beautiful audio can be.
And even though this will be sampled down to 64 kilobits, I still think you can get the full effect.
I mean, that was, that was not really blew me away.
New podcast news, um, based upon, actually, I picked, I, I didn't pick this up from the,
from this email, but this email did come in from, uh, John DeSauer, I guess his name is.
Um, and, uh, which reminds me, I wanted to plug it. He says, um,
uh, I'm new to the entire podcast in the world, I think podcast is going to explode over the next year.
I'm the meteorologist from my TV station KFVSTV in Cape Gerardo, Missouri.
Also work as the station webmaster, just set up a podcast of our, uh, new block.
That's a commercial free block that he'd like to include in the podcasting site.
So I got his feed into, uh, into the iPart.org directory, of course.
But I just want you to listen this because it's really, it's really trippy.
I listen to this, um, and even though I'm not seeing the pictures, even though it's a television newscast,
I still feel like I'm, I'm really a part of this news.
And it just gives me, even the sound that, that you can tell that it's coming from the TV, uh,
uh, from a TV recording.
It just kind of takes me there. It sounds really good.
You're watching KFVS12, you're live, local, like breaking source for news with Mimi Jquip,
Jeff Cunningham, Bob Reeves, and Wendy Ray.
Now, hot land news at five.
Education's going to be a big deal. It's going to be one of the biggest things.
A heart-end group puts its faith into a new plan to keep teens from turning to drugs.
Good afternoon. Everybody, Missouri ranks number one in the nation.
Well, well, well, well, did you hear it? Did you hear what she said?
She said, good afternoon. It's kind of soft. That's too bad.
But she said, good afternoon, everybody.
I don't know. I don't know. I'm okay.
A heart-end group puts its faith into a new plan to keep teens from turning to drugs.
Good afternoon, everybody.
Seriously, though. It's really cool.
The volume could be a little bit louder on that KFVS podcast.
But otherwise, I love it. I just love listening to it.
Got a couple responses to what we're talking about.
Yes, they would rockster who were teaming up with this new company
to do streaming, peer to peer transfer of music instead of downloads.
And I posted a couple of email responses to that,
which definitely counter what they're saying.
So I'm not going to read the entire emails to you,
but the show notes, but I'm a mosquito. What the hell is he doing here?
It's moving the winter.
So the show notes include all kinds of jurisprudence and legal shit
that definitely counters what those guys were saying.
So that's just a part of our ongoing service here.
As you go from podcasts to podcasts, wondering what the fuck
I was talking about yesterday. You can actually kind of follow along.
Yeah, we're very, very user-oriented here at the Daily Source Code.
Hey, what's up Adam? This is Julian talking to you
from in over your head rate.
Well, Canada, so how do a couple comments and questions for you?
So if you have the time to respond, I'd be really chill.
Let me see.
Yeah, I had some time right now, sure.
One, in the trade secrets that came out on the seventh,
you talked about the Mac mice, USB mic.
Now, I don't want you to plug anything on your show.
If you don't want to, of course,
but that's the mic that I was thinking of getting.
And I know it's USB, so there's a bit of delay,
but I wouldn't really have a problem with that personally.
So I was wondering if you could let me know
whether or not I should order the thing.
Okay, Julian, thank you very much for asking.
As I'm playing back this comment,
I'm teaching for the mic.
I wanted to talk about and I realized that's been packed, of course.
But it was Mac mice.
I think it's 49 bucks.
Mac mice.com.
The latency was too much for me.
I love the fact that it's, you know,
it's on a bendable swans neck that you would find
on one of those USB lights.
I thought the sound quality was quite reasonable.
A little bit muffled, but really quite reasonable.
Certainly for that kind of money.
It had a huge, nice heavy mega bass stand,
which made it very convenient to extend it away from the computer
and put it down somewhere else.
And it was really sturdy.
Although the drawback to that is if you pick up the mic by the mic,
then the bass drops off and smashes into your table.
I also couldn't get it to work,
which may have been related to my battery.
And I was going to check that before I did this podcast.
But as I said, it's been packed, but I think
there may be better USB microphones.
Dawn and Drew are using a logic tech,
which is the ugliest piece of crap I've ever seen,
but it sounds pretty good and they have almost no latency.
So that may be the way to go on that.
Let's see if he, if I'd do anything more questions here.
It's the first thing.
The second thing is that I was also listening to your trade secrets today
on the 13th of about the BBC.
Now, I just wanted to comment because it made me so angry.
Here in Montreal last year, I did a couple of shows for a reality TV series,
which I will not name, but they were exactly like that.
They say reality and the first thing I discovered,
there's no such thing as reality programming.
Not at all.
They want you to say certain things.
They want you to talk a certain way and walk a certain way.
You know what I mean?
And it just made me so upset to listen to that,
because they're like, you can't talk about this.
We can't talk about that.
But please get as much of this as possible into the show.
You know what I mean?
There's no such thing as a reality show.
And that podcast that they will show on their program
is not going to be the real thing.
And that's what I really love about the podcasting.
So keep it up and keep it real, I guess,
is what I'm trying to say.
So I think that's pretty much it.
Let me know what you think about the mic.
If you have the chance and keep it up,
and keep up the good work.
You look like you're having a lot of really good fun down there.
Bye-bye.
Yeah, Boeing indeed.
You bet I'm having fun.
And as I think I said earlier,
it looks like the whole BBC thing is going to fall through now
because the last possible time they had to re-record all this stuff
we did this hours we spent on shit.
Only for it to be damaged in transit.
I can't believe it.
It's Friday between like two and five p.m.
so it's half the amount of time that we spent originally.
And our house isn't ready.
It's just too much shit, too much stuff for sending stuff back.
So I'm going to have to call Colin tomorrow
and disappoint him.
And it looks like either it will never happen
or it won't happen this time, folks.
But I think there's, you know,
there's only so much I can do.
And we really tried to do everything for them.
So I'm fucking bummed about it.
I think I forgot like helicopters and shit
into the mix to make it even cool.
But there you go.
That's Murphy and shit happens.
Shit just happens.
Let's see.
What else was I going to talk about here?
Oh, something cool.
I was pointed out to me today
that Skype has a developer program.
There's a whole Skype API.
And I'm starting you know,
as Dave always says, I'm your programmer.
I'm like, you know, believe me,
you're more a radio podcaster than I am
programmer if we want to compare.
But I am kind of digging looking at this
application programming interface.
I think that's what API stands for.
And you know, we can basically, you know,
build this into production systems,
create voice message systems
that can loop directly to iPod.
I mean, you might just boggles
when you think of how you can connect
all of these wonderful bits together.
So on the show notes for today's podcast,
download page for their API
and their developer program.
Smart guys, this jannison,
you know, those Scandinavian dudes,
man, they're totally freaking smart about this.
Get the developers involved soon.
And it looks pretty open.
It looks like some good stuff is happening there.
And I spoke to, to gaff, kid.
God, people must, people from Australia
must hate it when people do their accent.
That's a fucking lame.
I've got to stop that.
I've got to stop the English accent too.
That's a whole Madonna thing.
It's fucked up.
Do not want to go down that path.
So Garth is on the iPod or lemon developer team.
Now, a member yesterday was really excited
on the source code where I heard
how these guys had, you know,
figured that Don and Drew did some really cool stuff
with their double ender audio recording.
Double ended double ender.
It's a double ender.
Yeah, we got to keep the podcast
when the vocabulary got to keep it straight.
This is really good.
Did you see that you see on my weblog
by the way that podcasting
was word of the day for the Dutch version
of Webster's dictionary?
What the fuck is that about?
Awesome.
I'm leaving Holland and, you know,
when I'm almost a day I'm leaving,
I leave behind a new English word
for their dictionary.
Gosh, what's this?
Boy, we're really, you know,
we're really pushing podcasting
to the ultimate limits anyway.
So the iPod, a large part of the iPod
or developer, the lemon development team
got together and did this multiple ended call
which they recorded.
Which is great because, you know,
they're listening to the users
and saying, how can we make this work
and how can we figure this out?
So Garth, I don't think he figured
that I was actually going to put that
entire piece on the podcast.
What's that?
Well, don't put it on my computer.
You like it.
But I'm, I'm podcasting.
I have some things.
But what, you don't want it, you don't like it?
Well, don't, don't shove it in my face.
Here, put it on.
Give it up.
I'm explaining about something.
Okay, thank you very much.
Thank you.
Would Christina?
Why does she just take this with you, huh?
Do your kids do that if they,
I'm not going to chuck it.
I don't throw food.
Just take that and put it back and close it up.
If your kids don't like something,
they say, here I got this for you.
You know, and they, they give you something totally disgusting.
Anyway, so the, I put it on the developer team.
They recorded their Skype call
and they kind of almost forgot to record how they did it
and what all the settings were.
But of course, you know,
we're all connected with these podcasts
and Garth, the, uh, sent me an audio comment
and titled How We Recorded That Skype Call.
My next time I swear,
I will just assume that anything anybody's recording
they're going to publish.
Ah, Jayce.
Ah, boy.
It's crazy.
And I'm just bringing to let you know.
Well, leaving you an audio comment to let you know.
What the missing details are from that
mixed-down session that you played in the last
daily source code.
What we did was, uh, everyone recording with audacity
send it all to one person and that one person
that mixes it down.
And, uh, there are only two tricks to it.
One is, if, uh, anyone's on windows
and recording with audacity,
there's a little microphone, um,
slider in the toolbar.
Slide it all the way to the right.
You should have Skype set to tune your audio
session settings on the fly.
But, um, it's got to range that it'll accept
and your levels in audacity will be way too low
if you leave the slider where it is.
Drag it as far to the right as you possibly can.
And that will eliminate the need for
using as much compression as you've heard
on my voice at least in that, uh, clip.
The other thing is, and you didn't hear this,
was all of us going 1, 2, 3,
and then all trying to hit the record
button at the same time.
That makes the job easier for whoever
it is a has to be, the call
because that person has to kind of
tweak the start times of the various
imported channels so that they can get
the conversation sounding normal.
That said, um, I can remember who did the mix
down for that one.
I think was Matthew.
And, uh, it was a fantastic job.
You couldn't even really tell that I was in Australia
and there were, um, uh, the United States.
And, uh, I mean, we could hear there was a fair amount of
lag in the conversation, but it really doesn't
come out the final product.
I liked that.
Uh, the great news for you and Dave is that
it really doesn't matter what software
is using or what is encoding radar.
Doesn't matter if he sends you raw, uh, web files
or MP3s, just along as you can import
whatever it is that he sends you into whatever
software it is that you're using the mix
down.
Now, just happened that I think we were all on
windows for our call and we were all using
audacity.
But that was just a coincidence.
And, um, I certainly encoded my session
to MP3 before I sent it in.
Uh, I don't know whether the others did
and certainly whoever was that mixed
it down, he was using a raw WAV and he had gotten
to MP3s probably with completely different
encoding rates from the other two blocks.
So that's PCZ.
Everyone records however they want to record
as best they can manage their own levels
and everything else.
Send it into one person.
That person imports the resulting sounds
as separate channels.
Tweaks, you know, you can compress everyone.
You can tweak the start and finish times.
Cut off the bit at the beginning wherever
I go as one, two, three.
Mix it down and publish.
It's that easy.
And, uh, I've got to thank Dawn and Drew
for, uh, illuminating the technique.
All we did was give it a shot.
Have a great day.
Bye.
All right, Garth Perfect.
And also Garth and I talked for quite a while on
Skype.
Um, and was really late for him was like,
quarter to two in the morning.
And his wife is in the hospital because
their second child want to come out a couple
weeks too early.
So, you know, he's kind of floating around
there.
And I know that feeling.
Um, but we talked about how to use
show notes of in and out liners or
opml file.
How we can incorporate that into the
iPod or software.
So, I'm really excited about all the stuff
that's going on.
Um, you know, we're just, we're
connecting all these bits together.
And users and developers literally are
partying together.
I know it sounds hokey, but it is.
You know, we're working on stuff and getting
something done.
And we all can be quite proud of
ourselves.
Time now for our one-minute tip of the day.
Hello and welcome to the one-minute tip.
The place to pick up quick tips to make you
more computer efficient.
Today's tip and special request for
keyboard shortcuts in Apple's iChat.
Well, this isn't so much a keyboard shortcut
just in iChat from Apple.
This is also a way to make keyboard shortcuts
for any application.
This is a great tip.
Go to the Apple pull-down menu and select
system preferences.
Then click on the keyboard and mouse
component.
Now at the top of this window, push keyboard
shortcuts.
So now down at the bottom left is a small
plus sign.
If you push on this plus sign,
what you can do is you can select
any application that appears
basically inside of the Apple environment.
Now type in the menu title just as
it's displayed in the pull-down menu.
Don't forget the capitals.
And then include the keyboard shortcut
and push the add button.
Make sure you do this when the application
is closed.
Next time you launch the application,
this keyboard shortcut will now become available.
Now there's a way to make keyboard shortcuts.
You know, so I actually did learn something
from that one minute tip.
And I did go, I actually did that.
And what's cool about this is
even with the shitty interface the iPod has
I could actually scroll back through that tip
listening to it and do it and follow along
on my computer and worked out.
And I like that.
And because subscribe to the one minute tip
just by finding that in the iPod.org
And I met some,
actually was re-acquainted with some old friends
through some iPod or press that
that's been floating around.
I got an email from
the Lascivius Bitties,
specifically from Leanne,
so hey Adam,
wonder if you remember the Lascivius Bitties.
I believe Vince Outlaw introduced
you to us on a San Diego radio show
a couple of years ago.
Well that's exactly right.
And I remember talking about them
and I can't remember if I played them on the radio.
I definitely blogged about them.
They have a new CD out and they love to send me a copy.
So anyway, so they heard an MPR show
where I was talking about iPod
and they're really excited.
I wonder what show that was probably
the WNYC interview.
I've always liked the Lascivius Bitties
that they're kind of music.
And actually what's cool about is
the first album that they released
I think they've done about four is the one that I have
and they actually provide full length MP3 samples
on their website.
And it's Bittiesforever.com,
BIDD IES,
numeralforever.com.
All that information in the show notes
for today's podcast at dailysourcecode.com.
But just listen to a small sample
of something from the new album,
which I'll be able to play in full
of this podcast.
This is a bit of this track called famous.
Listen to this and that and I won't talk about it.
Oh, I will be a Barbie doll with huge fake tits.
No hips at all.
And I hate us attitude.
And oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Every morning I'll get high on
colored pills.
Martini's dry.
A little wing and just a touch.
I want to be my famous better than all
of my fellow watch better than all of her.
I want to be famous slowly and alone at the end.
I'll end up bitter and ugly and old.
Not just my body, but also my soul.
But a legend is my goal.
I don't imagine I'll be when I'm famous.
Not that we don't give for the little people.
All left is what I'm famous.
I'm famous.
And it's four girls and they sing these harmonies.
And there's just something, I don't know.
It's something sexual about it.
You know, kind of that lounge vibe to it.
And of course, their lyrics are updated.
You know, and I just dig it.
And this is actually, I think, the song that struck me the most.
The first time I heard the list of these videos.
This is Coney Island.
Something about a minute and a half.
But it's a real good representation of their work.
I love it.
Here's the list of these videos on the daily source.
And those, come from Pennsylvania.
Best from best Virginia.
And dance from Tennessee.
They know me, where they grow me, in Wyoming.
I can't share a new habit.
I can't share a new habit as for me.
And it knows, come from middle soda.
Coats come from Dakota.
But why should you be blue?
For you, you're from Coney Island.
And little Coney Island is famous for you.
List of these videos and probably just about half of the Coney Island song.
I'll get some more tracks from them up on the source code pretty soon.
And that's it for the final podcast from the castle from Coney Castle.
We'll now be moving to Coney Cottage.
And overseen us two bad that all of your stuff has to be sent back.
Well, there's too much stuff so we have to move your room back.
You don't give a shit, do you?
As long as you have a laptop and your horse.
Alrighty.
Hey, that's it. This is the final podcast from the castle.
Next time we speak, I'll not officially, but we'll pretty much be living in the UK.
Get about a month to dig around before we have to get registered in everything.
But I don't know if we'll be able to get a podcast up for tomorrow night,
but you know that I'll be there with y'all in my thoughts.
My brothers and sisters, put your hands on the iPod and feel the power of the podcast.
As always, comments are welcome.atomiccurry.com.
Don't expect a response immediately in the next couple of days.
Audio comments are extremely welcome as well.
I'll leave a comment on my weblog live.curry.com.
And of course, you can find all the archives and the latest source code on its very on weblog.
Which is dailysourcecode.com.
You can also find the show notes for each show there.
Okay, so it may be Friday, possibly even Saturday,
and who knows if I'm lucky tomorrow for the next show.
Take care.
So daily source code for Wednesday and November 17th, 2004.
Bye-bye.
Thanks for watching.