Well everybody, how are you doing? Welcome to the very first podcast coming to you from the Starbox
I have from Gilford right now I'm getting a whole bunch of people looking at me quite strangely
What the hell is that guy doing over there in the corner? He's clearly talking to himself
And what's that thing he's actually talking into? It's a wonderful
I'm gonna see you back in the explain on the front event of the day and explain to you exactly why we're coming to you from the Starbox
Some Gilford where I located on Marcus Street right off the high street, which is completely located in the center of the lovely town of Gilford
This is the Starbox where the having upstairs which kind of looks like a what's it called kind of like a frat house
It's got all these crushed velvet chairs full of all kinds of stains that you really don't want to wear
And they've got the music cranking here. They've got the tunes going there's a whole bunch of people here who are connected to their
To the Wi-Fi, which is
But more than I can say for the cottage at the time being is gone through quite a bit of crap in a couple of days
And let me try to explain and let me tell you what I'm going to be doing here for as long as it takes essentially
So yesterday was December second and I was promised that my telephone line at home, which is
Connected by British telecom that it would be provisioned to a DSL line, which means basically they they unplug it at one end
And plug it into another socket and then you have a DSL connection which means you can have a telephone line running over it
Or you can have broadband running over that same line
Now there's a whole bunch of providers you can choose from in the United Kingdom
And the way that works is the infrastructure is basically put in by British telecom
There's nothing you can do about that that's the same in many countries
I'm not quite sure in the states who owns most of the copper wire probably 18T owns a whole bunch of it
But in the Netherlands it's KPN. It's all the you know these used to be government organizations that they would run the phone companies
So the infrastructure is British telecom
They offer a broadband service which is limited and needed to 30 gigabytes a month
Now we've been through that at the castle, so I knew it didn't want that
And I wanted an unmetered service and there was this and I did a lot of research by the way
And I called up companies I talked to them because I wanted to make an educated choice and do it right
And I got a lot of help from the blogger sphere and people who listen to the source code
Giving me ideas even though I hadn't really disclosed the location of where we were living
Now everyone knows because I'm so pissed off that all places the mini silicon valley of the United Kingdom
Which gulfed in some respects really is that you can't get a home based DSL broadband at the time being
Because British telecom says there's no more ports available to let me continue
I chose UK online because first of all they have an unneeded service
Talk to the guys and tech support they sounded really nice really helpful
Very knowledgeable about what they were doing
And decided to go with them now they're just the ISP basically British telecom still has to plug me in and activate my line
And then I'm essentially just logging in through you know just logging in over the network
So really it's all back-end stuff
So it doesn't matter who I would go with
And no matter what provider the physical connection of the DSL line comes from British telecom
So they even set up a date which was December 2nd and they told me they told the ISP UK online
Which is UK online dot net of course links to everything in the show notes for today
You know that they were going to provision my line which basically means the guy goes down to the exchange and you know switches my line over
So it didn't happen yesterday I called up like five after six last night because it could be provision between
830 AM and 6pm and they said well hold on a second
Now it looks like it still hasn't been provisioned when you call back in the morning
And we'll be able to call British telecom and find out what's going on
So I did that this morning and they called BT and British telecom said well, you know we're really sorry
But they're just no more ports available so we can't plug you in no matter who you're with until someone leaves or until a port becomes free
Well that's a problem particularly when you told me we're going to do it
And I can't blame the the ISP they're just kind of sitting in the middle and you know they don't know what to do
So I called up British telecom verified the story and they said you know
And I said well what if I take a broadband from BT doesn't make any difference or we can't help you
Well am I on the list yeah of course you're on the list well where am I on the list or we can't tell you
Well how does it work you know well since we have to be impartial to all providers there's some magical cue somewhere
So it sounds like a whole cacophony of crap sitting there
Just unclear to what's going to happen, but the one thing I will tell you that you cannot have a community like this
Which is literally filled with researchers, scientists, professors, students
I mean it's a go go look at Gilford on Google and I'll supply a couple of links to the research park in the business park
You can't have people come here and live if they can't get DSL broadband and if they can't get it reasonably quickly
So this should be seen as a community wide problem not just a podcast community problem and by the way
Having the prints of pod without pipe is fucked up ladies and gentlemen
It really sucks
So a whole bunch of people helped out you can see the comments on my weblog live.curate.com
Some folks were even at Lee Wilkins for instance I'm going to try and call Lee on Skype in a second
Lee Wilkins knows some people some monkey mugs with inverters telecom
And he's going to try and run stuff up the flagpole internally
Receiving it anything changed other people sent me links to satellite broadband companies
I looked at a lot of that and even though they do have DVB which is digital video broadcast in the UK which is much lower orbiting satellites
And I guess comparable to DAB
There's basically every single service besides being outrageously expensive anywhere from three to three hundred to seven hundred dollars a month
Outside of your installation charge of a good two thousand dollars there's bandwidth restrictions
Which is exactly what I don't want right
Excuse me that's the coffee mocha
Coming back like bad Mexican food for lunch
Okay, so
Other options were
Cable now apparently I do live in an area that NTL cable
Does provide access to
I registered sent to my details they sent me emails saying they will contact me that was four hours ago
Of course they haven't contacted me yet
And regardless the soonest they'll be able to install anything will be on the 20th of December which is I can't live that long
It's just this like it's like not having hot water in your house
I cannot live without broadband. I told Patricia I said I will have to fucking move
This is only one step lower than on the scale of crap as the dogs and cats having to go into quarantine
So we'll see what happens until then
And I've gotten past the pissed off stage now. You know I was really really angry really angry this morning as you might well imagine
Now I'm in a just a problem solving mode
So if it means that I will have to sit here every single day every week day until I get broadband installed
I've to sit at Starbucks and do the podcast from here and look like a total fool
Then I will if that's what it's going to take. In fact starting today every week day
You can find me at the Starbucks and Gilford on Market Street is right off of the high street
You can find me upstairs kind of in the corner close to the
Electrical outlet. I've got my full kit here. I've got my SM7 sure microphone
It's the one on the on the stand. I've got the table stand. I've got my my M audio breakout box
So if you bring your own mic we can plug it in we can plug in instruments even
But every day at 2 o'clock in the afternoon. I'll be doing the podcast from here
And I'm cranking up with some music right now to get into the mood
Good with my American heartbreak
It's a Michael Butler's band from Rock and Old Geek Show here's sick and tired
Well, who's out of you on?
You want the clock? Well, the G I was the judge
Remember every day, look time lost, getting dinner day
I can see what's going on
You can see what's going on
I'm swinging out, I can see what's going on
We're so sick and tired
Everybody's sick and tired
I'm so sick and tired
We're so sick and tired
We're the picture for you
We're green dead and blue
We're the shine through
We're crossing baby when I say
Nothing for you
I can't get in the way
I can see what's going on
You can see what's going on
I'm swinging out, I can see what's going on
We're so sick and tired
Everybody's sick and tired
I'm so sick and tired
We're so sick and tired
Everybody's sick and tired
We're todas痛 up
Well, you've changed all my life
You've changed all your clothes
Always mind and so disturbing girls
Now ya see me now you don't
When you say to your Goddess
In my mind
We're so sick and try it
I'm so sick and try it
We're so sick and tired
Everybody's sick and try it
I'm so sick and try it
We're so sick and try it
I'm American Heartbreak sick and tired coming to you on the daily source code for, well,
shoot, what is it?
December 3rd, 2004 coming to you from the Starbucks on Market Street right off the
high street in Guilford, in the United Kingdom, just the stones throw away from the cottage.
So now that we all know where I live or more or less, let's see if we can get Lee Wilkins
on Skype here.
Let's see if we can get him on Lee, hello Lee, Lee are you there?
Hello Lee, can you hear me?
Hmm, I heard him for a second there, it looks like we lost them.
Let's see if he's maybe just who now actually looks like he went offline.
So we'll see if Lee can come back in a sec.
Usually at this point, if I were on the radio and this were live, I'd say if you just
tuned in, then this is what we're doing.
But I guess that makes no sense because you've been tuned from the beginning presumably.
It would be cool if I could get Dave one.
Oh, I think it comes to Lee, let's see if we can get him in now.
Lee, hello Lee, Lee, can you hear me?
I can hear Lee, maybe he can't hear me for a second reason.
Hold on, let's see.
Yes, I can hear you.
Yes, I guess he can't hear me, hold on.
Maybe I have to change some setting here, hold on.
Yeah, I see the problem here.
The input should be set to, well, you should be able to hear me on this.
I understand Lee, me not hear you.
Well, I can hear you.
Turn on your speakers.
Just a thought, dude.
I mean, I can see there's, it's going in.
I can see that there's sound coming out.
Let me try the internal microphone.
Does that make any difference leaking here?
No.
I hear this.
There on.
I hear the Skype beat.
Shoot.
Come on, Lee.
Shoot, I guess he just hung up.
That makes no sense, because I can hear him.
Okay, we'll see if he'll call back in a second then.
Ah, you mind if I reboot?
No.
Go for it.
Okay.
Perfect.
Well, then I suggest, what should we do?
Shall we wait for Lee to reboot?
Because I really wanted to get him on for two reasons.
One, he's been helping me out.
Very nice of him.
He's been helping out with the, with the bandwidth problems.
The second one being.
Excuse me.
Oh, man.
The mocha.
I got it.
I can't drink coffee and mocha.
Before doing a podcast.
This should be a new podcast rule.
Can't do that.
Let's see.
Is there anything else I can play?
God, I don't have anything else prepared, really.
Any other stuff?
Let's see.
Dave Weiner, I guess he got up and went to bed.
Dave actually wrote a nice little piece on scripting news that I'll read to you all,
waiting for Lee Wilkins to come back online.
He must have something wrong with his, with the setup.
Because I can see that we had audio going out.
And I could definitely hear him typing.
Let's see what Dave wrote.
I guess Dave got up.
What time to get up?
Yeah.
317 in the morning Pacific time.
He writes on his weblog scripting news.
That's scripting news.
Scripting.com.
I was hoping that my partner in podcast.
Adam Curry will be back on the air today.
But apparently it's not going to happen anytime soon.
British telecom says they have no more ports.
That someone has to leave before he can get one.
And there's a wait list.
Of course, we're all really disappointed.
Not just Adam.
He's part of an international community.
Yeah, fucking A.
And I'm sure that the community is going to help out in this case.
Because I can just feel it.
I can just feel it.
Okay.
Let me see if I've gotten any more.
Any more suggestions have come through on the comments on the weblog.
And this is the problem with not having any broad band.
Just all your normal communications.
Forget being able to upload or download podcasts.
Your normal communications are just shot.
It takes 20 minutes to just have mail come in.
You know, let alone that there's no.
I can't cash attachments or anything like that.
So I have to remember which attachments to go back and get later on.
I mean, it's really, it's a pain.
Okay.
Let me see if I have any comments.
Yeah, it seems to be a new comment on the latest posting.
I did about bandwidth and deal further.
Let's see what that comment says.
Oh, this is funny.
This is from Nightwise.
Good luck out of my see.
You've taken quite the liking to your new title.
The Prince of Pod is indeed far better than the Sultan of Small Band.
Good luck at Starbucks.
Everyone feels my pain indeed.
By now we have 25 different comment links on the previous posting of people trying to help me out.
Let's see if there's anything new that came in.
Even saw my sister post on that.
Oh, boy.
There's lots here.
Let's see.
Moving back to Belgium.
That's a good option.
Do you haunt the cottage?
Let's see.
Okay.
I can have.
Oh, this is nice.
Someone could.
Someone has a staff and Antwerp called the CEO of British telecom request.
An interview was part of an international documentary film entitled The World's Most Backward Telephone Companies.
Oh, that's good.
Everyone says I should use my name and use my cloud.
I don't know about that.
Let's see.
What is Drew?
Oh, Don and Drew.
Drew checked in.
Drew actually has a satellite link.
I think at the farmhouse in Wisconsin.
And I don't think he's very happy with that either.
Okay.
Now let's see.
Let's see.
How about a.
We could do with the serious bitties.
I haven't played one by the serious bitties in a long time.
Oops.
Hold on.
Jason's up here.
Okay.
Thank you.
As a problem with Skype out these days.
Just like I turn on Skype and then within three seconds.
I've got people all over the place.
Insight messaging me and, you know, calling and requesting requesting chats.
It's a drawback.
Real drawback.
Treeplayless serious bitties.
Then we're waiting for for lead to come back online.
It's only two minutes and 43 seconds if you want to skip ahead.
This is called the truck song.
Enjoy.
Oh.
If I had my truck, I'm going to Minnesota.
And there I get a lot of stuff to put in my truck.
And if I had my truck, I'm bringing it all back to you.
And then maybe I do, you're in the flatbed of my truck.
Oh, if I hadn't my fast speed,
I know we'll jump flatbed.
Cherry red love buggy.
Well, we want to be famous.
New year up to many girls.
Just for be and so lucky.
If I had my truck, we'd get out of the city
and go to where it's pretty by the crisis of my truck.
And if I had my truck, I'd leave by the dinners,
the robbers and the winers by the crisis of my truck.
My dream is a wish you live for.
That comes from your very soul.
And dreams there are no stoplights at all.
And everybody's beautiful.
If I had my truck, we'd never have to worry
because we're never in hurry when we're driving in my truck.
And when we're in my truck, there's no such thing as my way
because the only way is a highway street to heaven in my truck.
Oh, if I had my fast speed,
I know we'll jump flatbed.
Cherry red love buggy.
Well, we want to be famous.
New year up to many girls.
Just for be and so lucky.
We want to be famous.
New year up to many girls.
Just be my honey and my truck.
LeCivius Bitties and the truck song here on the daily source code for Friday,
December 3rd, 2004.
We are two days away from what the Dutch would call center class.
I think I probably explained this before.
Certainly written about it on my weblog.
That the Dutch, although Christmas has certainly become more of an institution
mainly because of commercialization.
They have their version of Santa Claus.
This show up on his white horse with his black peat helpers,
which is literally what they're called black peats.
And they are black.
Talk about discriminatory celebrations.
And they go from door to door from rooftop to rooftop on the 5th of December.
And put presents in children's shoes.
Of course, originally these were wooden shoes that they did that.
So even though Christina doesn't need to have anything in her shoe.
Just because of the family that we still have all living back in Holland,
we're kind of following along with the celebration.
But here in the UK it's all Christmas meant.
Everything is Christmas, the high street.
Let me explain about the high street.
Every town basically has a high street.
It's kind of what we call the main drag.
And in Guilford where we live, the high street is closed off to traffic until 5 or 6 every single day.
And it's great.
You can walk.
It's cobblestones.
It's beautiful, you know, quite little streets.
But also the most modern and the most fashionable.
I mean, you don't need to go to London if you want to do some shopping.
You just come to the high street.
And right off to the high street is a market street.
And that's where the Starbucks is that I'm at.
And I'm using the T-Mobile Wi-Fi link.
Only costs like there's Lee.
Only costs like 30 pounds for the week.
So let's see if we can get Lee and Lee.
Hello Lee.
I don't know if they're comfortable.
So I can hear him.
That's what's crazy.
Why can't Lee hear me?
I don't understand.
I'll send him an instant message.
I can hear you.
Come on Lee.
Say something to his dude.
Maybe we should try this with someone else and see if see if I can get it to work with
with another person.
I'll send him an instant message right now.
I'm going to try something else.
Stand by.
And say hi to every one on the source code.
Come on.
Say hi.
Let me try and call someone else here.
Hold on.
Let me call Ron Bloom.
He's my former partner at the company.
We took public in 96 called Think New Ideas.
And I got him running on Skype recently.
I can see his online.
And usually when Ron's online, he'll pick up.
I think he just turns the computer off if he's not using it.
Shoot.
This is not doing the way I wanted it to do.
Okay.
Let's try Dave Winner then.
Although it looks like Dave's asleep.
We'll give him a shout anyway.
See if he's up and about.
We need some dialing music.
Do we have any dialing music?
I don't think we do.
Here we do.
Here's some nice dialing music for your bottle.
Trailer for sailor rent.
Now doesn't look like that's gonna work, does it?
Oh, this blows.
I ain't got no cigarettes.
I bet.
Time wrong.
Boom.
Is it?
Hey.
For a bit.
Boom.
Man.
The means by no means.
Prince of the pod.
Hey.
We should make that sound.
Shit.
Okay.
I don't understand why Lee Wilkins can't hear me.
Let's try it one more time.
Hello, Lee. Can you hear me?
Shoot.
Okay.
Oh.
Boy, did my Skype just crash there?
Yeah, did hold on.
Maybe that was the problem.
Maybe it needed to be uncrashed.
Can you hear the room?
Hey, we should redo the song.
Prince of the pod.
Cool.
Hey, let's listen to him while Skype is restarting.
No other than names.
And every hand I've never been down.
And every lock that ain't got.
Broadband around the same trailers for sailor rent.
Rooms to death.
If this sense.
No.
That's.
I ain't got no sugar rest.
I'll burn.
Telling you that you can make a new hit.
Prince of the pod.
In the 12th of April, my love.
Man means by no means.
Prince of the pod.
Okay.
Let's try Lee again.
Lee.
Hello Lee.
Damn.
Lee.
Hello Lee.
Oh, this is sucks.
It's really fucking sucks.
This is not what I planned on doing.
Hold on.
Oh, that's probably Lee calling me now.
Lee.
That's why I say.
Hey.
I can hear you.
Fine.
Yeah.
You can't hear me at all.
Okay.
We'll hold on.
We'll do it this way because now you can.
Can I call me?
Call me on Skype.
But don't hang this line up.
We'll just talk this way.
Because I'll be able to record both ends.
Uh.
Yeah.
I could Skype out.
Hold on a second.
What?
To this number?
Hold on a second.
Let me.
Okay.
What give me the number?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll call you right back.
That was actually a fairly intelligent idea Lee had there.
I could just try to Skype out.
Which means I'm going to use the telephone.
The telephone version.
Okay.
So let's see.
It should be.
Uh.
Country code.
Four.
I'm going to just enter the number.
One.
Two.
Okay.
Let's see if this works.
I'll be cool if that did work.
I wonder maybe I have to put a plus.
Plus sign.
Okay.
Hold on.
Field.
Gee, this is a lot of fun in it.
Okay.
This should be.
Come on.
There we go.
Ooh.
Just might work.
Lee.
Oh man.
Skype fucking crashed again.
Fucking bugger.
Wow.
Did that sound English or what?
But God damn it.
Okay.
Let's suck.
Skype shouldn't be crashing.
One away.
We're now.
Okay.
30 minutes into this podcast.
I'm still going to try and keep it at 40 regardless.
Oh man.
Okay.
Starting up Skype again.
Let's see if.
It must be something wrong.
That's clearly.
Okay.
So I'll put my plus in there.
Four.
Okay.
Let's try this again.
If long as Skype doesn't crash, then we're good.
But we need a new version of Skype.
That's for sure.
Lee.
Can you hear me now?
Don't tell me you can't hear me this way either.
He can't.
God.
This is all.
Ah.
Well, there's clearly something wrong with my Skype set up then.
That's for sure.
Let's see.
Maybe if we change.
Hello.
Lee.
Hold on.
Don't go away.
Don't hang up.
He hung up.
Shit.
Okay.
I'm just going to try in the old way.
I'm going to ask him to call me on the phone.
So clearly there's something wrong here.
Okay.
We'll just do it that way.
We'll just have him.
I'll call him on the phone.
And this way we'll be able to record it.
Hello.
Lee.
Can you hear me?
No.
I'm sure you can't hear me.
Okay.
Hold on.
Come on Lee.
Where are you, boy?
Okay.
Call me on the cell.
Call me.
Then we have it.
Okay.
There.
Yeah.
Okay.
Buddy.
How are you doing first of all?
I'm doing pretty well as you can imagine.
I'll explain it in a little while.
What happened.
It's not so much me on the blood.
It's trying to put on a very face.
Let's set this up properly.
Because Lee, I've known you for maybe a month or two now.
I met through, well, through podcasting one way or the other.
And Lee is kind of like a stalker.
Yeah.
But a good stalker in a way.
And he's been, been skyping me and we've been talking off and on for a while.
And we hooked up by a telephone just a couple days ago.
And he told me this gut-redging story that I just wanted to let everyone know.
Because I think that the daily source code listeners could easily help with this problem.
Lee, you just want to explain what happened.
Because you were, you would move to the States, right?
You were going to go, you had a job line up there, not too long ago, right?
That's correct.
On the 25th of May this year, the UK company that I was working for sent me to the States to help with the US operations.
Which for a 22 year old and being given it opportunity, you know, you're like, yeah, yeah.
That's correct.
Yeah, exactly.
So we're in four weeks.
You know, on the first of May this was arranged and by the 25th of May, we touched down in Atlanta.
So as we landed, we were kindly put up by one of the members of this social networking site that I worked for.
So we touched down and you know, she hadn't, there was a few problems there, which meant we would kick down.
Because our dogs ate a tomato plant and I hadn't even started to grow.
When were your dog ate a tomato plant?
Yeah, she kicked us out because of it.
What out of your apartment?
No, the yard of somewhere where we were staying.
Right.
So we'd, and during that time, you know, as you know, if you yourself from your park, your blocks this morning,
getting broadband, you know, almost within a few days, finding somewhere to live is not easy.
No.
So you had your two dogs, you took with you to the States.
Correct.
We bought them from London.
We, to get them from London to the States.
All we had to do was have the microchip.
How certificates.
Right.
And that was pretty much it because the UK is considered as a rabies free country.
Oh yeah, definitely.
Yep.
So we got them to the States and to cut long story short.
I was fired.
Or I was a subcontractor.
I was contracted for them.
Yeah.
So you moved your entire life, including your two dogs.
And then your contract was cut.
Yeah.
We sold everything.
We were standing somewhere.
We just lost Christmas.
We kicked out our whole apartment.
You know, dogs' ball of stuff.
It's a huge table.
You know, that aside because we've done a full cow.
Yeah.
And because it is new opportunity that we thought would be great.
You know, for young 22 year olds to do.
Yeah.
And to travel and move to the States.
Of course.
It's a beautiful thing to do.
And I thought I wanted to do it since I was 16.
I wanted to study there at first.
So, you know, I grabbed the opportunity as quickly as I could.
So we got to the States and we were in that land.
And then we got fired.
And we moved to Houston.
I hope I find in Jenny, my girlfriend's and work.
Right.
She's also 22.
She's 20.
Okay.
Right.
She was a bit guided.
Actually, she couldn't drink legally in the States.
Even though she could do so hard to hear any UK.
Right.
I think in that sense, she's glad to be on.
Yeah.
At least there's some benefit because what happened is.
Now, you guys were, you see, you,
essentially, you decided to come back.
Right.
Since things didn't work out in the States.
Yes.
But then because you'd been there so short and you hadn't really had time to focus on it,
you didn't have time to get your,
the dogs, the rabies shots.
They needed to come back into the country, right?
Correct.
And I, and I just don't think all about you.
I'm an expert now when it comes to the, when it comes to rabies and getting your dogs and cats in,
because we barely squeaked under the wire.
So, so basically they have to go into quarantine.
That's correct.
That has to go into quarantine for six months.
If we can get them, if and when we can get them to the UK.
But what do you mean, if and when you can, where are they now?
They're coming at Atlanta.
And this is what's making it more exciting.
Because of the, you know, they're happening through, because of Delta.
We'd spoken to Delta two weeks prior to our flight.
And they booked our dogs on the flight.
And we just assume that they've booked them as a fantastic cargo because, you know,
they should know what they're doing.
And I'll ring them up two days before the flight.
And a day before I'm due to drive 900 miles from Houston to Atlanta.
Just ask us, because I want it to know that requirement size is for the kennel cases to travel in.
As you said, the woman said, no, sorry, pets don't, pets can't fly.
This is almost like, like, my broadband is like, yeah, sure, no problem.
And then on the day off, it's like, oh, I'm sorry.
That's a problem, right?
Yeah.
Yes.
And plus on top of this, you know, money was tired.
And I had to try it.
So I didn't have access to a phone or anything.
And I've got a day to sort out the dogs.
So you basically didn't have time to sort it out at all.
No, we, we, I managed to find a, uh, a ball game kennel that we were thinking perhaps just
leave them there for a few days.
But as soon as we got there, I'm telling you these kennels were the worst kennels that I've ever seen.
You know, I wouldn't want my worst enemies to live in these kennels.
And this is the delta kennels.
This was a company that dealt are used.
Oh, shit.
So what, what kind of dogs are these Lee?
Uh, we have two little jack russles.
Ah.
And we've just missed their birthday.
Uh, Alfie's birthday was last week.
Well, what's the other dog Alfie and who?
Benson.
And Alfie and Benson.
Okay.
So, so let me just recap here.
So if I understand properly because of the incorrect information Delta gave you.
Um, and that you had to drive, you know, a thousand miles didn't have a phone, et cetera, et cetera.
You couldn't get your dogs on the same flight as you, as you and your girlfriend Jenny had coming back
to the UK.
So they're now stuck in Atlanta or in Houston.
They're stuck in Atlanta.
Okay.
How do we get them out?
What needs to happen?
Um, well, because we don't need set aside $220 that we thought Delta told it was originally
going to cost.
Um, the fee had not.
It comes down to don't do it.
And the only people that can fly pets legally,
route of Atlanta into London get week is continental.
Right.
And, you know, I, at the airport, I've done the pig in as much as I could.
Um, with me stuff flights and it all went a bit crazy.
But that's neither here nor there.
But to fly them out with continental, it's going to cost around $1,500.
Oh, geez.
And that fees grow in by 20 dollars a day because of the kennel costs as well.
Right.
And this is the horrible can all that they're in.
Yeah.
And the girlfriend, you know, to be honest, I know she's going to listen to this.
And she's probably going to buy my head off.
She's almost, she's so close to losing the plot.
She's talking to the dogs that aren't even there.
Oh, you're kidding me.
She's not sleeping.
She's beside herself.
Of course I understand.
This is exactly what would have happened with Patricia.
I totally understand.
Oh, this is horrible.
Okay.
So, um, when I heard this story, I said to Lee, I said,
we got to do something about this.
And I know how many people subscribe to the daily source code.
And did you, were you able to set up a tip jar like a PayPal tip jar or something?
Lee?
Yes.
If anyone's willing to help out.
You know, we will be great.
For if you haven't got Alfie and Benson.com.
That's Alfie.
Spel it.
A-L-F-I-E.
And Benson-B-E-N-S-O-N.com.
Okay.
So, there's a PayPal link there that they can donate some money to getting Alfie and Benson back.
There is correct.
Okay.
Well, that's excellent.
Um, you know, if every source code listener were to just donate one dollar.
Yeah.
But you wouldn't have to work for the rest of your life.
But I'm hoping that we can get enough.
And, you know, and let us know when you have the 1500.
Okay.
So that we can, uh, we can celebrate that.
I'm pretty sure that we can get at least 1500 daily source code listeners to donate, uh,
one dollar at least.
I'm going to, I want to put in my donation right after we hang up and, uh, and, you know,
let's, let's get Alfie and Benson home.
At least they'll be home in the UK.
And then they still have to sit and quarantine for six months.
That's credible.
We just found out we've actually got 12 days to fly one of them back into the country
because he's choose some medical, um, I don't know there will be girlfriend.
If she feels with that sort of that she's, he's chosen tablets and stuff and injections.
Or it doesn't give you, it doesn't have them in 12 days.
Oh, this is a horrible story, Lee.
Yeah.
I feel so bad for you.
We have so bad that if you check out Leiratus.com we even put on laptop out there for sale
that the only laptop that we have.
that we have.
We don't want you selling her laptop.
Now I don't want you selling your laptop.
I'm sure that the podcast community can hop in here and help out.
Should be totally doable to get 1,500 bucks totally.
What else do you think?
I just like to thank you for giving me the chance to tell my story.
No, Lee.
It's listen from one pet owner to another who's been through the scare and I got off
lucky.
Especially to have your dog sitting in America in a kennel that you know is all that great.
It must feel horrible.
It must feel just terrible.
It is.
It's very good.
Okay.
All right, then, Lee.
We're about 42 minutes into the source code.
So I'm going to wrap the show up.
I'll go and donate to the first dollars in just a few minutes.
We'll get the podcast out there and let's hope that we can get Alfie and Vincent home pretty soon.
Thanks.
Thank you very much, everybody.
Everybody.
All right, Lee.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Okay, buddy.
All right.
So that's Lee Wilkins on the daily source code with a real sob story.
Been waiting to get the story out to you for like three days because well, it wasn't able
to do it because of the lack of bandwidth to be able to do a Skype call.
So please go over to Alfie and Benson.com and help out Lee and his girlfriend Jenny.
It's just a sad story.
Those poor puppies.
Those Jack Russells are just sitting there and some horrible kennel in Atlanta.
So let's help them out.
And then get me some fucking broadband.
Will you please?
Because that's what I really need.
I'll leave it at that for today's source code.
I'll be back Monday here from the Starbucks.
It's your daily source code coming to you from the Starbucks on Market Street.
We'll be here every single weekday at 2 o'clock.
Come on in and join the party if you want to.
It's right off the high street in Guilford in the UK.
Comments.
Adam at curry.com.
Please don't add the comments.
And any three is attachment but send a link to it.
That way I can download and once I get to the Starbucks.
Once again, thanks for tuning in.
We'll check you out on Monday.
Have a great weekend everybody.
Bye bye.
Thank you.