Hi everybody, it's the Source Code and today is September 7th, 2004.
I'm Adam Curry and good evening or good morning or good afternoon wherever you're listening
to the Source Code.
Thanks for downloading, thanks for subscribing.
Welcome to you today or this evening I should say from the bunker in Amsterdam.
That's the house that we've had in the middle of the city for the past four years.
We call it the bunker because it used to be a museum and it's completely fortified.
It's got alarm systems up the yin yang, double enforced doors, bulletproof glass, all this
crap.
And Patricia and I are staying here tonight.
It's 10 minutes to 10 p.m. so a little bit late with the show because wow, had a very busy day.
We got up, let's see.
I got up at six o'clock, which is still my time to rise, apparently.
I still haven't gotten out of the morning show rhythm, I guess.
I was going to say algorithm.
I haven't gotten out of the morning show rhythm yet.
And at 6.30 we have to get up to get Christina off to school properly anyway.
And we had to drive for about an hour and 15 minutes to Grandmaster View today, which is
a flat-screen company that I own a share in.
I've been around since it's half inception.
And it's actually, you should check it out, grandmasterview.com.
And it should be coming to the States pretty soon.
We're already in Germany, in Spain, in Italy, and of course the Netherlands and Belgium.
Really huge flat screens.
I'm talking like, what do we have?
Two, I see the largest.
stock model we make is two meters and 25 centimeters diagonally.
So that's, what is that?
That's about seven feet.
So these are pretty big.
And so just, you know, I try to get up there once a week
and hang out with everyone.
Basically, you know, production is running.
So it's all marketing.
And I am part of the whole marketing scheme.
Everyone knows in Holland, Adam Curry,
helicopters and flat screens.
And after that, we went off to one of our partners.
And Patricia, by the way, had never been up to Grand Master View.
So it was really nice to show her that and I had a quick meeting.
And then we went 15 minutes further up to Kuehlenburg,
which is just around Utrecht in the middle of the Netherlands,
to a company called Design Concepts,
the one of our partners with Grand Master View.
What they do is they do these really beautiful frames
around our flat screens and do them in leather
and different types of material.
And they have a showroom where they're selling their furniture.
And they have...
at least five different setups where they have the living room setups.
Only now they have it in addition to a beautiful living room.
They also have one of our screens custom designed to fit that particular style.
So Patricia and I checked that out and I think we probably bought a couch or something.
I'm not sure.
She saw something she liked a lot, but it was really cool.
And I think that's a great way to combine two different products.
And it's working because we actually have one of our salespeople sitting there in
the in the design concept store.
You can check out design concepts at design concepts dot NL.
So let's see that got us back.
No, after that, then I had to go off to see the accountants for our quarterly sit down.
Most of you are rolling your eyes and going, you know, accountants, tax lawyers,
whatever, I actually enjoy it.
There's nothing better than having your accountants and your lawyers and your
tax lawyers all at the table and knowing that each one of those guys
is charging you three to four hundred dollars an hour.
So I just make the.
best of it. I make sure I get plenty of all the tea I want and I make jokes and we have
a pretty good time. I don't mind it. They're supposed to be saving me and helping me and
usually they do. At least I think I've found a team that's pretty damn good. And that
took obviously took quite a while and then by the time I got home it was time for Patricia
and I to go grab a bite to eat and then of course I passed out on the couch. I
think Patricia might have passed out as well. We both kind of a woke around 9
o'clock this evening I said well guess what you know I want to go record the
source source code and I hadn't had a chance to crack my computer all day
since we left the house. Man I hate that so much you know there's so much email
that's come in that I just can't even start to look at right now I'm just too
tired to do it. There's all kinds of things that need my attention and
that's oh man. And of course I don't even know if there's more any audio
stuff that's come down the pipe. Luckily tomorrow we're driving home. I'll have a
chance to catch up on any program.
that I may have missed.
Let's see, so I do want to talk a little bit about...
Let's see about iPodder. I had a couple of updates there.
What did I have? Oh yeah.
Looks like we have two new versions coming up,
and tomorrow I'll know for sure,
and by tomorrow night I'll have updated ipodder.org.
I saw on my email just a brief scan that there is now a Java version of iPodder,
and there's also a Coco version,
which is I believe the Mac OS X native scripting or programming environment.
I'm not too sure, but I will be checking out both of those programs
and putting them up in the directory as appropriate.
If you know of any feeds, please let me know,
because I'd love to add something to the MP3 RSS directory feed,
so people can subscribe to that with their MP3 devices.
Also got some feedback on using the metadata,
which is a big word for all the information you're stuffing.
to a file that you send along. Basically, that's the stuff that when you play the source code
on your MP3 player or in iTunes or whatever you're playing it on, that's why it actually,
instead of just giving you a file name, it says source code, Adam Curry, and then it
may have a date. It may show you a genre which should be speech track one of one.
And then maybe like the past two or three shows, I've actually put a subtitle for
the show in there. And so that should run across your display of your MP3 player.
And on the iPod specifically, I started off with the title is source code and then
the date and I spell it full out. So it's source code September 7th 2004.
Apparently when you're in the playlist menu and you're browsing through
different shows, you only really get up to like half of the name of the month.
So it's source code August or source code September.
Clearly not handy when searching for a particular title.
So I got to figure out what I'm going to do to change this.
I don't know if I want to put the date first and make it a seemingly easier to parse date.
So for today, should it be 09072004, source code?
Or I don't know.
But clearly the way I'm doing it is not making it very easy to archive and browse in iPod
and playlists.
So duly noted, let's see who did I get this email from.
This was from Paul Pilots.
And I will definitely work on some kind of naming convention that works a little bit better
on the iPod and I guess presumably on other MP3 devices.
And please, if you're subscribing to the source code and you have iPod are running through
Windows Media Player on any other device other than the iPod, please let me know.
I'd love to know people using it that way as well because the reason I'm sitting here at
5 to 10 in the evening.
because I'm getting a lot of feedback and I'm getting a lot of people are
listening to the source code also
So, you know, it seems like stuff's working.
Okay, now I had promised you something yesterday,
which I'm now going to bring up.
It's a real clip.
So I'm mixing all different kinds of media here today.
I remember I told you, I was discussing,
I was discussing, oh, the big DJ voice.
I think it was where, you know,
DJs always have to talk really loud
and have to really enunciate everything
and they're hitting on it, punch and make it sound
like you're hitting home when you're talking to that listener.
Now, a lot of people do this.
And a lot of people record their shows,
pre-record their shows.
I'd like to do it direct to tape
or direct to MP3, as it were in this case.
Casey Kasem, we've probably heard used,
I guess, I don't know if he still does the American
top 30 countdown, what is it?
The American or the Casey Kasem's top 40.
He probably still does that show, it's syndicated.
around the country actually around the globe I've heard it all over the place so at a certain point in the show
He does something called the long-distance dedication and it's someone
You know who lives in one part of the world or one part of the states and have a song played and dedicated to someone else
And there's always a story behind it's a little bit sappy in fact the whole show KC Kasem show is so sappy and is so
Well, so it's so early 80s
well at one point
You hear the real Casey Kasem as I'm I'm confident I've only met a couple times
But I'm confident this is exactly the way he can be if he's extremely pissed off
Certainly at the height of his Casey Kasem days when people would run around do anything for him because he was
Mr. Casey Kasem, Mr. Countdown on the radio
Check it out this little bit where Casey Kasem told hi. This is Casey Kasem
American top 40 has moved to a new time
I hope you'll join me this Saturday morning at every Saturday morning at 2 to
Okay, so there you go American top 40
Now listen to the dedication and listen to Casey lose it on this one.
Now we're up to our long-distance dedication.
And this one is about kids and pets and a situation that we can all understand.
Whether we have kids or pets or neither.
It's from a man in Cincinnati, Ohio.
And here's what he writes.
Dear Casey, this may seem to be a strange dedication request, but I'm quite sincere
and it'll meet a lot if you play it.
Recently there was a death in our family.
He was a little dog named Snuggles, but he was most certainly a part of...
Let's come start again.
I'm coming out of the record.
Play the record, okay?
Please.
See when you come out of those up-tempo goddamn numbers man, it's impossible to make those transitions
And then you got to go into somebody dying. You know they do this to me all the time
I don't know what the hell they do it for but goddamn it if we can't come out of a slow record
I don't understand it is down on the phone
Okay, I want a goddamn concerted effort to come out of a record that isn't a fucking up-tempo record every time
I do a goddamn death dedication
Now make it and I also want to know what happened to the pictures I was supposed to see this week
It's a god last goddamn time
I want somebody uses fucking brain to not come out of a goddamn record
That is that's up tempo and I got to talk about a fucking dog dying. Well, he's a fucking ponderous man
Ponderous fucking ponderous
Ponderous
And don't we all feel like that once in a while there's a yelling everybody and boy does it sound good when you yell at someone and
You've got that compressed mic sound you've got the headphones on you can hear your voice really well and just go yell about your
fucking dead dog dedication. Perfect radio history moment.
Now let me take you right into a song because it's our song of the day I felt like playing
something by the motel so sit back and enjoy. Only the lonely.
We walked. The loneliest man. We smiled. Without any style. We kissed, fought, together, wrong.
No intention.
We laughed.
About each other's strengths. We lived. Without each other. Thank you what everyone would do.
Without me and you.
It's like I told you. Only the lonely gets laid.
So dark.
Here we go.
To nothing we know, our feelings go lowing
Way up steaming
You better, the time we were together
So long ago, with that girl, remember all I know
Is it makes me feel good now
It's like a song you, all the way below you can't play
All the way below you, all the way below you can't play
So long ago, with that girl, remember all I know
Only the lonely, only the lonely can be
You're early 80s, huh?
The motels, only this summer on your daily source code live from Amsterdam, coming to
you from the bunker on the Emperor's Canal.
I'm going to leave you with one final thought.
As I said today was going to be rather short just because it was so hectic and so much
to do and I haven't really had a chance to even look at my aggregator really barely.
I was reading a Q&A with Bill Gates.
I think Dave Weiner pointed to it.
And at one point, and it's obviously talking about competing devices with the iPod
and with iTunes and their competing service with the service that will
compete against the iTunes music store.
And here's the quote that Bill Gates gave says,
but the work we've done with these device manufacturers to get them to build
support for subscription music in.
That's a big contribution.
It's kind of a weird sentence, but basically what he's saying that with Windows Media Player.
The work that Microsoft has done to get them to build in support for subscription music has been a big contribution.
I'm thinking, you know, subscription, this is exactly the stuff we're doing.
This is real subscription stuff.
You know, you can always build in a money channel if you need to, but you know, why is it all music that we're talking about?
Stop focusing just on music.
These things can be used for a hell of a lot more than just music.
Pure transfer of information, data, you know, just like the source code.
But it is good that they've got that subscription all built in.
Anyway, that's it for the source code for today.
I'm going to hit the hay tomorrow's reasonably easy day for me.
We have a production company coming to take a look if they actually would like to rent this place for several months
to do a Dutch version of, I think it's the Apprentice.
Well, that would be nice if we could rent this place out.
And pretty soon we're going to be looking for new digs in the UK.
So I'll keep you up to speed on that when we meet again tomorrow.
On the source code.
Take care everybody.
The power.
And of course, if you want to respond, send email to adamantcurry.com or leave a comment
on my weblog, live.
The power of your intelligence.