Hey everybody, it's Adam here at Ricky's Highett and Paula Walther.
Hold on a second.
I was listening to Coverville in their Abba Special podcast.
Just got in, pretty long fight about 14 hours altogether,
and got the Wi-Fi configured, had a quick bite to eat.
I'm too tired to do a full-blown daily source code,
so I hope you'll excuse me for not doing that.
It looks like Dave and I are going to do a high-quality trade secrets tomorrow,
and yeah, that's the stuff coming up.
I'm sure there'll be plenty of podcasts in the next few days,
so it shouldn't be too bad.
And thank you Don and Drew for the extra long Don and Drew show.
It really helped on the flight.
And I got my Doom bug y'all ready for you by the day.
Hey, that's it.
Source code tomorrow.
And those of you on your way, Rob BloggerCon.
See you soon.
Bye.