podcasting, all's live, and a curry.
The power of the door is in the door.
Well, hey everybody.
Good.
After actually a good late morning from Curry Castle.
As right as you did, a source code for Monday.
We are living in November.
It is the 15th day of the month of 2004.
Live from Curry Castle.
The power of the door is in the door.
Or maybe we should say almost live because of course it's not my recording.
Wow.
I had time to assemble all kinds of stuff for the show over the weekend.
I have a list of this incredibly long.
So many of the audio comments.
I mean, we've been dropping stuff that I absolutely wanted to get on the show today.
But it's just too long.
I think we're going to be close to an hour.
So I wanted to go through some stuff.
It's going to be a little bit wagging today because as we speak, the movers are here.
They are packing up our stuff.
It's a multiple day operation.
They already were in Amsterdam last week.
As you recall, packing up some of the stuff there.
I basically told them, look, he just stay away from the bar for the next hour or so.
So at least I can get this podcast done.
But I'm sure people will be eating out asking all kinds of questions.
Patricia's upstairs.
Christina's here in the bar.
Well, it's just a couple more days.
I don't want to give all the details because I know the Dutch.
I know the Dutch press is certainly listening to the daily source code.
I don't want to give many ideas about when to go stand at airports.
And shit like that because just don't need that, honestly.
But yeah, as I said, it's definitely a multi-day operation.
It's a lot of fun.
And even when we're gone, the piano will still be here,
be waiting to pick up, it's just, it's kind of nuts.
So a lot to talk about today.
And there's also, well, just to start off with Christina,
I'm glad you're here.
Remember you had the day off on Thursday and didn't remember what it was?
Yeah, vape is still strong.
Right.
But it's armistice day.
That's what it is.
I got an email here from Rob.
Actually, a comment here from Rob.
He says, Adam surprised that someone living in flangers would not know something about armistice day.
The end of World War I.
When Germany surrendered to the Allies at 11 o'clock on the 11th day of the 11th month of 1918.
So it was the 11th of.
Well, yeah, he can be a little smart nose,
because he knows what the hell he's talking about.
So we learned something.
And I could not believe the amount of comments that I've received about my iPod or ear problem.
Now, I'm not talking to you anymore, Christina.
You don't have to.
Hold on, there's the phone shoot.
What should we do?
Yeah, it's my banker.
I'll put it on hold for one second.
I'll be right back.
Right, okay.
I'm glad I took that call.
You know, I'm trying to open up bank accounts and do all this kind of stuff.
Get everything ready for, well, for us living there, for us being there.
And it's just not easy, you know.
And without a bank account, by the way, without a UK bank account,
you can't get essential things like cable and internet,
internet and, you know, cell phones and all this stuff.
So anyway, I was talking about iPod or ears.
iPod or ears is kind of like tennis elbow or mouse arm or I had mouse finger,
which I think someone sent in a comment about.
Talk about that later.
But basically, from having these little ear buds in the whole time,
and I've had headphones on my entire life, both radio and flying,
and actually they're the same headsets in many cases.
But I've never really had the little ear buds in for extended periods of time.
And check out this email.
I've gotten a lot.
See Andrew Chernau says, he has the same problem.
He says, maybe you should invest in the pair of headsets.
Headphones if you want to go into longer recordings.
He's suggesting, what is he suggesting?
Sony.
I guess that is true.
I have a pair of Sony headsets around here.
You know what he's really?
I like being able to monitor what people are going to hear.
And I figure that if people are listening on these ear buds,
of course, lots of you may be using an eye trip or something
to broadcast FM signal to your car radio.
But still, I want to try and have as much of the same experiences
the listener is going to have.
So I don't know if headphones is really going to work for me.
René.
Let's see.
Oh, René talked.
Yeah, heard me talk about my finger mouse issue.
And I've got the Bluetooth mouse.
And could I please provide make and model?
Yes, it'd be happy to.
Because I actually like in that quite a lot.
Let me see.
It's in here in my bag.
I hold on.
And that works.
Actually, that works quite well.
It's like now my headphone wire isn't long enough to reach.
So we go.
This is by Mac mice.
So I guess Mac mice.com.
The mouse BT Bluetooth.
That's what it's called.
It just looks like a regular white Mac mouse.
Yeah.
So Mac mice.com is where you can check it out.
So it's designed in Tennessee, USA.
And then really small letters.
It says manufactured in Taiwan.
Okay.
Doesn't matter.
It'd be working.
So that goes back in the bag.
And what's the next one?
This is all.
Again, we're continuing here with the.
I potter ear.
Here we have.
A podcast ear is what James.
Ah, this is James the invincible.
Of course.
James is Donna Drew's buddy.
Let's see.
Oh, what did he say?
He was listening.
Oh, he said I.
So he's actually suggesting a model of Sony.
Let's see.
I went through a bunch of other stuff.
Awesome set of Sony ear buds.
Okay.
It was the MDR ED21 LP.
Although they seem to be deprecated.
So maybe they're out.
But this is James.
And he must know about ears.
This is the guy with a huge shotgun hole piercings.
And he's earlobe.
So he's got to be an ear guy.
So we'll check that out.
Of course, the production notes of the daily source code are going to be online available
with the posts that went out today.
So I'm actually posting James's the copy of all the emails in there.
So you can read back whatever the serial number was.
And the answer more to say about the promiscuous bullet guys.
But you'll read that one.
You check it out when you check as it even out from the production notes.
Final one here for the headphones suggestion Stewart Hunter.
He says he's using the Sony MDR W08 headphones.
Very lightweight.
They sit slightly inside the ear rather than being stuffed right in like an earbud.
Now that may be a solution.
He provides a couple of.
Oh, okay.
Richard sounds in the UK are selling them.
So I can actually buy them in the in the UK after the move.
All right.
Well, thank you very much for the for the comments there.
Again, those will be in the production notes for anyone who is also interested in getting something else
than the then iPod or ear from ear buds, finding some solutions to that.
And also something that happened over the weekend.
You may have seen me post about it on my weblog.
All of a sudden my battery for the power book just died.
And now of course it's not just all of a sudden right.
These things don't just happen.
I believe there was a system update.
And if I look online, you know, if you just type in the Google Powerbook 17 inch dead battery,
you're going to see all kinds of issues.
And it's really not clear if Apple's batteries have problems.
I've never seen a battery go that quick just from apparently okay to zero.
In fact, it doesn't even recognize the batteries in anymore.
There's no lights on the battery when you post little test indicator.
So the first thing was a real bitch to figure out how to restart the power book with a dead battery.
And you have to go through this power management unit reset sequence,
which basically means you hold down shift control, alt, and then you hit the power button.
Let go weight five seconds, then power up as normal.
It'll reset your clock and everything, but it will start up, which is kind of what was the most important part.
So somehow I've now got to figure out where to get a power book battery.
Because here's the scenario I see that I'm running into.
We're going to move.
I won't have a battery, which means I'll be tethered to power.
Won't have any type of broadband in the house just a dial-up line.
Of course, I don't think that the Wi-Fi of the city will reach to my house.
So I'll have to drive into town.
Of course, I have to sit in the car because I'll have a battery to sit anywhere with the power book.
So, you know, or I find an apple store.
It's just, or maybe today I'll drive up north somewhere and find an apple store and get it all going.
Let's see.
Got an email here from Tony from Oz.
Tony says, where are I?
Yeah, I'm good day.
Adam, we're going to call Center Christ.
I won't put my last name in because I'll probably get sacked for that.
Maybe I should take this out of the email here right now.
I'm going to take that out since we're going to be publishing these notes.
Okay.
There you go.
Your name is now safe with me.
I love your podcast.
They are raw, man.
They are like getting stone with your mates and listening to shit.
You normally wouldn't listen to.
Well, dude, that's exactly what...
That's exactly what's happening here.
He says, I spend probably 10 hours outside every weekend in the yard.
Hey, it's Australia.
Non-rugby league season, of course.
Man, your cast breeze me through the weekend.
Thank you very much.
Maybe you can pop the question.
Okay.
He's the the question.
A member of the coalition of the willing.
When apple iTunes might immigrate to Australia.
Well, that's a good question.
By the way, he says, is immigrate is that the right word?
I don't know.
Shoot.
I really hope that you get set up.
I guess you can't...
The European Union now has iTunes and iTunes's music store, I guess, is what you mean.
Hmm.
I don't know.
I guess it's...
What is it?
I guess, yeah, I don't know.
I have no idea.
That's kind of sucks.
The only alternative, I guess, would be to use an American credit card, or European credit card.
Okay.
So that's a market that still needs to open up.
Hope it happens soon for you there, Tony.
Now, I got so much to do today.
I'm just going to breeze through as many of these things as I can.
A lot of stuff that came in over the weekend as the iPod,
was just churning away, particularly on blog digger media and
God knows, openpodcast.org, and I came across an interesting way of...
Playing back your voicemail.
If you get a voicemail, and this probably is some guy who broke up with his girlfriend.
And she leaves you a real nasty voicemail.
You could do a couple things with it.
You could play it for your friend, and you could listen to it.
Or, of course, you could mix it all up and turn it into a podcast.
Hello.
I think you're the biggest fucking loser I've ever met in my life.
This message is for kids.
I'm Mr. Dana.
I'm just calling.
And I'm just...
And I'm just calling.
I'm Mr. Dana.
I'm just calling because we're against the weekend.
So you can play it over and over again.
But it over and over again.
I think you're the biggest fucking loser I've ever met in my life.
And I think you're the biggest fucking loser I've ever met in my life.
Over and over again.
You're the biggest fucking loser I've ever met in my life.
I think you're the biggest fucking loser I've ever met in my life.
Especially the biggest fucking loser I've ever met in my life.
And I can't believe you.
Then I can't believe you,
and I can't believe you.
I can't believe you ever thought you had any any any
any can't put me.
Hello, hello, hello,
I think you're the biggest fucking loser I've ever met in my life.
Thank you, and thank you, and
and I can't believe you, thank you, and
thank you, and thank you, and thank you, and thank you, and
thank you, and goodbye.
Isn't that awesome?
Yes, thank you for your message.
Tony Kong is, uh, this is slowly, uh, well,
certainly slowly, but surely, turning out to be our good friend,
my good friend from Boston.
WGBH, the first public radio,
broadcaster to hit the podcasting scene with morning stories,
and
met him out at BloggerCon, had a really good chat with him.
It's a very interesting guy, and he's been posting his morning stories,
which he produces for a WGBH in Boston.
He's been putting those up on podcasts, of course, you could find that for me.
I potted out org directory, and usually he starts off by saying,
you know, today's morning story is about, and then he kind of leads into it.
But for the, I think this is the first time we're actually hearing Tony,
and I'm not going to play the whole morning stories, because you, you know,
I want you to subscribe to that, and, and, you know,
get your morning stories the way you should be getting it from the feed.
It's also, it's, you know, these about four or five minute stories,
a lot to, a lot to play through if I want to get through the other stuff today.
But I think this is the first time that we're hearing Tony actually,
introduced, you know, his morning story's episode, and kind of,
well, you know what, he's podcasting for real.
Hi, this is Tony Con, the producer and the director of morning stories on WGBH Boston.
Just back from BloggerCon 3 in Palo Alto, which was an incredible event with ripples
that we'll be going on. I hope for a very long time.
I want to thank you all who came up just to say hi to say that you enjoyed morning stories,
and that meant an awful lot to us. We're going to keep on bringing them to you.
And also, who just checked in to say hi, and to make sure that we stay in touch as this
incredible revolution keeps on working itself out.
Today's morning story is in celebration that we can stop that.
That's the whole intro to the morning story. Patricia just, hey, hon.
Hi, man. I'm, uh, I figured I'd do my source code now, so that then after I'm done,
they can come in, they can rip everything apart between boxes, yes.
And an army of, uh, how many is like eight guys, eight guys, and six guys, six guys?
One handy man. Yeah. And, uh, it goes really fast.
It's no shit. I'm like, yeah, I'm like, yeah.
Because otherwise they peck your dog. Well, actually, that could be a benefit.
Can we just put her in a big box and, uh, shipper off? Okay, um,
do you need me to do anything? Because I'm just want to, I'm just going to finish the show and then, uh,
and then I'll help them pack up the bar. They need some money.
I need some money for all you have to get some, uh, a coffee and a whole amount of second.
It's next for them. Um, where do I put the money? Oh, yeah. I remember right there.
You need it now? Yeah, I'm going to shit. How much seen me?
Do you have, you, but you need money. You just need money, right, to walk around like money?
Okay.
Walk around and spend that somewhere else, but on, on ourselves.
Yeah, that's what moving's all about, everybody.
Okay. Um, oops, moving right along. Uh, we have another friend that we met at Blager Khan,
Jaime, and he has some news about his Spanish podcast.
Hi, Adam. This is Jaime. Um, well, I want to just give you the news.
I successfully recorded the fourth and final installment of my podcast in Spanish.
It broadcast must go into the story. And, uh, I've successfully completed these with
no additional costs using just the hardware that I had in hand and free software that I found
in the internet. I've explained, uh, every single step I took to record my podcasts and how to
publish them, how to write the external tags, et cetera. And they're available at
Bapis.org forward slash podcast for anyone who speaks Spanish and wants to
wants to know how to do these. So, you know, it's like a couple of seconds from me to understand what
Jaime was saying, because I'm like, what? He stopped his podcast, but what he essentially did, I think
it he created instructions in Spanish on how to podcast. That's awesome, uh, and it really appreciated.
Although, Jaime, I think you should continue, man. Don't stop with a podcast. Damn, you know,
we finally had a Spanish podcast. Keep it going. That just would be my hope that you might do that.
And anyway, I can help you know, just let me know. Um, I noticed that you were basically
coding your RSS files by hand, which, uh, there are easier ways to do it. And, and if any of
any of those production reasons is what made you stop, you know, let me help you out, because uh,
I'd love to, you know, I'd love to put you in the pod squad, man. Let's, uh, let's keep the Spanish
vibe going. So, uh, anyway, if you're thinking of doing a Spanish podcast in iPod.org, under languages,
and under the Spanish, no, you'll find Jaime's podcasts, or I guess it's just how to, uh,
how to podcast in Spanish. Email from Tony Mullins, who's been listening to all kinds of podcasts
for the past three weeks. Now he says it doesn't own an iPod, but uses Doppler, uh, Doppler. I think
it's a plug-in for, or it has a podcast plug-in. I'm not sure. I know it's an aggregator. Um, he says,
uh, he's, you know, getting into it, wants to set up a podcast. He's got a band, check this out. Um,
a band called Big Toon. Uh, you can find BigToon at BigToon.org. Our latest CD is a couple of tracks
I'd love for you to check out. Possible play on your RIA three daily source code show. Um, what did
you score? It was a pattern of a team. Damn.
No, that would have been bad if they backed the retainer. So anyway, um, I appreciate it.
I appreciate, um, you sent me the link at Tony. Send a couple links to, uh, to some of his files.
They are 100% money says and 100% RIA three. And I kind of like this one. So,
put out. So, set Avenue. You're going to check it out here on the daily source code for Monday,
with the Fifteen K
One last break, to leave it as half
Another one's gone, he's never around
Sometimes things just work, it's turned itself upside down
Yet you say, I'm the moon
We never
Here's a playin' on their horse that they are
They don't have a chance to go there far
My mom's crying in her house, she's just outside
You want to help, but you don't know how
Get to say, I'm the moon
Yet you say, I'm the moon
There's a man I know from a little time
You never did wrong, and it's true you've grown
It's never for and it's true for true
That he walked down the streets and said, I'm the moon
Yet you say, I'm the moon
Big tone, for big tone dot org
It's a sad avenue on your daily source code
For Monday, November 15th, 2004
I really appreciate all the comments and emails about the BBC stuff that we posted up on Friday
I wasn't quite sure how people were going to respond to it
But I think the conversation that Dave and I had on Skype
Was quite clear, and I'm sure the BBC have checked it out as well
I hope they understand
I think everyone understood that this was exactly the apex of
Big old media and, you know, new small media
Where the big media needs to do things a certain way
And there's certain expectations
And that's probably what people expect at home viewing as well
And I was happy that we were able to provide the exact opposite side of the equation
And I do believe that the culture show will have a
Some form of, I think it's a real video stream available when it comes out
I think it's the 23rd of the 25th, they'll let me know
And I'll post that accordingly
And perhaps someone can record it while in the UK
Perhaps by that time I'll actually have a television
And I'll be able to record myself myself
Maybe she got one of those, maybe I'll get an I view
Or some kind of PVR set up so I can make an MPG out of that myself
But it was kind of fun
And also, you know, Dave was doing the exact same thing
He's appearing in Newsweek
Not quite sure what it's for
Yeah, I don't think he's told anyone what it's for
Maybe he has, but I'm not sure if I can talk about it
Doesn't matter, you'll see it
And it was the same thing we were laughing about that
Because what did they want him?
You know, they want, you know, Mr.
Granddaddy, Pintdaddy of web logs to be in a cyber cafe
You know, changing the world
And as Dave pointed out he was doing the exact thing that I was doing with the BBC
Because he was posting pictures of the photographer
Doing the shoot while he was actually there
You know, it was up online before this guy
Even clicked off his first shot
So, you know, that really shows a whole
You know, world of difference between
Old media and New media
If that's even a fair representation
But dude, we really need each other to bootstrap to the next level
So, hopefully that was all understood
And everyone enjoyed it including
A good friends at the BBC
Moving along with a couple of bits
We got some promos
And you know what?
He's consented to Miss Walker Khan
This is the rest of the web audio
4, 2, 4, 11, 12
I'm pretty excited
Because I'm going to make this short
Because I'm not even very soon
I'm on my way out
I am headed to LagerCon 3
It's going to be awesome
Podcasting session
I can't wait to meet everybody there
It's giving me very cool
I'm actually just going to check the website one more time
I'm going to make sure I got everything straight
November 6th
October 6th
Okay, got a missed it
All right, well, I'll see you guys at the blogCon 4
I'll get that one right, okay
Thank you, and good night
Of course, it's still sound a bit empty
In the podcast theater
But it's under construction
And a few weeks there's going to be some great material
On podcast theater Marquis
Delivered in podcast form
If you're a radio drama writer
If you're an actor
Part of a trip or a created a radio player story
If you want to be a part of restoring radio drama
Serials and soap operas
Comedy, classics horror, experimental theater
You're interested in the theater of the mind
Both guns had actually summoned up his own father
To accuse his son
Before all the work
And trust
Terrifying and wonderful
To watch
Return with us now
To those willing days of the afternoon
Podcast theater Marquis is the place for your audio trailers
Podcast theater
POD-C-S-T-T-H-E-A-T-R-E
Dotcom is where the dream plays out
Services ticketing
PayPal for your productions
Let me hear from you by email
Podcast theater.com
I'm not really sure what podcasts theater is all about
And I'd like that promo
I love it when you just post something on openpodcast.org
Or something shows up and actually says
Podcast promo
That's a good way to get my attention
I'll upload anything you got
If it comes out like that
Here's something from the mobile podcast
Hi, this is Ruffle Holliman
You're listening to my trio podcast
Now I just want to say a couple of people pointed me to Russell's recent podcast
I believe his wife was out of town
And I quite sure why
But in his longer podcast
He sounded somewhat inebriated
Mobilepodcast.org
From my palm to your pod
Nothing but net
I've got an abbreviated message to send out today
Don't have a whole lot of time to talk
But something came up and I thought that it was important enough to
A special abbreviated podcast
And this one goes out to anybody out there who's currently
Producing a podcast or perhaps contemplating
Producing one
That's you
One of the really great things I think we can all agree on
About this new phenomenon is the fact that it is completely unregulated
There's no government agencies involved
There's no rules
Basically there's nothing to stand between you
And what you have to say to the world
And right now that is just fantastic
But I wanted to alert everybody
To a situation that is brewing
That very well may change that
Okay
So this sounds serious
I know it has for me
I've already received a slap on the wrist
For a previous podcast of mine
And I felt it was worth
Warning the rest of you out there
The podcast in question
And I don't remember exactly which one it was
But I was discussing some of the funny things in the news
And I made a comment about the fact that
Well that my wife can't seem to cook anything
Unless cream of mushroom soup is in the recipe
And well
That's right she heard it
So I've already been put on notice
I am podcasting under a probationary license
I was fine two blouses in a pedicure
And told that one more interaction
And I'll be at the jewelry store
So anybody out there who's married
Or has a significant other
It may not be an FCC listening
But there certainly is someone
So watch the back
And
It's the spousal communications commission
Alright so this is Russell Hollis
This is my trio podcast
Thank you for tuning in
MobilePodcast.org
Please come check us out
From my palm to your pod
Nothing but net
I don't want your palm on my pod
Okay, I can't wait you say Russell
Definitely don't want that happening
You should hear is his full length podcast
It was funny he was home alone
And definitely
By his own admission
Someone a new brain
Good morning
Welcome to today's podcast
Brief Daily podcast
Offering words for the wise and the otherwise
I'm Scott Brenner and today is November 14th
Building on the positive comments
I got regarding my first podcast
Today's word is interstitial
Like that first podcast
We're disambiguation
Interstitial is one of those
Possibly pretentious
Specialized jargon words
Straight literal definition of interstitial is
The space between two states
In the context of the web
It refers to the page
Between pages
Two great sites
It frequently used them are Yahoo Games
And salon.com
They used them to show you an ad
Before you get to the stuff you really want
In the case of Yahoo Games you get to see an ad
Before you get to play a free game of back
Salon uses them the same way
You want to read this article
Watch this ad
Salons interstitials are pretty interesting
Because of the high concept multimedia
That they use in them
Often movie previews that kind of stuff
Or movie trailers
I guess that's the fancy word form
And the articles are pretty good on salon too
There are many other context where the text
We got interstitial
That's today's word
I guess we must have missed a little
Although I'm sure it was a word of the day
That's today's podcast.com
Subscribe to that from the ipod.org directory
Or go to the website and subscribe directly
I like that
I like a word of the day
And I did like today's word being interstitial
Interstitial
I wonder if
They came into interstitials on podcasting
I guess I would just be called a bad commercial
It sounds like everything there
You've got to watch this stop
So we can't have interstitials
Or maybe
Interstitials, maybe podcasts or the interstitials
Between your music on your iPod
Is that possible?
Got some exciting news
The Ken and Cindy show
Or should I say it's the Ken and Squip show
Two people who I used to work with
Ken Clark worked at MTV for God
He must have been there
For several years
As the VJ talent coordinator
Before even I got there
We worked together for the
Man
All that I was there for seven and a half years
But the last two years I think
I hired Ken away from MTV to come and work for me
And then when we started to grow our company
He moved into the company and he witnessed everything
All the way through
Going public
And Cindy
I hired her right off the internet
When we had just started on ramp
And we were looking for some people to help sell
And market with creative ideas
And so that was Cindy
So I know both these people fairly well
Actually I know them really well
Let's see
Ken, you know, Ken
Even used to babysit Christina
He's a member of the family, right?
Ken, right?
Yes, okay
He still speaks Dutch
He used to be at the house every single day
Ken, Ken
He always speaks his Dutch words
Anyway
And then Cindy
I know intimately because she puked on me once
But that's a story
Only she can tell
So they're podcasting
And they're in the directory
I think I put them under a comedy
Also under well they're in one of the what's new
You can you can find it easily
I potted out org
Let's just listen to a little bit of the Ken and
Squip show
I have a joke to tell you
Oh go ahead
What is perfectly adorable
Go to snoo
And there's seven tiny little dancing
But snow outside
And now lives
So we are sitting with us
There are nothing other regions of the universe
Spits the Ken and Squip show
When your house comes to the day
And Cindy the Squip
And now from our spanking new run
Last video from the upper west side of Manhattan
Here's Ken and Squip
Hello, Squip
Hello, Kenny
I should point out right here
That today's broadcast
Is brought to you courtesy of Skype
The latest and internet telephony
Yeah
That's Skype as in www.scipe.com
You might want to give a whirl
Because we're by coastal
So they're actually doing this old podcast via Skype
And listen to this first show
It's really funny
They actually had Patricia and I
With tears rolling down our cheeks
It's dry humor
Very dry humor
And just like this podcast
It's not safe for work
Yeah
One, two, three, four
If you could get a Martha Glenn's phone number
You know, I'm playing the cover of the one
So it's microphones off
It is?
Oh, hey Adam, how are you doing?
It's Brian from covervill.com
I wanted to drop you a quick line
To thank you first of all for
All the publicity you've got in covervill
On the last few days
I really appreciate it and my bandwidth
Is just through the roof
Thanks to you man, so appreciate it
I also wanted to
I want to let you know
How often do people thank you for sucking up all their bandwidth
Now that's a beautiful thing
Oh, that ended this year
I'm going to be doing a
Countdown kind of a casey case
Some style best covers
And for Countdown
Where I'm going to take emails
From anyone who wants to email me
With their favorite cover
And you can email me at Brian at covervill.com
Or you can post something on the weblog
Or you can call my voice mail
314-24-89957
Ring
So if any of your listeners want to
Send me their favorite cover
I'm going to tell you all the results
And my last five or six shows this year
Sometime in December at the end of December
Will be a Countdown
Of the best cover
And they don't have to be from
They can be from any time and it can be something I've played
Or something I haven't played
But just wanted to pass that on to
So you can pass that on to your listeners if you like
And
See if anybody's interested
But thank you very much
And love the daily source code
Boy, boy, boy
much cool. So cover real coming out with a countdown at the end of the year. All right. Well,
just let me know when I know if it's going to be on the cover real feed, if you're going to put
up a separate feed for it, but I will certainly let everyone know. And you know, people are using
the source code stuff for so many different things in different places. Hey, my name is David Johnson.
I'm from the Seattle area and got my first iPod about a month ago and stumbled across
the iPod or stuff while searching for nifty tricks and tools to do things to do with my iPod.
And I just wanted to thank you for the brainchild that you created that is podcasting. It's given me
things to do in the morning. You know, I read magazines a lot faster than I used to. And so now,
when I'm out of magazines, I have something to do during my morning constitutional. You've given me
fabulous reading time as it were in the bathroom. Thanks a lot. And also have to throw a plug in.
I just started my own podcast talking about computer security and updating that regularly as
issues come out. And it can be found at www.edave.org. That's the e-dave security news.
Thanks again for iPodding. And hey, have a good move, huh? See ya.
Hey, Adam Scott Westernman here with a quick note of thanks for the work you Dave Winner and
others have done to make the podcasting dream real. You're certainly inspired me.
I've revolved. The last couple of years I've hosted a website celebrating the history of my
favorite 1960s Detroit radio station, WKNR. You can check us out at kiner13.com. That's k-e-e-n-e-r13.com.
Well, since discovering the daily source code about a month ago, we've been podcasting
and it's been great fun. Plug our RSS file into your iPodder and check it out.
It's feeds.feedburner.com slash the kiner blog. Or you can click on the XML link at www.kiner13.com.
Now, do you hear something here? I mean, this is a radio guide. I love hearing this because radio
people are so hot on podcasting. And there's one thing that there's a huge benefit coming out of this
is that you have to understand that there are people who are trying to codify and archive
radio programs to such a meticulous degree because all that shit is normally lost. It's the same
with television. If you really want to go back and find something in archives, it's very, very
difficult. Same thing with podcasts. What's going to happen? Eventually, they're going to be
runoff onto a CD or whatever an archive, they may be about to stay around. I think these people
are really important. In fact, as a guy at Tom Schoeding in Australia who archives all of my stuff,
I never asked him to do it. I just have or just about to send off a box of 300 cassette tapes
of shows that I've done. He's going to digitize him and make him available online.
So when you run across someone who's doing this and you see how powerful it is being
able to do that on a podcast, it's great because we're building up an archive that otherwise
would not exist. Slash blog. We podcast every Saturday. And this week's show features an interview
with Andrew Reeve, the author of a classic book about the famous Paul McCartney Death Hokes.
Oh, cool. This is that Saturday. Hope you enjoy it. And by the way, one of these days,
we ought to do a simultaneous podcast via Skype. I'd love to have you as a guest and it would be
fun to share one piece of one of another's programs with our respective listeners.
That sounded nasty, but I think it's a good idea. Anyway, best regards from the
cornfields of the Midwest and I hope you're moved to England is going well.
And you know, they don't just grow corn and then corn fields, you know, I'm pretty sure
they grow more. So I have to come and visit you. John Oblang sent us an email, 11
the daily source code. He said, you played run your mouth. You run your mouth from the band
electric on the, what is this? October 20th show about 32 minutes into the show. So here's the
label. Those artists came from a lot of great music. It's from Solana Records at Solana Records.com.
And this is John. I, let me see, this is from John. There's also Eric Friedman. I guess these
are the guys who kind of run Solana Records. And you know what? You came back. You, you
figured it out. You're trying to promote your stuff. I'm very happy to play this song again. I
really like it the first time. You run your mouth and I'll run my business baby. This is
electric on the source code. Check it out at Solana Records.
You tell everybody I'm busted. You taught so much. You got me disgusting. You run your mouth.
I'll run my business brother. You run your juicy mouth and I'll run my business brother.
You run your juicy mouth and I'll run my business brother.
Always telling me what to do now. I wouldn't do that if I were you. You run your mouth.
I'll run my business brother. You clamp your liver lifts and I'll run my business brother.
You clamp your liver lifts and I'll run my business brother.
Tell everybody you're my pal. You why not telling me how to hand a mark now?
You run your mouth. I'll run my business brother.
You flat your face and I'll run my business brother.
Always telling me what to do. I wouldn't do that if I were you.
You jam your jaw. I'll run my business brother.
You jam your jaw and I'll run my business brother.
You tell everybody you're my pal. Why not tell me how to hand a mark now?
You run your mouth and I'll run my business brother.
I'll check it out. You clamp your liver lifts and I'll run my business brother.
You clamp your liver lifts and I'll run my business brother.
You tell everybody I'm busted. You talk so much. You got me disgusted.
You run your mouth. I'll run my business brother.
You run your mouth and I'll run my business brother.
Tell everybody you're my pal. You why not tell me how to hand a mark now?
You run your mouth. I'll run my business brother.
You run your mouth, I'll run my business brother, that's from Solana Records, it's
Solana Records.com, that's a electric.
Let's see, well we're well 40 minutes, oh we're about 45 minutes into the show,
this is where most people would expect me to stop, we're going to have at least
another 20 minutes of the source code, so you could pause it here and remember,
come back at 45 minutes, you can't set a bookmark, come back at 45 minutes
because still to come, some of George Carlin's new audio book, a bit of
whole week radio, a 1 minute tip, and then two excerpts from the Gilmore
Guying that played this weekend, so you can decide if you want to send it later,
that's what's coming up, oh and of course I'll be doing all of this in my
underwear.
So we're turning the whole podcast, we'll not podcasting, but audio
comment thing, I'm using the garage band, sound for, or and all that stuff,
actually, which I knew what you use because it always sounds really good, but if
it's just garage game, that would be really great, at the stupid mention I'm
going in my ear and heaped that thing, it just messes you up and he can't shut
it off once you start this thing.
So loving listening to the daily source, the way my name's Elana, I look
Dublin with my husband, Brendan, and our son, and obviously I don't sound
Irish.
We've been here for about five years and I don't sound like Madonna with her
fake little thing, we're just gonna be in here, we love and listening to
daily source code, he and I listen to it most days when he's working, he'll
be listening to it, no, listen to it, well I'm checking my email and stuff, well
he's listening to it and we're always cracking up and stuff, about things and I
just heard about the one about David Bowie and Patricia, which was hilarious, it is
really nice to know that you're larger than Bowie.
Boy, oh yeah, I mean, not to be some kind of pat on the back.
Yeah, not just in the back, yeah, boy, oh yeah, boy.
I think it's all good, I'm gonna work on doing my own podcast at some point, but I
want to do one about cooking.
I know there's one other person out there doing cooking, I haven't listened to it yet,
but I'm gonna check it out and see, but no, it's maybe he and I can join the forces or
something, but loving it, keep it up, it's all good, thanks a million, later.
Okay, Alanna, yeah, no problem, you're very welcome, cooking a podcast would be good,
you know the BBC where they were here, they're actually focusing on that and I went to
the directory, I think there's only one podcast, the vegan.com, the vegan podcast, that would
be very cool.
So yeah, thanks for the other comment, no, you did not at all sound like Madonna.
So I went into the iTunes Music Store the other day and I had already registered because
now the European Union can buy stuff from it and immediately what I went to the audiobooks,
I found out that audible.com actually provides all of the audiobooks in the iTunes Music Store,
and I got marketed immediately, I was very happy about it, it popped right up, that
George Carlin has a new book out, I didn't even know the book was out, let alone the
audiobook, it's titled, When Will Jesus Bring the Pork Chops, and I haven't heard,
I've only heard an hour, about an hour and 50 minutes, almost two hours of it, and the
whole thing is I believe about seven or seven and a half hours, it's the unabridged version,
and it is once again just totally beautiful, every so many years, George Carlin comes out
with his view on life, his take on what's going on, and it's current, and it's political,
and it's certainly politically incorrect, but you can't help but just wonder the power
of pure intellect that goes into what he writes and what comes out of his mouth, and when
he performs it for an audience or whether he's performing it in an audiobook, it comes across,
it really does, and I'm going to be picking snippets from his book for the next a couple days.
Question? Yes, question? Stop the show. Yeah, stop the show. Yeah, and the turning and everything
in the bathroom, so do you have all your stuff doing? All my stuff, shaving, creams, and things
that keep you young, and maybe I should put all the more to rise this? What should I put
in, and where should I put the stuff that I need? I better do that now then. Yeah, I'm going to
have to do this with this to go with this side. Okay, you want to help me? So, I'm going to ask for that.
I don't think you're all.
Yeah. Do you think I'm the heart? Yeah. I kind of both. Yeah, I'm a bandica sneller.
They've never been up, the audience has never been upstairs, huh?
The source code has never been upstairs upstairs in the castle. Certainly not in our bedroom.
Or the bathroom. Okay, okay, okay, okay. So, I need that, need that, need some guys pack.
Yeah, shaving cream, the mystery. I try to send me a message.
Okay. Maybe you think you're done?
I'm telling you, a blogger con.
No, think about this. It was like three or three of the people and we started eight o'clock in the
clock and we talked a lot and we had coffee and then what do you think? I don't know.
But how do you think that what was the experience for everyone who'd been drinking coffee and talking
and then look at the listerine? I don't know. What were you doing? People were stanky.
Oh, have people in there? Yeah, I'll take the people in there.
I tried to keep tabs on the phone. I had my mint. What else do I need?
Okay, so they can't take these, but how about this? I mean, this is going to dump that into
something and just keep leaving in here and take it. It's going to pack that right up like that and
they'll unpack it and we'll be with that stuff. Why don't you call me? Where's the top to that?
And you have to throw it out. Okay.
Okay, do I have a hair? A blow dryer? A blow dryer?
Where? I don't know.
Yeah. What about that? You packed up?
Yeah, everything's going to be packed up. You moved before everyone's gone found.
This, this they all going to pack. Yeah, that's fine.
But they got to pack. Okay, so they're not going to pack these.
Then what's dirty? Yeah, then what's packed? Christine has to pay no.
I'm going to take my belt before they pack that.
I'm going to pack this. I'm going to pack that. I'll have no house coat to wear.
I'll have no house coat. Can they pack that tomorrow?
She needs something to skip it. Can I just go finish my show? Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now, Christina. Christina, you better get something for you to wear tonight. Otherwise,
you'll have nothing because they're packing it all up and no mom said you don't have anything
for this evening yet and you better do it because I don't know for night close. Do you wear a
like to wear underwear and a t-shirt or what are you wearing?
You sure it's on your bag. Okay. Mom got the impression it wasn't. Sorry about that. Okay.
Here's George Carlin. I'm a modern man, a man for the Millennium digital and smoke-free.
A diversified multicultural postmodern deconstruction is politically anatomically and ecologically incorrect.
I've been uplinked and downloaded. I've been inputted and outsourced. I know the upside-down
sizing. I know the downside of upgrading. I'm a high-tech low-life, a cutting-edge state-of-the-art
bicostal multitasker and I can give you a gigabyte in a nanosecond. I'm new wave, but I'm old school.
And my inner child is outward-bound. I'm a hot-wired heat-seeking warm-hearted cool customer.
Voice-activated and biodegradable. A interface from a database,
medatabases, and cyberspace. So I'm interactive, a hyperactive, and from time to time, I'm radioactive.
Behind the eight-ball ahead of the curve, riding the wave, dodging the bullet push in the envelope.
I'm on point on task, on message and off drugs. I got no need for co-conspeed. I got no urge to binge
and purge. I'm in the moment on the edge over the top, but under the radar. A high-concept-low
profile, medium-range ballistic missionary, a street-wise smart bomb, a top-gun bottom-feeter.
I wear powerties, I tell powerties, I take powenaps, I run victory laps. I'm a totally
ongoing big-foot slam dunk-rain maker with a proactive outreach, a raging workaholic, a working
rageaholic, out-of-rehab, and in denial. I got a personal trainer, a personal shop, a personal assistant,
and a personal agenda. You can't shut me up, you can't dumb me down, because I'm tireless,
and I'm wireless. I'm an alpha male on beta blockers. I'm a non-believer, I'm an over-achiever,
laid-back, and fashion-forward, up front-down-home low-rent high-maintenance. I'm supersized
long-lasting high-definition fast-acting oven-ready and built-to-last. A hands-on-foot-loose knee-jerk
head-case prematurely post-traumatic, and I have a love child who sends me hate mail,
but I'm feeling, I'm caring, I'm healing, I'm sharing, a supportive bonding nurturing primary caregiver.
My output is down to my income, is up. I take a short position on the long bond,
and my revenue stream has its own cash flow. I re-junk mail, eat junk food,
I buy junk bonds, I watch trash sports. I'm gender-specific capital intensive user-friendly
and lactose intolerant. I like rough sex. I like tough love. I use the F-word in my email,
and the software on my hard drive is hard-core, no-soft porn. I bought a micro-wave in a minimal,
about an in-evan, and a megastore. I eat fast food in the slow lane. I'm told free,
bite-sized, ready-to-wear, and I come in all sizes. A fully equipped factory-authorized hospital
tested clinically proven scientifically formulated medical miracle. I've been pre-washed pre-cooked,
pre-heated pre-screen, pre-approved, pre-packaged post-dated, freeze-dried, double-wrapped,
and vacuum-packed, and I have an unlimited broadband capacity. I'm a rude dude, but I'm the real
deal. Lean and mean, cock-blocked and ready-to-rock, rough-tuff-and-hard-to-bluff. I take it slow. I go with
the flow. I ride with the tide. I got glide in my stride. Driving and moving, sailing and spinning,
driving and grooving, well-in-win-in. I don't snooze, so I don't lose. I keep the pedal to the
metal and the rubber on the road. I party-hardy and lunchtime is crunch time. I'm hanging in,
there ain't no doubt, and I'm hanging tough over and out. The cool is that George Carling,
the wind up today is Daily Source Code. We'll have to do the rest tomorrow.
We just had to go on that little tour upstairs to go pack up my toiletries. So what I'm going to
save for tomorrow is a Holy Radio, another audio comment, the one minute tip and the stuff that I
has, the excerpts that I pulled from the Go-Hor gang. So we're going to make it just about an hour for
a day. So tomorrow is another move day. As I said, multi-day sessions here.
So probably you have even less around us. Nothing to play with, as you always do, or keeping the
airport for laptops. Actually, because you just can't figure out about to be packed up as well.
As I always comment, and we really love the audio comments. Adam and Frey.com. Leave a comment
in the live.grade.com, or check out the new shows, the archives, and DailySource Code.com. I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye, bye, bye, everybody.