Hey, good afternoon. Good morning. We're a good evening, depending on where you are. Welcome to Trade Secrets. I'm
out. I'm curry in Belgium. I'm a parcel. Dave Winner at 5am in Seattle. You're such a trooper, Dave.
You're such a nice. I hardly even get a chance to like open my eyes. I don't want to lie to you.
Let's do a Trade Secrets. Yeah, that's so cool. All right. Let's do it. You got to do it.
The thing is we talk and then we, we, we, we jabber a little bit and then we're done. And then it's like,
I don't want to do a show. No, I got nothing left to say. So, yeah. It's like a turtle. Yeah. Well, it's good to do
one. We haven't done a Trade Secrets since podcasting became all the rage. Right. Which was last week.
Yeah, I'm pretty good. It's, it's good. How was your trip? You got back from San Francisco yesterday?
Yeah. It was really an easy trip. I found a hotel in just the perfect location.
It's easy into San Francisco, easy down to the peninsula. So I can get to Palo Alto. And I spent a lot of time at Stanford.
Working out the details. Got a whole bunch of things settled for blogger time three,
which is on as you know that ever six. We found room for everybody who was on the wait list.
Yeah, that's a lot of things. Well, I kind of figured at some point that when things, when the
registration slowed down that, you know, basically when they were really raging, I had to put the weight
list on because I didn't know how high it was going to go. And it was like middle august.
And we had to, you know, leave room for Stanford people because, you know, they're one of their goals was that they'd be participating in
firecons. So all things put together, said, okay, let's cut it off at 250 because we know we can do that.
And let's win a lot bigger than 250 to me.
Yeah, we're officially at 421 right now.
And that's pushing it because at the same time we're 421.
We're not that high in terms of dollars and we're going to need to feed people to provide them
investments and mundane stuff like we have to pay for to clean the rooms.
And we have to get Wi-Fi, right?
Got it.
We have Wi-Fi on it.
And the webcast, which you'll be very interested to know, we've probably talked about that actually.
Well, we haven't talked about the fact that Doug K has generously offered to take care of most of it.
Well, it turns out that I don't think that's the way it's actually going to work.
Well, it does news, you better tell me what's going on.
Well, it's interesting.
I mean, I talked with Doug before we went, you know, basically Doug was on the speaker phone at the meeting at Stanford.
And so I was there with John Harrison, who was the AV guy at Stanford and Lauren Gellman, who is with the their Institute for the Internet and Society,
which is the Stanford counterpart to Berkman Center.
And there, Lauren is like the Stanford person who I'm working with on this conference.
And so Doug has a stick that really works.
You know, I mean Doug's IT conversations and coming up the other end of Doug's work is going to be like one beautiful, you know,
every regard of beautiful product, you know, podcast, what audio, whatever you want to call it.
I mean, it's thinking of Bob and MP3 and lots of different formats and it's going to stream and whatever.
However, only one of his, he's only going to live stream one of the three set concurrent sessions.
Right.
So that's problem number one or opportunity number one is, but the other sessions would be recorded.
Pardon me.
All the sessions would be recorded though.
I don't see, you know, if we can do it, I don't see why not webcast all the sessions too.
If we can, I want to try to do that.
Okay.
Last time, we had a deal with advanced net with Jeff Jarvis and they had huge capacity for webcasting.
And, you know, at the very last minute, we thought, okay, let's ask Jeff Jarvis and Jeff said, yeah,
and they helped us out and we were doing like, you know, huge amounts of webcasting through his network.
So that was good.
And they also, it was really interesting because I had been trying to explain to Doug about how the hobbyists decided this is so important.
You know, but here we are, we're doing podcasting and, you know, what is podcasting, but amateur radio, right?
And it's very much like blogging is amateur journalism, right?
Right.
And so, but Doug thinks in terms of professional and he thinks that what he's doing is enough and some sense it is enough.
But it's not for me.
I want to get this thing wide open for anybody, for any for you and for any of your podcasting.
We're going to have a lot of AV geeks there.
And it's just a podcast.
Right.
And, you know, I'm not going to tell them that hey, you know, well, Doug's doing a professional job and, you know,
therefore, blah, blah, blah, you know, because that's, you know, they're going to go, well, Dave, what happened to the blogging religion here?
And I'm going to go, uh, good point.
So, and what really convinced me of this was that the Stanford people asked me about that after the meeting was over.
This is what about the random people who want to, you know, record this or whatever.
And I said, right on, exactly.
You know, and that's the, that's where why holding these conferences at universities is such a good thing to do because
universities think that way.
They, they're not looking necessarily for the maximum policy.
And especially at a place like, you know, Stanford Law School and a Berkman Center.
It's, you know, it's, it's the internet for the people basically.
So we're going to, we're going to try to come up with something where we're not only just
going to record and do his usual very great job, but that it's also going to be wide open.
There'll be a way for anybody to tap into the audio out in all three rooms.
Really?
Those are stuff.
Yeah, well, that's what we want to do.
Yeah.
And they just have to work with us in advance.
That's going to be the requirement, okay?
So how do people get in touch with it?
If they want to, if they want to help out and get in touch with an advance.
I, I'd like them to get in touch with you.
And then you tell me what your people, you tell me what they,
I need more email.
Thank you.
Yeah, you do.
I was thinking about you, right?
I was thinking, I didn't get any of that email.
You know, I don't get enough of the new podcast.
The please add me to the directory emails.
Oh, add it if you keep it.
If you start whining, they're going to stop sending it to you.
It's a little secret.
You have to say you love it.
I love it.
Now I got to, for other people already working on the directory with me.
They're, they're making their OPML branches and it's working.
So I'm offloading.
You know, I want, that's on my list.
Totally.
I was listening to that on the plane from, from San Francisco to Seattle last night.
And I was so proud of you out in that you like totally understand and can explain the whole concept of these included directories.
Well, that's my dream.
Now that, but now that I'm actually doing it, I understand it.
And it's so simple.
Yeah.
Still a little, you know, unless you're using radio user land, I haven't really come across a tool that does it exactly right that really exports.
Well, perfectly.
Now, that leaves me right into my next item on my list.
Oh, wait.
Don't tell me, I said, I said, didn't do something for you.
Damn.
Totally perfectly.
It couldn't be better.
Alright.
It really couldn't be better.
Okay.
I was listening to your daily source code last night as I was saying on the plane and heard you go into the story of OPML.
And, you know, but a lot of people don't know.
I mean, OPML is a very popular format in RSS aggregators.
Yeah.
Because in radio, we chose to use that as our way of listing, you know, sets of feeds.
And radio was pretty influential in the early days, so basically everybody did the same way.
And, but what people don't know is that as you were so well-telling them,
is that OPML is actually a very rich format which can do more than that.
And it can do, you know, nested directories.
And it can do this thing called inclusion.
And it's also the underlying format of the radio outlineer.
And here's the deal at him.
We open source that code.
Okay.
And that's all part of frontier.
Aha.
Yeah.
Radio builds out of frontier.
I mean, that's a little secret, basically.
There's no such thing.
There's no separate code based for radio.
All of the C source code for radio was also released as open source.
And that includes the outlineer.
It includes all the OPML code.
It includes a complete TCP stack, including HTTP.
So that, you know, moving these outlines around is something that, and providing a user interface for editing.
And editing them is something that radio does so natively that, you know, it's hard to stop it from doing it, basically.
So the, you know, a same kind of thing could be done with that that was done with the iPodder.
We could get a project going to create, you know, the easiest to use outlineer out of the code base that's there.
And it would be Windows and Mac.
And, uh, and could, of course, be ported to any platform, including like Linux.
And we would have the bootstep for something that will be so incredible when it actually works.
In other words, that this can go in so far beyond, I mean, I don't want to say it because podcasting so incredible, but it can go beyond podcasting.
And into a whole sort of knowledge tree for the universe.
Well, it's really exciting because, you know, when you start a directory and I've started many directories and then people send you links, you know,
it's, it becomes a real drag to maintain it, you know, and if you're not, if people send you an addition and it's not up in the same day, you know,
people get bored and then it's just not alive. And by, you know, this delegation, which is also decentralization,
and, you know, gives no one any real power, certainly not an decentralized power, but only over, you know, whatever tree they're working on,
just the offload, and you can see the possibilities immediately.
Immediately, you see, oh, well, duh, of course, this is how this supposed to work.
And it's so simple, it really is.
Well, it's the outline equivalent of the link. And, you know, and it, and outline, you know, it's just that's all we do,
but follow the grain of the outline and say, okay, what would a link look like in this space?
And if you go back to the outline as we did in the 80s, this would be the equivalent of what we call cloning,
so that an item and all of its descendants can appear in as many places as you want to.
They also call them file aliases in the Macintosh and they call them shortcuts in Windows.
So, it's the concept of a pointer. It's a computer science thing that they always seem to have mystical powers when you use them,
and this is no exception.
Is that like a send link as well?
Pardon me?
Is that like a send link?
I don't know what a send link is.
Okay, that's in unix where you, you can say, okay, this file path, it's a symbolic link, it's not real,
but if you point to it, it'll take you to the real file.
Is that the same thing?
Yeah, that's totally like it.
Okay, got it.
Yeah, you see everywhere in user talk, the user talk scripting language, it's the address symbol,
general, it's a pointer.
So pointers are like major, big deal, but having them in an interactive product like an outline or
where the outline or then can, you know, try expanding one of these things when you open it up in your outline or
there.
Yeah, it's quite spinning one of your links and see what happens.
Yeah, it's like the outline or something.
Yeah, it just keeps going.
If you go on this many levels, steep as you want.
Now, here's something else that people might not know.
Is that, okay, Adam, you can include their OPML in your directory, and that will have
the effect of including their directory in yours.
But they can also include your directory in theirs.
Right.
So that if they think they have, you know, this is where the ego starts coming in, right?
And so people go, well, geez, I'm not going to be subordinate to Adam.
You know, everybody's good as Adam.
Unfortunately, or fortunately, or whatever, that happens a lot in the computer business.
It's also true, just, you know.
Yeah, well, it's true, but you know, sometimes following your pride is a good thing to do so that it's
for the greater good.
But, okay, so even if that isn't going to happen, then what can happen is if you've got
the master directory for the pod space that include, they can include your directory.
And there's because you have an OPML rendition of yours.
Right.
And when they do that, when they do that, they will also be including everything that you included.
So, there's nobody.
It's just like saying, nobody has the top homepage on the web.
Right?
Nobody has the top homepage directory.
And this is a major, major thing, because it's this thing really catches on.
Then we can get directories on every subject.
And we can also get two or two directories on every subject.
Yeah, it's amazing how amazing this role hasn't happened for weblogs.
You know, the people who have weblogs have directories.
You know what, it was the order which things happened.
Actually, was what made it not happen for weblogs.
Because before we had any idea, this idea post-stage weblogs,
this outline, you know, directory stuff came after weblogs.
Right.
But at the time, it came online.
There were already tens of thousands of blogs.
And so, people had learned to accept complete chaos.
Okay.
Then Google had come along and had been doing a pretty good job of indexing them.
And there were directories like Yahoo and Google has directories.
Oh, yeah.
And all kinds of directories with them.
Yeah.
I presume lots of politics.
And politics.
Yeah.
Lots of politics in there.
But what was it going to say?
Yeah.
It could go a lot further than simply just for podcasting,
to be for everything.
And you have three versions.
You being the daddyo of, you being the daddyo of the outline.
I heard you say it about 10 minutes ago.
This must be like the ultimate dream to have one big outline,
traversing the entire universe.
Yeah.
Oh, we called it the World Outline.
I mean, that was done when we first put it all this together.
It was like the World Wide Web and there's a World Outline.
So in a sense, there's one outline.
But in there are an incident number of ways of picking it up.
And yeah, you know, I just talk about frontier being my life's work.
That's actually not true.
If this thing happens, then I'm going to hang them up.
Boy, because I haven't gotten another idea in me.
Well, it's funny because if you look at podcasting, which, of course, is built on RSS,
which is at least a corner of your life's work.
Yeah.
And what's happening with the directory now, it seems like it's exploding.
And I'm just sitting here waiting.
And I've even seen people write about it.
Okay, the hype will be over in three weeks.
But, and I'm just going by bandwidth consumption.
Let's just make that an easy one.
It's, I know what you're going to say.
So I'll just tell you how much I'm pushing out per day.
It is now up to 37 gigabits a day.
And I'm still doing the same amount of shows.
Well, so, you know, of course, you're supposed to say,
Hey, we need a bit to our end.
Oh, it's very good.
Hey, Dave, I got some, I got some listener feedback here.
A message for you, actually.
Yeah.
Yeah, hold on, I'll play.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Hi, Dave.
This is Aldo Costignata from Medfield, Massachusetts.
And I'm sending this because I wanted to reply in a way
to Dave Winner's comments that you out on your show the other day
about a link being one of the fundamental components of the web.
I got me thinking, and I guess I've been thinking about this before.
I heard that that really one of the kind of defining characteristics
when I got that perhaps we don't think about it.
Perhaps this is something to be the community out there that's particularly
the open source community thinks about a lot.
But is that the web provides an incredibly efficient way
to measure ideas, to measure the value of ideas very early
before without requiring huge capital investment.
And I think this notion really if it hasn't been discussed much
is one that's really worthy of focus and discussion,
because I think it has huge implications, particularly for those people
that are developing just for the love of it.
You know, the iPod or community in essence.
And that if the community can harness the value of an idea
or can measure the value of an idea really early on,
and can measure that throughout the life of an idea,
then I think that that can give those people that devote themselves
to it a lot of freedom in terms of finding interesting ways
to get financing basically to get paid for what they do
without, at the same time, having to give up the freedom
in which they do it to, you know, they don't have to work for a corporation.
Things like that, that's the core concept.
And I guess what I want to do is just put that concept forward
and see if there's interest in really trying to understand it
or to find out if it's already something that's been thought about
and dismissed and just put it out there.
My email address is Aldo Aildio at the world,
so if this ever gets out to your community
and there's kind of an interest in researching it more,
it's something that I'd actually really like to dedicate some time
to research, because I think it could have really fundamental impact
on the way we view open source and distributed development
all of those things.
All right, thanks a lot.
Could you hear that Dave?
Yeah, I heard the whole thing.
I think it's bright.
I'm not sure about it, it can generate financing,
but, you know, there's a reason why the web
has attracted all the hippies, you know, because, you know,
as she's lighting up one, God, which I mean,
yeah, I'm right there.
And where is the gadget?
This is what we don't talk about,
but let's talk about it anyway.
Okay, but, and Gadget was reviewing trade secrets.
Yeah, and I thought they're doing a great job,
and, you know, and, you know, support what they're doing.
I'm a big fan of him, Gadget.
And they said that, you know, basically, this is the best form of radio,
because Adam's always doing bond hits on the,
and they kind of, they kind of said, I'm doing it too,
but I want to get that really clear.
I'm not.
You wouldn't live in a country where you've got to jail for that shit.
So the next thing I don't want to hear is the DEA knocking down
my door going, uh, DEA.
What do you do?
Dave's not here, man.
Dave's not here.
Anyway, to go back with, what was just me?
I'll know, I'll know.
I'll know.
I'll know, Castaneda.
Yeah, I mean, the, the web was about disintermediate,
or the internet is about disintermediation,
which means, the fancy words, which means, uh,
getting rid of the intermediaries.
And, um, you know,
not that we didn't need intermediaries, because we did.
I mean, in the era of centralization,
it was all about intermediaries, um,
you know, the big TV networks and radio networks.
Um, you know, where do you get to news from the big airlines?
Uh, everything had to be big in order for everybody to have it.
And the internet says the information doesn't have to be like that.
I don't have to be big in order for anybody to have the information that I produce.
So as a result, you know, for the first 10 years,
which is really about where we're at now,
first 10 years of the web,
we were focusing on text because the pipes were, you know,
that's all we could actually handle.
Pretty narrow.
Right.
And then the tools, the content development tools,
the editing tools, the, you know,
all the stuff that we're using now.
Well, it isn't new.
It got really affordable.
Oh, I tell people this all the time, Dave.
I mean, I, I invented the,
yeah, 40,000 dollar website.
You know, that was, that was, yeah.
And why?
Because it was people power.
Guys writing code by hand and writing it in note pad and VI.
And, you know, now it's the, the 40 dollar tool literally can do the same.
If not better.
Right.
And so money now is, well, it is still an object.
It's less of an object.
And, um, and that means that we can now try to do radio.
And, you know, Adam, we've been waiting trying to get this to bootstrap.
You know, like I did a project last year with Chris Lydon,
um, who was one of my colleagues at Berkman Center.
And Chris did a series of interviews with bloggers and, you know,
luminaries and these great stuff.
And we produced an RSS 2.0 seed with includes enclosures.
And, you know, people, some people listen to it,
but it wasn't like daily source code.
And it didn't take off like, you know, Dave slutters stuff
or, uh, any of the things that we're seeing.
And, you know, it may be that it wasn't a critical master.
Maybe that time wasn't right.
No, I didn't.
There was no eye powder.
I think Chris Lydon could do a great job now,
if he would continue to release stuff on his RSS feed.
And that, I think that's the only thing that happened today.
Is that right?
I think it was more than that.
I think the eye powder was instrumental,
but I think you doing one every day, right,
a very big difference.
Are you doing?
Yeah, hold on.
My battery just died.
Talk amongst yourselves for a second.
I just got a...
No, I'll tell.
Hold on a second.
Let me grab my bag.
Hold on.
Okay.
Maybe I should place the music.
Well, Adam is out for it.
And, uh, I haven't had something.
I think I has something to do with this.
This is all about casting is all about.
Don't tell Adam that I did this.
Here we go.
They're good.
I don't know.
Come on, guys.
Come on.
It's become my favorite song.
I live that one so much.
Are you back?
I don't know.
I've got to make a turn this thing off.
Anyone there?
No, hold on.
I'm here.
Are we recording?
Yeah.
I was funny.
I'm here.
I thought you missed a turn this up.
Hold on.
I just got to replace the battery.
My transmitter.
Hold on.
How cool.
We have to hold on while he's battery.
Yeah, Doug K is going to interview me at four o'clock my time.
So I had bought new batteries.
We'll ask him not to listen to trade secret.
No way.
Oh, shit.
Just hit my head on the left.
All right.
Now, wait a minute.
I was going to say, oh, no.
You know what happened Dave this morning?
I was up early because I was interviewed by the Australian Broadcast Corporation.
Or is it company?
You are such a video player.
I am.
I'm bending over and saying, come on.
Are you Aussie?
I bought me here, baby.
So, so I looked it.
I was looking over the iPod or dot org site.
I did something really cool.
I actually rewrote history.
There's a section there that just called the history page.
And it was kind of like just a running ramble of thoughts.
And I've been telling the story so often for the past week to, you know, in interviews.
Then I decided, let me just write down that story because that's the story.
You know, and I could embellish a little bit more.
But you should look at it because I went back and I traced the web blogs.
I traced the web blog postings.
I traced everything that happened.
And it was, and I actually, and I wrote about this.
I said, there's a couple things I did because I knew that I really wanted this thing, this iPodter.
And I wasn't doing daily source code until I built iPodter.
And in fact, the name daily source code at the time was chosen specifically to appeal to developers.
That makes sense, right?
And so I released the iPodter script.
And then I actually blog this.
And I said, hey, I'm just going to produce this every single day.
So you all have something y'all, so y'all have y'all have something to work with.
They talk like that in the middle.
No, that's how developers talk.
The y'all talk y'all y'all.
So that's how it happened, Dave.
And that was the difference really.
I mean, that's what it was.
It was just the people who looked at the script and said, oh, that's interesting.
I can do that better.
That's what it was.
And I put a link to that.
Yeah, did you see the history page?
I do.
I think I represented your your contributions correctly.
If not, let me know.
Yeah, I'm still really trying to take the back seat here because, you know,
it's you're doing, I mean, I don't want to stroke you too much,
but you're doing such a good job here.
And every technology would be good to have somebody who sort of like,
you know, doing the art of it, the content.
And then somebody else is sort of thinking about, okay,
well, what's the next step in the infrastructure?
That's why we're a great team.
That's why we're good.
Yeah, no.
We're good.
We're, but we should say that.
We should, but we should say we're good.
It's a, it's a blogger con.
We should hand them out too.
I do.
Hi, we're good.
I'm a blogger.
I'm good.
You can go with that.
No, I'm a pot actually.
Doug K had a really cool thing.
He was trying to figure out the, the verbiage of pot casting.
Oh, man.
Um, and so he asked the question, well, what, okay,
pot casting must be the creation of this, right?
What we're doing right now, or we're getting ready to do a podcast.
Because the podcast is when you wind up and you throw it, right?
Yeah, you get this.
The podcast is, we're pod pulling.
Right.
And so just what he came.
Yeah, right.
So I'm going to go there with.
So he said, then, what is listening is listening also podcasting?
Or is it podcasting?
No.
It's a podcasting, exactly.
And so, and it's funny thing.
What is this that I had bought that?
You bought that domain name.
Yeah.
I remember a podcast, and then I, and I still have it.
I have an interesting one.
I have a, I have a really, really good one.
But always use, I kept the still name for many, many years.
It's, uh, clambumping.org.
It's a little bit like the bad thing that I've never, my clambumping.
So somebody asked me, I, you both got this interview too.
I bet you did.
Which one?
The yesterday, eric at, uh, OGR.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Written, written interview.
No, I actually do those voice. I never do written interviews.
Oh, he sent me a whole bunch of questions. I was the only written one I did. I figured.
And that's actually based on that.
How are they?
I what?
That's the best news holiday. I write all day anyway.
So I think I have been doing it here.
Right. So yeah.
I spoke to him.
Yeah.
He has some good questions about making it.
So yeah.
Well, he asked if there was a connection between Howard Stern and podcasting.
It was also happening at the same time.
And I said, you know, well, it's good. Basically we're all spreading out.
We're trying out a lot of the ideas.
I honestly think that the satellite radio is going to catch on to podcasting and use it effectively
before they get Howard Stern.
Oh, really? I think it'll happen before.
Yeah. Well, before 2006.
Why not?
Yeah.
They have a distribution system.
Right. I mean, can you imagine having XM radio for your home?
And connecting it up to your computer.
And, you know, doing the TV thing from your computer.
Or conversely.
Conversely, having what they should have a channel that does nothing more than
subscribes to five different feeds and just broadcast whatever it comes up against.
That would be cool too.
That's exactly exactly right. Why not?
Or, you know, give you a guy like Adam Curry, right?
I mean, do you have a track record for doing this stuff?
Yeah.
Give me a goddamn channel.
Put me on the bird, baby.
Actually, I was just going to give you a hundred million dollars.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me retrieve that statement.
Look at me saying.
Oh.
Channel the bird.
100 million dollars.
I'm calling NASA.
We're blessing off our own damn spaceship.
Hey, don't get it started.
I like the way you open the business.
Would you shuttle for 75?
I could barely do it.
I should probably work that out with them.
Maybe we will pick cash for like 65 if you want to go for that.
You get cash.
Yeah, right.
If you want to tax three, tax three, get it for 50.
I want to blow the doors off of broadcasting.
That's what I want to do.
This is, I think I'm finally finding my life's mission.
I mean, I was listening.
Did you hear the Steve Wazniak speech at?
No, I haven't.
Well, it's keep talking about it.
Yeah.
Well, it was, it was podcasts.
IT conversations put it up.
And I sat there listening as Wazniak,
who can't be much older than I am.
What is he easy about your age?
So about 49?
No.
He's older than me.
Probably.
Yeah.
Because he was out of your heart.
He was doing the same things as a kid that I was doing.
I was reading Tom Swift Jr.
By the way, it's been, I've been keeping this secret.
But hey, this is straight secret.
So I'm going to keep it this secret for a long time.
I've secretly been doing an audio book of Tom Swift.
Because they're all on the Gutenberg project.
These books are more than 100 years old.
So of course, that would mean that Wazniak,
that old too.
But he also used the radio shack 101 projects in one.
You know, all that shit.
I was like, my God.
But I had, you know, at a certain point,
it switched to broadcasting when I was about 15.
I built my first transmitter.
He was also a ham radio operator and built stuff.
And just about when I got to the end and the,
and the or and the logic gates,
is where I went off into broadcasting.
And I think I made a mark.
It may be a hairy one.
I made a mark in broadcasting.
Certainly on the MTV and on the radio stations around the world.
And then it was the internet.
I was right at the beginning of,
yeah, I was certainly one of those responsible for commercializing the net.
Whether that's a good or bad thing is up in the air.
I think it's good personally.
And you know, and then I just had like five years of
dicking around and nothing really,
you know, learn how to fly helicopters.
That's nice.
And it's, you know, tried to start a couple things
and lost some money here and there and made a little bit.
And, you know, but just became the user,
which is what I promised myself.
And then all of a sudden boom, you know,
here's, oh, wait a minute,
there's something else.
And I'm kind of leading the charges.
It's really exciting.
You know, this may be what I'm supposed to do.
That's what you did in the last.
That's what you did in the last five years you learned.
You are assimilated and, you know, learned how to do.
We all did.
I mean, you know, five years ago, five years ago,
I had never, you know, never once the standard.
I mean, I had once things would become standards, right?
But I didn't know how to, you know,
how to get other people to do what I was doing.
And to start tripped over that, you know,
that basically, if you want somebody to do something,
then you need to do it first.
And that's the big secret.
You know, you can't stand back and say,
well, I'll do this and everybody else would you all just do that?
No, it doesn't work.
They simply won't do that.
They won't do that.
They won't do what you're doing.
You know, say, okay, well, who do you do?
We'll just copy you and whatever.
And, you know, that was the first quite frustrating
because I said, well, she's already doing that.
Let me do that.
You do something else.
And then I realized that, that,
okay, I just learned to accept that.
Okay, number one.
Yeah.
And then I started when I, when the thought popped in my head is,
I wish everyone would do X,
and then all I did was start doing X,
and seeing how great it was.
You know, I can't believe it.
And I always meant it.
You know what I mean?
It wasn't like I was saying that.
I wanted to do it.
Right, I was doing it saying it was great
because I was really, you know,
well, what I was doing.
And so excited and trying to get everybody else excited about it.
And so, you've now done that.
And that's, you know, that's something to be quite proud of.
I mean, you actually got people to copy you.
And that is how you create these swells of activity.
And then the question is, does it have legs?
And I'm sure this does.
I mean, I was sure, I was sure it had legs,
and we were sitting in a hotel in New York.
Yeah, was a 99, wasn't it?
Yeah, I knew.
I think it was 2000, but, you know, it was like,
when the light bulb went on for me,
and I, oh shit, that's a good idea.
You know?
So, so, how did this like, hand-dude?
Yeah.
Like, celebrity.
Did he figure this?
Yeah.
You're, you're, your star had to fade a little bit before.
I, a, before it can really shine.
Well, before they're ready to let you have another career.
You see, that's true.
That's true.
Say that about you anymore.
They don't hear that.
You know, they don't say okay, well, Adam Curry.
I'll hear you forgot with the hair.
You don't hear that.
But, sorry.
Not much.
It's still around.
Yeah.
It's a reference.
It's like, a beat.
I have, yeah.
It's a beat.
But, I have to explain to some people who you are,
and what your background is, people,
and just you didn't know.
You think, well, do yousware were they in the 80s, right?
They obviously weren't around what you were doing and where they forgot or that's also possible
I forgot a lot about the ages to
Well, you don't think they say about the 60s if you remember to be weren't there
So I've been listening and I've been subscribing to the coma 1000 news feed. Oh, that's so awesome
Yeah, I got one that I want to play. Here's a short news story. These are great because about 45 minutes and they come in neatly bundled pack
45 seconds. Sorry. Yeah, this is this is a this is from her who gives us tips on how to use our computers and as it may be left
But I you know
This is also a good way to you know
Well, I'll talk about content routing in a second
But here's a herb with is a computer tip. Oh, don't click that link the opt-out link on spam email messages clicking it won't do any good
An according to message labs a leading email security service. It may let a hacker take over your computer
The spammers are putting special code in those click here to opt-out links the moment you click on it. They turn your computer into a zombie
Bob Sullivan technology correspondent for MSNBC says they do that by hiding a Trojan horse program on your system
Once this Trojan is installed on your computer, they can do anything with your computer that you could do
They can send out as much spam as they want for your computer, and that's probably why they're doing it, but they can also move around the internet using your computer
They could use your computer to attack another computer and of course they could feel all your personal information from it. So how do you protect yourself?
MSNBC's Bob Sullivan says the safest thing you can do is to read your email and plain text and not HTML format
You should also have your web browser in a high security setting. Keep your anti-virus software up to date
You put a ginormous condom all over yourself and you're computer
And ever click the unsubscribed link in a spam message and that's today's tip. I'm her voice bomb the consumer man looking out for you
On Como 1000 news. I love that. I feel so much safer. The herb is looking out for us
Oh, it's a good guy
He's great, but he's saying all the right things
I got to go and see those guys. They're local. I'm here in Seattle there in Seattle. We've got to find that. We've got some soulwriters here
But they're doing is so incredibly cool
I want to tell you a little story. Yeah, go for it. It's a real much time
We had the Thursday evening meetings at Berkman. We would do them every Thursday
There's open meeting for all blotters, not just people at Harvard, but just anybody in the area
And people that would come in town and they'd come by and see us. One of the regulars of those meetings is Lisa Williams
And we were talking about, that's a good example of what we're talking about
The nature of the web came up or blogs or whatever
And she said that blogs are like, you know, food that you can eat
Like, okay, like food you can eat with chopsticks
And asked for an explanation said, well, you know, if you look at what
You know, Chinese food is, you know, is that they design their food
So that it can be eaten with chopsticks and you stop and think about it and it's true
There are these little chunks. They're already pre-sliced everything's already free
They just pick it up and put it in your mouth, which isn't like Western food
Which is designed to be eaten with a fork and knife
So you like the steak is like that, right?
And then she was saying that the blogs are like Chinese food
That way, they're these little morsels, little, you know, those standalone things
And that's what struck me about the kamo, you know, podcast seed
Is that what they're doing like you said in your daily source code
Is that, okay, they're now giving me the daily news in a form
Where, okay, if I'm not interested, just hit the fast forward
But then I'm onto the next one.
Now that's a revolution.
And the next step, of course, is, you know, subscribe to the general interest feed here
Or the sports feed or, you know, that's the next step
Yeah, it's, it's putting a lot more, the user is a lot more in control
And yet there's nothing about it that says you can't like make money doing this
There's another business models are negated
However, they will have to deal with more competition
Because there's not this scarce resource called bandwidth
I mean, or frequency effects or effects or effects
Spect malfeventor compltement likely
Let's not turn, sorry, I'm not young, you can jersey
But yeah, it's wonderful they took the lead
In what you're doing with the wg vi8 Boston, that's fantastic
Yeah, there there's a lot more of that, it's so exciting
I got another, kind of audit comment
Have you ever listened to the Don and Drew show?
I've only heard clips from New Yorkshire, I had not listened to it yet.
That's funny, man.
You really have listened to it.
Yeah, it's funny.
You know, they wind up talking about how, you know, Dawn is saying, okay.
So when you sit down to pee, you know, does your wiener get wet?
And it's like, it's like, and they're really honest.
These are really honest ones.
He was a question thought everybody's mind, right?
I mean, yeah, I guess so.
You know, it would have been a war in Iraq if we knew the answer is out.
Hold on.
Here's a comment, Drew sent in.
Actually, it was probably for the source code, but since this is my recording
Venture for today, we'll use it here.
Hey, Adam, it's Drew from the Dawn and Drew show.
I just, that I try out this audio comment type of thing.
It just seems like the cool thing to do these days.
But I was checking out your podcast today and you were referencing
What's this name?
Go Hagen.
He doesn't for us.
Yeah, Adam, it's Michael Go Hagen.
Michael Go Hagen.
Okay, here's some feedback.
Michael Go Hagen, he had, you know, he was mentioning the whole genre thing.
And I just thought that was really interesting because I hadn't really
realized that it was even an issue.
I had been doing it since the,
I think I did it from like the third show.
I started adding all the metadata and then I went back in and
read it all the metadata, even back to the very first show.
But he grabs all of them as it was going through the metadata,
the ID3 tags inside iTunes.
I realized that you could type in the genre tag.
So I just went ahead and put podcast.
And I've been doing it ever since.
And I just think it's, you know, it's pretty cool that I was just like
forcing that genre upon anybody and everybody's iTunes.
So interesting that, you know, that was what you guys are talking about.
And, you know, I'd been doing that and not that I'm like the pioneers
that or anything.
I just think it's cool.
I think it's totally appropriate.
And we should definitely force our agenda on the masses.
So yeah, hey, awesome show.
Thanks again for, I mean, you inadvertently plugged our show again
by playing that podcast from Canada.
All right.
So then he goes on to thank me profusely.
But these are just users, man.
These are just people who are just digging you doing this.
You got to be careful.
I found out the back calling people users.
They think they don't like it.
I would like to see themselves.
Yeah.
They don't necessarily see themselves that way.
The other thing I was thinking about is listening.
I didn't hear most of what he said.
Because the assistants are getting ready.
Yeah, okay.
You must be doing an iPod or skin right now.
No, I have everything off.
I've almost shared drugs or disconnected.
I'm standing on a list.
I'm probably doing one there.
Yeah, you probably.
You're aggregating your aggregator's sucking shit down.
I think Adam, it's getting pretty close to time for some awards.
Yeah, I think you're home page.
That's the thing.
Well, now I'm not saying this is just, you know.
The reason is that people mostly, we talk about this with developers, right?
You know, what a developers want.
90% of what a developer wants is to be appreciated.
That's part of knowledge to be seen.
You know, it's a visibility through their creativity, which is the best way for somebody to be visible.
You know, you don't want somebody to be, then,
to have to create visibility by, you know, flaming you on a mail list.
Right?
Right.
So, you know, so we're still in good viable hands here.
And maybe we can figure out a way, you know,
can't just be, you know, I don't know how we do it.
But it'd be great to sort of give everybody
who's done a podcast right now,
some way of being part of something, like an initiation or, you know,
because these are the good energy people.
These are people who are going to remember when it was wonderful.
National association of hardcasters.
That's not the, M.A.
M.A.
I'm going to the map for the meeting.
That's a big show.
No.
Left work out.
Yeah.
What are you doing at or around bloggerCon or how it has to happen after bloggerCon?
Because that's okay.
That's okay.
Okay.
We're going to have a podcast.
This is what Doug K asked for.
We got to do it.
We're going to have a podcast just in our side.
There you go.
Okay.
Yeah.
It'll be a good podcast.
It'll be recorded about 80,000 different ways.
No doubt they'll be a record of that one.
It's like a jambory on the air.
Everybody.
I have a question for you.
I gotta ask you this.
You were going about your college radio experience saying,
Everybody.
Right.
Where the fuck does that come from?
Well, what happens a lot?
How would stir that way of pronouncing it?
Oh, that way of pronouncing it?
Yeah.
It's because that is a takeoff of a takeoff of a takeoff on the way old fashioned
announcers talk and what you notice in the radio business.
Guys, on the real radio, not podcasting with broadcasting.
They're always, you know, you'll set stand next to them in the studio and listen.
They're screaming most of them like everybody.
It's a W-T-Z-E-1 100.
We'll take all the 100 out.
What did it do for D-Z-1 100?
That's from D-E-1 100.
Right.
So.
I've had this.
Wait, hold on a bit.
While I regain my exposure.
Right.
Well, so then the other one is.
107.5 W-L-T-W playing the best of the set.
Yeah, like the eighties and the nineties.
We're the mix.
Yeah.
I can do that one.
Sports on W-T-W.
Yeah.
No, that had to be kind of like the muffled microphone.
It was like Jonathan Schwartz on W-N-E-W.
That's him.
No, you're overdoing it.
He was the focus and seeer.
He was sort of like your best friend,
but the best friend of your girlfriend.
Right.
So he would like, he could do the trade secrets.
I mean, you know, he would get the idea that he knew how to get the chicks.
So you wanted to do a little trick.
You wanted to do a little trick to figure out how to do it.
So that you could get some kids.
Well, so what I think it all happened.
How would Stern really brought that into the front of the media
when Hank Kingsley from Larry Sanders show.
Hey, now.
Hank Kingsley.
Yeah, it's time for Larry Sanders.
And so Howard Stern started doing a lot of that.
But in the meantime, at radio station, this has been this way forever,
since I guess, you know, a rock and roll radio started.
Guys who weren't on the radio.
So like the program director and the managing or the general manager,
or the music director, they all, you know, have this like special
little language that they speak with the air talent,
often like the morning show guy who might also be the program director.
And then, I'll talk about it.
Hey, man, man, man, man, man we got good ready season, man, man.
Yeah, man, man, man.
I'm, I'm a, I'm a, I'm a, I'm a, I'm a, I'm a, I'm a, I'm, I'm a, I'm a, I'm a, because, you know,
world, such intradable communicators.
We have, we have our own little special short hand, and, and ask anyone
in radio, they'll confirm this.
It's, it's horrible.
So, you know, you just get into the habit of just
slipping into it, and, you know, the automatic thing is,
Did I ever bought a hanging nail?
I'm dead Marna!
That's so.
That's great.
But listen to the radio, and that's the difference
between radio broadcasts and podcasts.
That's the first thing you hear.
That's why I say it's like college radio,
which was incredibly cool, man.
You get listen to college radio back in the 80s.
That's where it was happening.
That's where it was.
That's where the REM came from, you know.
Well, I did actually listen to FM radio when I was in San Francisco
and it was actually kind of nice.
There's a station called KFRC, which is oldies format.
And they played since I was a hadn't heard in a long time.
Right.
That's what I like that.
It's nice, you know.
They played a song called Those Were The Days, Those Were The Days,
My friend, I love the name.
We thought it's a right.
It turns out that I made an answer came on and explained
that it was a Russian song.
Yes.
I think the name was Hopkins, Mary Hopkins.
And that was a wonderful song.
So, you know, I was like, I sat there at the parking lot.
I listened to the song.
And I just listened to that.
Cheers.
You know, I was just said, because it's true.
Those were the days we thought they'd never end.
You know, we were young.
We're getting close better.
Get a damn close.
Oh, man.
Dammit.
You mentioned that which I'd known, what?
I go ahead, do you wish it known what?
I wish I'd known then what I know now.
You know what?
Yeah.
Sure.
I mean, yesterday, on the source code,
I played Frank Sinatra, comply with me.
Yeah.
So, here's something really weird.
Today, in slips, my, into my iPod or so,
I actually check that on iTunes.
The latest Geekspeak, which is the, the gamer Geeks
who have podcast.
Yeah.
Check them out what they started with.
This is, it freaked me out.
And it took me a second, and I won't let you hit
the whole thing, but you'll understand.
Fly me to the moon.
Yeah.
That's how they started.
Listen, I can tell you didn't read scripting music yesterday,
because, yeah, I did.
I did.
Oh, you did.
Yeah.
You did.
I'm waiting for you to tell me the story.
What?
I'm waiting for you to tell the story.
Oh, yeah.
I was getting off the tram at SFO.
Listening to the daily source code.
I had just, you know, returned my rental car
going to the terminal, and Adam Seussville, I'm going to
please sign, and the song comes on as I'm going down.
It says, welcome to San Francisco International.
And it's, uh, come fly with me.
Got that.
And I go, fuck, I'm going flying.
Got it.
All right.
Not bad.
Everybody.
They're revolving.
Yeah.
They're on the other side of everybody.
He's from Seattle, Washington.
And that was a winner of their game.
Yeah.
Listen to the radio and you're going to start noticing this.
You will start noticing how these guys talk.
You know, it's, you know, it's, you know, and they're so
cookie cutter, always in the, in the middle of the day,
there's always the midday girl.
There's always, that's when the women are always on.
Has to be, you know, midday is after the morning show
and before afternoon drive.
So it kind of carries you over.
And, uh, and it's for housewives.
That's why they always put women there.
It's like, actually, when I was a kid,
any WFM, which was my station, had Alice and Steel.
Alice and Steel.
Yeah.
You know, I heard, right.
The night bird, exactly.
As she would be on like a 2 a.m.
Yeah.
And, uh, and, uh, and he'd go, oh my God, she must be a mysterious woman.
She's on it 2 a.m.
Yeah.
The perfect face for radio, my friend.
See, and the other, and then she used to play, um,
there was a song that forget who sang it.
It was called, I usually like it much better in the morning.
Yeah.
And it was a woman, a woman singing that, and maybe you could find that somewhere.
It was really something like it so much better.
I'll have to look at it for it later.
I like it much better in the morning, which was an unusual thought to me.
You know, because, whatever, I was passionate, obviously.
I was 16 years old.
Yeah.
Yeah, you were listening to the night bird.
And seeing, uh, here's the generation gap, Dave.
When I moved to New York in, uh, 87, and I was 20 something,
we had Robin Bird on Channel J.
Oh, God.
Have you ever seen her?
Because, yeah, that's the faint echo of what I was talking about.
It's my baby bag.
It's my box.
Come on, baby bag.
My box.
You can bang my box.
That was a great show.
I love that show.
Listen, when I noticed it was going on with Jonathan Schwartz,
and Scott Meaney was another one.
Yeah, Scott Meaney.
You need that.
Yeah, we're hippies in the East Village.
You know, they were long-haired hippies.
Just like they were in Hadesburg.
K-Fog was, I don't know, I don't know anything about
San Francisco radio, zero.
Docs, sirals, and I was one of these things about San Francisco radio.
Well, yeah, he does.
There's two stations in San Francisco Bay Area that were seven,
all made a big difference.
At least as far as I know, were K-Fog, which is still there.
And that was a progressive rock, uh, you know,
the equivalent of WWW.
And then it was K-Pig.
K-Pig.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not quite the right idea.
I think they were.
They had a string.
They went for a long time.
But they still streamed.
They were like one of the big things I don't know,
but they were still there when I moved to the Bay Area.
In 79.
And I lived in Las Cadas.
That was the first place I lived.
They were close.
I was close enough to Gilroy to actually pick up K-Pig and it was great.
I couldn't believe it.
They were playing things like little feet, you know,
little right.
One of my favorite things.
Right.
And, you know, they played the, they played the dead.
They played all the, all the sort of stuff he never heard on FM radio.
Of course, they were too good.
I guess to last the Docs, you know, we'll talk about that.
I'm sure Doc will be there at, uh, at our time.
I mean, we got to do so many podcasts when we're, when we're at blogger
content.
I'm just looking forward to putting cool stuff to go.
Chris Biden did that at the, uh, first blogger content.
He did.
It was really good.
It was very good.
In fact, he interviewed you.
Yeah.
We should dig that one up.
And who else did the interview that was really good?
K-Rose.
Yeah, you were.
K-Rose is podcast or we didn't call on podcast, but I remember going, okay.
Webcast.
We told him for some reason.
I'm so glad that.
They were cast from the web.
I don't remember.
We'll have to go back and listen to see what we call them, but, uh, you know, Chris
did some, I mean, that was the first time I heard Daily Costs, and he interviewed
Daily Costs.
Right.
He did.
Julie Powell from, uh, hold on a second day.
My cat is freaking out.
Hold on.
I got to go.
Let the cat in.
Come in.
Come in, baby.
Everybody.
Get out of my cell.
Yeah.
Go.
Maybe someday we should do a trade secret that's like, well, I can't be a secret to
the message.
They have wireless microphones.
Yeah, I'm back.
But no wireless speakers.
Yeah.
Okay.
So I was telling the people about how someday we ought to do the domestic trade
secrets where basically all we do is just clean the house and flush the door.
Yeah.
Reality radio.
Maybe you can leave it running well.
I go shopping.
It's the boner cast.
Lovely.
So yeah.
I had dinner with Steve Gilmore.
That's one thing I was talking about.
Less time.
Or the night before.
No.
Night before.
Yeah.
It was night before.
And.
He said.
Can't wait to meet him.
Yeah, I asked him to see it.
I met you.
He said he had.
And.
He says what we're doing is a comedy show here.
Oh, then we can get a listing under the comedy.
Note in the directory, which is maintained by someone else.
I'll have to submit a link.
You'll have to get down on your hand.
I will.
Please add us to your.
Please.
No.
By flowers and tell them how much you love them.
Yeah.
The way she heard or whatever.
I said flowers.
Tell them that you really care.
I love you.
And I love it.
And I really care.
Right.
So what else is Steve's?
I can't wait to meet Steve.
Because he's been such a tremendous driving force.
And at the end of every single.
Gilmore gang boy.
If he doesn't come out and just plug podcasting some more.
It was really great.
I was listening to the interview with Kim Collision.
And.
Collision.
You know, I wanted them to ask her question that they didn't ask.
You know, if she was always talking about walking.
I don't know if she listened to you.
Yeah.
I listened to the whole thing.
It was extremely difficult times.
Yeah.
Why was it difficult?
Well, because I got the idea.
You know, and I just hear.
Oh, I hear a lot of marketing speak after a while.
You know, I just get tired of it.
You know, I get it.
You're providing service to open source.
You know, stacks that you'll sell.
I get it.
It's great.
There's companies doing that.
They're going to be more.
And this is probably going to be a really good one.
Well, there's a geek fascination with Kim.
You got to understand.
She can really talk to it.
Anything she wants.
Just too.
Yeah.
And you guys go, oh, really.
Oh, that's fascinating.
Boy.
Yeah, and this is what I know.
It's on her mind and it's really great moment in there.
Where, um, at the end, you know, compelling it.
She apparently had given a speech at this invitation only $2400 visae confidence on boxing,
which, by the way, it was like a Republican confidence on the environment.
Yeah.
I read the quote on Sl everlasting news.
That was funny.
Yeah.
Got a lot of play, of course.
And actually, I actually go to a response from
from a venture capitalist on that, and a friend of mine, Hank Barry, and the conversation
turned in very interesting directions, you know, actually, he came out and visited us.
Anyway, at the end, they asked, so Kim's speech was, apparently, was a lot about, you know,
podcasting and blogging and RSS, and, you know, obviously, we think it's so cool, you know,
which don't seem to have anything to do with us doing, right, open source stuff.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
That's a good casting.
We have a new one, ladies and gentlemen.
We're going to bring you stuff.
Casting about it.
Yeah.
Pretty soon.
It's in the queue right now.
So they asked her about that, and Kim, she just flew it up.
It's like, oh, this is all the cool shit blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
There you go.
Okay.
That's cool.
How did that happen?
Why isn't she doing all that stuff, you know?
I don't know.
She shouldn't be.
It's probably, it's a venture capital thing.
It's another one of those where probably they had a CEO for this company, the client
or Perkins guys.
And something happened.
He blew it all up.
Or the entrepreneur was said he could be the CEO and eventually wore him down and Kim's
to be couldn't.
And Kim Kim, it's Kim like the, the, the stand by CEO and residents of us.
There's no, there's no, there's no stand by.
They have a stable of them.
It's, it's the way the system works.
Yeah.
Basically, they move you out of one company and then you get, you get a hangout until, you know,
it may keep showing you companies until you're okay.
I like that one.
They put you in the CEO of that one.
Oh, hey Dave.
Hey Dave.
Let's start a company and then let venture capitalists take us out.
Really cool.
I actually did that one.
I'm in too.
Yeah.
Let's talk about it.
Don't go anymore.
That's a great.
It is a great.
That was funny because I heard, um,
I don't know if Steve was at that dinner, but he certainly did call on her at the end of at the end of the Gilmour gang about podcasting.
Yeah.
That was kind of cool.
And he didn't really attack her.
He had lots of room there, which was nice.
Oh, totally.
You did quite a lot.
After his work.
Where's your lock in?
Yeah.
You know, she was talking about everybody else's lock in.
It was like, say, okay, he has dirty underwear.
He has dirty underwear.
He has, okay, Kim, what about your underwear?
He's a dirty stack.
Yeah.
She stacked.
I'm not going there.
I'm sorry.
Do you have to put a disclaimer in somewhere here Mr. Winer?
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
No.
All right.
On that note, the long time ago.
On that note.
And I have.
You know, I have, um, you want to listen to something you want to end it.
Where about an hour into this?
What do you want to do?
Um, what do you have?
Well, it's about, let me see,
It's about, let me see how long it is, it's kind of long, but it's really good. It's six minutes.
It's, um, I plugged this yesterday on the source code, the Truthout Overview from Truthout.org.
This guy who's been, it was doing his own podcast, and it's just so good.
It's just, let me describe it.
I'll just play a little bit of it. I'll pin it about, I want to play the beginning and about a
minute of what he's doing. You'll get the idea pretty quickly. All right? Okay.
Because it's something you should subscribe to.
Good evening. This is William Rivers 5, and this is the Truthout Overview for Friday,
October 8, 2004. Our lead for today comes from the editorial board of the Demorans Register,
and is titled Orwell Goes to War. The essay reads, in part, as follows. We live in Orwellian times,
where obvious falsehoods are asserted brazenly as, the day after the final report of the
Iraq survey group confirmed that Iraq had no weapons of mass destruction and no active programs
to produce them by President Dick Cheney, blindly asserted that the report justified the invasion of
Iraq. No, Mr. Vice President, the report shattered the last four-learned hope that the war was necessary.
It established that Iraq posed no threat to the United States before the 2003 invasion,
or any time in the foreseeable future. You get the idea, right?
Yep. Yeah. It's really, really good stuff. And he reads his own essays and other newspaper articles
you might not come across. It's a podcast, but it's just like a weblog. He's routing information,
all these people are routing information around. I just routed information by playing this. This is good.
This is just good stuff. He's a good feed to subscribe to.
What's the feed? Where is it? Hmm. It's in the podcast directory.
Oh, that's all you need to do. Yeah, on ipodr.org. It's a truth out. The truth out overview is what it's called.
So you should be able to find it. That's what we need. We need to be able to search the directory
tree really quickly. We got to do all kinds of stuff like that. Is that possible? It's distributed
does that work? Oh, anything works. You know, we've got it. Well, here's the deal. We've got to talk
to the search and get them to crawl that tree. And then, okay, that's step number one. I'm glad we
got a chance to do this. That's step number one. Then once they've crawled it, when they find one,
they should just display it like a directory. Yeah. It's done. Yeah. That's done. It's so cool.
We've now completely disintermediated Yahoo. And God knows they need to be disintermediated.
Even they would agree with that. Like, by now, probably not. Well, but then who cares what they say?
Great. I don't care. I don't care. Jeremy's won't take that.
Oh, he doesn't care what I think. Can you believe that guy? I mean, basically, he goes and asks
Tim O'Reilly, whether he has any conflicts of interest. Like, don't you own Google stock
Tim? And of course, Tim Gidon Google stock. And it was a good question to ask. Yeah. And so I
quoted him asking the question. And I was like, you know, somebody, you know, wasn't that long ago?
I should have just about time somebody had the balls to ask O'Reilly that question, you know?
And what's the question to explain the situation? Because I know what you're talking about. Okay.
Well, what happened was, what happened was that Tim O'Reilly, Google was getting a lot of heat for
something that they did. I don't remember what it was. You know, there's big get a lot of heat.
And it's, you know, there's a big company and they're in a leadership position. And heat is a good thing.
He got it. It was Gmail. It was Gmail. It was about Gmail. It wasn't right. It was the privacy issues.
We out and the privacy issues. And I had, I think I had written this was like, there were no worse
than anybody else. And come on, get a life. This isn't really a privacy issue.
But people were freaking out. The state of California was going to pass the law.
You know, making what they were doing illegal is just so ridiculous. Yeah. So Tim O'Reilly comes along.
And writes a thing basically saying, this is all bunch of bullshit. And, you know, you can't, you know,
hold them. But he went way over the line. I thought, I forget what he said. But some of the things he said
were like, come on, you know, don't go so far. Don't get so crazy about Google.
We've got to be realistic about them. And, um, and with Jeremy's wife who works at Yahoo, you know,
his, his, um, his was making him soar. And you could see this happening over and over.
Is it Yahoo, they feel fair amount of resentment for Google. Because they get credit for doing
the things that Yahoo did first. They get credit for doing first. Everybody says, oh, Google so innovative.
But they're actually just copying Yahoo. That's the way. So, you know, you know, what?
Well, I hate that. I hate that. And I support Soadney and that one. I think that we ought to know
who do the innovation. Okay. Let's get grounded. So, Soadney asks the question, you know, hey, Tim O'Reilly,
don't you own a lot of Google stock that you did as close as when you wrote that. And of course,
yeah, you kind of do need to disclose that. And, uh, or at least, you know, when somebody asks,
you should answer, right? Yeah. Instead, Tim goes, you know, blah, blah and blah, blah. And never really
answers the question except he kind of shows you I do. But, you know, it's sort of like,
that comes in paragraph eight. But, you know, first he has to say why the question isn't
a fair one in hell, blah, whatever. Tim O'Reilly, usual, long, windy, very sort of like, you know,
I'm Mr. Cool, perfect and clear. Well, there goes my invitation to Philip M. Dave. Thanks.
Well, that goes Miami. You can just stroke him anyway you want. But, um, so anyway,
they take a long story very, very long, continuously long. I quoted the Wadney. I said, well,
thank, I didn't say anything. I just give the Wadney colon. How much stock does Tim own Google
stuff? And all of a sudden, you're the bad way. I'm the bad guy, right? Always kill the messenger
Dave. They always kill me. No, I'm not the messenger. There's a Wadney's a messenger. But,
you want to know the problem is the Wadney's an O'Reilly author. Oh, we're really happy. They said,
well, were you expecting a royalty check this week, you know? It's a tech industry. It's a
worrisome entertainment day. The tech industry is just so bad. So we go to your checks and entertainment.
Yeah, well, you don't get it. We don't have no words. We're catching up. We're catching up quickly.
You have money, Kims. What are you talking about? Yeah, no. All of that.
All right. What do you say? We hit the theme music at the fuck out of here.
I think it's time to get the fuck out of here. Because we got to keep our standing in the comedy
listing on the director. Yeah, we can't become boring. All right, Dave, thanks, buddy.
Hey, Adam, have fun. Okay. It's davidscripting.com, Adam at curie.com. This is trade secrets at secrets,
dot scripting dot com. We'll talk to y'all soon, bye. See you by Dave.