Hey, what's up, everybody?
It's just Karen.
And this is Junior Bitches from the Lunatic Radio.com show.
And you'll listen to Adam Curry on the daily source code podcast player.
You know, that dude with the fantastic hair from MTV.
Yeah, he was beautiful back then.
How are you doing?
Hey, everybody.
Welcome to your daily source code.
It is Wednesday, December 15, 2004 coming to you
from Curry Cottage in the United Kingdom of the great
pile of Britain.
Something like that.
Hey, friends, family world leaders.
Welcome to the Big Show.
I know the GM Pack Day, which puts me at recording the show
at 11 o'clock this evening.
I spent most of my time at Starbucks, though, as usual today.
But not doing a podcast.
I had a visitor from out of town.
This time it was Clark Boyd from WGBH in Boston.
You know, GBH, of course, from there.
Excellent morning stories podcast.
Hold on a second.
I've seen a phone call here.
Oh, wait a minute.
It's my friend.
Hey, Dave, how you doing?
Good.
I'm in the middle of the source code.
I just started the show and you called.
I figured I'd pick up.
Yeah, why don't I call you back after the show?
I'll just run through everything and you're going to be up for a while.
Oh, that's right.
I'm going to be up for a while.
Yeah.
I'll call you in about an hour.
Okay.
Oh, man.
See, now that would have been great if I had a way to actually
conference Dave in, clearly, that's up on his mind.
So anyway, it's your daily source code.
As I said, I had a visitor from WGBH in Boston today.
Clark Boyd also does a lot of shows that are co-produced with the BBC.
Actually, this morning I was at the BBC again.
This time it was for a program called mouse mat, which kind of makes me laugh,
you know, because I guess I've always learned to say mouse pad
instead of mouse mat, but mouse mat works for me.
I actually have a mouse mat.
I use a like a Persian rug, a miniature Persian rug is my mouse pad.
So I actually do have a mouse mat, a flying mouse mat.
Magic, flying mouse mat, I guess.
So what it happens is, you know, the BBC of course is in London,
and I'm not going to slip out to London.
So they have a BBC Southern Counties radio, which is located at the
University of Surrey.
Surrey.
Excuse me.
And so they've basically got a special little corner there,
where they have an ISDN set, and you sit there,
and then the phone rings and the system picks up,
and then you hear the London studio, and you've got a microphone
and a headset, and you kind of have a conversation.
So that was fun.
Then I picked up Clark at the train station.
His train was on time, Clark work.
We went to, well of course, we went to Starbucks,
and I downloaded and uploaded and showed him, you know,
basically the podcast set up.
He's a techie.
He's a geekhead.
So he was totally into all the different wires and connectors
that we've strung together to figure out how to make these podcasts.
So it was good.
Only, of course, it took a lot of time,
and I did take the time, and I was happy to do it.
But, you know, so by the time I got home,
and actually, I found out that there is gridlock traffic
and gulford, if you're caught near the train station
around 536 o'clock, you're totally screwed.
Who knew there was gulford gridlock, but it's there.
It really is.
So it took me a good while to get home,
and I still had to get cat food.
So it's, again, life gets in the way of the art
that we're trying to create here with the podcast.
Still have an excellent show lined up for you.
Tomorrow, by the way, is the day that Alfian Benson come home.
These are the two cute little doggies
that were stuck in limbo in Atlanta.
Locked.
The key soon to be thrown away.
Lee Wilkins and his lovely girlfriend Jenny, you know,
totally in despair.
Now, the dogs are coming back tomorrow.
Totally 100% with the help of the podcast community,
the daily source code.
I know it may not seem like a huge amount
in the world scale of things,
but it was just beautiful to see how everyone came together.
And the doggies are coming back, and that is excellent.
And they'll still have to be in quarantine for six months,
but at least, you know, they will be visitation rides.
Conjugal visits, maybe, anyone?
Hey Adam, after hearing you ask people
to donate some money, you get Alfian Benson back the UK.
I want to Alfian Benson.com
and start to go to the old process of donating some money to them.
Unfortunately, I never did donate.
After creating a PayPal account for my could tell,
I would have to transfer money for my bank
or pay some sort of charge to enable my credit card
to use that.
Either way, PayPal claimed that I would have to wait
three to four days, I think, to get money transferred over to them,
so I could use it online purchases or whatever.
They must have changed their policy
because I certainly recall setting up my first account.
I know even a European account, and I'm a verified European member.
There were that means.
It went pretty fast, as long as you can lay down a credit card.
But it's in light of all the scams that are going on,
and there isn't a day that goes by that don't get the,
hey, you know, here at PayPal,
we just want to check and make sure that you're secure.
Yeah, click on this link.
Man, I hate those guys that do that.
Anyway, let's continue.
So, I thought to myself, you know, by then,
the money's part of me raised to help out Alvin Benson,
they're probably going to be on a plane back to England.
So, I've been trying to come up with a solution
that takes some ideas that I've heard you come up with
over the past few weeks,
and, you know, build upon that,
you know, I think we could help out the podcasting medium
and help out people at the same time.
Basically, my idea is in the long run
to have the podcast equivalent of public television,
like PBS.
How about radio, like MPR?
You know, you had the idea of taking a series of shows
and grouping it together
on either one server or one XML fee,
something like that.
Well, I think we could do that,
and also combine that with a sound method
of raising some money.
Instead of doing your traditional marathon thing
that you see PBS do,
we could instead have a really cool online website
that would,
the primary thing would be to have as few barriers.
No, I think we should auction off dates with dogs.
It's possible to get people donate.
Support a lot more than just PayPal, you know?
You know what?
I guarantee you we can do this.
I guarantee you, totally.
There's a whole area that's wide open
for this kind of stuff in podcasts.
Let me see.
That's the one thing you wanted to say.
Just want to move on to that whole one.
You have a lot kind of thing.
Go to go.
Really made a big difference.
I don't know.
What is it?
It's sort of a rainy day fund.
Okay.
I'll say that for a rainy day.
Yeah.
I'm sorry that you weren't able to get hooked up with PayPal Robert.
I have to be honest.
I have used PayPal,
and I've used it for donation purposes.
And they take a pretty big vague on the stuff that you,
you know, that you send.
I think in some cases like five or ten percent,
it's an amazing amount of money,
which seems like kind of, you know,
well,
I guess it works on the really other micro payments.
And that's how it,
but the minute you get into like hundreds of dollars,
or even thousands of dollars,
it kind of starts to defeat the purpose with their fee,
that they take from the middle there.
I wanted to talk a little bit about,
well,
basically some stuff that's been coming down the pipe that people are talking to me about.
Okay.
The first thing is the Heineken podcast.
Everyone has pointed out the Heineken podcast to me.
And I just want to clarify,
maybe the posting that I put on my,
on my weblog.
I know a lot of people at Heineken.
I met once or twice Freddie Heineken.
He's passed away now,
Patricia my wife.
She is met Freddie Heineken many times.
And I think they actually got a long,
pretty well.
He passed on about two or three years ago,
amazing guy.
And fabulous company, Heineken.
I mean, think about it.
What are they selling?
You know, water,
selling water,
primarily water,
and some other stuff thrown in there.
So it's a great company.
Family company,
been around for a long time.
It's a great brand.
And they have kind of,
I've always felt they've had a bit of a
a virgin records or virgin brand kind of vibe to them.
A lot of autonomy for local countries to advertise.
And they can be pretty wacky and do wacky things.
It comes up with creative great ideas.
They usually make use of small advertising agencies.
I knew some of the Heineken USA folks.
Of course, I knew more of the Heineken folks in the Netherlands.
And so when I heard Michael Butler of the Rockin' Old Geek Show,
who, of course, is a podcast pioneers.
Been on the podcasting scene since I was,
since way back when in August.
He's a Heineken fan.
He's a Heineiman all the way.
That's just no doubt about it.
You look at his ID3 tags.
He's a Heineken logo.
You look at his podcast logo.
It's basically the Heineken logo with Rockin' Old Geek Show in it.
And he loves the product.
He really does.
And he had been trying to get a sponsorship.
And I'd been listening and following along with the show where he called up Heineken.
He called up some Heineken office.
And they were really nice about it.
But hey, basically we can't help you out.
We can't do a sponsorship before.
It only wants us just a case of Heineken.
Right?
So I put in a couple of calls to some of the smaller agencies.
I know here on the Netherlands.
And I said, hey, dude, it would be so cool.
Think of just this entire community will be up and,
and applauding for Heineken.
If only you'll give this guy a case of beer a month or something.
I just do something.
You know, sponsoring some small,
for Heineken insignificant way.
But it'll make a big deal of difference.
And, you know, here's a very happy use of your product.
You know, what more can I say?
And by the way, a lot of people listen to him.
And a lot of intelligent people.
And a lot of, well, all kinds of people.
And people who like to drink beer.
So I put the call in.
And what I guess what came back.
I mean, there is no such thing as coincidence.
Now there's a small agency for Heineken.
That is creating a Heineken podcast.
And it was a small agency for Heineken.
And it will besides the fact that you can't use Safari or
or internet explorer browser on a Macinton.
Well, forget it.
If you're a Mac, you basically can't drink Heineken today.
Which is very aggravating.
The music is something totally different from what the rock and roll geek show is all about.
And it just looks kind of a, I don't know if it's 100% related.
But this thing is the shame.
And I put out a call to the, to anyone who's involved in Heineken.
You know, we can, we can, we can make this even better than a Heineken podcast.
Why doesn't Heineken underwrite one of the premier pioneer podcasters?
And you already told you the price.
You know, and of course, I'm a business man.
So I want my bottle a month out of it.
You know, come on.
You know, the sun don't rise from nothing here.
But please consider it.
How it's turned into a pretty good job when he,
when he promoted Heineken.
This is one way that the rock and roll geek could have done it.
But I think he would do it differently.
But what the heck, here's an exam.
Heineken beer, baby.
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
Oh.
This, by the way, is a part of my grandmaster plan.
David, I talk about this all the time.
It's happening right here.
Wouldn't it, you know, all, you know, with podcasting,
people are going to skip past the commercials if you have advertisements.
News flash, revolutionary concept.
Let's make the commercials interesting.
So people will actually pay them and not play them and not get paid for it.
Yeah.
Come here, baby.
Yeah, come on.
Oh.
Yeah.
It's orgasmic.
Oh.
Okay.
Well, you get the point, right?
So, hi, Nickon.
Come on, man.
Let's get that case over here.
Well, yeah.
And while we're talking about the rock and roll geek,
we might as well crank up some tunes by his band.
American Hardbreak.
Here's bitch.
So you got some bitch in a tube.
It's nothing new.
With you now fucking through.
So you got your little Superman's.
I'll be made up of thin my hands.
Take your ways.
It's not about you.
You're threatening to run away.
Hoping I beg you to stay.
Hold your breath.
You're almost blue.
Promotion nothing.
True to my word.
I'm still here.
You're still working hard.
Tell me your why.
Why are you still hanging around?
So you got some bitch in a tube.
It's nothing new.
With you now fucking through.
Promotion nothing.
True to my word.
I'm still here.
You're still working hard.
Tell me your why.
Why are you still hanging around?
Tell me your why?
Tell me your why.
Why are you still hanging around?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, silloo, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah you, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah
It's your daily source code a whole lot. I'm doing that drunken thing again once I don't know what it is
This is something that I'm seeing all over the place somehow when you're capturing audio on your Mac and Tosh
Eventually a delayed builds up and it's just like it's milliseconds, right?
But it doesn't matter what you're using. I happen to be using audio hijack pro, but actually an email was swirling around today
That it's still hard. It's we do not have good podcast software at all at all
We need to find something. There's a company out there called de let
Dot let or dot some people pronounce a definitely dip the day let D-A-L-E-T and they make
Radio station software. It's PC based and just it runs on you know a regular PC
But it uses some extra hardware bits, but their interface is totally right for podcasting for making radio on
On a computer if they would make a like for a light version that would be you know a huge market sure
You know, they sell basically the big radio stations and big broadcast corporations, but I think a light version would be not only possible
That totally cool just one more thing about
American heartbreak
They're going on tour any day now not coming
Through the UK unfortunately. It's a very expensive country to tour in
Especially considering that the pound is now about almost two dollars
So and you know, and yeah, they do spend a pound like a buck back home
Sure, milk may have kind of a similar value in price, but now not an easy place to tour
I know the guys are going through Rotterdam. I should check it out because
My plans have changed now as well mom got the call that she goes into the hospital on
Sunday
So the 20th Monday the 20th is when the operation takes place
So my plans are shifting a bit. I'm of course going to go leave earlier
Which may mean that with some luck maybe somewhere around the
Love to find out after find it from Michael Butler when they're playing the playing in Rotterdam
They're playing in Berlin, so maybe I can catch a show that would be cool. Anyway, great song song there
Always happy to play American heartbreak on the show
Just want to let you know that
Yes today as I was talking about the some of the OPML stuff
You know, I'm not the only person thinking about this good old
Drew from the Don and Drew show was all over it and he's sending me OPML files that contain the archives to all of the Don and Drew shows
Basically a placeholder so that his document will change whenever you want to take a look at
What's going on with Don and Drew for instance on the pod squad page
Or and this is what I tried from the iPod or directory you would basically have a you know
A live update
The OPML version works beautifully. I mean I can plug in anything I want
Unfortunately the directory doesn't want to eat that code so we kind of got to figure that out
But it's coming together. I feel I feel the vibe. I feel something happening with this OPML stuff
It's happening something's coming together. So if you saw a note of the directory break
horribly that was I was Drew and I'm mucking about trying to figure this out and
Also a couple of some contact with some of the iPod or developers who are also now trying to figure out you know where where can we
Pull this OPML in and you know, what are the consistent factors?
I've had the horrible habit of putting a title on top of my OPML files of my production show notes
Which basically is a directive that that makes a page render with the title being the title
But there's a hash sign which kind of screwed up some some stuff. I think for the for iPod or X
I'm sorry. I think was for the iPod or lemon team
So I'm still trying to figure that out one thing that I've started doing though is in the album
title
The album ID3 tag where normally I'd say you know here's what's on the show now
I'm putting the URL in there to the
Production notes for that show to the OPML file so
Maybe that's something that you know that that some of the iPod are going to be able to suck out of there and and use and display is information
I don't know you can certainly test against my stuff and drew stuff and give us some feedback
You know, let us know and we'll also keep an eye on the the iPod developer list
Is this great? I mean drew a such a nice guy
You know he's working with me on this and he's letting me totally fool around with his wife. It's great
I'm such a lucky bastard
Adam this is Chuck Tomasi of Chuckchat.com. I'm a long time listener first time podcaster
Just wanted to pass on a little feedback and thanks regarding all your pontification about RSS and podcasting
As in the UK a couple of weeks ago on business but due to terrible scheduling distance and in person visit was out of the question
Would have been great to catch up with one of the podfathers of podcasting
I've been living in Scotland near Edinburgh
It was funny noticing a lot of the things you were talking about in recent weeks on your podcast things like the large power plugs with switches next to them
The pop-in light bulbs in the lamps and so forth. I haven't got a chance to do some driving on the left side of the road using
Manual transmission
It's like having all your clothes on backwards and trying to right with the opposite hand very strange
I kind of cheated with my opportunity to drive because it was 2 a.m. and there wasn't anybody out on at that time on Friday morning
But it was the safest way for me
Even inspired me to create my own podcast which I've called Chuckchat
Hopefully you've got your broadband by the time you get this. Thank you for a wonderful show
And keep up the good work. Thank you everybody. Oh, hold on. Hey, let's hear it for Adam
It was more to the message. Thank you, Chuck
Okay, no, I don't have my broadband yet. No, sorry Bob. I don't have my broadband
I was actually going to read an article that a couple of people pointed me to about
Britain's digital diet
Actually I posted the link and see it was at Craig Patchett who who sent me this link
Basically people in the UK are carrying around an enormous amount of data. I'm sure it's the same in the states as well
But hey, you know, it's a it's a BBC story so
They're gonna talk about the UK in this case, but instead of that I'd like to read another story
I would read you a story kids
Um
The first person who pointed this out to me was Ross Jones
Ross has been all over my bandwidth situation. This is from the register
I written by Tim Richardson published
Tuesday
December 14th, 2004
In the evening
I'm sorry, 11 48 in the morning
Grinch me time. Okay, here we go. I'm gonna read this to you because this is it's it's so typical. It's so beautiful
titled gilford runs out of broadband
Sudden surge in demand for DSL broadband and gilford has left BT that's British telecom
On the hop and net users twiddling their thumbs waiting for high speed net access
BT wholesale which provides DSL that is resold by ISPs such as AOL UK
Tiscally and want to do UK has confirmed that all capacity at its gilford telephonic change has been used up
New DSL broadband customers in the affluent Surrey town must wait until BT installs extra capacity in its exchange
The UK giant telco says this should come on stream by the end of this week
News that gilford had quote run out of broadband was contained in a blog by Adam Curry a mover and
Shaker and podcasting in essence radio broadcasts for MP3 players on December 3rd he wrote
I just got off the phone with British telecom who informed me that there are no ports available at my exchange and
Someone would have to leave before one becomes available. Yes, there is a waiting list and know
They can't tell me where I am on the list since it's sold out to multiple ISPs
A spokesman for BT acknowledged that all the available broadband connections in gilford had been used up
But denied that new users would have to wait until someone dropped off before being hooked up
He told the register quote we do have people so I do the accent. Yeah, I think so
We do have people waiting on that exchange the capacity has been reached but new lines will be installed this week
The situation was not ideal he added but it was not typical of what is going on
gilford was hit by a sudden surge in demand
BT was also unable to say for how long the exchange has been full
11 days at least according to curie or how many people are on the waiting list for broadband
Excellent
Excellent reporting thank you very much Tim Tim good job Tim Richardson and full of shit
By this week you're right
You're right
Of course I just went through all the trouble of canceling the other ISP
You okay online. I come on. It's not true. I can't believe it
But you know what we got their attention and that's what counts and I really appreciate it and
They will know that pod casten has come to town everybody
more on bandwidth
today if you
looked at the RSS file you'll see that
The daily source code was not coming from the server we've been using for the past couple of weeks
which was
The server at opml.org atom.opml.org
This is a test and the reason is that we've seen that you know there's basically something
going wrong in the network
now that the amount of subscribers has increased significantly
And downloads are breaking probably primarily
downloads that are done by automatic iPod or clients
It seems that people are having better luck with
with their browsers downloading browsers but that kind of defeats the whole point of iPod or
Anyway, you can see the post things we've pointed to it in the production show notes and in a on my
on my weblogg davis
Really it started up you know it was great started this
Technical focus group on scripting news to you know see if we could
Basically track down the issue white it was breaking for for people and
And we're pretty sure it's it's the bandwidth that
We're being provided but we're not 100% sure so let's see what the results are
If we put it on an older server that well worked but we don't know if it's going to work with this type of volume
So it could be a total disaster you may not be hearing this show at all this show may have been lost in in bid hell
Maybe bit torrent is is where we're going to where it's all going to come down to
I think it's got to be there pretty soon because otherwise
You know, I'm not going to be the only one that's going to have this problem. I hope not
Let's see what are we at now pretty good about 30 minutes perfect. I wanted to play something that Tony Khan
Morning stories podcaster and by the way, have you noticed that morning stories is is changing
Where it used to be just morning stories with an intro by Tony now is the intro by Tony
You get the morning story and then there's like a whole kind of crew there, you know
It's like it's the Tony Khan crew zoo with WGV age and it's nice to hear you know
There's some good banter going on. There's some good shoot in the shit which is not your traditional MPR
Style I guess and I'm really enjoying that more of that, please more of that
And Tony did a conference recently. He spoke at a conference at Gisperkman at Harvard and
And he put together a sampler
On force I didn't see see the conference I couldn't listen to it. I didn't I think it was webcast
But obviously my continuing lack of broadband is not allowed me to
To download that I think I hope maybe there's a podcast that I can still subscribe to to get all of the sessions from that up to hunt around
But he put together this sampler which he gave me access to and I was like
It was so nice to hear a whole bunch of different voices and some of the stuff from earlier days of podcasting
I just wanted to replay this. There's a lot of me in it, which is not the reason I'm playing it
But really it's just a it's a nice flow and it's it's a whole bunch of voices that you'll recognize immediately and it's
It's nice and I want you to hear it's about four and a half about five minutes, but worth a listen
This thing on 30 seconds
Welcome to the podcast from the kate and it's Adam Keratt of curries with any source code where users and developers party together
And the glory of the internet the radio brothers podcast
It's Tuesday November 30th and this is the news about independent Christian music
Hello friends and neighbors. This is David Slashford. This is the evil genius Chronicles
The rip and read blogger podcast
From conservative perspective
The digital experience podcast and food non-real music news and information podcast reviews in a
Front political talk with Dan and Crane
You've on recently radio show today show features cursing women
Will powers dancing for mental health
If I'll go well, I got a curdle panic. Oh whole computer crash showed it and get saved so I was fucked
Hello
Hey, good, you know, I'm in the middle of the source code
So can I call you back on like 15 minutes
Shit all over the Louis 14 the Louis cut-tours
You but I want that I don't want a free mouse pad. I want my mouse by the mouse and that
Shit my entire cup of tea spilled all over the desk
It didn't spill on the keyboard. Well, I actually did spill a bit on the keyboard
all over the breakout box
over the mouse pad
Christina
Okay, let me see what can I do? Well, I continue to clean up here. Listen to the bit of the the sports pod, okay?
Yeah, you'll enjoy that
Wow, I'm watching it
And Indiana Wow, I've never seen anything like this in the NBA. It's disgusting
What happened is uh, Ron or Tastel Ben Wall is someone hard not that hard, but a little bit hard
And
Whoa
Fans are just coming from behind
Hi, I'm Todd Mappin. Thanks for tuning into the iLive Radio.org podcast today
We are coming to you from Burgerling, Germany and my goal today is to find the wall or
What's left of the Berlin wall anyway
Spent Saturday night. It's been night with about 500 other geeks
Waiting in life in the new Nintendo DS
Something else that might surprise you people in smaller towns near St. Louis say
They stands again from the negative publicity. I'll tell you what they're talking about coming up tonight on holiday news at six
Welcome to real reviews films worth watching on Michael Gohagan today
We're gonna talk about a fun film
1999 the Limey it is directed by Steven Soderberg one of my favorite directors and it stars a great cast
Terence stamp plays the kind of title character Dave Wilson. I think if we as sex right now
It would give us a good rating right on the show
I think we should good thing this isn't a video show
Make up make up
I don't understand why keep having to leave this is your show then you need to be writing down topics because I have topics another topic we were gonna talk about was gonna be
Frontline on PBS last night about how Walmart's destroying the world. I mean this was something that you were so interested
I'm not gonna ring my hands over this election if nine eleven had never happened
John Kerry would be present in elect today. I have no doubt about that
Jim goes on Jim Gary
I'm still shaking my head over this a new democratic slogan in the 2006 midterm
quote you would vote for us if nine eleven hadn't happened
Your spit is hanging and you have a fight because it's for democracy and yet when we have democracy
You don't support him you would join your two because he's not doing what you want him to
He's not even if you like he want him to and become that because of that because of that
You commit a coup d'etat
I want to tell people the boycott wall
It's the only choice because they don't have everyone else out of business. Well
Yeah, but I don't even think there was anything in there being with Chris. They still have downtown
It was shitty and it was she before Walmart came. It was shitty after Walmart came. I wrote on the text weblog about this
Thanksgiving episode of WGBH morning stories
I thought was fantastic. He'd been blacklisted and knew he'd never see another paycheck
Unless he cooperated with a committee recanted his views and informed on all his friends
Instead that Thanksgiving he invited them all to a feast with
We can't just a really dark period in American history, you know
That's uh people think of that and it's kind of housey in time
There's like a 10 15-year period where we locked up the Japanese because of their ethnicity
We you know the whole house on American activities thing there was a lot of horrible shit going on back then as
There is today by the way
I guess eventually people will try to figure out how to make money on this
If I gave you five dollars could I be your first commercial commercial person sure? I could say
No, you can't see anything. It's 25 dollars. We might eventually have a sponsor or do a quick review of a product and you know
We'll always tell you exactly if it's a advertised men or something we like
I'm still drinking honey. I love the product whether they give me free beer or money or not
I'll still drink that product so I found out today that there's a rating system for podcasts
So you guys go there and vote
Yeah, so we can be number one and take over the world and you will be my first lieutenant
I will no not you
You listening yes you I'm talking right to you
No one else just you what ring do I guess I'm talking
Don't listen to him. I'm the boss
Jew he's a figure out president
I'm Dick Cheney
Would be here on your podcast. I mean it's the sweetest ever
I know I'm so inspired I might I might pay pal you guys like two bucks today
I can split it however you want a bucket of these or
You know you go into Starbucks
I don't have permission to play
Abba
See Betsy doesn't understand
Copy left or create of comments or any of that type of license
They're like no, it's not
I understand you're picking through somebody else's garbage. I understand that
It's not the human
It's a it's part of community
It's a community. That's neat. You can go sit in a field and eat carrots and share your open source
We got to make money
That's all I'm saying. I love it. Oh my god
Do you think she would give me permission to play her music on it? She would be like
Music bad face is provided by the generous permission of the general readers
Chantelreaders dot com by their albums
by their albums
They're very very good
By them
Okay, the show just keeps getting better and better keep it up Butler. Huh. Thanks dude
I don't think it's getting better, but I appreciate the nice words and it gives me the
Cards to keep going on with this thing. I'm having such a blast doing this
I've been really fortunate and the fact that I've got so many listeners just tells me that some people are enjoying it
And I can't tell you how gratifying that is. See you then mentioned our podcast and we have popped up in there
Yeah, someone that me 10 dollars that podcasting wouldn't be around next year. I don't really want to
Wow cuisine. I'm learning how to speak Spanish. I am
Learning the incident. There was a an article in the London Times podcast in the next big thing
You've always wanted to be star
It's my job
To make you a star
somehow you have a good ability to communicate a lot of geeks can't communicate. I know what I'm ready to what
This is an easy way to do it. I don't see the other people. I can't see the other people. I can't see any of it.
And I think that the BBC is doing more podcasting experiments than we're aware of
Andrew Whitehurst sent me an email also and I'll just like you.
Like the day you walked into my life. So unmistakably like every other woman. It's so different in so many other ways
And you well, you were my second choice. I love you, baby
Well, I'm going to wrap this up. Do you want to say hi to everybody?
Say it right here. I like my mom. Say bye bye.
Bye bye. All right, everybody. Good night. It's late. We're tired. We're going to go watch a movie
later. Can I ink on it? Take these everybody. I'll see you. Thanks for listening. Thanks for
subscribing, y'all. Bye bye. The source code can be found in its archives later. Show and the podcast
RSS feed and daily source code dot com. I'll check you out tomorrow everybody. Take care.
How amazing was that? Let me just turn this down for a second. That's the end. Hold on a second.
Oh man. Wow. I apologize. It wasn't five minutes. It was 10 and a half minutes.
That was really good. And I remember so many of those moments. It's only in, yeah,
Jesus man. This is good shit. This is really cool. And it went long so I'm not going to be able
to talk about the I River hack that I wanted to, but that of course will be here tomorrow.
Because I got some interesting news about the I River after my review from yesterday.
Wow. I'm going to actually listen to that podcast thing again. It was more than just a
sample. This had a whole flow to it. I mean, it was, it was a little bit of history in there as well.
Excellent job. I'm sure Rick had something to do with it. I'm sure the Tony has,
has his, uh, it's got his team working on that stuff. Man, what an amazing, amazing amount of work.
Okay. Perfect time. 42 minutes. Going to leave it at that for today. I started a
phone call to make today. You know that. So I'll be back tomorrow for the Thursday edition
of the Daily Source Code and we'll be learning about hacking our I River. So you can always
send me email about that if you've got more on the topic. Add them at curie.com. Send
it as an attachment if it's under five megs. Take care. I'll see you tomorrow. Bye bye.