Bye everyone and good afternoon in South Korea it's Monday.
And it's about what is it 430 in the afternoon and coming to you from Curry
Castle in Belle
It's frightening. I'm trying to do everything virtual. I'm sitting here with hot metal touching hot metal and trying not to burn myself
And this is mainly because I got a real panicked email from Doug Kay said oh, you know your the latest source code was out of phase
Now out of phase is this is what the best way to describe that
You don't you don't really hear it if you're listening to it on on headphones
and and look at it this way you know so you send an electric current through the
wire to connect to the speakers and that produces a vibration now if it's out of
phase then what happens is the vibrations are happening but they're
happening exactly the opposite direction so basically the sound is
So, and that's usually a wiring configuration and that was pretty sure the culprit was going
to be the patch cable that I hacked together yesterday to get the 3 to get from the 3.5
millimeter jack headphone jack out from the power book into the mbox virtual or the mbox
external audio device and which has XLR inputs and so I actually called my father-in-law he
used to build studios back in old patch cable days and he told me exactly
told me where the soldering iron was in my own home which was pretty cool. I had no idea where it was.
So Doug, thank you very much for pointing that out and hopefully this is all in-phase. It sounds
good to me now. What I don't have is a phase meter. I have no idea. I have so much software
running out. I have so many things patched through. It's just unbelievable. I just did a test
with iChat AV and that works perfectly. I can also send stuff back down the line.
Now to do that, what I need to do is I need to just in iChat, I can open up the preferences while
the iChat chat is continuing and just select a different input which is actually from a Q monitor
from the MP3 player, the DJI 1800 software that I have. So that works perfectly well.
And just got an email from Steve Garfield. There's good news and he's thinking of me.
Let's see. Apple's next generation operating system.
That's going to be Tiger will include an updated version of the company's core audio technology
They'll deliver new tools and functions to improve the audio handling experience of Mac OS X applications. This is obviously
cut and paste it in.
So Tiger's version of Core Audio will also support the...
Oh here we go.
The creation of aggregate devices,
allowing developers to combine multiple audio devices together
under the auspices of a single audio device.
Exactly what...
For example, developers can take two devices with two input channels, combine them to
create a single aggregate device with four input channels, and then let core audio take
care of routing the audio data to the appropriate hardware device.
Lovely.
Very, very cool.
Okay.
So, got to figure out how we can let people know about what we need and how we can get
some more cool stuff done.
I was in checking out the iPod or developer list and I actually got an email, the
latest version of iSpider and I figured it was time, I've seen a lot of different
versions go by, I think three in an hour, three version updates at one point, but this
software kick ass, it's really, really good.
The only thing it's missing now is it's almost
installer, you double click the installer on Mac OS X, there's also Windows installer,
it just opens up, you install the software answering one or two of the typical questions
like where do you want it to be installed.
the tip of the very common Apple installer, package installer I think it is.
And it creates a nice little folder in your application folder and everything's all set
up.
It talks to iTunes perfectly.
It also sets up a cron job.
I heard David Slasher talking on his Evil Genius Chronicles that the cron job is set
up to run every single hour.
I checked it is.
I've just got a 00 and the rest of it.
So we'll run at the top of every hour.
That is indeed one thing that maybe just in the install process you could answer a question
to say, hey, I want to.
But these times and the other thing that doesn't quite have in the install yet or doesn't have
at all is an overview of what feeds you're subscribing to, the opportunity to uncheck
a couple of feeds or maybe add another one.
But we're so close.
And I got to say, iSpider is really good.
I'm very happy with the performance.
And add to that that it also recognizes bit torrent enclosures.
What it does is so if you've created a bit torrent, then instead of distributing the
MP3 file as your enclosure, you're going to distribute the bit torrent file as the
enclosure for each show.
iSpider recognizes that, brings in the enclosure, opens up a bit torrent client,
downloads it, and then transfers it to your iPod.
So it's phenomenal.
Really, really cool.
And I can't wait to try that out.
I've just been experimenting a little bit with a couple different.
bit torrent creation programs. In fact while I was doing that I did something wrong. I'm not quite sure I was messing around with the server that I have at the hosting.
running, which is off right now. I did something weird and then Python just, you know, got away from me.
And at a certain point, I tried to kill all the Python processes and it was just out of memory or
whatever, just it couldn't handle my request anymore. So I had to have it physically reset
at the hosting facility. So I'm going to chill out a little bit on messing around with bit
torn on the server. Took hours to get them to reset it. But I heard that even Dave Slasher was
thinking of switching. He created Get-A-Closures, which I've been using up until this point. And
only today have I switched over to using iSpider. And there's only one thing that I don't believe
is in the code, which would be just a great addition and something that would all iPod or
script should really do is after it's finished, it's finished, it's run, it's completed getting all
the new enclosures, putting them into the playlist, then just do an update iPod.
And I don't know, I think you might have to specify the name of the iPod, which means
we'll have to figure out how to get that name when you connect it to the dock.
I don't know how to do that.
I'll look into it.
But maybe that's just a variable you said.
I think with me it's updateAtom's iPod.
And that would just make it the last perfect bit because now in the morning, if new
shows have come in, then I have to lift the iPod out of the dock and re-dock it
to get it synced up with the latest shows that came in.
Or I have to go to iTunes and tell it to update the iPod.
It's just one minor step.
And I'm just afraid that people are just leaving in and they're thinking,
oh, OK, I'll get all the latest shows while really they're getting it two days
late because of a delay on downloading overnight and then a delay on the next
time it's been synchronized.
And then, of course, something we haven't talked about.
It doesn't really matter all that much.
is naming conventions.
Now you know what, it really doesn't matter I guess.
I think if we're all talking the same thing here.
So just keep everything under iPodder.org.
What I'm struggling with here is there's so many
different names and brands and things running around,
even though this is a total open source project.
I just wanna make sure that if someone's looking
for a great iPodder script that they're not
overlooking, you know, iSpider because,
first you have to come to iPodder.org,
then you go into the downloads directory.
Oh, okay, let me see these different ones.
What's iSpider?
You know, after you've gotten to three different
other types of scripts.
So we just think about, are we all gonna call them iPodders
and specify what they are, you know,
iPodder slash or dash whatever,
or do we just want all kinds of names?
It doesn't really matter to me.
It's just I think at a certain point,
we're gonna be done with the iPodder development.
At least on the receiver side.
And then hopefully we'll all start on the publishing side.
I just want to make it easy for users as possible.
And that is the type of stuff that we
want to talk about here on Source Code.
This is the place where users and developers party together.
And of course, a big feature request, which will come up
soon.
And I think this is maybe this is the right time to talk about it
since we're going to be dealing with subscriptions
on the installation process and also going back later
and adding or unsubscribing from feeds is OPML support.
That makes a lot of sense.
Maybe that's even the simplest way to edit these subscriptions
is to do an OPML file.
Of course, you need some kind of OPML viewer or editor to use.
But somewhere I think that that should be in there.
Makes sense.
And we probably shall just look at the aggregator world.
And most of the answers are going to be there.
Let's see.
I wrote down.
Oh yeah, there was another thing, another topic.
I saw on the iPod or dev list, which is at Yahoo groups, is something called Coral.
And it probably is just like archive.org.
And the way it works, basically, is if you have a URL that points to a file, and I think
it has to be at least five megs or bigger, you basically put either a part of a URL in
front of the file name, or in Coral's case, you add something onto it.
You actually add a Coral.org, or I have to check it out.
And you have to specify a port as well.
Anyway, so you're basically just adding something onto your URL of this piece of
content at the beginning or the end.
And what happens is that request doesn't go to your server, it goes to a cache.
And they have a whole network of caches set up around the internet.
A lot of them is at universities.
And then it'll basically store the file there.
And every next request, in theory, it's going to cache it.
to bring in from the cache and not from your hard drive or from your server.
I've used this with archive.org.
They have a, what is it?
They call it free cache.
It's freecache.org.
It's a part of archive.org.
And it was working for a while and it worked really great, but then I think stuff started
to fall off the edge or after a while it does get deleted if the file, it gets deleted
from the cache if the file isn't being requested enough.
And I heard a couple things just surfing around that either it wasn't working
or maybe it was broken temporarily.
And Coral sounds like the same thing and it certainly seems to be working
because I tried it out.
But I don't know if that's really a good solution to the bandwidth
and storage problems that we're looking at with the iPod platform.
Because if it's running through university networks, eventually that's just,
we're just going to run into a brick wall and we won't be able to
replicate all the work that we probably by, by then will have put into it.
else that's good. Moveable type is, and I posted this on my web blog and on the, on the, on
the, I think I put it on iPodder.org as well. Moveable type, there's now a plugin available
that will allow you to add enclosures to your blog post. So it also spits out an
RSS 2.0 with enclosures syndicated feed. And there's a couple links around them.
There's also one of my weblog live.curry.com where you can check it out. I don't use
Moveable type. I never have. I have no idea how well the plugin works, but just want
to make sure everyone's aware of it. And more on the iPodder dev list. Yeah, so some
folks are starting. Oh, wow. Listen to this bird for a second. Hold on.
Just walk out.
Of course now that I'm outside you immediately stop singing come on
There he is here.
He's in this tree here.
Let's see him.
Okay, enough nature intermezzo. Back to work.
We're talking about talking about
Now is it going all these keeps going off so yeah, so on the iPod of dev list where a lot of people
publishing. So that's good. And I think we're pretty close to really being able to focus on that.
And I'm, you know, we're just going to have to continue the conversation and figure out what we
think is the is the best way to do this. And I'm feeling that some people are going to come up with
some really interesting angles to how we can make this as easy as possible for everybody. And it
also appears that screen scraping is out. It's like everyone has said, Hey, you know, okay,
not such a good idea. And that's kind of dying off. And there's some some talk about, you
know, what's the best way to, you know, to keep this development group going? I personally
really like the Yahoo! list because it has an RSS feed you can subscribe to it, you know, email
notifications, it's free. And you know, the only other alternative I've heard so far is a wiki.
And I don't, you know, I understand what they do, but I just don't get wikis. It's,
it would be too difficult for me. And now of course, I'm going to a lot of wiki people saying
check this out. But it has probably just wasted breath on me, you know, you know,
how you get attached to one one type of application or one type of car or one type of woman.
Alright, let's see, why don't we play a song? Yeah, yeah, yeah. Now it's kind of, I was
going to, because it was, you know, it's a really rainy day and it's cloudy and it's
just, it's not really nice. I was thinking I was going to play something nice and rough
and now I hear this bird singing so beautifully. I almost don't feel right about playing
this but we need to kind of wake up for this Monday. That was Cooper here. No more Mr. Nice Guy.
I got no friends, got no readin' papers, I'm back in this theater room.
And the past is gone
Mr. Nice Guy on the source code.
No final bit of drums there.
Let's see, just two quick things I wanted to play for you here that I picked up, even though I was really busy in the past couple days.
This is probably the shortest podcast ever from Raster Web Audio, and it's just so silly that it's only 13 seconds.
I think you'll enjoy it.
This is Raster Web Jokeo for whatever day it is.
The guy walks into a pole and says,
Ow! Hey, didn't there used to be a bar here?
Who put this pole here?
Thank you, goodnight.
I'll be here all week.
And I caught the second session of Live from the Formosa Tea House.
It came in, they have an RSS 2.0 feed, lovely, and it came in automatically.
And these guys are getting pretty good because I was really jealous that when I heard the beginning of the show,
listen to this, they've got it really sounding very professional. Check it out.
Live from the Formosa Tea House.
Wow, from the foremost e-house.
Oh man, that's so cool. I got a whole jingle going on.
Now I gotta get a couple of those set up.
Wait a minute, maybe I can... hold on.
When I was working at Z100 in New York,
they had a top of the hour jingle that went,
serving the universe from the top of the Empire State Building.
Maybe we can do this.
podcasting across the universe almost let's try it with reverb instead of with echo I'll be better
podcasting across the universe
podcasting across the universe it's the source code code code
cool
All right enough playing around for today. I'm gonna wrap things up and I'm gonna hopefully Dave and I'll
this week. I'm going to be pretty much home all week except for Wednesday in the afternoon.
I'm going to Rotterdam. I've been scheduled to
a speech for some company, a paid gig, you know, so I actually got to concentrate on that Tuesday and figure out.
people.
As always if you want to respond send me an email.
You can always get the latest source code and the archives and daily source code