Adam Curry, rocking in Surrey, mashing up the T-world, radio-plash-say, mind the movie
we can tell us...
Yeah, how you doing?
Welcome to the Daily Source Code as promised the Expedition on this Sunday, December 19th, 2004 coming
to you from Surrey, from the college.
That bears the name of Curry.
Just what uses a developer's party together?
Unbelievable.
I was just about to hit the record button when the phone rang and it was Dave.
He's on his way.
What's going to work his way down south and then he's then I'll be cooking up with him
beginning of the year on the East Coast and he says, hey, he's a drive and everybody.
Okay, so I apologize profusely about Friday's source code.
It just did not work out as I posted on my weblog.
Patricia had some emergency bridge work that had to get down and you know, you need your own mechanic for that.
I have to say for a country where people are not known for their wonderful teeth, which is certainly the United Kingdom.
They have some excellent dentists. We did go to well, there's a whole row of dentists here in Guilford.
They're all thanks to each other and she went there for some like emergency like cement.
There's do something, you know, give me some gas and tape and some some string, some bailwire.
And they were, those people were, yeah, they knew what they were talking about, but still obviously Patricia has her, her own guy and Amsterdam.
So, quick day trip back and forth to the lowlands and of course,
we had Patricia's parents, my in-laws coming, they're here, they came on Saturday.
So there was a lot of shopping to get done and Christina and I went out and got really wrong Christmas lights, you know, the pink kind.
We rushed back because we had to go across the street to the neighbors for a lovely, pre-Christmas supper.
It was so nice that they invited us and a couple of their friends, also neighbors from around the way.
And so Christina and I had a really rush and get all the shopping done, everything for the weekend.
And we also got a really, really, really gotty Christmas tree.
You know, about 75, 80 centimeters high, but with the fiber optics in it in the branches.
So I first you take it out of the box, you unfold it all the, I can take a picture of this thing.
And then it has, what's the halogen light underneath in the base?
And that just rotates and changes color.
So it got like yellow and green and red and purple and pink and I had that in front of the window.
So while we were having dinner at the neighbors, Patricia was on our way back from Amsterdam and got back from the airport and saw that.
I was like, ah, ah, yeah, I live here, right?
And her parents arrived all in one piece, so that's nice.
And so it's just been really, really busy.
Excuse me.
Still running around getting all these, all the, you know, the last bits done of just, just basically moving in.
And of course, I still have no broadband to speak of.
Well, I've been doing pretty good with, um, with the podcast.
I've been keeping up okay.
I've found the number of way to, uh, to, to Jerry rig the, the iPod or clients that I'm doing some, uh, some other scripts and stuff.
I'm really getting back in the watch out ladies and gentlemen.
I'm really getting into programming again.
Now there's this open source version of Frontier.
Now that I had anything to do with it, but, um, well, actually a couple of things.
I migrated everything over curry dot com and live dot curry dot com and www dot curry dot com.
And, um, and not daily source code dot com yet.
That's still in its original place.
But everything is now moved to a new server.
It's all, you know, all URLs are pointing to the same place.
Um, the RSS feeds are still in the same location, even though you can update to the new one if you, if you want.
It won't make any difference.
So all of that stuff, um, freed me up from using radio user land.
Which, you know, I had so much running so many different sites and so many different applications and tools and renders and god knows what over the years that I'd had that put into my,
into my tools folder or my www folder.
There was becoming a real resource hog, um, but I needed it, you know, first of all is the outline.
I love writing it in an outliner, um, but just running the thing was a little bit too heavy on the resources.
So now I have this, uh, OPML is what it's called, uh, make sense.
So we'll just call it the OPML, uh, app.
Um, and I'm using that.
I've been using outliners for, for preparing my podcasts, uh, since day one, of course.
And using them for the, uh, for the show notes.
And now it kind of just sits there.
It's, it's literally doing nothing.
It's just kind of cruising along.
And today, um, you might have read on my, uh, it's Sunday.
By the way, did I mention that?
It's the 19th.
Uh, I had a really weird dream that I was, I was actually walking along an OPML outline in the
iPod or directory.
And I was jumping off to all these different notes.
I was jumping off to different countries.
And it was, it was twisted.
And then when I, when I woke up this morning, I said, yeah, that's it.
I got to write a crawler that, that, you know, walks along the, uh, the OPML path.
And I actually, um, I spent about five or six hours.
And, uh, I've got it to kind of crawl along.
And it doesn't jump off to the external links yet, but it will.
Um, and essentially what I want to do is make something that makes my job easier.
Um, it'll crawl through the entire, so if you, if you can hold off on updating any notes,
um, for another day or two, that'd be great.
But it basically, it'll crawl off, find anything that's new.
It'll maintain its own database of, uh, feeds.
But it'll also crawl into, uh, other databases.
Uh, and we're just, basically, everybody's doing, right?
It's kind of populating, uh, uh, their own stuff.
Um, and it will, uh, uh, it will update the, what's new,
node with anything that's new.
And it'll also automatically post, um, new podcasts to the ipadr.org homepage.
And I might have, uh, I have to put some kind of step in between there,
because I'm sure that somewhere we're going to get spam or something, we don't happen.
Or something, we'll probably just break more than likely the code that I'm creating.
So, um, uh, anyway, that was, that was what I was kind of doing this weekend.
Oh, yeah, hold on a second.
So many, so many requests for more cowbell, not that I can give you more cowbell,
but damn, I can sure give you some drum cadence, everybody.
Tyler Clark sent this one in.
It's the golden regimen marching man from Blue Springs, Missouri.
Suburb of Kansas City.
I love this.
More cadence.
So, part of what I've been, uh, thinking of here is, uh, once I figure out how to really work
with these OPML files, this is exactly the kind of stuff that I want you to be able to
click to and just pull in the, you know, this whole file is whole drum cadence.
So, you have to go hunting around for it.
I got to automate this stuff.
Got to make it easy.
Of course, when I get my four megabits of broadband, that will be a happier day.
When we talk about that later on in the show.
Also got a long distance dedication on that daily source code.
We'll just finish up one more minute of March to the stadium.
That is a curry.
Hello daily source code.
I've been a podcast listener.
The daily source code for two weeks.
And I have been a Mac user for about two weeks.
I've been a Mac user for about two weeks.
And I've been a Mac user for about two years.
And I really enjoy the program.
I enjoyed the temptations track.
I was a really jamming tune while I was driving to work in my Honda element.
I learned out of the six speakers with a subwoofer kicked in.
I hope you get your DSL stuff worked out.
And I was in England.
I lived in England 20 years ago.
And I thought British telecom was asked backwards back then.
Not surprised that they still are asked backwards.
Hang in there.
Cool program.
Love it.
Thanks buddy.
Boeing.
Was that it?
I guess it was.
A little bit of music stinger there on the outro.
Yeah.
Check that.
It's a daily source code.
Adam Curry on your MP3 player.
And if you have an audio comment send it off to me.
Adam at curry.com.
If you can keep it under three to five.
Yeah, about under five megs.
It'll be cool.
I'll just cash it to keep the email client.
Actually, I'm going to set up a separate email account for that.
And I've also been setting up new servers, new bandwidth stuff.
Getting everything ready for my trip tomorrow.
I'm going to the Netherlands.
I'll be staying in Utrecht.
My mom is going in for operation tomorrow.
So it's a big big day.
And I'll be staying in Holland for a couple of days.
Pretty much in the hotel or in the hospital.
So if I'm not in the hospital and they've really shitting visiting hours, which I've got
to work on that.
It's like five to eight.
What the hell is that?
They should have some late morning visiting hour or something.
So I'll work on that.
So I'll keep you up the speed and what's going on.
And there will be a podcast for Monday.
Although it may be late.
It may not be until late Monday.
But then hopefully I'll have some news for you as well.
I'll be tomorrow.
I said, this is a special source code because I screwed it up and just couldn't get it together
on Friday.
And it really hurt.
I got to tell you.
I had so much to say.
And I was like, I really didn't want to do a show.
But just couldn't.
Just could not.
And I still had stuff to download, which is still the hardest part.
I have to have so much preparation done without this fricking bandwidth.
Because I just can't sit here and wait 30 minutes to download one song.
I have to think days ahead sometimes.
Great news.
The latest podcasts to join the scene.
If you check out ipodder.org regularly, if you subscribe to the XML feed, the RSS feed.
NASA.
That's right.
Space boys.
Now podcasting.
They're later stories.
A lot of people jumped all over this.
Helped them out a little bit.
Setting up their feed a bit better.
We're basically naming their MP3s.
All story dot MP3.
We've been around that way.
We've already figured out what naming conventions have to be and what you need.
Let me see if they actually have any ideas.
I don't even think they have ID3 tags.
Let me see.
Probably not.
I'm just checking right now.
No.
Not at all zero.
Okay.
Well, hopefully they know how to fly those fucking things into space.
Why do workouts work?
This, by the way, is a NASA podcast.
By science at NASA.
By exploring how and why exercise causes muscles to grow.
Scientists hope to help astronauts avoid muscle atrophy.
December 10, 2004.
Most machines don't improve with use.
Old pickup trucks don't gradually become furars.
Just by driving them fast.
And the pocket calculator.
I hope you write to themselves too because this is wonderful.
This is, this is has to be the best couple minutes these days on my iPod.
This is just wonderful.
I won't change into a super computer by crunching lots of numbers.
The human body is different.
As weight lifters know, the more that people use their muscles,
the stronger they become.
And unused muscles do not remain preserved.
Neglect causes them to waste away.
All right.
Any production show notes for today's source code.
I have a link to the, to the feed.
So you can subscribe to that in your iPod or I really suggest you.
You do because it's just one of the stuff.
Just if you take it in or out of context, I guess.
It's really hilarious.
Now the entire story.
That's about five, six minutes.
It's well worth it.
Very, very funny stuff.
Hey, Adam.
This is Richard Smith from yesterday.
Radio vaulted.
New podcast.
From the cross was constant.
I was wondering if there's a way with iPod or if you can only.
Say you want the latest podcast from like say to daily source code.
Instead of downloading all of the daily source codes,
I just transferred over from a different podcast reader.
And I'm using iPod or now I'm kind of liking iPod or
it doesn't really allow me number one.
It doesn't allow me to function as.
It doesn't allow me just to download one program.
Right.
It will allow me to download all of the programs instead of just one.
I don't know if there's a setting on iPod.
I'm sure you're talking about the iPod or lemon.
But I know what I know where he's coming from now.
I think.
Is that he wants to take his subscriptions with him.
As well as his history.
And subscriptions, of course,
an OPML file is perfect as a reading list,
as a listening list, as your own personal station.
You know, although I try not to make the Tvo comparison.
When it comes to this stuff, there's really nothing wrong with it.
If you have a Tvo, you know that you're basically subscribing to shows.
And not, you don't subscribe to CBS.
You know, you subscribe to the late show with David Letterman.
So when you have all those different programs,
what you want is you want to be able to just imagine me to take those with you.
Right.
And then pop it into a Tvo at your vacation address or something like that.
Forget it.
Let's just keep it in the iPod around this easier.
So you can do that with OPML.
You can do that with a lot of regular text news aggregators.
And I believe that most of the iPoders now support
import, if not, also export of OPML.
Interesting, though, what Richard, I think, what I think he's saying is he also wants to take his history with him,
which I guess could also be contained in OPML file.
But I'm not too sure about that.
Let's just listen in a little bit more.
Also, it needs a space saver program.
So that will delete the last program played.
Oh, man.
Boy, is he actually Richard is totally asking for Tvo functionality.
Totally content management.
Another big one that the iPoder developers have to look at.
So if you're downloading the addition of the 15th,
it'll delete the 14th of the source code instead.
If you've heard that way, you can save space that way.
It's just some thoughts and ideas.
And I'm hoping that the iPoder developers will come up with in the future
and besides the OPLM stuff.
So will the OPLM's ideas also work for like the Dell DJ and some of the windows,
so it says as well.
MP3 players as well.
Really?
They work with women with MP3 players.
And he meant OPML.
He said, oh, MPL, but that's okay.
We're working with something.
So it says as well.
What's your question?
And some of the windows says as well.
MP3 players as well.
Just as few thoughts to keep the windows side of the listeners happy.
I wonder if if there's any MP3 player out there that actually can do anything with MP with OPML.
And there is good news about the iRiver iFP799.
There is indeed a way to change or upgrade the firmware so you don't have to go through all the DRM stuff.
I'll talk about that on tomorrow's source code because I've had all lined up.
I've got audio comments.
I've got links.
I've got emails.
Anything you want about hacking that up.
And I was able to put the file on there.
An OPML file onto the iRiver player.
Guess what?
It didn't do anything.
But you can see the file system.
You can browse it.
So I'm thinking that maybe, you know,
I'll have to look into the firmware or whatever that works.
Apparently someone knows what's going on with the firmware.
Maybe we can make something into the firmware that will read OPML would not be cool.
I would certainly put any MP3 manufacturer who was interested in doing that.
You know, would give them an instant audience.
You know, if think about being able to browse through show notes,
think about being able to browse through directory and setting,
you know, setting, what could you set?
I don't know.
You know, I'm sure you could, well, basically,
Tevo on the go.
Okay, quick broadband update.
As you know, I'll be in possession of some Wi-Fi for the next couple days.
So don't feel too bad for me.
I think I told you on Thursday that was it on Thursday?
Maybe it wasn't.
Yeah, I did.
I wrote on my weblog.
That's what it was.
NTL who I had this backup plan.
So I've got the easy net guys.
I've got the router to big business broadband set of four megabit down,
725k up.
They can't install until January 4th, which double sucks,
A because I won't have until January 4th.
B because I won't be here.
And it's, well, that means that it may not work by the time I get back.
I had a backup because two weeks ago I had ordered a cable modem
through NTL, which is pretty much the only cable company in the neighborhood
and they could hook us up.
And they gave me an install date of December 20th.
I wouldn't have been here either for, well,
I might have depending if they were coming in the morning after noon.
Of course, they always come at the end of the day.
They've been here either, but at least it would have been here.
And they called up earlier the week and said,
Oh, well, you know, we're sorry.
We can't make it.
It'll be the fourth of January.
I said, well, that's no good.
And you said the 20th, yeah, but we're not going to be able to make it.
But the whole point of that was that you could make it before the 20th.
You said the date.
You agreed to it with me.
Well, we're sorry.
So am I a cancel the order?
Uh-huh.
Got an email.
Was this a comment?
Yeah, that was a comment.
About the anti-L anchors.
Adam, you better believe it about NTL.
They're company with the most unbelievably arrogant call-out engineers.
And there's a fault that needs fixing and phone tech support.
You have to explain the concept of networking, too.
My personal favorite is the time I run up with a problem on a PC with two Nick Cards.
Want to a broadband mode on one for the land.
And the tech support guy told me I couldn't do that because the computer wouldn't know which of these
Cards was for which connection.
Sure, that wasn't an outsourced support.
Um, so obviously I've still been hitting Starbucks.
Oh, yeah, I had this question about why how Starbucks came up with their, uh, with their drink sizes.
You know, what's up with the tall, the Grande and the, uh, and the venti.
And comment on the weblog from James Fairbane.
Starbucks drink sizes.
They did use to have a short size.
They've got rid of it and added venti at the top end.
Venti is Italian for 20.
And refers to the 20 fluid ounces that's the volume of the drink.
And it is fricking huge.
I mean, it's like a fishbowl.
So next time you order a venti latte, take a moment to realize that you're asking for a British
pint of coffee.
Oh, and what's the scariest statistics?
One of their bigger drinks has as many calories as 37 spoons of sugar.
Oh, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
I always feel good.
Patricia actually came into on, uh, I guess that was maybe that was Thursday.
I was at Starbucks.
I was, you know, there in the corner and the little in the smelly chairs.
Put a close to the power outlet.
And also they had this, hello.
I don't know.
Because she never seen me there.
She never been to the Starbucks.
And she actually, all of a sudden, she felt like really bad.
Really, really bad for me.
And I got a top 10, the broadband top 10 from Jeff, shoot, you know, I should have,
I don't have a, like a David Letterman top 10.
Why don't I, I know what I can do.
Oh, a second.
I says what my production system will be just perfect for here.
We'll use some drum cadence here.
Well, I do the top 10 reasons.
Adam, can't get broadband access.
It is new place, curry cottage in the UK.
Number 10, the term broad ban.
A tad bit sexist, don't you think?
Number 9.
Asking for the big pipe means something altogether different and Britain.
Number 8, Starbucks is paying Adam to keep coming there for expensive lattes
and fast net access.
Number 7, overheard at NTL.
Adam Curry?
Who the bloody hell is Adam Curry?
Number 6, overheard at NTL.
If we give him two megabits per second, he'll want four megabits per second.
Where does it all end?
Number 5, overheard at NTL.
That internet thing.
He spows it to everyone to catch on.
Number 4, overheard at NTL.
It just wants it for the pawn.
Number 3, overheard at NTL.
He's got dial up.
What's the rush?
Number 2, overheard at NTL.
This guy called to order service, but all he kept saying was,
point, point, point.
And the number one reason that I'm can't get broadbed access at the cottage.
When he called NTL, he told him he was the Prince of Pod,
but the sales agent thought she heard me say Prince of Darkness.
I don't know.
I don't have like a pole that bounce off of when I bomb terribly on the top 10 list.
No, do I.
Oh, I've always got dug.
Hello, this is Doug K with IT conversations.
We didn't have a chance to put together a Gilmore gang show this week.
It's holiday season and the gang is scattered throughout the world.
So I hope what you'll do is take this opportunity to listen to some of the shows in the archives.
There's the phone ring.
That must be still Gilmore.
How coincident?
Hello Steve.
Hey Doug.
So, uh...
I think we're going to just rerack up, uh...
What?
Did it rerack it up?
The last show.
The one on identity digital identity.
We're still Winley.
And Dr. O's and Johnny Tell.
Yeah, I listened to that show.
I did.
I listened to the show.
And, uh...
You know, I haven't heard anything about it from anybody.
So, please probably a lot of people out there who haven't listened to you.
Yeah.
I listened to it.
I heard it.
Gilmore gang.
Check them out.
IT Conversations.com.
And, um...
Sounds like the, uh...
The source code and other podcasts.
I'm going to do a real good job with the lascivious bitties.
Um...
Now getting notes.
And of course, all the stuff is all in the, uh...
In the production show notes.
That the bitties are sold out on Amazon.
That's awesome.
I mean, actually it's not awesome, but it's cool.
So, um...
But you can always go to bittiesforever.com
And, uh...
Leon has emailed me that they're doing everything they can to make sure there's a...
Supply, a plenty for all you bitties fans.
And actually, they're about four bitties fans who did show up
that their show, um...
Last Tuesday in New York.
Um...
Which is cool.
And they really appreciate it.
And I think Leon's working on some kind of Christmas thing
or song.
I'm not too sure of it.
I don't know if she's going to be able to get it done at a time,
but I sure hope so.
And, um...
I love this drum cadence.
All right, stop.
I got it in the email from, uh... from Mark.
Um...
And this is a Dutch email.
So you can read that in the show notes as well.
But, uh, well, it's Dutch.
So you may not really be anything for you.
But, um...
sent me, uh...
sent... I don't know where the hell he got this.
You know, back in the day, commercials.
Actually, you know, how we now have jingles.
Um, and you'll probably remember, um...
like, uh...
Oh, depending on how old you are.
For me, one of the older, like, real long commercials,
which was maybe...
She would...
Maybe they were, like...
Well, hold on.
I probably have the coat commercials here.
Um, you know, they sold out to...
Was it... was it the new seekers?
Wasn't that it?
I'd like to teach the world the sing.
Uh, hold on.
I might have that.
In my iTunes.
Um...
Maybe under Coke.
Uh, I'd like to buy the world of Coke.
That's what it was.
Okay, hold on.
Let me just play a little bit for you.
Because literally, um...
These songs were...
What were they?
Like a minute long.
So here's just a quick example, right?
Remember this one?
Yeah.
So that was the new seekers.
But...
Essentially, even further back than this,
these used to be full songs.
I mean, they would have a beginning and ending,
and they would last up to, you know, like,
three to five minutes.
So it was real tunes.
This is actually pretty darn good example.
I remember singing that as a kid.
I love that.
So, um...
What Mark found is he found one that Patricia did,
and it has... Patricia tried to peg it.
She said it was probably around 71 72.
Um...
And it was for skull beer.
SKOL.
You probably... you probably heard of skull beer.
Uh... she says,
real apologies for the pronunciation,
but that was what it was supposed to be.
So when you hear her pronounce the English words,
kind of in a... in a... like a Dutch German Danish almost kind of way...
Apologies.
But here she is from the really old archives.
God knows where Mark found this.
Uh... singing the skull song,
which I believe she actually wrote some of the herpics for as well.
Yeah, we're gonna play here.
Come along now.
Yeah.
So the traditionalist,
it's called the traditionalist,
just a refreshing one.
It says,
you see for the reak you can be.
And by the way, this her sister Ivana is also singing in the chorus.
Trans eggplant.
yeah,
It's called the traditionalist,
call the original script.
Also,
she's sound tracks were used in the movie theatre as well,
but really long it will become her creation.
Tell me, do you want me to?
Do you want me to tell you?
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, Let's go, us go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go home, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go it's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, okay, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go Bitcoin's outta there, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go,
Christmas happy quanzachanica metoclo deononi more.
Maylake eliquitacua to all our friends in Ecuadorio, French,
Grenina.
Yeah.
And all just to Adam Curry and all of his listeners.
And did we say where we're from?
Boeing.
Wow.
Delta Park product.
Yeah.
It's a weekly show we do here on the internet.
And big, big, this is Jacobos.
Now Paul's going to sing a song.
Okay.
I didn't know it was going to be on the spot.
God rest.
Gmail, read your little man, let nothing eat us may.
I remember the but wait.
No, Jesus wasn't born on Christmas day.
Listen to our podcast.
Delta Park project.com.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
And now there's a gentleman.
Right.
That's not the song.
I'm going to put a one for you.
And now ladies and gentlemen.
Time for a long distance dedication on the daily
source code.
I need some more reverb for this.
You know I need reverb.
Reverb.
I still a bit more reverb.
Much better.
Oops.
Damn.
Dear Adam.
Yesterday I had an epiphany.
I was listening to you show on the Long Island Railroad to work yesterday morning.
Often laughing and smiling at certain parts of the show.
When a beautiful girl sat down across me and took out her green iPod mini to listen to.
I couldn't help noticing that she was laughing and smiling along to whatever she was listening
to as well.
I first thought, well she was listening to a podcast.
Could she have been listening to the same daily source code that I was listening to?
Well Adam, being the huge voice that I am, I didn't say a word.
Probably never see that girl again.
However, it got me thinking, what if iPods had Bluetooth built in?
And would broadcast your current song information to your neighbor?
It would be awesome to see what everyone else is listening to.
And it would be a great conversation starter.
I think podcasting is taking what is so far been primarily anti-social activity
listening to iPods and made it more social and interactive.
I think adding the sort of Bluetooth communication is the logical next step.
The possibilities of iPod podcasts and Bluetooth seem endless.
Okay, Dan from New York.
Luckily he gets back to the chick, right?
This room.
Oh, let's re-verb.
Yes.
If the pretty girl with red hair and the green iPod mini was sat in front of me on Tuesday's listening,
please write in.
Okay, Dan.
She hears this.
I guarantee you score my friend.
You see this guy.
This guy is in love with you.
Yes, I'm in love.
Who looks at you the way I do?
When you smile, I get to know each other.
Very well.
Okay.
I show you
from a plan
I got to know your goals.
I've heard some talk.
They say you think I'm fine.
Yes, I'm in love.
And what I do to make you mind
Down in love
isn't so don't let me be
Don't refuse to know my name
I'm in love with you
Say you're in love with this guy
If not I'll just die.
Down in love isn't so don't let me be
Don't let me be
Say you're in love with this guy
If not I'll just die
I don't just love that little D-R-M thing
I put in the middle of that
I'm sorry about that
I don't know if something froze
Anyway, I've rendered it totally useless for
You'll copy purposes
Guys and love with you on your daily source code
Winding up the show for today
And I forgot to tell you that
Now the files are going to be in three places
as some testing and some more work
Goes on behind the scenes
Dave and I are certainly working on more
The production process
So Mark is a big part of this
So now we're hosting the main file
Is on the dot mac account
Which is the one that's listed in the RSS feed
For the daily source code
Then there is the backup
Which we're running on the OPML.org server
And check this out
As well we actually had it for a little while now
But as of today also listed in the production show notes
A direct bit torrent download link for the daily source code
I'm not going to be putting that in the RSS file
Just yet we've got lots of stuff to work on
We have this namespace to connect that up to it
But if you want to check it out
It has the same naming convention
As you're used to for the files
On the OPML.org server
Check out the show notes for today's podcast
And you'll be able to link into that
It's just kind of the geeky part of the bit torrent stuff
Until we get that all automated
And that's going to do it for me
For now tomorrow
I am off to Holland
And I'll have some bandwidth baby
So as always
Comments are welcome email
AudioComments, Adam & Curry.com
If you keep it under 5 megs
Go ahead and just shoot it off and email
And attach it
No problem
We'll download overnight
Everything now is a Curry.com
So that's the best place to leave comments
And also subscribe to daily source code podcasts
www.curry.com
I will bring you a podcast tomorrow
With news on my mama
And everything else that happens
Between here and tomorrow
Take care everybody
See you