Well, good afternoon everybody! Welcome to the Daily Source Code, coming to you live!
Almost live. Bit delayed, maybe it was yesterday, maybe it's tomorrow. It's from
Flanders Belgium from Curry Castle. This is your daily...
Oh boy, got a lot of stuff lined up for you today. I know I always say that.
on a quick Skype call to Dave Weiner and I said you know I could do the stuff I
receive every single day I could put together three source codes it's just
how do I weed through all this stuff to find the good things right well
basically my iPod are does a
I've got a what's new playlist set up. It's a smart list. So basically the rules are it's just like an email
If it's happened to be played before and it's in this category then
line it up.
And that's how I get all kinds of cool tunes and stuff coming off the blog
dear
mp3 feeds.
Just so much so much stuff coming in.
And this is the source code where of course users and developers make the
pot-tay happen.
And I got to tell you last night I could barely sleep.
It was all day yesterday.
I was doing interviews mainly with journalists based on
the West Coast.
So it was LA Times, Wired magazine, Business Week, which was she was in
New York, had a great, great chat with her.
Susan is a she's an old radio pirate herself.
I'm expecting a cool article.
Let's see who else that I talked to.
I talked to publication in Minneapolis, St.
Paul, hoping of course to reach a prince through that interview.
And, oh man.
There we go. Leo La Porte has a radio or whatever.
So, he's going to interview me tomorrow.
That'll be a radio interview.
I've been doing just so much work on this that I got in bed last night and I just had
URL ipodder.org circling my head and I started to, I got like cold.
had to pull out a fan to cool down and to walk around.
I was buzzing.
I was just electrified, full of energy.
You know what that's like when you can't sleep?
It's just like sparks flying off your brain, man.
So that usually means that I'm really excited about something,
and I am because this is just so nice,
everything that's taken place.
So I've got a couple of songs that I want to play for you.
Of course, I also want to talk about some iPod'r stuff.
just bringing up the speed on what the latest developments are and what's going on.
And I've finally had some time this morning to start updating the directories on iPodder.org.
And I'm far from finished. What's cool about the directory, you have two. One is the software
directory. Now I'm still working on getting all that together. It's a little harder to
figure out who's doing what and where. But since I voiced that concern, I'm getting a lot of
emails with the introduction saying, okay, we're the new iPodder.net team. Here's who we are.
If you go to iPodder.org and you go to the shows directory, there's a hyperlink and you
click on it and you get a form and you can say, okay, I want to add this show.
Just type in the URL and the RSS feed of your show and I'll add that to the directory.
That resource is finally picking up a little bit.
But I also want to do a redesign and just get this a little bit tighter and make it
a little more efficient for everybody.
I've had some excellent offers of help.
Gregory is offered to help.
So I'm working on setting up some stuff to make it a little more easy to work with.
See what else we've been doing.
Oh, here's something.
Actually, I'll talk about that in a second when I get to iPodder.
First I want to do a request song that came in from...
Ray, I think it was, yeah, it was Ray Slakinsky.
I think I hope I pronounced that right.
Ray, I think he got me started on some bit torrent stuff.
He wrote a Python script.
I believe he's the author of Nucleus, which to this day,
I still have running up on my cloud in the server space
somewhere.
It just scans the supernova bit torrent files
for certain keywords.
If it finds one, then it pulls it in,
and then it downloads the file from the bit torrent.
And then, of course, also lets me know.
It notifies me that there's something new.
So that's how I get all my recent TV shows,
my American TV shows.
And he requested.
He's also obviously involved in a lot of iPod development.
And he said, dude, why don't you
play this song by Julia Hatfield?
Because this song happens to be about sticking it to the man.
I can just hear Dave Slusher.
His ears are perking up there in Carolina.
Wait a minute.
We're sticking it to the music man, to the music business.
So let's just get a little vibe going.
here on this Tuesday on the SuperSource Code with Julie Hatfield. This is Sell Out!
Right on. This is the Daily Source Code. I'm Adam Curry. Glad to have you along for the ride.
Okay. A couple more notes about iPodder. If you've been following along with the developments on iPodder.org,
I'm happy to let you know that we have three new Windows versions coming out
that will work with a variety of MP3 players and playlist management systems.
The installs, I've been beta testing some of the installs look really, really good.
System tray icons, all the stuff you'd expect as a Windows user
and I've actually broken out the Windows laptop to try and figure,
try and install them and see what they're doing. The Java version is pretty cool too.
I mean, it's just so much. But what it all comes down to when we've discussed this
on the iPodder development list is making sure that users get that first, oh wow, experience.
And I've had some varying results in the past, well in the past couple of weeks.
Basically, I've heard a lot of this banter going on saying, well you want your...
mom to be able to figure it out.
And that of course is true.
So it's all about the defaults.
And one thing that we've kind of been sloundering around with is what happens when you first
install an iPod or what is the first experience.
Currently, we've whittled it down to you subscribe to a feed or a couple of feeds and
it's going to go and get the first couple of shows on the first pass round.
Just so you're not plugging up your machine or you're bandwidth, you're getting some
joy at that first moment.
You're like, oh well, it's working.
But we thought this through a little bit more and after some conversation on the
list and also some requests came in through email is for a default feed and
a default file.
Now just hack something together, which is going to have to live with for now.
I'm not really happy with the URL, but we're going to.
to come off of iPodder.org so that it's identifiable as the default feed.
So essentially, if you're developing an iPodder right now, you put this feed in as your default
subscription to give the users an idea of what a URL looks like.
It'll end in .xml, which of course not all RSS feeds do.
But when you see it, it's a little easier to visualize.
And the feed basically will just sit there and be dormant.
It only has one file in it.
So that means it's going to bring in that file.
It's half a meg.
to get pretty much instant joy as a user.
And well, I'll do that.
Actually, I have it right here.
I'm just going to play the default welcome
that you will get whenever you flip open an iPod or upon a first install.
And if you have any ideas about how to make this better,
I just try to keep it short to the point as simple.
It's surely let me know.
So once you install iPod or if you hear the following,
you know that it worked.
Hi, I'm Adam Curry.
Welcome to the iPod platform.
Hearing this message means you have successfully installed
iPod on your computer and you should see a new playlist
on your MP3 player titled iPod test channel containing this file.
You now can add any URL that points to an RSS feed with enclosures
to automatically receive new podcasts by subscription.
You can use iPod.org as your guide to new software, news,
and pointers to new podcast directories and services.
We really hope you enjoy receiving and creating your podcasts.
And please remember, this stuff's supposed to be...
fun. So enjoy. Right. And I'm going to take the stick out of my ass. All right. There we
go. So anyway, it's just a, it's a placeholder now. And if we come up with a better script
or I'm not too happy with, you know, the, the just briefly passing over an RSS URL,
you know, is it, is it simple enough? Will people, will people get it? Do you need any
kind of knowledge of RSS? I'll tell you a lot of the journalists that I spoke to hadn't
actually used the news aggregator. They've heard of it. You know, they're working
on it. Yeah, I want to test that at home. One of them, I think it was the reporter
from Daniel, the reporter from Wired. He was using newsgator. So he was, you know,
very advanced and he knew that it synced up with this machine at home and the
machine at office, at the office. So there's all different levels, but I want
to make it as simple as possible. And maybe we need more fanfare and, and, and
some fun stuff or more production. But at any rate, now we have a default
feed. And if you want me to change that or change, you know, if you think there's any
ideas for the MP3, the first welcome MP3. And I think we can do better.
better. But just let me know. This is just a placeholder for now.
Okay, I already mentioned that I'm updating the show's directory.
Just a couple of pages I found around the net.
I'm going to go to this now, I hope. Let's see.
Russell Beatty wrote a pretty, and of course as you saw from
yesterday's show, I'm now linking to all these resources that I'm talking about
source code. And he wrote quite a nice bit about podcasting.
Let's see if I want to get a quote from here.
Now what he's basically saying is he's identifying something
I think I feel happening as well. Is it going to be the MP3 player
or is it going to be your mobile phone? And I think that they're
two sides of the same coin. We have MP3 players doing a beautiful job
playing and organizing MP3s and mobility and battery life.
And we have this basically this asynchronous...
where you connect your iPod to your machine
and it updates with new stuff thanks to iPod or whatever
you know, whatever you downloaded and paid for
if it comes to music it will also
automatically sync up your machine.
And of course what the iPod is screening for
is some type of connectivity that is wireless.
So I can fully see that being Bluetooth,
I can see it being WiFi, but also I could see it being
third generation cell network.
Could be UMTS or GPRS or ABC Element OP
whatever the hell all these acronyms are for
because a lot of cell phones now have MP3 players inside.
And I think that this is all just a function
of what kind of iPod or software do you need?
It seems to me that most handheld devices these days
are a lot of them are running Java.
So I think the Java iPod or development
is gonna be really important for cell phones.
Their storage capacity is growing but leaps and bounds
whether it's a...
half a gig now. I have a half a gig of my camera which fits happily in my cell phone.
Granted, the OS, just the power of the process, takes a little while to create a directory
listing everything that's on the card, but it does work. And you can certainly store
stuff on it. And what a cell phone does really well is connectivity. It's good at roaming,
it's good at picking stuff up, and it can be made intelligent to grab stuff off of the
network during off-peak hours. There's just all kinds of all kinds of ways to do that.
And I think that that's why iPod.org is going to be important for quite a while now
because this is
I've got this type of device.
I want to get my podcasts on it automatically.
How do we make this happen?
So that is the resource for you.
And Russell is saying that he thinks, and I got to agree to a certain extent, that he
feels that cell phones will get there quicker than the rest.
Hi, hon.
Bring me a candle.
Thank you.
Aromatherapy?
Relaxing.
What? Don't stick them where?
Those, those batteries.
Uh-huh. Thank you.
Go to Sada.
Yeah, yeah.
Patricia just came home from doing grocery shopping.
And she's totally into the production chain now.
She brought me two 9 volt batteries because I seem to eat a lot of food.
Thank you.
And I said, please go get him.
And well, she told me where I could put him.
And you know what?
The sun don't shine.
Anyway, also had a, let's see, there was a,
Scobal had an interesting post, Robert Scobal from Microsoft,
who was also becoming, you know, really quite a cheerleader
in all of the stuff.
Hold on a second.
I can find it.
Well, basically there was a conversation about iPods
with Steve Ballmer of Microsoft.
And I'll point to this as a part of the post for this podcast.
Scobal pointed out a lot of that conversation
and there's a transcript of it.
And well, I guess the bottom line is, you know, all,
everyone who uses an iPod as a pirate, right?
You're a thief.
That's kind of the gist of it.
And Scobal says, whoa, wait a minute.
You know, hold on.
That just ain't true.
Or at least he posted about this.
And because what we're doing with these podcasts, you know,
bar the music rights that we may or may not be infringing upon,
which is easily solved by not.
doing that, the content of the message is in the message, right?
But that's also solvable, I think.
You should be able to license that.
We've talked about that before.
But the one thing I'm really happy about is because I played a bit from the Gilmore Gang
yesterday.
The Gilmore Gang actually is posted now, so I don't feel too bad about previewing a
bit on yesterday's source code before the show was even up.
I think it was Steve Gilmore talking about Scoble pulling stuff out of his ass and
being such a supporter of this stuff.
And I said, yeah, you never underestimate the bandwidth of Scoble's ass.
Well, apparently he almost crashed while he heard that.
I got to be careful.
I should say warning, I'm going to talk about you now.
Be careful.
Put down your coffee.
Don't be dreaming.
Don't be driving a car.
Yesterday I had Hugo Schottmann on the show just briefly.
And I do want to hook up with him later this week or maybe over the weekend.
Hugo is really leading the charge in a lot of the set ups of how we get our audio working.
And we need more help.
We need people.
who were doing podcasting on Windows to send in screenshots, advice, just give me a URL
to point to because it's such a small percentage and I'm now even getting the questions, well,
if I just get a Mac, will that solve all of my production issues?
And no, in fact, I think it should be just as easy if not remembering a little bit of
how the PC architecture works, maybe even easier. It's just all kind of hidden within Windows.
Not that it's not, you know, that it's not hidden within a Macintosh, but in Windows you have a
little mixer panel and I know that you can you can mix and match audio feeds because I've done it,
I've done this before on Windows. So we really need some help on that. And while we're on that
topic, Rogamiba software who makes Audio Hijack Pro for the Mac and as they say themselves,
have no plans on porting to Windows, I think they're pretty close for the Mac, you know,
close on understanding what we need and they've got a weblog, I don't know if it's the head
of development but there's a weblog at rogomeba.com which of course will also point to.
We just got to keep the conversation going because they're the guys for the Macintosh
that can make this happen.
Something else and I really want to you know put a big shout out to the Skype Skype developers team.
We're working on Skype for Mac OS I think we're now at beta.
Let's check.
I have it running here.
Where beta, come on, about Skype.
What does it say?
Beta 0.10.0.1.
Right on.
You know, so obviously I'm not complaining too much because it is working
and by far it has the best sound quality far and above iChat, AV with AIM,
far and above the X10 stuff.
Skype really has the quality going and they seem to be able to keep
the connection a little bit longer.
But if we need to get to the developers of Skype, I don't know,
I'm sure on PC it's a little more advanced.
It was born on the Windows platform.
But for the Mac there's only one thing we need to make it the,
well two things, to make it the perfect application for enhancing
a podcast and doing a little bit more.
The main thing is we need to be able to switch
audio devices that the application uses.
Now this is, I know it's, and none of the, I'm sure none of this is trivial, you know,
when I just want to make one little thing happen in my iPod or script, it took me two weeks.
I broke everything and overwrote old code and, you know, it's, by no means trivial.
But a lot of Mac applications that use the core audio driver allow you to select between
different audio devices. So where you can, on the built-in audio device, you can select between
the default or line in or your built-in microphone. But I can also choose a virtual audio device,
like Soundflower, which we talked about, or an external one, like the DigiDesign breakout box.
But Skype doesn't allow you to set those preferences. And I think that it's, well,
from a development standpoint, what needs to be done is those hooks need to be put in,
so that you can select that in the preferences. Once we do that, you know, then, first of all,
it'd be a lot more stable because high-jacking applications.
applications and then adding applications to it that really aren't talking to the sound
drivers in the same way, just like Skype does currently, makes for shit to happen.
It crashes, it can just disappear, sometimes it gets really slow and buggy, and logging
may even be on for all I know within the beta client.
But if we have any way to get in touch with the developers, let me know, because
we need their help.
And we can make their product better.
And add to that the ability to conference two calls together.
And then we're really talking, because with Skype out, you can basically make a
phone call anywhere in the world for about four or five cents a minute.
And the quality is equal to actually sometimes, because you're just calling
a landline phone, it's a little bit worse than if you're calling someone directly.
What I'd like to do is I'd like to be able to make a Skype call with Dave,
for instance, that'll be a direct Skype call, no phone system in between.
And then like the conference in, another person or a phone call, you know, if we could add
one or two more lines to Skype then it would be great.
So any help that we can get on that is way appreciated.
Did you know that there's a new movie coming out about the life and times of Peter Sellers?
I saw one of the actors, a couple of the actors were on a late night talk show in England
while we were there over the weekend.
And it looks like a great movie.
And while I was thinking of that and just running through the iTunes playlist today,
I bumped across something that is classic Peter Sellers in reminiscence of the Beatles that
we played on Trade Secrets the other day.
Here's Peter doing his rendition of She Loves You.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is the end of the video.
Thank you for watching.
I have made several experiments and I have come to this conclusion.
So?
You think that you have lost your love?
Well, I saw her yesterday.
It is you that she is thinking of and she has helped me ever to say.
She says she loves you.
Yeah!
Yeah?
Yo!
Ya!
She loves you!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha!
He said,
You hurt her so!
Good!
She almost lost her mind!
Good job!
And now she says,
She knows that you're not the hurting kind.
She says she loves you.
Ya!
She loves you!
You know,
It's up to you.
I think that it's only fair.
I can hurt you too.
She loves you
BOOF BOOF BOOF
Alright, Peter Sellers, she loves you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, here on the source code,
and only a version that Peter Sellers...
some tunes, because hey, it's Tuesday.
It's like it's the day when we kind of are getting over Monday, you know, just getting
to the vibe of things.
Grace Jones pull up to the bumper.
I'm not a problem for me.
I'm not a woman who goes into a maze.
For love, you're a problem for me.
You don't have to be.
I'm not a problem for me.
For love, you're a problem for me.
Don't ride,
go away.
Wagging,
unquiet,
all right.
This night.
All the way down the hall,
the lord of you and me.
This place forever.
One you my friend
Life is short of it's walk
One you see tomorrow
Shining in the dream
You leave your heart on your heart
Short of you, my love
Can you love me more, see
You know, I just realized you were probably doing exactly what I was doing.
The minute a little break happened, you like crank up the volume, I did that on my laptop
Damn if I didn't fuck up the reporting
If Jones pull up to the bumper, baby, and drag it straight into Queens on the source code,
so that's lesson learned.
Do not turn up the volume on your Macintosh while doing a podcast.
So many things that...
There are times when I just say, screw it, I want to get all my mixing equipment out,
all my outboard gear and just only use the computer to record it.
I get as far as...
I go to the closet and I'm going to open this up and get all my gear out because I
know it's going to be perfect.
I say, no, we've got to figure out how to make this work.
We are very close.
We're getting a lot better.
I've got the next trade secrets that I do with Dave.
I hope to have a good Skype quality call.
So we're working on all of this test.
By the way, thanks to Tom from Down Under for the Peter Sellers Hard Days Night link.
He sent me that one.
Tom also, by the way, has been following my radio career since the early 80s.
Even at the Pirate Radio Station, I was working at an Amsterdam.
I had a radio show which started around 83, 84, which I did with a partner called Curry
and Van Inkel.
His name was Van Inkel, of course.
And, you know, we did hundreds of hours of radio and I have hundreds of...
of skimmer tapes and the skimmer tape is basically when you're on the air live and you crack
the microphone then it starts recording and these are all cassette supports, that was
the technology of the day.
Really basically just a micro switch, you open up the fader on your mixing board or
you open up that channel and it clicks the pause switch and it starts to record the
air signal so that after the show you can go back and listen to yourself and listen
to if you sucked or not, which of course we all think we sucked and that's a skimmer
tape and that's also an air check tape which you'll hand to the next program
director down the line say hey here's my stuff that I did on station A.
And what Tom has done, he's jumped on the iPodder wagon.
And he is, and I added it to the directory, to the iPodder.org shows directory,
and it's much more for my benefit.
But he's put his entire archive, he's loading that up into RSS files, which is great.
And I'm sending him two boxes of tapes as we're about to move.
I'm so happy I can do this.
I'm sending it off to Australia, and he's going to digitize all that.
And I guess he's going to put those on the feed as well.
So that's just another perfect use of this kind of technology.
If you do a show, if you do a live radio show, you're working at a quote real radio station,
then get an MP3 archive going, and just add that to your RSS feed so
that you can expand your listenership overnight.
Just briefly talking about a couple more things we could use.
If you're thinking about doing a podcast, and really a podcast,
it sounds like we're doing all this difficult stuff.
But if you have the balls to record your own voice, then you're already there.
And you can do that on almost any computer today.
You don't have to get fancy with mixing in songs and tunes.
You can even sit in your car and play something on the CD radio.
Car is great because you sit in your car while it's not moving preferably.
You've got a closed sound environment.
You're mobile so if it's loud, where the ambient noise is loud, where you are, just
don't...
You've got a power supply, you can start recording, and you can use your CD player, you can use
your cassette player, you could use your MP3 player connected to your car stereo, and just
put a mic...
It'll work.
It'll be a little, it's a hack, but it'll work.
And I've heard people do it.
But more importantly, if there's anything that you're an expert on, just like web logging,
if you do a top five stock picks of the day, record it.
And if you don't know how to make an RSS 2.0 feed out of it, let me know.
We'll try and help you out.
Or just join the mailing list.
Just check out iPodder.org.
We're happy to help.
Short is good.
Short stuff is really good.
I'd love to have just a little quote of the day.
You know, if someone could do one quote of the day, there's lots of quotes of the day services,
but they're all text based.
So here's something you could do.
You wouldn't have to write.
All you have to do is every single day just record these two lines and then whoever the
quote was by.
And it'd be nice if you could post the quote in text and link to the source or whatever
if we wanted to have it.
But those types of things I love to see on my playlist.
A joke of the day.
A stand up routine of the day.
These things really work.
Why do you think David Letterman's talk...
top 10 list is so phenomenal.
By the way, Dave, if you're listening, Dave Letterman,
give us the top 10 list.
Cut an audio recording of that and make a feed
so we can listen to it every day.
We love the top 10 list.
I shouldn't have worked on the iPod platform.
I think it will.
Okay, one more thing I picked up.
This is in the Equal Airtime Department.
I picked up from the Blog Digger Media Feed.
We've done lots of songs and mixes about President Bush,
so it's time for one about the next president
of the United States, John Kerry.
Democrats got a man named John.
Got no clue what...
Flip, flopper and roll in the equal airtime segment on your daily source code.
Hold on a second, phone is ringing.
I'm expecting a call actually.
So you know what, we're gonna leave it at that for today because I do have phone calls
coming in and I'm gonna get this compressed and shoot it up to the server for consumption.
If you want to respond, drop an email at adamantcurry.com.
Of course, the archives.
iPod or Fee, the RSS 2.0 with enclosures.
dailysourcecode.com slash RSS.
The power of your intelligence.
And of course, as always, my own.
Weblog live.curry.com
And keep those podcasts coming everybody.
Take care, bye!