Welcome to the podcast from the Kate and Jid is the daily source code this is where
users and developers party together hold on hold on I see you over there developer come on out come on join the party
you users over there on the left come on out on the dance floor
today is Wednesday it's December 1st 2004 we're supposed to say rabbit rabbit bunny bunny
whatever the heck it is it's supposed to bring you good luck and I wish all of that for all of you
coming to you from the United Kingdom where we're learning more about local culture every single day
this is your daily source code I'm Adam Curry it is seven minutes till 10 in the evening
I'm still a bit behind on my production schedule that of course is because of the
complete lack of bandwidth more about that later on in the show because I do have some good news to
report when it comes to DS 3 letters of the album that are so important to me well that
and KLA I guess that's still important maybe see easy is one two three okay I kind of a
sad note to start off on for today's daily source code we've been waiting for it and then
I know that sounds kind of macabre but the Netherlands has been waiting for quite a while and finally
father of the Dutch Queen Beatrix died today at 93 we're an artist we know was diagnosed with cancer
in November last week tumors had spread to his stomach lungs causing a great difficulty with breathing
he'd really been on the edge of life for probably at least five to ten years so it wasn't
didn't come as a as a complete surprise but still very sad day and the whole country is in
mourning and the country has had a lot to mourn recently you know that of course the death of
Theo von Hoch, the Dutch filmmaker before that two years ago Pimfortan politician in the meantime
close the the Queen's husband passed away and now her dad so she's also having she's not having
a very good year that's for sure and and Bernard was an interesting character I'll just tell you
a little bit about him that I know you probably heard of him in relation to the Lockheed scandal apparently
the allegation was that he took some kind of bribe to get Lockheed some business with the F-14 I
think it was and he took a million dollar bribe but I'm not too sure if that was ever successfully
proven and and what exactly that was about I certainly don't think he needed a million dollars I
think the royal family is wealthy enough the prince set up the world wildlife fund and that you know
the you probably recognize the logo by the panda bear so he's done a lot of work with that he
also was one of the founders of the building bird group I think he might have had something
to do with the Paris club as well very very influential on the on the young the huge
uber scale of money in the world and the prince always wore an orange flower a red flower I'm
sorry was it red flower no white flower a white flower there you go god I really I really know
what I'm talking about and rumor has a religion has it that he also drank a glass of honey
can beer every single morning for breakfast of course it being a fine-dutch product but he also
said that it really got him going was very healthy to have a glass of beer one glass of beer in the
morning at breakfast or maybe just after breakfast any loved his cars he had Ferrari's lots of
Ferrari's later in his life he didn't drive himself but he'd have his driver drive his Ferrari and
it's it next to him and he was rumored to have women all over the world and a couple of village
other illegitimate children you know exactly what you want from your prince you know he was in
all I think was really cool and we will certainly certainly miss him on the on the political
and on the royalty scene as well okay moving right along from death let's go on to what happened this
morning nine o'clock my phone started ringing and it was the BBC I guess my number is now
known at the BBC and so anyone who works at the BBC gives me a call this was lovely lady from
BBC world now I used to listen to the world service all the time when I was especially when I was
commuting back and forth between Belgium and and the Netherlands the radio studio in the morning
I really like to listen to it and it has an incredible reach the entire world does literally
tune into the BBC world service and so they said well we want to do a segment on podcasting
and we'd like to do that at 12 25 this morning like okay so who dropped out you know who couldn't
make it no no no this will be perfect and you know whatever so I said well you know I can call
in or whatever you said oh no we have a studio and gilford of course you do so even though
their main studios in London they have a studio which is actually a part of the BBC SCR which is
South Coast radio learned about that yesterday as I got a little education on the FM dial that I
had scanned and they do have a studio right on the campus of Surrey University and so she said oh I
have a card pick you up and the car was going to come at a quarter to 12 excuse me I'm a
one a day remember there we go so the car was going to come pick me up at a quarter to 12
like 10 after 12 I figured I'm going to call and and Marion called me and said no well the
driver's sitting outside your house said no he's not wrong address you figured it out so
finally what happens is you know real nice guy cab driver races you know off with me to get to
the studio on time get into the studio do the thing do a live bit it was good you know the basic
simple questions what is podcasting where is it going what do you think blah blah so did that bit
and then waited around a little bit for a car to drive me back and I was back around 115 and
that was just the beginning of the day then I helped Patricia we cleared out the dining room which
was basically filled with paintings had to put all of those up in the attic because we just don't
have enough space for all of our collection so we we've made some choices what we're going to hang
up in the cottage so spent a lot of time moving stuff up from downstairs up to the attic taking
stuff out to the garage tonight by the way is trash night kind of another humongous load which
have to separate between cardboard and all the other stuff so I'm going to do that before I hit the
hay and actually started putting some of the paintings up which meant one or two holes that
needed to be drilled and I'm really not good at this I can do it I guess but we're getting close we're
getting very close to making this extremely livable I'm really happy about that nice cup of tea
a lot of people mess about my mom and how she's been doing and I realized that I haven't really
given an update in a while I've given people updates privately who asked about it who inquired
and so we've been through all the tests and two weeks ago the final test were done and it turns out
my mom is a perfect candidate for an operation so there's no spread of the disease it's
all still in the lower portion of her lung the doctors feel confident they can do with removing half
of her lung but at this point they basically say well if you wake up and you have one tube sticking
out of you we removed half along if it's two tubes we removed a full lung either way she'll be able
to live on and and function on one lung if necessary in the lung cancer world this is really
really good news and we're extremely happy now we're just waiting for the spot in line
for you know I guess basically I'm going to call up two days before before she can go in
for the operation so we're all kind of waiting for that and there are the people who have you know
who need you know I have priority I need to go ahead of her we're still hoping that'll happen
before Christmas so we are looking forward to that thank you all so much once again for all your
your love and your prayers and all your thoughts it's it's really been amazing and very
very helpful to the entire family and big Dave Jacobs you might have seen this on Dave winters web
blog Friday six o'clock in the morning Pacific time he gets his new kidney and that
incredible news I didn't know that I guess everything just happened all at once you know
as far as I know how this works you know you get a call you got the kidney schedule the
operation boom so six o'clock Pacific time on Friday fingers crossed that'll be let me see
six a.m. 12 it'll be two p.m. in London on Friday so I'll be we will have all fingers crossed here
for big Dave Jacobs our love thoughts go out to you and I heard a speaking of Dave winters
I heard his morning coffee notes boy Dave has a lost his voice it was so cool for him to do
from the do a podcast regardless of him losing his voice I encourage you to listen to this if
you're a user or developer which means everyone listening to this show should listen to that
morning coffee notes all I mean just put a link to that right now so you know where to get that online
I'm doing that in my production show show notes so you'll be able to click right on it and get
morning coffee notes for December 1st 2004
So listen to that because it's a lot about being a developer being a user and how do we party together
at the end Dave put in a nice special message for me which I'll never buddy ever Bob
This was for you Adam it's it's what's 16 minutes into it and
you could probably get yourself to Starbucks in the time it takes you listen to this thing maybe less
Anyway, I just actually want to add that one out one note is that boy do we miss you Adam
man get your fucking uh you know get your high speed internet line so we can like do some of it
you know we miss you man and put it that's empathetic yeah and you're to add tip to my
my very good friends Don Andrew going on who are I just love both of them to piece I think
they're the greatest people in the world and you know I don't care even if she is bitchy
even if she is bitchy stay away from my woman whina still my favorite anyway
Alright thank you Dave and actually I saw that you've done the morning coffee notes
I didn't have time to get the Starbucks today so Patricia I went out for dinner and I just
threw on the uh the modem and downloaded the all seven megs while we were out to dinner and it was
there sitting for me when I got back so here's the good news tomorrow Ben with arrives at the
cottage today special delivery my ADSL modem showed up it's a beautiful 56 megabyte
per second wireless router plugged it in of course the DSL light was flashing meaning there was no
DSL service I gave the guys a call they said no problem tomorrow they kicked the switch
in the exchange and everything should be working no more intervention is needed your DSL line should
stop flashing and then you'll be up and rolling I did not by the way go with BT with British telecom
I'm not going to tell you who I went with yet the reason I didn't go with BT is because they still
have a uh a bandwidth cap 30 or not just bandwidth traffic actual data limit so there's 30
gigabytes per month and that's it and I'm like new bin down that road don't want to witness that again
I asked them I said are you sure you don't have any other kind of package no so there were a couple
of other providers providing good speeds and unlimited unmetored bandwidth so I went with one of those
so far so good everything seems to be doing okay tomorrow hopefully everything will just magically
pop on it'll all work and I'll be back um because and it's funny because I talked a
day about this before you know I said I'm hurting so bad you know with with the bandwidth because
just your life slows down to a tenth of the speed that you had forget uploading and downloading
podcasts I mean that's virtually impossible email attachments uh just you know ordering uh playing tickets
or hotel room everything takes so much longer it's just it's excruciating and Dave said
hey ma'am we are hurting along with you and I thought and said you know fuck it's true it is we're all
hurting you know I need my Skype calls and I need to be back in touch so tomorrow and I think still
we did a pretty good job within two weeks of getting uh phone line because I had I went from zero to
to DSL if we can get everything right and then Saturday the uh satellite guys show up I've ordered
a couple of sky boxes uh including the one with the digital hard drive uh primarily so we can get
our teenage daughter out of the living room with the only TV is right now with that free view box
lover to death but we've got you know she and she needs to have her own spot too you know
wish you she likes to sit in front of the TV watch corang TV or MTV or whatever other uh music
television she usually watches and then she wants to be on her laptop sit there on MSN chatting with her
with her friends you know and and then SMSing messages back and forth on the cell phones that's what
they do so gotta get that set up so that should be done by Saturday and then we're pretty good
you know got my credit cards uh local bank accounts uh actually paid my uh my phone bill online today
we have uh we're setting up our life and it feels really really good um and it'll be even better
when we have all of the the bandwidth we need coming in which also means by the way that uh we
get our phone line back because it's tough man sharing one phone line between two people who want
to be in the internet and you know people who want to call us and uh Patricia wants to call and
it gets expensive just doing on a cell phones even though there's not that much price difference anymore
and by the way I can't wait to use my Skype out account again because you know that's the cheapest
the cheapest way uh to make any kind of phone call and the quality is great and I'm just
things are looking up I'm really happy about that and I got an email as we continue to learn more
about the UK culture and inventions uh comment from anonymous connect anonymous connect says
Alexander Bell was born and mostly educated in Scotland before briefly living in Canada
he moved to the states when he was 20 through 23 and as you can see from his page on uh uh the
mother corps website here in Canada it is said that he dreamed up the telephone in Canada
and then constructed it in the states so here we have so we have uh uh all three nations have
some claim to Alexander Graham Bell uh depends of course you're talking to educated in Scotland
inspired in Canada empowered in the United States interesting isn't it history and how one
person's history doesn't necessarily have to be the other person's history got a Skype call from
Lee Wilkins yesterday uh the Jenny and Lee show Jenny and Lee uh the Jenny and Lee show dot com I
think is there a podcast a website address and he contacted me through Skype and then through cell
phone then he had a real horrible story just a sob story about his wife Jenny and him and uh and
their dogs and moving back and forth and uh it's it's a horrible story where you know the company
he was working for moved into the states and then within a week they had to move back because it
wasn't working out or something had gone wrong and because they had moved their dogs out they couldn't
move them back in because they didn't have the rabies shot so the dogs are now stuck somewhere in
Atlanta they have to have the dogs flown in from Atlanta because Atlanta or Delta messed up the
flights then they go into quarantine for six months so I wanted to get Lee on Skype and talk to
him about it and see if uh the podcasts community might want to help out and shipping a little bit
because they're really I mean I know how they feel because we had at least we had the same scare you know
that uh that are dogs and cats we have to go into quarantine uh but now Lee can't even get his
animals back from and they're they're little uh Jack Russell Terriers oh man they're so cute
and they're in Atlanta somewhere so I'm going to oops sorry about that don't hit the microphone
it sounds really unprofessional um I'll uh when I've been with Tomar I'm going to get Lee on Skype
and we'll get the whole story yes they also talked about um one of the problems that I'm
seeing with the iPod or at least the problem is kind of the vacation button um where
if you've been away or haven't you know been up to haven't been able to suck in your current
subscriptions or like me you've been van with challenged you know what you don't want is to reconnect
and then um basically the scan takes so long because it won't just bring in the latest dawn
and drew show it brings in every single dawn and drew show that I've missed in that period that
I've been gone and uh I was thinking that we need some kind of functionality for that and then I got an
email from um from Arabic and I've put this into the pod show notes even though it's in Dutch
someone might have appreciated um everyone is uh one of the creators of Doppler Doppler 1.1 and uh
he says that on Doppler if you right click on a feed you can select uh a contextual menu called
catch up catch up see a TCH space up so not catch up but catch up catch up uh and then what it does
is it adds every enclosure into the download history but without actually downloading it so you can
go back and download those download those later but basically you say you know catch up skip everything
but remember that you didn't actually download it but pretend like you didn't download it for now so
you can just get the latest stories and that's great of course Doppler uh only works on Windows
which is uh a bummer but uh I think there's some uh some art to look for there that uh that is useful
for other iPodders because you know what people do eventually go on vacation and we've got a big
one coming up Christmas holidays so we don't want to have people you know breaking their uh
their hard drives with you know by reconnecting and having to suck in all this stuff and and really
losing a lot of the benefit of what iPodder brings to the table and now um a little bit from uh
Ray was a witch was a witch was a witch not me to only got an eye neither of us can pronounce
his name right and Tony works with him there's uh ICM raw news for uh yesterday
thank you you are clear to voice print identification you see we're on a mission from
guy it's Tuesday November 30th 2004 and this is the news about independent Christian music
my name is Rick Wes Whips Chronos will be in concert on December 17th 2004
at the Jehovah Java coffee shop in Salem Missouri for more information check out their website
across music.com and this Saturday wobble performed with Sarah McKinnon in Chandler, Arizona
for more information check out their website at wobba.net and the verse the day is Proverbs 11 verse 30
the fruit of the righteous is a tree of life and he who is wise wins souls and an additional news
after winning 74 games of jeopardy and $2.5 million software engineer Ken Jennings lost this evening
and that brings this edition of the news to a close have a great night bye bye
specifically for you the independent Christian music raw news because it's a great example of a really
short podcast you know it's a minute and 20 seconds lot of information in there um i don't know
I just kind of like it and it's Rick Wes Whips yeah I was pretty damn close on that um excellent you
can find that in the ipod.org directory listed of course under the well it should not just only be
listed under religious podcasts but it is um and uh ICM independent Christian music news
gonna make it a short show today what are we 20 minutes into the podcast again because well
parsium uploading uh from the modem once again hopefully for the last time tonight uh secondly
i didn't have any time to go off to uh to my uh my uh bandwidth watering hole starbucks and
and grab all the latest music and podcasts and so i should start catching up by tomorrow
by the weekend i'll be completely okurant uh so just don't have all the stuff i usually like to
play for you i do want to continue with um my uh British uh for americans uh where we left off
yesterday was the arse about face um obviously there's a couple more arse uh pronunciations
or uh saying that they have here in the UK arse over elbow is one another way of saying head over
heels but a little more descriptive usually happens after 11pm on a Saturday night after too many
beers um i guess what we'd say in the states is arse over tea kettle arse over tit another version
of arse over elbow but a bit more graphic and forbidden during a super bowl show arse hole
asshole to you not very nice in either american english or british english arse hold uh what does
that mean it means drunk usually in the advanced stages of a drunk and stupor so it would be
be considered completely arse hold um let's see what is the next one we're still on a man how do you
like this as well um you chaps would say two or as well for instance if my friend ordered a
middle of light i would say i'll have one as well people usually just say as well okay so that's uh
some more british language culture let's see ass you'll be surprised to uh to find that an ass does
mean you're but but mainly it means a donkey in uh uh in the UK okay here's one backing i won't
be using this one uh any more backing tobacco uh but that'll be the sort you used to roll your own
you used to have a lot of backing bang we're into bees you notice that bang nothing to do with your
hair this is a rather unattractive way of describing having sex always gets a smile from brit
american hairdressers when they're asked about their bangs how's your bangs honey bar me
bar me so when tells you your bar me means you've gone mad or crazy for example you'd have to be
bar me to visit England without trying black pudding uh okay let's uh do two more here bees knees
bees knees the polite version of dogs bollocks so if you're in polite company and want to say
that something was fabulous that phrase might come in handy bees knees hi hon i'm uh i have a list
of yeah i got a whole list you want to do one okay you know what uh let me find one one man
i want to find a good one here bleeding glimey we know glimey
and shag i'm sure well i'm at the b i'm not an s yet okay please come over to the mic
it's very funny because for us Dutch for me then come over shag is is something you smoke
right and i just had that that's backing over here backing tobacco is backing but shag s h a g is something
you smoke yeah tobacco i've swashmoke to shag shag the smog shag how good was dinner huh
oh dinner was i was so good but we had fish right best best best best best best
a fried why is not no no no no so we had a good conversation at dinner
yeah about bass because we looked at the menu we both had bass yeah because when it's a guitar
it's spelled the same way but it's bass can i hear the bass please did i say that yeah
okay i love you yeah can i have the flag bass you but i'm music i want some i think music
right away so can i have some bass here yeah and the guy went boom boom boom boom
i missed your basement you see what i had to queueed up i actually wanted to play
mumbo Italyana was my last song i was just talking to Wilhelm from kota
oh tell me about Wilhelm tell us who Wilhelm from kota and i promised him that you
you sent him mumbo Italyana tell us who Wilhelm from kota is Wilhelm from kota is
the really the k yeah the record what is the record company boss yeah of uh
now you can actually can you um comparing with um
clive davis yeah clive davis yeah clive he's kind of like in fact he he
discovered golden hearing he discovered shocking blue um your Venus yeah that was him
miss a Venus mr. Venus uh who else uh earthen fire well that people all know earthen
fire but golden hearing was his name he didn't he and Freddie high and also um
the police didn't they own all the police published him for a while he's the big
big publisher he's got all the publishing rights yes any sounds like water companies and
trash recycling companies yeah he's he's he's the mobster
he knew it knew it knew it's hotels and Portugal hotels and golf clubs and he's a nice guy yeah
he's your mentor he's my mentor and my uh my record boss for years and we're going to do something
that making the DVD of my uh my whole career yeah from when i was 16 years old to now that was uh
before there was wood before there was you yeah well no when you were 16 hours there yeah i was uh oh
yeah that's right we were just talking about that that um he said i i met Adam when he was
what was he well our old were you you were yeah yeah he when he met
yeah i was doing the porn movie that's what he just mentioned that you did the porn movie
did the movie i did the voice for the porn movie i didn't do the actual one yeah because the
guys had the penis without the voice and you had the voice well i have the penis but he didn't pay me
exactly yeah exactly but you remember that you were a bit young but you had the voice for it
and he we were just talking about oh yeah baby i'm from the city health inspection
yeah remember the lines yeah so that's where we met each other because i was you were in the
I was in the other studio we uh i did the recording of the star sisters that just met me
and stars on forty five and while we were doing a while we were in that studio i heard you
in the other studio moaning uh and i said to my uh to my producer who who is this what what's
going on in the other studio so i had a look and there were you but you little
where what i looked like i had like a little dorky boy yeah very good and um you sweaty hands
you said hi i'm Adam i'm Adam i was seven i was uh 17 at the time 17 i have your poster hanging
you my uh in the bathroom yeah you're bathroom yeah no in my room you're right in my room yeah
and that's actually how we met was the first time oh i had met you many times with a poster
you don't really love you i'm sure i did i'm sure i said something like that yeah and strange
Tony con says hi Tony con i told you about Tony con he loves you he loves your voice he
thinks she's a very nice person he has no fucking clue how you look um i don't think so maybe
he's googled your name the picture maybe he's like google patrisha pie p a a a y
i'll then you get the playboy pizza yeah there you go everybody google patrisha pie p a y
please google me google me baby so he wants the mumbo y tliana what does he want to do with
he wants to put it in the DVD really yes you know to end the DVD with a song from uh actually
from now nobody can it's and it's in uh it has a creative comments license now i can't use it commercially
oh he doesn't know that yeah all right thank you very much all right baby um i'm going to
play the song uh get out of here and i'll come down and have some tea with you i have the candles
oh the candles are all right everyone so let's just do that one more time shall we mumbo
badyana oh
And mumbo, hey mumbo, it's time to get on a train
And chill out with a fish upon a galada
Hey cumba, I love how you dance to mumbo
But take it summer, fight for some new
Learn out to mumbo, if you wanna be square you never wanna be the winner
And mumbo, mumbo, it's time to get on a train
Mumbo, it's time to get on a train
And chill out with a fish upon a galada
Shake it baby, shake it buzzer, love how you take it me
Hey jump you, you're gonna have to go to school
So just make it little big, let me know
It's a like a me, get you so good, look you, but you don't know what's a good thing
Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
Shake it baby, shake it buzzer, love how you take it me
By the beats of real, don't know where to wanna be
Don't you dare your mumbo, mumbo, it's gonna tell it
Papa, there's nothing to become, baby, let's do it
Hey mumbo, mumbo, it's time to get on a train
Mumbo, mumbo, it's time to get on a train
You mix up, it's time to get on a train
Hold your calories, it's time to get on a train
Mumbo, it's time to get on a train
We're done, we are done
Shake it buzzer, shake it buzzer
I'm Trishipai, and mumbo, it's me, I know, on the daily source code
For Wednesday, the first episode
And I still owe you a complete list of all the musicians that played on that track
Because not a single sample machine was used
Well, of course, they used that in the mix
But it was all live musicians playing live
Horns, live drums, the whole nine yards
You can tell the difference, can you?
Alright, that's gonna do it for the source code
For today, hopefully tomorrow we'll have the fully enabled broad band edition
Come and leave from Curry Cottage in the UK
As always, comments are welcome through Atama Curry.com
We're blog Curry.com
And of course, say thank you for this
Share on the archives and then the source code
We'll leave you for now
We'll be back tomorrow of Thursday
We'll be the December 7th edition of the source code
Take it easy, everybody, goodbye