Hello there friends, family, go-
I'm Adam Curry, welcome you to the Thursday edition.
Today is October 7th, 2004 and we're ready to rock.
We got some interesting things happening today.
And that would be the fact that we're going to be doing a video about the
two days. Once again life has kind of gotten in the way of doing the podcast. I told you
yesterday it takes about an hour and a half these days to get everything queued up and
get everything pre-produced and then it takes at least half an hour, sometimes an hour or
longer to get the show going. And then another hour to make sure the compression is done
right and get up to the server. And today life got in the way of all the
to the flat screen factory for a shareholders meeting.
Which means I've been on the road all day.
Right now it is sort of living at 640.
I am at Skippal Airport in the parking garage in my car.
I'm just going to buckle in here.
OK.
I had to.
Well, you know it's one of these things.
I don't know if it's the same way in the States, but if you
want to get more than 250 euros, so about, what is that
these days, about $290.
If you want to get more than $300 from a cash
machine from an ATM, you have to go to a bank.
Banks, of course, suck because they know
the touristy close way too early.
So the only other place to get anything above that amount
is at Skippal Airport, which is kind of conveniently
on the way home.
No, not really convenient.
From here it's one road home.
And I'm just about to look at the, I'm in my Audi.
I have an Audi A8.
Love this car.
It's got all the gadgets you want.
It's got all the technology.
Yet it's kind of boring.
Not really sexy.
Now I have been my navigation here.
Let me just see.
I'm going to set up for actually.
start the car first. Okay, I'm going to set it up, take me to the castle, hold on,
there we go. And I'm not gonna put the guidance voice on because that's that's
kind of wacky. Although actually my, well now I'm not gonna do that. Okay, that means
top-up washer fluid. Okay, let me just check my my route here and go to, okay,
so Amsterdam Delft, I'm gonna get on the A4, 3,
between Delph. Okay, so it shouldn't be too bad. Let me see if there's a traffic report
memo.
On 35 files in the meester, they're high from 5 km long.
Okay, so there's 35 traffic jams. Each one is about...
Each one is about 5 km. What's cool about this traffic system is that it actually records
the traffic reports from the radio. So on all the stations here in...
Most of them in Europe actually, when there's a traffic report, they hit a button
so it'll interrupt your radio no matter what station or CD you're listening to.
But this car actually also records, and I have a list of like...
I had about 10 traffic reports there, each about 5 minutes apart.
Hey, you know what? It's traffic. You're basically fucked no matter what.
Tell you what, I'm going to get out of the garage here,
and meanwhile why don't we crank up some driving music, sniffing...
Drive and see
Ooh, drive and see
Yeah
Drive and see
Ooh, drive and see
Yeah, sniffing the tears, driver's seat on your right.
Sorry about that. It's kind of hard to drive and switch stuff at the same time.
Okay, now we're all set up. Okay, so I'm out of the parking garage. I am now
twirling. I want to get out of here people. Okay, you know what's great about
these navigations systems? Hold on a second. Let me just remove the
earphones. Oh boy. Come on people. Let my hand. Let my hand. Here we go. What's great
about these navigation systems is that when the road is changed as frequently
happens at airports then it gets really confused about where to send you but I
just follow the signs now. Okay, so I've got about well depending on traffic let
me see right now it's eight minutes seven and I'll be arriving at 825 now that's
if there's no traffic whatsoever so I don't even think my laptop battery is
gonna kind of keep it up.
up for that long. So we'll probably just be able to get a good hour showing because there
is a lot to talk about today. And what was nice on the way up, I had some time to check
out some podcasts. I've got to tell you, this has really taken off ever since I really
started focusing on the podcast directory, which of course can be found on iPodder.org.
It just keeps on coming. I mean, I think this morning I added another five. Yesterday
I must have added 10 or 15. And that's just the people have everything
all together. I'm getting daily requests for additions to the directory
from people who have a show that they have on their site or linked from
somewhere, but they don't have a feed-up yet. And trying to help most of those
people, most of them are getting helped out one way or the other.
Just close the roof there, give us a little bit of sound.
So I listened to some really good shows and obviously I was able to start
sniffing a tear song and I probably can do the theme song at the end of the show.
It's a little too much to be cruising through segments and pulling out bits today.
But I do have my iPod handy.
And what I'll do is I just want to talk about a few of these podcasts because it's just
so lovely.
And then when I get home, I'll edit in just a couple of bits so you can hear what's
up.
So it's almost live.
It's live on tape, right?
So first there's the Dawn and Drew show, a husband and wife team, which just
cracked me up.
And it's good to hear a woman's voice on a podcast.
And so far it's been men, men, men, men, men.
And so they just kind of shoot the breeze.
But they're fighting together.
You know, when you have a husband and wife team that have known each other
for a while, when they talk, they kind of feel in the blanks and they can
also rank on each other a bit from the Dawn and Drew show.
Welcome to the Dawn and Drew show.
I'm John Misselli and I'm Drew.
And this is our show.
That's right.
So listen up bitches!
Enjoy!
This evening, the role of Drew Domkis will be played by James.
Welcome to the Don and Drew Show.
I'm Drew Domkis and broadcasting live from the satellite of love.
That's right.
I'm Don Micelli.
For this evening, the role of Don Micelli will be played by Chris Moore.
The Don and Drew Show and if you want to subscribe to that podcast, real easy just
go to iPodder.org.
Go into the download and shows directory and you can find it right there.
And the way I'm doing it now, although I'm going to start to split it up into
different categories, is every single time as a new show added to the directory, it'll
be listed on top.
So it's kind of reverse chronological order.
Oops, I just, I'm going to believe this.
I just remembered that I have to make a pit stop in between here and home.
So basically I'm driving from Amsterdam via Rotterdam to Belgium.
It's one straight line, but I have to stop off about three quarters of the way in
If you're ever in Breda, B-R-E-D-A in the Netherlands, Breda, lovely town.
There's a coffee shop there called Purple Rain.
That's where my Moroccan buddies are.
And, well, it's time for another refill.
Moving on with some cool podcasts, I found...
just find it of course you know every single one I add to the directory I pretty much
subscribe to it at least
The Rock and Roll Geek Show. Now this is hosted by Michael Butler and Michael
Butler is the bass player for a band which I don't think I might have heard
them before American Heartbreak. They've been around for about seven years and
what I liked about this podcast is what Michael's doing and by the way what is
it with bass players who are named Butler? Have you ever hear of Giza
Butler? Black Sabbath? So Michael is doing a little bit differently. Instead of
recording a complete show he records little bits and they'll just pick it up.
So it's kind of like a diary and well here's a bit of him in the
morning after he went to a show the night before for the New York
Dolls and here's how he was feeling. It's Tuesday morning, the day after the
New York Dolls show.
I am so...
tired.
way to work and I do not want to be here.
Now of course, Al was not lost.
He might have felt really crappy.
But he also got a great ID for the show.
And when we talk about IDs in the radio business, that basically means, hi, I'm Phil on the
blank celebrity name.
You're listening to Phil on the blank radio program name.
And our buddy Michael got one from David Johansson at the New York Dolls.
This is David Johansson and you're listening to.
Unfortunately, the Rock and Roll Geek show.
The only thing that was missing from that is, you should have said you're listening to the
Rock and Roll Geek podcast.
But all right, close enough.
So anyway, so Michael really does this whole thing and I don't know what it is with him
and his wife, but he keeps threatening that his wife, who he says doesn't understand
what he's doing and probably doesn't agree with what he's doing.
He's taping it all in his bedroom.
Whenever she comes in, they start nagging each other and he keeps threatening to
record a whole session.
So we still have that to look forward to.
But really nice was a bit that he added onto the show, which
was a recording of.
On KSFU, which is a college radio station, promoting a show that they were doing,
and also played a couple of songs from their album, which I think they may be on some independent labels.
Europe. Here's the traffic jam. I'm already seeing that we're slowing down to a crawl.
That's good. Give me some time to queue up some stuff even if we really come to a standstill.
What was nice about hearing the College Radio show interview was that all of a sudden it
hit me. Do you remember, and many of you will, back in the 80s, certainly at MTV,
primarily, College Radio was always cool. The buzz. College Radio is playing this.
This is up and coming. College Radio is cool to listen to because it's basically almost
uncensored. It's non-commercial. It's just kids having fun and people saying the truth
and playing their heart out and getting their chops down. It reminds me so much of what
we're doing with podcasting with one major difference is that College Radio,
you can only really hear College Radio when you're near the College Radio station.
In case of you, I'm sure has a huge transmitter, but when I was in...
Salem, West Virginia, I went to Salem College and we had a 10 watt sunup, sundown FM transmitter.
It would just kind of do the town of Salem.
And what was the call letters?
It was WITB, which depending on what, if you're on the day air shift or the night air shift, the day shift meant we're in the
shift of course since we're into Bong heads that was my my college radio days
I still have my you know the varsity jacket from the radio station WA TV air
personality and curry bullet so but it was cool and and college radio is cool
and these podcasts hey someone someone's holding up his iPod hold on roll on your
window I'm just taking off to name here come here
wait yeah
but a month or okay dude yeah right dude we checked out a guy just drove up next to
me and he's honking his horn and he's holding his iPod up and he's saying I'm
listening
God damn, I said I'm recording one right now. So Raymond buddy
Wow, that's very cool. See this is what I mean. This is what it's all about. Oh, that gives me a boost of energy
That's fucking great. Okay, so so this is what it's like, you know, it's it's college radio only work clearly
We're mobile in more ways than one so
American heartbreak I really like the songs that these guys are making you know, it's it's very 80s
Intended to be that way and I think the guys probably were around in the 80s
They played in a couple of different bands Exodus. I think I remember Exodus and they were heavy metal
And I really heavy and now they're I'd say that the music they play is
Yeah, it's punk rock it kind of it's a little more 80s and maybe a little more rock than punk than say
Green Day or blink 182 or a good Charlotte
But it does have the harmonies, you know, and it's just it's good rock and roll
And here's a song that they chose to be played on
KSFU. It's one of their favorites from their upcoming album. Released or unreleased doesn't
make any difference because we're going to crack.
We've freed them, Ontario!
I can be a candy or a nasty to a wreck.
That's the end of my video.
I'll see you guys in my next video.
Bye.
We are the last of the people in our land
live from the Audi A8, driving on the A4 on my way to Breda from where we'll continue on to
Belgium. And you're along with me for the ride. And I've been going through just a couple of podcasts.
Let me see. I had one more that I had listed, I think, on my... Let me see. They have one more
listed on my iPod. No, it was cool, though, although not necessarily a podcast was...
IT Conversations brought me Steve Wozniak, almost two hours of him. And once I'm done with this
recording, as I said, I've got 44 minutes left on the battery. So, you know, hold on, see, there's traffic.
There's 12 traffic jams and all of them are about two kilometers. So about...
get rid of that. Yeah, that was really cool to hear the was and I haven't finished
myself to listen to the second portion but that's so nice to
receive that because I tried to listen to the Nome Dex conference live and I
heard some bits of it but I actually missed the was in the ex session so
it's cool that we can have that. Now let me tell you about tomorrow
before I forget, tomorrow being Friday, once again life will get in the way of
actual work getting done. I had agreed, I don't know if you know this
organization called War Child. War Child is a, they're pretty much global now I
think. It started, it actually started as a Dutch initiative and it's
a foundation that is mainly concerned with looking after children who are
victims of war and if you see any of their promotional material you realize
that even if there's war a hundred kilometers away from where kids
sorry, it has such a profound impact.
And they do a lot of very, very good work.
And a friend of mine is on the board of War Child here in the Netherlands, could also be
the European board.
And she owns a restaurant.
And she asked me, they're doing a Feast for Peace, which means a whole...
actors and other celebrities will actually serve dinner at her restaurant.
And so of course you pay like $200 for a plate and it's going to be fun.
I actually waited on tables for about three years.
I think I saw the experience. I don't think the suit fits me anymore, but I'll figure that out.
Now, this restaurant is in Nike, which if you were to drive that, it's almost can't get there from where I live.
You have to drive, you know, Caddy Corner. It just takes twice as long as if you could drive it in a straight line.
And I figured that since I didn't want to do that and I had an invitation to stay overnight,
I certainly don't want to drive back at midnight.
on tables and probably having some good fun.
So I'm going to sleep it in my friend's house.
But I'm going to fly up.
I'm going to take the helicopter.
And I think, based on the way this is going,
it shouldn't be too much of a problem to record the source
code tomorrow as I fly from Antwerp.
I'm going to take off from Antwerp Airport tomorrow
up to Nacetic.
And I'm flying solo.
So you guys will be along for the ride.
I have no idea how it's going to work out.
And of course, I do have to concentrate.
It is kind of important and I definitely won't have a hands-free.
You know, it's going to be like, I'm going to get in the helicopter, I'm going to start the recording
and you're going to witness everything from start-up to lift-off to the flight.
I think I have to do a couple of crossings of some control zones so you hear all that.
You'll hear out some other crap on the radio.
And we'll just talk, we'll just shoot the breeze and we'll see how it goes.
But I clearly won't have hands-free.
If we're an airplane it would be okay because then once you're up in the air, you know,
you have a hand-free and you shoot.
most of them. You can do whatever you want. You want to know what I can do.
But in the helicopter you need both feet and both hands pretty much at all time.
one hand on the on the cyclic which is what you'd call the stick you know that
makes you go forward left forward back left right whatever and then the
collective which is that handle that kind of looks like a parking brake which
is on the left that actually gives you the power and everything's in unison
when you pull up the collective you know you've got to depress your left foot
a little bit and you've got to move the cyclic forward so it's all kind of a
ballet motion and there's just no room for well there's no room for error
first of all so I'm looking forward to that so the source codes will be a
little bit different and then of course over the weekend all of
We're pretty much guaranteed that we'll have lots of new bits to play.
So look forward to that.
Let's see, what do I want to talk about?
There were a couple of things.
Hold on, let me just take a drag here.
This, by the way, is not what you think it is today.
I'm cheating. Just a little bit of tobacco.
Just to remind me that I'm smoking something.
So I'm being totally safe.
Oh yeah, and also when we fly, we don't smoke either.
I want to talk a little bit about the election.
And on Trade Secrets, Dave Weiner and I, if you haven't heard the podcast, I suggest you check it out.
Hopefully you'll subscribe.
Secrets.scripting.com, or of course you can get to it from iPodder.org.
We talk a lot about President Bush, about the elections, about the state of the country, about the war in Iraq,
something that even though I blogged it, I maybe just want to talk just a little bit about Iraq, because I went there.
In February, we did, and God, I wish we had podcasting then,
I did an entire week live from Camp Smity in Asamawa,
that's southwest of Baghdad, in Asamawa, Iraq,
where the Dutch Marines were stationed, still our station.
Actually, the Marines were there, now they've changed.
the Air Force that's there now. And they have regular ground troops. It's a little confusing,
but it's just different departments.
uniforms and different vehicles, but otherwise it's pretty much the same deal.
And so, so, so, so, A, when I saw the presidential debate and they were talking about the coalition,
or the lack of the coalition, and sure, Bush came up with Tony Blair, you know, what do
you say to Tony Blair when, you know, there was no coalition?
Well, yeah, of course there's, we know that Tony Blair and the United Kingdom were in
the coalition.
But a lot of other countries got sucked in besides just Poland.
God, our president remembered Poland.
We never mentioned the Netherlands.
We got 1,200 guys and gals there right now, two of whom have been killed in action.
Never read that in the press anywhere in the US press, not that I found at least.
So, you know, we're feeling a bit of the war, granted not on the same level as the
states, but it's also a big issue.
And, you know, the Netherlands got Shanghai into it.
No one wanted our marines to go.
Our marines, of course, went and we support them.
That was the whole point of the broad.
was just to support the troops, which is not a very European thing.
It's a very American thing, and that's why it's often frowned upon,
but we just said, fuck that.
We turned everything on its head and we went out and we went to support the troops,
and it turned out to be absolutely just beautiful.
But anyway, the Netherlands got Shanghai'd in, and I'll tell you why.
Part of it was the Joint Strike Fighter.
I don't know if you've ever heard of this,
but this is the new jet fighter that all the NATO partners have agreed
that this is the one they're going to build.
There's a lot of money involved in building of it.
A lot of money had to be paid to be a part of the program,
and the way that works is then your country can bid on projects.
Well, guess what? How many projects did the Netherlands get for...
And on top of that, the new NATO chief, Jaap de Hoop Schaeffer, who you probably heard
his name pronounced as, Jaap de Hoop Schaeffer, he's a Dutch guy.
So this was all politics and it was all lined up.
If the Netherlands wanted to have their spot on the global stage in NATO, if you can
still call that a spot on the global stage, then of course they had to participate in
the invasion in Iraq.
I didn't participate in the invasion, but they have been participating in the
rebuilding of Iraq, which has changed since I was there.
But when I went there, and I've never been in military service, I had no idea.
I've never been to a desert.
I've been to the outback.
And just a couple of impressions.
The first one is that it is very, very dangerous there.
But it wasn't at the time necessarily dangerous
because the coalition forces were seen as an invading force.
In fact, when I was there, the people in Asimawa,
and I went to five different marine camps in the surrounding area,
including Taliil Air Base, which is the biggest camp of all in Iraq,
which is even more southern Asimawa, but that's where they've got...
Well, that's a huge US Air Force base.
The Dutch are there, the Italians are there.
I didn't hear George mention the Italians.
Pretty big country there, George, looking like a boot.
You could have remembered that one, but no, you were...
The Japanese have 800 guys there, so granted that's nothing in comparison to the US, but
I saw with my own eyes how the Iraqi population was elated.
They were so happy, and it didn't matter what country you were from.
The troops, the kids were running up and down, running after the jeeps and sticking their
thumbs up in the air and saying, you know, we're happy you're here because they've
been doing rebuilding.
I actually saw it.
I saw the rebuilding of schools.
I saw the rebuild of the water plant.
The refinery, which by the way, if you know anything about refineries, and I didn't
until then, building a refinery is incredibly difficult.
It's very, very expensive.
It can cost hundreds of millions.
But also training Iraqi police force, the ICDC, which is the Iraqi ICDC
stand for, the Iraqi Coalition.
defense initiative something like
And the vibe was basically good.
Where it gets dangerous, where it was dangerous at the time was the transport.
We actually drove from Kuwait City in Kuwait all the way to Asimala.
That's about 350 miles, I think.
And it was just two Land Rovers, our crew, which was five guys, and then four Marines
who escorted us.
It's crazy because you don't know what to expect, right?
And you're driving away from Kuwait, and then you pass the border into Iraq.
And it's a six-lane highway.
Granted, the overpasses and the bridges that you travel under
don't connect on either side of it, blown to bits.
But it's a six-lane highway.
It's unbelievable.
Now the thing is, you have to drive in the middle because
transports from Kubite all the way to Baghdad come over this one road and
that's where all the trouble would start is hijacked if a truck just had a
breakdown it would have to move off to the side of the road within minutes in
the middle of the desert upward pop 50 60 people just you know coming closer
and closer and if you're anywhere near town it could be five to six hundred
if a truck is left alone within an hour and a half it's completely stripped of
cargo every mirror light steering wheel piece of rubber every usable bit and of
course riots happen because you know people are you know fighting over the
spoils of whatever is left and combat combat that what the troops resorted to
doing eventually is if a truck broke down they couldn't tow it away they
blow it up they torch it and they blow it up right on the spot so there'll be no
no problems but of course you know you've got bad bad people ever
everywhere, and you have to drive in the middle of the six lane highway because of what they
call IEDs, intentional explosive devices.
Basically means that they'd stick a bomb in a dead dog by the side of the road and you
pass by and it would blow up.
So at the time we were there and we went and met with people in villages
I went with the commander of the the Dutch Marines without
Protective gear on without flak jackets without helmets into the town
Just to go to the barber shop to meet with the locals and show that we you know had all the best intentions by not wearing our
protective gear
And it was really, I was very, very impressed and very impressed with the work that our
Marines were doing, very impressed with the central provisional authority, the CPA, which
is what at the time was Paul Bremmer's fund and how money was being dispersed.
I witnessed it.
They could not put on a show for me there because we would have seen right through it.
And we had access to everything, could talk to anybody, anything we wanted to do, and
we were broadcasting it.
We were blogging it.
It was phenomenal.
However, it did change.
And it changed because there was no change, basically.
from outside of Iraq, terrorists, people who hate America, who hate Europe, who hate anyone,
maybe who's not Muslim, possibly, they're coming from all over the place. They're coming from
different countries. They're coming into Iraq, and they are one of the main causes of trouble.
So it's not the Iraqi people. And I think I'm probably preaching to the choir when, you know,
that we all know this by now. But the one thing, and I guarantee you the Dutch troops are leaving
in March, they said they'd stay until March and they're getting the fuck out.
because the country is pissed off that they were sent there under false pretenses to start
off with weapons of mass destruction, brought into a coalition with all kinds of political
bullshit so that we could get our spot on the world stage with NATO and all that, and
they're tired of it.
And the masses here are, what do you call it?
There's unrest?
They call it unrest, yeah, unrest.
People are, you know, strikes are planned.
They're just not happy with the government at all now.
And our troops will be coming back in March.
And I think that the work is pretty much done.
And when I say the work, and this is why I bring this up, they have rebuilt the schools,
they have rebuilt the water plant.
I can't speak for the refinery, but you know, I'm not just not sure what's going on there.
They have trained local police forces.
They have trained the ICDC, which is kind of like also a security force.
I think they've probably weeded out the bad elements because that was very hard.
you know, who's telling the truth, who's bullshitting, all of a sudden you're handing him an AK-47
so he could turn around and use on you.
And the work is done.
The only other thing left to do is to pick up troublemakers.
And now there's just trouble.
And there's no more bombs being...
There's no more...
It's how can I best say this it's over it's done with you know the the the the shit that that Saddam created particularly in that area has been
We built, taken care of, things are set up.
They have 10, 15, maybe 20 years to go before they can reset that.
But now the only thing we're doing is just protecting our own ass.
The U.S. servicemen and women, all they're doing is they're protecting their own ass.
They're not protecting U.S. assets or interests.
They're protecting their own ass, and rightly so.
Because it's not U.S. interests.
It's George Bush's interests, Dick Cheney's interests, and Halliburton.
It's the Carlyle, is that it?
The Carlyle Investment Group.
That's who's interests they're protecting, and they're not being fairly told that that's what they're doing.
And in this country, and in most countries in Europe where I can speak the language,
or have been able to read whatever they're talking about.
Everybody knows by now and fully agrees and are not being there's no media bullshit about
oh yeah but you know Iraq is responsible for 9-11.
It's not true.
Everyone here is saying hey where where's Osama bin Laden they're on to it.
will be a much better place if at least George Bush is no longer president and Dick Cheney
is no longer vice president and Donald Rumsfeld
where he can put young lives of young men and women at risk.
Easy for me to say, of course, being 40
and not being eligible for a draft,
although I do remember having to register
in the early 90s, I had to register for the draft
when the first Gulf War happened.
But this is crazy, it's just crazy.
And I haven't really been able to talk
about the experience as much, having been there,
because you really build up such a bond
and a brothership and sister ship
with these people, with the troops there and the Marines.
And I really got...
And we need to get them out. We need to get them out. Iraq is...
I think Baghdad. Baghdad is fucked. Baghdad is a big problem there.
There's no more records. They can't hold an election.
The town hall with all the... there's no registration. Everyone has to go register again.
It's a scam. It's a freaking scam. And as far as I'm concerned,
we need to get out. And the only way to definitely get out on any reasonable time scale
is to get George Bush out and get someone in. And I would obviously say John Kerry,
who is going to promise us that he's going to get our troops back within a reasonable amount of time.
We're going to hold them to it. Or we should just show our power and go vote
and kick him out as well. We have that power. Absolutely have that power.
And now with these podcasts, I think we have additional power.
Now we have the power of voice. We can really talk about what our feelings are.
But still, I think sometimes comes over even a little bit better than...
than the written word, which of course is not to be underestimated.
So anyway, I have registered to vote by proxy.
It is very difficult to do that.
You ever notice how they never make it easy to do that stuff?
It's just why I thought MTV was great.
You get your license, you get your voter registration.
The motor voter bill I think it was, and MTV really plugged the hell out of that.
Doing this by proxy, it's like, yeah, you might be able to fax it,
but you're pretty much going to have to mail this stuff back and forth.
How election day falls almost exactly six months
From tax day
It's on the opposite side of the calendar
I say we should have election day right after you pay your taxes and what and after you you figure out what you paid your taxes for
Okay, let me get off the soapbox here. It is by now 722 is getting kind of dark. I can see that we've been at
It's been a pretty uneventful ride, so far.
Thinking of anything else.
Ooh.
Yeah, there's one thing I did want
to talk about when it comes to users and developers
partying together.
I've been thinking a lot about iPod or how it works.
And of course, I hope you saw that iPod or 1.0 has been
released.
This is for Windows and for the Mac.
It works.
I just called a buddy in the States who has Windows and
someone who I know is a total user.
And he installed it and got the welcome file and everything
worked.
But then he said, OK, but now when I want to subscribe to
something, I knew it was coming, right?
When I want to subscribe to something, why do I have to
like click on this link?
When it comes to mankind and doing that with technology, it's a big hassle.
And you can see there's proof of this, there's prior art if we just look at web blocks.
There's lots and lots of icons that will let you subscribe to an aggregator.
So there's an icon for blog lines, there's an icon for feedster, there's an icon for
radio user land, which is okay.
But when it comes to iPodder, I don't think that's the way to go.
I don't think we want to have, well, this is for iPodder Java,
this is for iPodder X, this is for iPodder.net, this is for
iSpider or PiPodder.
We don't want to have that because we just want to have one single uniform.
But now this is, and I can probably just see Dave Weiner rolling his eyes right now
saying, no, don't go there.
You can't do it, it can't be done.
I just want to put a call out to the developers of the iPodders and
the users who are partying with them on this.
We should think about a standardized module.
And we've already done so much really good work when it comes to standardizing how we're
doing things.
And we all can be so proud of that in such a short time span.
But we should consider making a module and making that into iPodder so that you can
subscribe to a podcast from a website just by clicking on a logo.
Now, of course, it's easy to put in.
I even saw someone made a podcast button.
So that art is already there.
And of course, you can just link your RSS file or URL.
a little logo, but you're still going to have to do a copy and paste.
Now the way this works with the Weblog software is, so I'll just take RadioUserLand as an example.
You basically have a little tiny web server running on your own machine.
So when you click on that link, it's actually pointing to the web server on your machine.
And then that web server receives the subscription URL and then knows to send it off to the aggregator
portion, so to the iPodder feeds.
It's not trivial to set that up.
By far it's trivial.
And even harder is to make the subscription engine the same for every iPodder.
I'm just throwing it out there to see what comes back.
But if we want to really complete the final user experience.
really really really can make this fly. We have to be able to tune into our podcast
and that tuning in has got to be a little bit more simple than the copy paste. I
know that
You subscribe to stuff, people using aggregators do it all the time.
But I doubt that people using blog lines do it all the time.
I think probably a lot of people using blog lines, which is a centralized aggregator, will
only subscribe or most likely only subscribe mainly to web logs that carry the blog lines
subscription logo.
So something to think about before we get into a whole bunch of other features and functionality.
That's a glaring thing that we should at least think about.
that should be possible
uh...
let's try
to not have a lot
david yes i can hear david whiter screaming saying no no no no he's
screaming at his ipod now
but i think it's actually possible i want to give it a shot you know as long
as i don't break anything in the process we keep all the others
I think we'll be okay.
Um... boy.
Man, I've got a dry mouth from all this talk.
Um... tomorrow, as said, on the podcast.
Which you may not receive until Saturday, now that I think about it.
Oh no, wait a minute, my buddy will have a connection with me to pop it up.
Yeah, I'll be able to do that tomorrow before I actually start doing the waiting thing.
We'll be flying together.
So I'm looking forward to that because it's probably going to be the first podcast ever done.
Yeah, from the air.
Alrighty, let me just see if I can do this, the final bit here, hold on a second.
Just moving my finger across the screen.
Oops, I don't want to do anything too drastic.
Okay, uh... yeah, that's it everybody.
Thanks for listening to the source code for October 7th.
The power of your influence.
And we'll see you tomorrow.
I'll come into you from...
We'll see you tomorrow between...