I was due to the very source code every day.
On Dragon Casting with Adam Curry.
The power of the door is going to go into it.
Hey there, good afternoon, everybody.
I mean, a mobile ride.
It's the source code for Tuesday, October 26, 2004.
I'm not a curry company to you from Flanders, Belgium.
It's just a little past noon here, and we're podcasting from Curry Castle.
I've been working a little bit on my audio levels today, of course, to show that when
I was yesterday, although it recorded without a hitch, was completely overmodulated.
And what's nice about this little yep device that I got is that it didn't really crush
it well, what it did is it just limited the sound into one big tire, some thing, the
things too.
But working on all that, I know exactly what I need, I need a little portable mixture.
I had my eye on the long battery operated, and I can do everything all straight.
So I have the audio level set and so I can hear myself perfectly and create the podcast.
I said, it wasn't intended.
On the show today, lots of cool bits found from around the podcast universe.
Some audio comments that came in and of course, some pod tunes for you, the non-R-A.
Non-R-I-A music that I've been scouring the internet for.
I'm still trying to get recruit people to send me their band stuff, and I have received
some stuff from people, but not all of it is particularly something I wanted to play on the
daily source code, meaning that somebody just was like, it was like real hobby stuff.
And it wasn't what I wanted to share with you.
I'm looking for some cool tunes and they're out there.
I know they are, so we just got to get more people who are making music, interested in
podcasting what we're doing.
Actually, I guess I could talk about this right now because I received an email
that in the most recent issue of wired magazine is a CD that comes packaged with
it's full of R-I-A-A free music released on the creative commons license, which is cool.
Now, I found a podcast that actually has every single track from that CD on it.
So, I'm going to take that with me today.
I'm driving up to the Netherlands for a couple of meetings in the old cash dance again,
right?
Gotta go to the airport.
And we've already recorded that trip, so I decided to do the podcast early, but that's really cool
that wired is jumping into this and think about that as distribution.
And have your tune on a CD distributed by wired magazine.
I don't know what their circulation is, but it's got to be pretty damn cool.
And the source code, always looking for cool stuff to play for you.
Yes, they have played Burn, Goodie Stewart, Burn, Goodie Stewart, Burn by Royes Zimmerman
at Royes Zimmerman.com.
He has a nice political tune that he whipped up, and I wanted to share that with you right now.
This one's titled 90%.
90% of likely voters have made up their minds.
Have made up their minds already.
And 80% of that other 10%
little states where they won't make a gosh-dark, bit of difference.
And so they're spending 9085 million dollars
to persuade 7 people in Ohio.
So if trans-section were to move to Cincinnati,
and vote as a block, and rush off their chance.
This holy lecture could be decided by summer moments,
who become NASCARDES.
There you go.
90% brought to you by Royes Zimmerman from Royes Zimmerman.com.
And as I'm also recruiting people who have got some music they want to promote on the show,
we just send me a link to a URL where I can download it and some information and some background.
I've been scouring through different websites.
I really like GarageBand.com because not only does it give you a ranking of what users think,
and users of that site think is really good in different categories.
The band has individual page and tells you whether they have a label or not,
whether you can download it or what the different licenses are, if applicable.
And there's lots of sites like that all around.
When I'm looking for, I guess, now, a lot of work goes into the source code.
It takes me about an hour to prep each day.
And of course, as I'm reading email, I'm always thinking,
oh, this is something I could do on the source code.
I can use this.
People are sending me audio comments.
Please keep those coming by the way.
I love them.
But I'd really like to do different types of music shows.
Maybe there's a blue show of pod tunes that we can put together,
or maybe there's any different genre that you want.
But what I'm really looking for in that case is a producer.
I need someone who will basically use me as the voice for their show.
I'll be happy to produce it and put it all together.
So if you give me the MP3s that need to go into the show,
whatever show it is, as long as we see eye to eye on the type of music,
it'll be fun.
So I need for whatever if to weekly show,
which would make the most sense, I think.
I need the MP3s and the background information.
And then I'll take care of all the rest.
And let's see if we can put something cool together.
That people would subscribe to a new music show.
But I need someone who's out there continuously scouring through everything
and finding the stuff that's hot that people are talking about.
Really scouting some stuff.
So if you're interested in that, send them an email.
Adam at curry.com.
Maybe you've always wanted to do a podcast.
I can tell my microphone wires.
My headphone wires hitting the mic wire.
Maybe you want to do your own podcast,
but maybe you don't like the way your voice sounds.
Maybe you just don't feel like doing that kind of stuff.
Let me be your podcast whore.
So seriously, I'm looking for someone to help me produce something like that.
I think that would be extremely cool.
An email here from Geek News Central from Todd.
He says you talked about the Samsung yep.
But did not let us know which device she bought.
Also which one you ordered.
The one that has more options.
He said he also lost a show last week.
He's paranoid as hell about losing shows recorded on his computer.
And I understand.
So maybe even if you're just using it as a backup device,
it's good.
What I got Todd was the, I think of the box here.
It's the yep 55 V.
It's really ugly actually.
And it has, it's a brushed metal look, right?
Which of course is anything but metal.
And the highlights, the accents are orange, if you can believe it.
So it's pretty lame looking.
And that's what I'm using currently.
But the one that I, I've ordered two of ordered.
And I river 790, which is very comparable to the Japanese thing that I have on order,
which is easy.
It's digital Zen, X-E-N, digital Zen audio player.
And that thing is really awesome.
It's, let's see.
It does MP3, MP1, 2.5,
Windows Media, SF, AdVorbus.
You know, it can, oh, what's really cool about this is it can,
it can import a text file.
And it'll do a text to speech.
I haven't heard the quality of that.
But, and it really lets you set the bit rates in, you know, much,
much more sophisticated fashion.
It's got better IQs.
And you can look at that on www.easy-av.com.
So Echo Zulu-Alpha Victor.com.
Let's see.
Let's take it out to an audio comment that came in.
So what's this about?
I think this is about geocaching.
Adam, Mike from work for bandwith.blogspot.com here.
MP3 mailing you from London, Ontario, Canada.
My friend Sarah and I were driving down the 401 highway in southwestern Ontario,
listening to your Friday, October 15 show.
Never do that with your girlfriend, man.
That's just not a good idea.
And Sarah commented when you were talking about geocaching and podcasting,
that she didn't really like the idea of other people telling her what she should
like and dislike without having some sort of credentials to give an informed opinion.
I think that she has a bit of a point if someone has a crappy experience in one restaurant
or in one city or one town shouldn't really shade the experience for everybody else,
especially if they have some sort of graduate that are not really letting on about it.
And also think a good idea to have a few unfiltered non-corporate opinions on something like that once in a while.
As we made a way further down the highway towards Windsor,
I think we're talking about involved into a better idea of doing something like this.
Have things like the Zagat restaurant reviews or the AAA Auto Club,
travel books, have some sort of down-loadable MP3 content.
Oh man, you just mentioned like two things I'd love to see on RSS.
I think that's where this comment is going.
I was talking about geocaching and you could have enclosures attached to a geographical data,
GPS data, basically.
And if you're in a certain spot or within a radius within a certain spot,
it would fire off an MP3.
You could have a real walking tour of stuff.
But yeah, of course.
I mean, anyone could set it up so you could have the review of good restaurants and bad restaurants.
And everything is subjective of course.
But I like what you're saying here because you're talking about some great information flows
that we just really need to have that would be perfect for any RSS.
Just text RSS.
And that could be podcasted to you.
When you subscribe and very specific to the point of having up-to-date current restaurant reviews
for San Diego or Ben Breakfast outside of Boston,
and be more up-to-date than the books that they pass out acting like a ratish eats or
addendums or something.
Why don't have local tours boards get on side with us as well.
When you go to maybe a expedient or travel-osity,
have them have some sort of content that they can propose to you for the local hotels.
For example, if you can imagine subscribing to a last minute feature where someone actually describes,
or maybe, and of course, last people are talking about this as we move beyond podcasting.
The same infrastructural work for video, absolutely.
We don't quite have the platform of MP3 players for video yet,
but it's coming because in my search for the perfect MP3 encoding device, external recording device,
you know, I came up against the audio player and there's another one from Phillips,
and there's some good stuff out there, man.
They're playing divics, and it's coming.
It's happening, and it's happened pretty damn fast,
and this on the day that Apple is releasing their new iPod,
right, the color iPod, and U2 is doing the whole shindig for that,
a lot of the marketing.
I'm hoping that, you know, if you have a color iPod,
it might as well, well, shoot, you know, it might as well do video,
or at least, quick time, right?
Just a thought, guys, we'll find out more as the day progresses.
And here for you, this is cool.
This came from OpenPodcast.org.
It's actually its OpenPodcast number 46.
I love this.
I hope it shows up every single day.
It's fabulous.
The podcaster's tap dance.
48% of those cool beliefs the president will be chosen by the courts,
and the real winner will ultimately be frozen out of the job,
some fear there will be a riot.
Like in the catering ships, because the losing party won't fire.
Ashley Simpson's first number went fine on Saturday night,
live but the second song started singing before her lips arrived
in the position to match the words of the song.
So she's long off stage and said her bed played it wrong.
57% of Americans have sex outdoors,
51% at sex on the first date.
48% they don't get them, but they're not whores.
12% at sex and work.
They couldn't wait.
Halloween has been cancelled out of Washington State School,
because it takes time from their studies and the scientists
just so cool dirt the feelings of real life,
which is it makes them sad to sing up some blood
and pointy hats and noses cackling at high pitches,
stay tuned for late breaking pop dates.
That's the tap dance and podcaster news.
That's the podcasters tap dance here on the daily source code,
and just have a visitor coming through,
a real estate agent checking out the value of the house.
And you right now is in the bars.
A bed is writing down that it's very extensive bar studio area of the house.
If you start up, I'm going to show you the book.
I'm going to show you the book.
Let's see, we gotta go out now to New Zealand
where we have a comment about metadata.
Hey, I didn't miss a mark from New Zealand here.
I didn't actually think I'd record a comment,
but I'm just out driving recording this on my P100.
I don't know if I'll be able to get this off the phone
to send it to you, but whatever.
Yeah, I just had this pretty cool thought.
I was just thinking about trackbacks, web laws and podcasting.
And I just, I had the sight here that we're losing metadata here.
I was looking to the source code earlier.
And you're playing these different excerpts from different tasks
that you've found that are really interesting.
And I sometimes, you know, paid up.
You're really cool to listen to the full thing.
But I don't know if any, I don't know where these speeds are,
or where these files are.
I don't know whether I already haven't downloaded or whatever.
Now, thinking what would be cool is this,
you had additional enclosures listed in your cast.
So that there's a police car, I don't know if he's,
nope, he's not following me.
Yeah, that you have additional enclosures in your cast and your feed.
That's say, hey, I referenced the source.
So then I potter can also download these additional files
that you have referenced so that I can listen to them in their entirety.
That would be really cool,
because I wouldn't have to hunt them down.
And then I was thinking you can extend whatever I pot,
I pot blanks off or this is an open medium,
to actually listen to these media.
Yeah, so that'd be quite cool.
So then you can just, yeah, that would be very cool.
And actually, I was thinking about that mark,
while I was taking a shower earlier today.
And then it hit me, it's so simple.
I'm already using radio user land or actually combination of radio user land
and manila, but all based on the frontier application.
That's what I'm going to use to create the perfect podcast production system.
And this is, I've been looking for, you know,
a next mission in podcasting.
And of course, I'm loving it making the podcast.
I'm looking, you know, to do more shows
if people will help me produce them.
I'm really excited about that, because, you know,
it's a matter of just, you know, getting through the show
and putting the love and the passion into it
because of part of the music.
But really, I've been wanting to contribute more.
And you know, I'm not a programmer, right?
We all got that down.
I wonder if anyone out there is still using my original iPod or Apple script.
I doubt it.
But I've done a fair amount of user land scripting in my time.
Just ask Dave Winner, he's saying,
I've done shit with his software that isn't technically possible,
and it's perfectly suited for radio production.
I use it on my morning radio show,
but more as a content management system.
But now you're right.
You know, we're talking about things like metadata.
And it should be as simple as, you know,
me dropping my sample clips into a folder
that's where it should pick up, you know, feeds and details
because we just strip out the RSS.
You know, all of this stuff can be done.
And well, for Christ's sake,
the application is called radio.
I mean, was this foresight or what?
I mean, it's perfect.
It's going to be perfect.
And I'm quite sure that, you know, we can then start
to connect our production systems.
You know, I can export stuff.
And this can all flow into the directory.
And, oh, lions and tigers.
Oh, you know, all that shit.
Oh, my.
It's going to be great.
It really, really is.
I'm looking forward to this.
So, a great idea.
I'll play it just the end of his voice mail note
because he gets so wrapped up in his metadata.
Listen to the source code already here.
It's quite long here.
He gets lost.
I said, hey, I want to listen to that full thing.
That would be so cool.
I'm also thinking about trackbacks.
If I go to this original source medium,
and then I might get an enclosure to say, hey,
Adam Curry also left a comment on this and made a commentary.
So then I get those them.
And you just get this full big circular blow out of bandwidth.
Yeah.
I've got a, I've got a shoot.
I lost.
Kind of got lost in this car.
I'm going to go to a fine room going.
But I'm, yeah, I'd love to hear your thoughts on that.
Oh, be great.
Geocast that where you got lost and put that audio comment in there.
Perfect.
Great idea.
And thank you for the inspiration because.
Excuse me.
That's exactly where I'm going to go.
And it's going to be on the next two months.
And also frontier is open source now.
So we could, and it's cross platform.
So Mac and Windows.
I use it every single day.
I already use it for a lot of my podcast production.
So it makes so much sense to do this.
And then we can actually, you know, like,
bake applications that would, you know,
be open source and available for people to,
to build off on and use.
And we can tie all this shit together.
And, yeah, it's great.
It's great.
In fact, it's, it's, it's wonderful.
It's, it's wonderful.
And I have a song that, that kind of,
sags right into that from grudgeband.com.
And this is good.
The history of hip hop.
Drama, teek, and then flow.
Did it?
You're now too dead to American movie classics.
Today's feature presentation.
Wonderful.
Tell me.
Can you tell me where hip hop is like,
back in the day?
Well,
it's a whole lot different to what it's like now.
It was wonderful.
Listen.
Hey, yo.
Yeah.
We're love, baby.
We send this opportunity to tie your pop community.
We brought to the store this culture back to where they used to be.
No, I'm sad.
Back when it was wonderful.
Come and yo.
Back in the day, it was nothing like that.
Well, it's a whole lot different to what it's like now.
It's a whole lot different to what it's like now.
Right away.
John Machique and Ben Flows is wonderful.
What a wonderful world.
Your daily source code.
I'm wondering if I gave you the wrong date check.
It is October the 26th, 2004 to the ad.
I might have said 25th,
but it's Tuesday, it is the 26th.
And we're going out to a very excited
person who's new to podcasting or podcast catching
rather Ryan from Oklahoma City.
Ryan from Oklahoma City.
Why didn't Ryan?
Good evening there Mr. Curry.
This is Brian here in Colorado.
Hold on a second.
Did I say it was Brian?
Let me listen to that.
Okay, let's listen to that again.
Mr. Curry. This is Brian.
Brian. Okay.
Colorado.
And why did I think it was?
Oh, okay.
I messed it up.
This is Brian from Colorado.
Ryan's next up.
I'm sorry.
Well, I just kind of happened to
crap.
The tables kind of creaking here.
Hey, crap, man. We all got the same problems.
Yeah.
All right, so I'll just try to hold still.
Anyway, this is Brian here in Colorado.
And I just happened to pass this whole
podcasting thing here.
Well, just in the past couple days
I was really impressed with it.
Your stuff in particular isn't really interesting.
And just the level of professionalism really
boiling.
Well, it sets the bar pretty high for all the other folks getting involved in this stuff.
So anyway,
well, you were noting in some of the other folks at the Gilmore gang.
Everybody seems to really think this stuff
is really taking off like crazy
and all the cultural implications
are well, it seemed to be pretty far reaching.
One thing I was particularly impressed with
and this lead into my question for you is a lot of the NPR stuff that kind of
is starting to show up.
Stuff a future tense.
And also the morning stories from WGBH.
It's really type of stuff that I typically listen to on the radio.
And so, well, I guess my question for you is
a lot of this stuff from NPR and other sources
has been showing up on audible.com
and also consequently because of that
in the iTunes music store.
And of course, when you download that,
you can put that onto your iPod
and I'm sure other devices as well.
And take it portably.
And so a lot of shows like Cartoc,
this American life, and stuff like that.
People download pay for it
and they get to enjoy it.
Arguably, podcasting has an edge
on that content and do the fact
that you get to tie it in with the RSS feeds,
which is pretty cool.
But then again, you know,
audible.com gets it stuff on iTunes.
Music stores, of course it's got, you know,
it had started into that.
Well, let me just stop there for a second, Brian,
because it's, you know, that's exactly right.
This is exactly what audible
and Apple should be listening to
because audible actually has subscription programs,
you know, like fresh air
as you say a couple of NPR programs.
And some of them are free.
I don't think you have to pay
from most of the public radio stuff.
In fact, there was an interview with John Stewart
on there that I believe it was free.
But it doesn't matter, you know,
why doesn't audible make subscriptions
available?
They already know how to do the money part,
because they're happy to take my
buck amount to whatever it is that I pay for fresh air,
maybe it's even a little bit more,
you pay upfront actually, I think.
So then just give me an RSS feed,
you know, that I can subscribe to it.
It's, you know,
your DRM stuff won't let me copy it anyway.
So, you know, the,
the file presumably is useless for anyone else.
And, you know, you can do all kinds of authentication.
Yes, that's exactly right.
And so should iTunes music store,
just be doing exactly the same thing.
You know, let me subscribe to a podcast
and then, you know,
shit, they own the whole platform,
make a button that I click somewhere
and it just orders it for me.
You know, oh, yes, it makes so much sense.
Particularly with,
I wouldn't be cool if today
during the announcement of the new iPod,
someone mentioned podcasting,
wouldn't that be, wouldn't it be awesome?
It could happen.
If it does, you'll,
you'll know about it tomorrow.
That's for sure.
Okay, now let's go over to Ryan from Oklahoma City
who's excited about podcasting.
Hey Adam,
this is Ryan,
a loyal source code listener
from Oklahoma City
in a recent transplant
from Dave Weiner country
out in Seattle.
And, you know,
when I left Seattle,
one of the things I was looking forward to
most was escaping the traffic,
which is absolutely horrendous out there.
And today,
on my way home from work out here,
in Oklahoma,
it was major,
Seattle flashback time
because we had traffic
backed up from majors.
I'm like,
the ageu,
but it, for miles,
it took me an hour and a half to get home.
Something about it,
check from Wisconsin
with pink hair
doing iPod poetry
on the i35.
I'm not sure what was going on there.
On Don and Drew.
Anyway,
I freaking love
bumper to bumper today,
man.
I had my iPod packed
to the gills with podcast,
not a moment of my commute was wasted.
I got my daily source code
fix.
I got a few laughs in
with Don and Drew.
And I checked in with
Como 1000 news from
Back home in Seattle.
And I loved every
minute of it, man.
So I would like to give
a thank you to you
for the source code
and for all of your
effort on podcasting.
Bye.
I always sound effects
provided for free,
my friend.
And I'd like to give
the listeners
of the source code
a big boy.
A little iTunes tip
that helps me manage my content.
I have created a smart play list
with two parameters.
One genre contains
podcast.
And two play count
equals zero.
So that as my content
is downloaded to the iPod,
my smart play list
appropriately enough
titled new podcasts
is populated.
And as I listen to each show,
it's kicked off
the new podcasts list
so that when I come back
to my iPod later,
and I'm scrolling and searching
for what I'm going to look
through next,
I do not have to
contend with shows
that I've already listened to.
And it just makes it a
little bit easier
to get through all of that
awesome content.
So out of my hope,
I get a podcast
coming to you
from Oklahoma City going
pretty soon.
And a big thank you
to you and for all
of the folks out there
that are podcasting.
So take it easy
and I hope to talk to you
soon, man.
All right.
Another satisfied
customer of our podcasting
movement.
It's my point behind
writing from Oklahoma City,
and he was talking about
Don Andru in that
audio commentary
and I encourage you to
send yours.
Please, to Adam at
Curry.com.
You can email it
if it's not too big
or just send me
a link to a URL
where I can go and download it.
And don Andru
are back on the air
They were off because of a
bandwidth issue,
and I was listening
to their the most recent show
and the subject of David
Bowie came up
as they were talking
about the freak show
that they went to see.
This is as an example for like the perfect length show.
All right enough talking about that.
Okay.
So we saw a free show tonight at Fred Bust.
Um, a fat man got half naked, a cute man jumped on glass in ugly man, stapled money
to his body, and a total fucking loser ate a baby rat.
That was nasty.
That one guy also stuck a pin right through his arm.
Yeah.
Any eight fire, but this does leave the devil.
And then your cute guy also did the little deal with the ball.
Oh man, that was fucking hot.
What is it called?
Um, David Bowie, Labyrinth shit.
Yeah.
I don't know.
We're going to have the producer look it up.
Yeah, that looks really cool.
He totally had it down.
So you guys seen Labyrinth, right?
And it's not really David Bowie, it's somebody else.
Doing the glass balls.
He's like, turn on bucks, Sarah.
Man, when I saw that, I think I was like eight, and I literally was like, my private
two weird.
And I had a thing for David Bowie ever since.
And for some reason, I don't know why I had this idea.
Um, I thought David Bowie was a vampire.
It's a real?
Yeah, like.
So I had this whole eight-year-old sexual fan, as you know, you've got to wear a weird
wife, man.
That he would come into my room late at night and bite me on the neck and then we could
be vampires together.
So I would sleep with my neck exposed so that when David Bowie came by to bite me, it
was easier.
It didn't really occur to me that, you know.
Had you ever seen the hunger?
No.
I still haven't.
What?
Yeah.
I've seen the movie The Hunger.
I haven't.
What's the vampire?
I've never seen it.
I think we might own it on tape.
No, I don't.
We might.
That's a good movie, the bow house, in the beginning.
The producer's giving me some notes on the hunger.
Um, yeah, so David Bowie, I'm totally fuck you.
You're my mom's gonna kick your ass.
I could shake her.
My mom's gonna kick your ass.
Maybe your boyfriend knows him.
I could totally use Adam Craig into the movie.
Wait.
So yeah, right, Benz was fun.
We went.
Okay, so.
So, you know.
Well, on the second.
So, oops, sorry.
Don has this David Bowie thing ever since she was eight.
Yes, you're totally doing, and she wants to get in contact with him.
I've met David Bowie a couple times, but source code listeners, something that I haven't
spoken about before on the show, is that a long time ago, well, now, first I got to
say that Patricia, my wife, we've been married for 15 years.
We've been together for 17 years.
She's a little bit older than I am.
She's a 55, I'm 40, so she's 15 years older than I am.
Although, she likes it to be like 14 years, you know.
So right now, it's the difference actually 14 years, because I just turned 40 in, you know,
anyway.
It doesn't matter.
It's, in fact, the older you get, the less it matters, right?
But she knows David Bowie, intimately, I believe, from the 70s.
So I'll tell you what we're gonna do.
See, 34 minutes on the clock, so we could talk about this for at least six minutes.
Let's see if I can find your Oscar Teller David Bowie story.
Anja, it's Patricia airs in the room.
Hi.
Yeah, I'm becoming a boy.
She's the only one who's on the floor, right?
Yeah, I'm getting my balloons for life, I'm getting my yay.
Yeah, I'm out.
I have new folks, Marka.
Yeah.
I'm coming to Casa.
Yeah, I'm ready for you right now.
I'm taping as we speak.
Oh, I'm coming to my studio.
I'm coming to your studio.
Yeah?
Everyone's really excited now.
Oh, they're listening.
Yeah, they're waiting, because, you know, they're waiting to hear.
Your David Bowie story.
She's a boy.
So this guy is appraising the house for,
because the other people need to get a mortgage.
Yeah.
The fuck is that?
Okay.
Coming to the, coming to my, into the source code studio.
This is my, oh, come on, Jess.
All right, everybody.
Ever bought it?
I'll sit with you here, because I got this idea.
I'll tell you what, I'm gonna put the mic in the middle,
so it ends out.
So I can listen on the headphones.
Now you can sit there, if not, sit over there.
Yeah, hold on.
There you go.
And then we'll put the headphones on, so I can listen.
Okay, let me.
Well, you have to interview me.
Yes.
Okay.
Hi there.
Hey, you're really cute.
I thought you were ready.
Are you a lesbian?
God.
Okay, so.
I'm every woman.
Yes, okay.
All right, so Patricia's my wife.
I already explained that you're just a little bit older than I am,
so you have some more of some better stories from early days.
They think you are older if they see us to get it.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, explain.
Yes.
Yeah, because I look like shit,
and you look very beautiful.
I'm firm.
Very firm.
And I'm sad.
My ass is sad.
Yeah, but you're still in a chair.
We've your left up on your left.
But do you love me?
Yeah, I do love you.
Okay.
So when did you, let me just jump right into the conversation.
When did you meet David Bowie?
And what you do remember what year it was?
I think it was round about 1969.
1969?
I was five.
I know.
And you were, so you were like 1920 years old?
I was 19 years old.
And in these days, you had those song contest,
festivals.
You had to go to.
Well, what do you mean you had to go to?
Well, if you want to be famous, and if you want to.
You're really cute when you're in a film store.
If you want to be famous, or do you want a real career,
you had to do these things.
So it was something else.
It was something else.
Like the Eurovision Song Contest, like that.
It's a sort of, yeah.
But then it was held in lovely places.
Oh, you know, when they still had budget.
Yes, if they had budget, beautiful, big orchestras, like 40
piece orchestras.
Oh, okay.
So it was lovely.
You know, you never knew what happened.
And so, you know, it was the best thing to do.
Okay.
So I went to Malta.
Malta.
Lovely.
Never been there.
It was very beautiful, very sort of a rabie, a rabie,
a rabie and kind of, yeah, sort of that.
And in much people, they were the same.
Yeah, lots of English people.
So probably that's why we all had to go there.
So you had a Germany Austria, you were representing the Netherlands.
And I was representing the Netherlands.
And there he was.
It was David Jones.
David Jones.
He wasn't even David Bowen?
No, no.
That doesn't count.
That wasn't David.
David Jones.
And he was representing the...
He was, he was more old.
But he was for England, of course.
And he had these...
What is this guy's name?
Who did the Beatles?
George Martin.
Yes, he had George Martin.
He was producing him.
He was his, yeah, and his musical director.
Everybody has his head as his own music.
Oh, okay.
It was way sheaker then then they're doing now.
This is the point.
I don't know.
100 million people watching.
It was beautiful.
It was all over Europe on TV.
It was, you know, it was very important.
Were you already selling albums at this point?
Yes.
Every, what they did was every country sent their biggest talent, or it's a talent
that they think, you know, it's going to, that could be a very big star.
Okay.
But you were already a star.
I was in Holland already starting my career and selling records.
So, okay.
It sent me to Malta and...
Did you like the drink?
No.
I have coffee.
Okay.
So, when I met David was, okay, there were no many very hip people there, and I was very
hip.
Right.
It was all sick of shit.
It was now most of them were a little bit, yeah, a little bit of a kind of...
Well, but this was the end of the 60s, so it was like, where you were hippies?
Crowners and I know.
Were you smoking dope?
Uh, yeah, I probably, you know, coming from Holland.
Don't remember.
Sure.
I don't remember.
I never remember.
Yes, we, I never remember.
But so David probably picked me out because he thought, well, that, Jake looks cool.
So I hang out with her.
Look at him.
Oh, you're blind me.
Look at them.
Who does?
So he was telling me about his new girlfriend that he has.
She was an actor.
And she looked a lot like Barbara Stranger.
Wait, Angie was that Angie?
That was Angie.
Oh, no.
She looks a lot like Barbara Stranger.
She looks like Barbara Stranger.
She has her own.
Yeah.
She was a young, uh, Barbara Stranger.
And she was a great actress.
He saw that.
Yeah.
He thought, uh, the character of Broadway.
But he was probably in love.
So he was involved.
He was doing a boyfriend at this time.
I was, I guess, I, yeah, I had a boyfriend.
Yeah.
But in these days, you look like Barbara Stranger?
No.
Yeah.
Down there.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
But in these days, when you were a hippie, it didn't matter.
If you, if you just met nice people, you hang out with them.
There was no age, you know, you could make love or, uh, yeah,
and it was great.
I told you so.
I don't love them.
And no, you, you, you hated when I tell you that.
Yeah.
We had to wear like, you know, truck tires.
I know.
But in these days, now, you could make love.
And the only thing you had to do is maybe protect yourself a little bit.
But, you know, for being, for getting pregnant, actually.
For getting pregnant.
Nobody was thinking about anything.
So everybody was a hornier's house.
And, uh, so we hang out a little bit.
And we, you know, and we had fun.
But although I thought, I didn't think he was sexy at all.
He didn't look sexy at all.
He was very strange.
He was, he was, uh, skitt, guitar was hanging around his neck
the whole day.
And he was playing it.
And, and, uh, everybody said,
oh, can you please tell the guy to stop?
What was he playing?
Oh, sort of things.
Um, so we went to the, I remember.
We went to for a walk on the beach.
And, um, he was singing songs for me,
because he was making an introduction.
Probably.
He was trying to make an impression.
And we was quite boring.
And what song was he playing?
He was playing, um, I remember.
He said, do you like this song?
Listen, I'm going to play.
I thought I heard it already.
But, okay.
And he played round control to Major Tom.
And I, and I thought, oh, man.
And it never ended.
And, uh, he was based on it.
Yeah.
And he was in the record.
And he said to me, don't you think I sound like John Lennon?
Oh, really?
Yeah, he thought he sounded like John Lennon.
That's what it was.
He was a big idol.
Yeah.
He wanted to sound like it.
But for him, he wasn't a star yet,
but he was actually, I think they sent it
because I thought there was something going on.
But we don't know what.
She did for color eyes.
So, and he said, I just got a, um, a record to deal.
And, uh, that's probably going to record this song.
And I thought, man, I hated already.
It sounded horrible.
And it, and you had to see him because he was,
he was, he was not wearing swimming trunks or anything.
Yeah.
He was wearing diapers.
He had sort of, you know, he wanted to be different.
And that's, you know, he still does.
He was wearing diaper.
He was so different from the rest.
He was wearing a sort of, you know,
what you see when, when Jesus, you know,
you see in the Bible.
Like drawing cloth?
Yeah.
Really?
So, sort of, it looked like a diaper.
Like a Roman thing or just,
No, nothing on.
He was very skinny.
Very pale.
He looked like a turtle.
He liked it.
He just liked it up.
You know, he was so white.
And, and, and brown.
And brown.
The whole day.
And I thought, man.
Stop.
So, um, and he tried, and of course he tried to kiss me.
You know, these things.
Wait, what was it?
Did he have the orange hair?
Was that the Ziggy hair?
No.
Just blonde hair.
Nothing.
No.
He was not attractive at all.
Yeah.
Now he always had.
And it's teeth were like horrible.
Horrible.
One, two, three.
You were even considering kissing that mouth.
Well, I kissed a little, but I thought,
Geez, no.
And you could feel like the jagged edges against your tongue.
Yeah, I guess so.
I guess so.
And then I remember his girlfriend.
I said, yeah, my American girlfriend is coming over.
And, like, she's very nice.
And we could have.
We could get together.
Yeah.
And maybe have a trio.
Oh, maybe she's so much.
Yeah.
And I thought, geez.
And I saw her coming.
Oh, no.
Not Barbara Streisand.
So they were trying and trying with nothing happens.
So, but years later, when I was really, really famous.
Well, that was that.
It was the song festival.
And he didn't win.
I didn't win.
I don't know.
It's not like that.
No, no.
He was not.
He tried.
And he was actually.
Trying the whole time that I was there.
Yeah.
I was way too pretty for him.
And he was a star.
And he had a shitties.
No, no, no.
He was not a star.
So what happened was after that.
It was really a hit.
Yeah.
He came in.
He thought, that's a song.
That's a song.
That's a fucking song.
The whole day.
Yeah.
So a couple years later after he had a couple of hits.
There was the.
Is that the question?
Yeah.
When he had his first hit, he think,
Should have done him.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But then then he had, after one hit that red hair.
And he started, came out and everything.
Yeah.
And I had to do a big event that is, that was every year.
That's called Kangala Dudes.
Kangala Dudes.
Yeah.
It's a great gala.
No.
It's an Amsterdam.
And it was very famous.
Very wide was there.
Adobe Gray, the three degrees.
So this was like 74, 75, maybe?
Yeah, I see.
So no, 74.
74.
And the grandgala Dudes.
And they asked me and my sister because we were also doing a lot of backing vocals,
because we were in the best backing vocals you can get to back up to back up some
some ex from America.
Yeah.
You guys were cute.
And we were very cute.
And so we did it was a big orchestra there.
And very wide.
We had to do the backing vocals for very wide.
His backing vocals, but they couldn't sing that well.
So we were behind the curtains doing them.
Yeah.
We backed up.
Doing the backing up them.
And we did some backing vocals for the three degrees.
Just to make it a little bit fuller.
Because when they, you know, on the record sounds better.
But that was like a real honor because that was cool.
We thought it was good cake.
Yeah.
And it was fun.
It was very musical.
Yeah.
You know, you were on star.
Sure.
And then I was standing.
We had to do a couple of things in front of the solo stage.
So the audience could see us.
And I knew I heard that David Bowie came in.
Because he was one of the guests too.
He was performing on the show.
Now he was performing somewhere in our Amsterdam.
But he was a guest in the audience.
And what is wife?
You sure you don't want to drink a water?
No, no, no, no.
You want to take a sip of coffee?
Yeah, I'm so cute.
You never told it.
Oh, you're dribbling.
You're so excited about David.
Yeah.
Now.
So I was working.
And he probably saw me standing there and said to Angie, isn't that?
There's a picture that we met a couple of years ago.
We met a couple of years ago.
Yeah.
She thinks he's lesbian, but she's stuck out for me.
Let's go.
Let's go snobber.
So afterwards there was a drink, of course, with all the stars.
And this was still the seven.
And I was walking around there.
And I bumped into him and he said,
I thought he was you.
How are you?
Oh, it's so good to see you.
And you look so pretty.
And even pretty.
I don't know.
I didn't fix it.
Very hot.
Because he was, you know, he was sick.
He started with his suit.
So he had the orange hair.
It was here.
And he had this little thing over his suit.
He had that out of the party.
Yes.
No way.
Because you know why?
Because he told me later.
Because he had a hat.
No one of his, you know, one of his eyes had a cataract.
Yeah, something.
Something.
Because one of the, you know,
The different color.
There was something going on.
Cool.
So that wasn't just a section.
So it was not even.
But it looked.
Of course.
Yeah.
And the teeth were still fucked up.
These were still crooked.
Not anymore.
I've seen.
Yeah.
But it was wonderful.
That's why it's.
I think she demanded to do.
Yeah.
He said do.
I'm not going to run.
I have a baby.
I think this is the time.
Fix your teeth.
So.
Um.
Uh.
Someone said, we met each other.
And he said, you would,
Would you like to come to the hotel and have a drink with me?
So we had downstairs.
We had a drink in the lobby.
And Angie was there too.
But in the meanwhile,
I heard and I've seen a little bit of it.
And he had quite a fight with the Angie downstairs.
She was very drunk.
As she said, I'm so pissed.
Right.
I'm so pissed.
And yeah.
Yeah.
I'm pissed.
Now pissed.
And she behaved horribly.
Because she's, she's a rough lady.
Yeah.
And he was very ashamed of her.
And that's why he wants to go back to the hotel.
And he said, would you like to come with me in the limo?
And I said, well, actually have to go home.
I haven't seen you for a long time.
So that might be nice.
So I went for a drink.
Oh, and you didn't think of that moment?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
I didn't know.
I mean, he had to slay thee with him.
Oh, no.
I'm a decent girl.
Of course not.
So we went upstairs and had a lovely talk about it.
It is room.
Yeah.
It was one of, it was in the big,
The biggest sweets in the Amstahl hotel.
And we had a drink.
And we were talking about the early days.
Because what happened in the meanwhile?
Yeah.
And I was telling him that fucking song can't believe it.
Oh, yeah.
I told him that.
I said, can't believe it.
Really?
You were right.
It was it.
And.
Oh.
And did he say, yeah, told you so?
And he was really sweet.
And he was smoking.
Really his head off.
You know, cigarettes.
A joint.
Of course.
He was an Amsterdam.
Yeah.
And you just get a high just for being in the room.
A little bit with him.
Oh, no, no, no.
I smoked.
And he, of course, he loved that.
So it was just, it was very romantic.
And he started to touch my hair.
My, my shoulders.
My, you know, my whole body.
And I thought, boy.
Okay.
His fame is now.
Yeah.
And that was nice.
I know he's much nice.
I thought he is David Bowie.
Of course, you know.
And I said, if I tell my sister,
I walked away.
And I didn't do that.
I said, are you crazy?
Yeah.
I can't.
So I went along.
And he's a great lover.
I have to say.
Anna.
Really?
Yeah.
Don't want to hear that.
But he's a great lover.
He has a lot of, so full of the girls.
That.
And done.
Done.
This.
Are you listening?
He is a great lover.
He's unbelievable.
Patience.
And he wants to give you everything you want.
He'll think that's not a good one of those when he did.
He led you from your head and that's him to your head.
Tell me if you're head.
He's not afraid.
Not at all.
His penis size is medium.
Not numbered that day.
Not yet Nad, thank you for answering that question.
So my secret day thereEnse means.
Oh, that's what he's going.
That's all he hopes to do.
So I, they, he's calling him.
Right.
He's calling.
That's right.
Hi, David.
I'm sorry.
We're going to play his routine Dolph Fries Judge.
I have to say nothing.
Something else matters.
That's inspirational. Very nice, nicely shaped, but nothing is he circumstance? No. No. I remember that.
Yeah. No, no, no. Just a normal English Dick. Dicky.
But it was nice. He went, oh, and he went on and went for a second time.
There he is calling again. He was going to say it was actually three times.
Really? Yeah, I remember that. And after that, I brush my teeth with his toothbrush, because I always liked brush my teeth afterwards.
And then, you know, when I know that you hate to hear this, I know that.
No, because knowing that my penis is bigger makes a world a difference.
Oh, okay. No. This is okay. This is valid.
We didn't know each other then. Yeah. Yeah. I want to do what I'm going to do.
And after, you know, when I was in the bathroom, I heard Angie coming in, and she was screaming at him.
Did you run the bathroom brush? I was in the bathroom and I thought she's going to get out of here.
This woman is going to kill me. And I heard him.
Yeah, I hear him shouting to her, and you're just such a pig, and you cannot behave.
And this and that, and I can do whatever I want to. And you know, you do that too, and blah, blah, blah.
So they had a big fight, and I slipped out.
It's not that bad.
It's not bad.
He never saw him again.
Yeah. And oh, yeah. We saw him.
We saw him on a mantra.
Yeah.
But that was with Angie.
No, no, no, no. He was with Kiki, go, go, go, go.
He was really weird. He was weird about that.
He was doing, he was strange about it.
Because he, this wife, his wife, then.
Yeah.
Whatever her name was.
Before.
What is her, his wife now?
Eman.
Before Eman, he had a very jealous, jealous wife.
I remember that.
And I read that a couple of times in the magazines.
So he didn't want to recognize, but he was waving at me.
And then we saw him sort of party from Joan Jett, remember?
Yeah.
He was there too.
And he was waving his smile again.
But he was still.
Yeah.
But he was so jealous.
He's not a very social person.
Yeah.
Well, he was fucking diapers on the beach.
What do you expect?
Yeah.
Fundus is wonderful.
So that was my story with David Bowie.
I really appreciate that.
And he, and oh, and I'm in his book.
Because he has a little tiny book.
He had a little black book.
Yeah.
So there's a little pocket book.
When he's booty call.
Yeah.
Sort of what he tells about his life.
His life.
All the chicks he had.
Yeah.
And there's pictures in it.
Really.
Yeah.
And there's one picture where I'm really, I'm in the picture.
But we've been taking, you know, have a proof it.
I've been taking it.
You've been taking it.
There's actually two questions.
Yeah.
You think David Bowie's a vampire?
Dawn wanted to know.
Dawn used to dream that David Bowie was a vampire.
And would come at night and bite her and they'd be vampires.
Yeah.
She wish.
Now he's a sweet guy.
He's a sweet guy that he's a little bit insecure in a couple of things.
Yeah.
He's not very.
He doesn't talk to you.
Yeah.
Isn't that strange?
At the same time.
Almost the same time.
Yeah.
But I don't have a bypass.
They have same.
They couldn't help me.
But that's strange.
Yeah.
I don't know.
You think he can still get it up with his bypass?
Well, it depends on.
I have to say, now you're not kidding because we know that from my dad.
So Dawn, you know.
So you don't have to worry about that.
Yeah.
He may appeal to you.
Because of the medicine.
If he has to take a lot of medicine, that could be a problem.
Yeah.
But still.
He's very good.
He's quite a talent.
Oh, he's very talented.
He's very talented.
He's talented.
I have to say.
I have to say he's a very nice, sweet person.
Normally, I would play space.
I'd already hear.
But, you know, that's legal.
Oh.
Yeah.
I would not love to do that.
That sucks.
Why?
Because, you know, I can get sued for playing.
For playing music that when I'd love to play.
We have to play stuff that can't play our memories.
That's illegal.
That's actually the man.
Yeah.
It's the law.
Oh.
Doesn't that suck?
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's play space out of it.
Thanks.
That was a great story.
Love you.
Love you too.
Thank you.
Ground control to major time.
Take your protein pills and put your helmet on.
You can't go to the train to major time.
Six, come and think.
Count down engines on.
Three, two, check, kick, watch them.
And they guys love you with you.
Yeah.
This is ground control to major time.
You've really made the grade.
And the papers want to know who shuts you in.
Now it's time to leave the capsule if you dare.
This is major time to ground control.
I'm stepping through the door.
And I'm floating in the most peculiar way.
And the stars look very different today.
Here and I floating around I didn't care.
Far above the world.
I'm into this blue and there's nothing I can do.
Don't want past one hundred thousand miles.
I'm feeling very still.
And I think my spaceship knows which way to go.
Tell my wife my love the very much you know.
Ground control to major time your subject,
That's something wrong.
Can you hear me by your tongue?
Can you hear me by my tongue?
Can you hear me by my sitting er of the mood?
And there's nothing I can do.
David Bowie was space oddity from the end of the sixties.
I ran a lot longer than intended on today's show.
We're an exactly an hour, but of course, when you get the sit down with Patricia for about 30 minutes
and talk about David Bowie and the size of his penis.
Hey, damn man, you just can't get that on regular radio.
You know what I'm saying, Bowie!
And that'll do it for the source code for today.
Tuesday, October 26, 2004.
Thank you very much for tuning in.
Hopefully you stay all the way to the end, because I think that was well worth it.
And this is one for the archives, eh?
So that's it.
I'm off to the Netherlands for some meetings, and of course, I'll be back tomorrow.
Our awesome intro.
Comments via text or even audio comments.
You can send them to Atomacree.com.
What is your comment on my weblog live.curry.com?
And all the archives and the most recently updated source code are at dailystorescode.com.
You'll find the podcast feed as well.
Did a source code.com slash all the says.fx and all.
Who knows what the rest of the week will bring, but this was certainly an interesting ramp.
I'd like to check you all tomorrow. Bye-bye.