Well, everybody, welcome to the thank god and spread edition of the daily source code.
My name is Adam Curry coming to you partially from the cottage in the UK from Curry Cottage
and we're about to go to a new location, actually studio A8.
So here's the deal.
I was scheduled to be interview today for Wired Magazine, which I presume was all about podcasting.
Anly knew it, came to Guildford and she actually turned out that they're doing a whole big piece on radio for Wired Magazine
and that they're actually featuring me and part of that is podcast.
That was all about podcasting, but turned out to be a semi-profile on me, so of course it took me much longer than expected.
It took me hours to talk about myself, you know how that goes.
So after about three hours of pushing room, hanging out at Starbucks and talking about my life,
of course, eventually the question came, can I watch it do a podcast?
I said no, no, you cannot watch me do a podcast, you can be in a podcast with me.
And this is not the right place at Starbucks, at least because, you know, I have two headphones and really close micang because of all the noise.
So I suggest that we then walk up to the parking spot where I have the Audi and we use the A8 studio to record a little show.
And it turned into kind of me interviewing Annely and she interviewing me and what we talked about all kinds of stuff, like start fucking, and well you name it.
In fact, you're going to enjoy it right now. Today is Friday, source code.
Enjoy.
Okay, so perfect point to slide into the beginning of the podcast from the A8 studio A8 in overlooking downtown Guildford.
What does that mean studio A8?
That means that I'm sitting in the car studio.
I have a little bit too much reverb actually for the car studio.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I turned the reverb off.
Ah, much better.
Here with Annely.
Do you want to be identified as...
Sure, you can identify me however you want.
As a journalist here today from Wired Magazine.
Yes, that's right.
Okay.
And we've just sat in Starbucks for...
I can't believe we sat there for about three hours.
Yeah.
And actually, we're not sticky or there's no problems.
Well, when I got up, I did feel the chair, like kind of the covering lifted up with me as I stood up.
Yeah.
I noticed that girl who then said, okay, please sit there.
Didn't she say that immediately?
She did.
She wanted our seat.
Cause next to the outlet.
Outlet.
Yes, the power.
Electronic power.
So Annely came...
Now, we've been in contact for about a week or so.
And she asked if she could come and interview me.
And I figured it was more about podcasting than anything,
but now that we just spent three hours talking about me.
Yeah, that's what I was telling you.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about himself.
I'm good at that.
Yeah, he's, yeah.
You can tell.
That's what the Saliliqui is all about.
That's right.
Yeah.
He's a practice, a practice self storyteller.
Story.
No, no, no.
You know, that's interesting because...
Because that is what I've done my entire life.
The minute you put on a pair of headphones and you have a microphone,
you're kind of talking to yourself.
And I've always imagined that there's probably one other person listening.
Whether there were thousands, tens of thousands or hundreds of thousands,
or perhaps millions where they were watching on TV.
And it feels no different to this...
The podcasting or being on MTV.
In fact, on MTV was even easier.
Do you know that actually that we all were kind of talking to the crew?
They were standing right next to the goddamn camera.
The guy, you know, the camera up would, you know,
you could see and put his head around smiling or whatever.
Or the associate producer who would be there, you know,
trying to make sure that you're saying all the right things
or hitting all the promotional items.
And basically just be talking to them.
And you feel good right when they laugh and stuff like that.
Yes.
I want the camera got a laugh.
Exactly.
How did you know that?
Did you watch enough MTV to pick up on that?
It's true. You can tell that it's playing right to the camera.
Totally.
And I see some of that now.
Do you remember when E started up and E was kind of like
MTV of entertainment before turning to what it is now?
Because that was started by Lee Masters,
who was kicked out of MTV by John Reardon,
just some inside dirt there.
And it was exactly the same thing.
You're doing all this entertainment news,
but basically laughing with the camera crew
trying to, you know, get a rapport going.
Yeah.
And so we essentially had the same thing with podcasting.
Only the feedback doesn't necessarily come from the camera crew.
It comes from, you know, the podcasters themselves.
And the e-mail listeners.
Yeah.
The e-mail, well, you just, we just went through
some of my, my production that I, that I do for the show
with basically scanning the e-mail downloading all the MP3s.
And I haven't had a chance to listen to everything.
So I might put some of those things on the next show.
But I just wanted to figure out what exactly you're doing.
Because you, I mean, you must, first of all,
you had something else to do, right?
It wasn't just, you didn't just come over all the way
to, to Guilford just for me.
But no, I was just in Guilford for you.
I, I can go for it.
But you went London for other things, right?
There was other stuff you could do.
I came all the way to London just for you Adam.
Really?
Yeah.
And you're not shitting me, right?
No, I'm totally not.
Don't change it because we had a really good rapport
because it's totally true.
I flew all the way out to London.
And it's like, I'm so paid for me to come out and talk to you.
Who?
Uncle Sy.
Uncle Sy?
Oh, he's the, is he the dude?
He's the dude.
And wired?
Okay.
So, he's not the founder of wired.
No, no.
He just owns it.
He owns Condonast.
Oh, okay.
So he actually personally?
No, he didn't personally call me and say, hey.
Okay.
Condonast.
But that's Condonast is like big.
They own, like, lots of languages.
You can't even, I'm like a fly on his shoe.
Like he has no idea.
Don't put yourself down like that.
No, I mean, on size shoe.
I mean, I'm sure there's other people who care, who care more.
Okay.
So.
And, you know, no offense side for listening.
I mean, just to, just so I can understand this.
So someone says, there's a, do you mind just walking through it?
How the work?
So there's a meeting.
There's a meeting.
The high level thinkers at wired magazines get together.
And they come up with something smart that they want to cover.
You know, cover.
Like in this case, radio.
Okay.
Oh, radio.
That's the, yeah.
And, you know, some secret that we will not disclose stories or assign to various
people that are all about the, you know, the sort of mutations that radios going through.
Now that technology is changing.
Right.
We were talking about before, right?
Challenges to radio.
Yes.
From, you know, new technologies and radio really hasn't gone through that.
And, and so then, you know.
So for XM, that's kind of, that's kind of what that is.
Yeah, I mean, that's out, that's out there's so far.
And there's actually now, there's a program that some guys invented, which allows you to record XM.
And then enable it and, you know, store it.
Yeah.
Sort of.
But where do you store it?
In the car or at home or.
You store it on your media player on whatever, whatever, you know,
Okay.
Your audio player is.
Yeah.
I don't mean to say media player like the windows.
No, I know.
Generic.
Thank you.
Thank you for, yes.
Thank you for clarifying.
That's important.
Please do not use the window media player.
Why not?
It's evil.
No.
DRM.
And Microsoft in general has some, I think, poor policies regarding its media player.
But we could talk about that later.
Okay.
But yes.
So this is for a big radio article.
Well, it's about, so there will be articles about radio.
And I'm doing the article in podcasting and featuring Adam Curry.
See, this is the part that really I loved.
The Prince of podcast.
Yeah.
You heard that.
Don't tell me you've heard that.
The Prince of podcast.
Did you hear the song?
I haven't heard you encouraging people to create the song.
I haven't heard any Adam Curry for like two days.
I mean, except in person, which is, you know, which is, of course, as much better than.
But it's different, you know, when somebody is in person.
You know, it's weird to like hear somebody on their podcast and meet them in person.
You keep wanting to like not look at them and just hear their voice.
And it's like not so distracting.
There's like a person attached to the voice that's really in my iPod.
Yeah.
So what are you doing?
Well, what I was doing is actually I was going to see.
I have my iPod here and I put my eye trip on because we're in the A8 studio.
Right.
What I was going to do is I was going to play something over the sound system here.
So we can record it through the microphones at the same time.
You know, you can also hear it because you're not wearing headphones.
And I don't have a, it's not a real studio.
No.
I don't know.
I don't even know.
I like the fact that there's a map of Gilford on his little.
Isn't that the shit though?
It also has little icons for where you can check this out.
Check this out.
That red sun looking.
Shit.
I don't know.
What is that?
Yeah.
Is that a places you can go to get tattoo door?
And we should check that out.
Well, watch this.
Watch this.
Because this is a DVD navigation system.
So watch me zoom out.
And you'll see.
Does it show like planet earth?
Wow.
So I can go to any place within this map, which is all of Europe.
Let's go to, let's go Berlin.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let's go.
Let's go to Berlin.
So country.
Right.
We'll select Germany.
Town.
This is being loaded.
It's a big ass country.
It's not that big anymore.
Well, for a whole bunch of towns.
Hold on.
But we could go to an obscure German town.
Well, Berlin.
Berlin.
In multiple languages.
Okay.
Berlin.
What is Berlin here?
It's a little Berlin.
It's a Berlin in Dutch spelling.
I want to go to special destination or just a street.
Let's go special destination.
Yes.
Maybe we can find out what that is.
Yeah.
It's a little sun.
It's a landmark.
How about an ice skating rink?
Fine.
Ice skating rink of Berlin.
I don't understand why the ice skating rinks aren't also landmarks.
Well, not necessarily.
There might be, could be a landmark.
Here.
Ice, ice, portala.
Do we go there?
Ice, portala?
Yes.
We even got the phone number.
We now set a destination.
Start route guidance.
When it starts us with the globe.
I just want you to know right now.
We're seeing a slow zoom.
Okay.
There it is.
There's our route.
If we leave now.
We will be there at 330 this morning.
Great.
Well, all the way.
We have to go underneath.
We have to take the train.
All the way from Gilford to the ice rink in Berlin.
Yeah.
We could be that at 330.
If we left right now.
That's great.
Well, that's the power of technology.
Isn't that wonderful?
And it also has the traffic monitor system.
So what the traffic is going to be like?
Well, what it'll do actually.
It'll route you around bad traffic.
Wow.
Yeah.
And they can shoot.
Okay.
Now, what I was going to do.
I was looking for the Prince of Pod.
I can't believe that you haven't heard that.
You haven't heard enough.
I know clearly.
My ears are not.
I have not.
Hold on a second.
You see how easy it is to fill up 10 minutes of.
Of of MP3 space.
We just did 10 minutes.
I know.
Just looking at maps.
It's easy.
And people eat to shut up.
Well, let me see if I can find Prince of Pod.
It's true.
I mean, I was willing to listen to like 20 minutes of you not being able to launch Skype.
With Lee.
With Lee Wilkins.
Lee.
Are you there?
Oh, dude.
Oh, man.
It was just like hanging out with my friends.
We were like.
Oh, no.
Oh, almost.
Hold on.
That's the BBC traffic report cutting.
Hey, Jenny.
You're all.
On the internet.
In that cool.
Someone has a traffic report.
It cuts in.
It just keeps letting you know.
Here at the ice rate.
There's a little bit of traffic.
Okay.
I seriously want to play a song for you, though.
I seriously.
Okay.
Hold on.
See how much I hate this iPod interface.
Now, how long it's taken me to find something.
He's doing that thing where you like spin your finger around the dial.
He's using his thumb, though.
A lot of.
You do it with your finger.
The index finger method.
Really?
The thumb.
I don't have the thumb method is.
You know.
That's.
That's interesting.
The thumb.
No, the thumb method is the only.
I only know the thumb method.
You got to learn the finger method.
It's.
I think it's faster.
But it's.
It also requires two hands.
So.
Okay.
So I'm going to.
He's testing the finger method.
Yes.
The finger method sucks.
Okay.
I want to play some with severe spitties.
Excellent.
Now, you've heard of him, right?
I have.
Have you actually seen him live?
I haven't.
No, I just heard him on your podcast.
And I was like.
Okay.
I'll do.
I'll play.
You do have to meet him.
In fact.
Oh, let me.
I'll have to pull this up for a second.
Well, this is.
What's setting up?
Well, it's.
The listivious bitties are performing.
I'm such a mess.
Are performing Sunday night in Manhattan.
Of course, there's not the email I was looking for.
I want to put that in later.
I guess.
This is me taking a drink of water.
Go for it.
Do I have.
See, Leanna sent me.
Leanna from a severe spitties.
It sent me email.
There's so many different email accounts.
Okay.
I'll post about this in the in the production show notes.
But essentially they're doing a show on the.
14th.
So that's Sunday.
Sunday Monday.
Well, today is the 10th 11th 12th.
It's Monday.
Then I guess.
Well, in Manhattan at 11 o'clock, no cover.
And if you use the secret word.
Yeah, which we have to come up with.
Then you get in free at the door.
So of course, it would be.
What's a good word?
What's a good secret word that people just want to say podcast.
So that too.
podcast is good podcast or source code or.
Yeah.
Or you could do like something that was, you know, more self-promotional.
Like I love Adam Curry.
Yeah, no, no, no.
Because that would be wrong.
Um, no, I'm just still trying to figure out where her email went.
I had it saved obviously.
I'll find it.
Now, it should be.
Just podcast.
Yeah, I think podcast works, right?
Okay.
Yeah, it's broken.
Okay, podcast.
If you meant, and I'm going to give you all the details.
Uh, what we'll do is we're going to play some list of these
Bitties.
And let me see if this is working.
Yeah, I think it is.
Yes.
Okay.
Um, I'm going to play famous.
That's one of my favorite Bitties songs.
So we have to kind of be quiet what place.
Then otherwise you'll, they'll hear us.
Okay.
But it'll be cool.
Here's the CBS Bitties.
So I have to find the right spot, so it doesn't crackle.
I want to be famous.
I want to wear minks and sattens and pearls.
More than just any old girl.
I want to have eyes as blue as the sea.
I want all the people to look at me.
I want my own show on TV.
I want to be that girl.
I want to be famous.
Eat out at sardies.
I parties at spy.
I want to be famous.
Got to Paris on private flights.
I want to have lovers buy the score.
Movie producers knocking down my door.
This is the faith that is in store for me.
Oh, when I'm famous, I will wear a great trench coat and fake red hair.
So that all will know that it is me.
When they see me, how they'll smile.
At the point of the day I start to get laughing.
It was like there's a team and when they have all the fashion, sort of like old times.
Yeah, I like that, I love that.
Yeah, I know, I love that.
They give her a buddy, a little bit.
Yeah.
Kind of like lounge singer.
I think he played in circles this time.
Oh, I'm sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm planning to keep that up.
But he knows.
Oh, I will be a Barbie doll with huge fake tits.
No hips at all.
And I hate us attitude.
And oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Every morning I'll get high on.
Colored Hills, Martini's dry.
A little way and just good touch.
Oh, oh, oh.
I want to be my famous better than all of my friends.
Oh, much better than all of her.
I want to be famous, lonely and unknown at the end.
Oh, I'll end up bitter and ugly and old.
Not just my body, but also my soul.
But a legend is my goal and a legend of me.
When I'm famous, not a will give for the little people.
Oh, they have tears when I'm famous.
Hey, my friend.
Welcome to Adam Curry's Jazz Cafe.
Everybody.
All right.
That was the serious bitties.
I want to be famous.
You can check them out at bittiesforever.com.
And I found the email.
So it's Tuesday.
There's a, I even got me information wrong.
It's Tuesday.
There's a no cover show in Manhattan at 11 p.m.
It's the bitties holiday party in Manhattan at the living room.
Any idea where that is?
It's 154 Ludlow Street.
And there's even an, I'll put this in the podcast show notes.
2125337235.
One set 11 p.m.
And here's the deal.
The end suggests you could give your listening audience a secret code.
So they can come up to me or the production manager Ben.
Say the code.
And they will know how many people came.
Thanks to the podcast.
Maybe she's just during the, during the set.
Just say anyone here from the source code.
Raise your hand without talking.
Yeah.
There's another way to go.
My be better.
But also the, the secret word is pod squad.
That's what it has to be.
Pod squad.
Pod people.
Yeah.
Like we're going to come up.
Similarly you.
Oh, no.
But anyway, definitely go check out.
It's a no cover.
So go check out the, the bitis, the, the listivious bitis at the bitis holiday party in Manhattan at the living room.
Tuesday to some of 14th 11 p.m.
154 Ludlow Street.
I think great thing about these podcasts is you can basically use the thumb or finger method to replay that message and find out exactly where it is.
Still here with with Analy who's come to lovely gilford.
Uh, to talk about pod casting and did you get enough about me and you think you know enough about my life?
I feel like I do.
Yeah.
You didn't have any of the sex questions I expected.
There was none of that.
Yeah.
I mean we could do the sex questions now.
Okay.
So I'm waiting for you to interview me some more actually.
I think that'll be really cool.
So, you know, how was sex with Michael Jackson?
You know, when I met Michael Jackson was the weirdest thing the first time I met him because we
met him.
This is when I had to give him the Michael Jackson video Vanguard award, which was created only for Michael Jackson, so he would.
He could only be given to him by you precisely.
Yeah.
You know the story.
And the reason why the sex part.
I had those sex with Michael Jackson.
What's the point?
But here's what was weird.
So this was at MJJ Studios in Los Angeles.
It's not in some weird back-ass road to.
Beautiful studios, right?
So you walk in there.
And what was weird was immediately.
I saw that they were at least 10 kids running around.
And how he Mandel was there.
Which is.
Which is weird.
I mean, well, thank you.
I don't know.
It's like, you know, maybe.
Was he pulling a glove over his head?
Well, no.
Maybe the how he Mandel was supposed to like keep the kids busy with it.
And with his body's world voices or something.
Yeah.
You're doing a lot of the body's voice.
It was scary.
You know, adults in Michael's life.
At that point, we didn't know about any of the allegations.
Yeah.
And I still don't know if it's true.
I mean, I have to say a lot of the evidence or what is being called evidence points that way.
But that's hard.
I have no idea.
Did they just read his house again?
Yeah.
He's fucked.
He really is fucked.
And you know that Tommy Matolle, you know, Tommy Matolle is right?
No.
Tommy Matolle.
He runs Sony Records.
Oh, OK.
And he was married to Mariah Carey.
Right?
There's a whole story all by itself.
Tommy Matolle hates or at least when I was in New York and in the scene hated Michael Jackson.
And Michael Jackson is so insecure and so childish really.
That all these promotions to do when this was the bad album.
Literally, of course.
This was the bad album.
And so the head Michael in the in the limo and they're going from, you know, from station to promotion or whatever.
And Michael kept saying, I really have to go to the bathroom.
And Tommy Matolle would not let him fucking pee.
It's so awesome.
On purpose.
Not to can't do it.
Can't go pee here and not.
We've not let him take a piss.
He hated him so much.
Just be in this cup.
Really?
I don't know what happened.
I think he held it until he was back in the hotel.
But that was horrible.
No, Michael Jackson.
Very sad case.
I think.
Very sad.
Could let's be honest.
Boy can sing.
Boy can dance.
Very, very musical.
Very musical.
But he has turned into a zombie.
More people than me have said that.
But yeah.
I don't know if that's just what you see.
This is the thing.
This podcast is real honest.
And there's nothing.
People can tell who we are and they're hearing us.
And there's nothing in between this microphone and everyone else's ears.
But you don't know what you're getting from Michael Jackson.
What's real or what's not real?
A two second sound bite on TV.
But you can tell that he's a zombie from the two seconds.
I mean, you know, he's the one.
I want to say yes.
But I have a feeling that some of that is also accentuated by the way it's edited.
I don't know.
Even the stuff that he edits him, that he's, you know, he's in control of editing.
You think that he's not.
I don't know.
He's a zombie on the stuff that he had that he had control of.
I thought it was actually pretty good the stuff that he had.
Yeah, I guess so.
But you see that he's trying to control it.
That's what was irritating about that.
Even that documentary that he made.
Did you see that?
No, no.
What was the documentary?
Well, there was two documentaries that the everything came to
ahead with this English guy who did a documentary.
That was like a tell all experts.
Yes.
But at the same time, he Michael Jackson has own cameras rolling and you saw
the other side, which totally exposed the English documentary to be set up,
kind of, you know, edited to make him look funky.
But what at the same time gave away is how controlling he was trying to be over
his own destiny and the way he was having his stuff edited.
Wow.
So with Michael's view and sensationalist view.
Yeah.
Okay.
So I didn't have sex with Michael Jackson.
We've established that.
I've actually not had sex with any famous people accept my wife.
I've come close.
So what was the closest you got to star-fucking?
Mandy Smith.
You remember her?
I vaguely remember Mandy Smith.
Mandy Smith was the Lolita 16 year old that Bill Wyman married.
Mm-hmm.
Then Bill, the Rolling Stones.
And it was a big to do because he essentially had sex with her when she was like
14.
But they got married when she was 16.
And then she had a song a record out.
Mm-hmm.
And she came to the Netherlands to promote that.
Well, I was doing TV and she was totally coming on to me.
Totally.
Now at the time being, I had a client-designed relationship with Patricia.
It was very famous in Europe.
Mm-hmm.
And she was married.
So we came up with this great plan.
Because she's really nice.
And Mandy Smith, the time very sweet girl.
So you had a chance to be the star-fucking two women at the same?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Not at the same time, but during the same time period.
Yes, but it was different.
Because Mandy and I had real no real interest in each other.
But we had the same problem.
She was being stalked by paparazzi, et cetera.
Because she had this relationship with Bill Lyman,
which wasn't really known at the time.
But she was going out with Bill.
She wasn't married to him yet.
It was like six months later.
And I had this whole thing with Patricia, which was supposed to be not known.
So what did we do?
I invited her come over to Amsterdam and we went out together.
And then everyone was talking about us.
It was the verdict.
And then of course there was this point where we said, well, we just have sex.
This is where we're faking it anyway.
It's like man, never mind.
Oh, no.
Because now she loved Bill when I love Patricia.
It was like, but that was about the closest.
So do you think that that means that like the Tom Cruise Penelope,
Cruise thing deaf?
Tom is totally gay.
Come on, the gay.
Who is it?
We're totally not having sex at all.
I have no idea.
You can be gay and have sex with women.
Oh, sure, sure.
But I mean, your story kind of is shattering.
My illusions about the fact that, you know, he's probably, because I was sort of enjoying
imagining Tom Cruise, you know, having to force himself to have sex with him.
To have sex with him.
Just to have his punishment for him for staying in the closet.
You know, it's like, you will be forced.
I gotta tell you though, that must be so hard to live your life like that.
Yeah, I can't even imagine.
Because George Michael is just come out, right?
Really, this is...
He's now going and he's doing a tour for promotional tour for his new album.
Yeah.
And he's been on the BBC several times.
You know, just going through this whole thing.
And he said at one point, he said, I have to do the English accent.
Otherwise, doesn't work.
Oh, my God.
I couldn't believe it.
It was like, here I was.
I was the number one pop star on the world.
And I was a fucking poof.
And he was freaked out about it.
You know, because he was mainly huge in America.
And he was like, he was really freaked.
And he couldn't let he couldn't be himself.
And I remember, I couldn't even get an interview with him.
He was so freaked out about life and everything in general.
He couldn't deal with it.
He still can't deal with being famous, really.
He just wants to be a writer and a singer and a producer and all that.
And a poof.
And he's a major poof.
And he's very good at it.
But I think...
But more importantly, Rob Helfer came out.
I mean, that's like way more important.
But that was such a...
For some reason, and for those of you don't know, Rob Helfer
to Judas Priest, he came out several years ago.
And he had like a new band, a new new, like...
Like almost as well.
Like almost as well, man.
But no one really cared.
Did he lose...
I mean...
Really?
Did you...
Did you lose interest in the band?
I was happy.
But I had always admired them.
As a youth, my first concert with...
Was you depressed for real?
Yeah, for real.
It was so cool.
And I learned the whole thing about, like, holding it
if you're lighter to light.
Like that.
Yeah.
That was my first experience.
Excellent.
And I was like, oh, and all that time, he was a homo.
That's so awesome.
We didn't know.
Boys, you can be a tough metalhead and be queen.
And actually, if you play the records backwards,
it does say...
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
At all the time.
No.
It wasn't saying worship Satan.
It was saying...
You know, the bitties actually have a piece of back masking.
I found that I was listening to the album.
It was true, they really do.
That what I haven't played it backwards yet.
But you don't really.
No, but they have a piece that's backwards on the album.
I'm going to check it out.
There's a back masking piece.
It probably is just literally a piece backwards.
That is probably nothing more than that.
But you're right.
That's it.
So anyway, so yeah, Tom Cruise.
Yeah, Tom Cruise.
Tom Cruise.
How'd we get on the whole homo thing?
I don't remember.
It was...
Something about sex.
And it was you not having sex.
Right, not having sex.
That person who is your beard, even though it was a heterosexual beard.
There was a heterosexual beard.
Oh my god.
And it's fun because all those years at MTV,
you'd think...
Because we were very separate from the offices.
Officers were at 175 Broadway before that 1775.
And we were down.
We actually had the studio right next door to the Sally Jesse Raphael Show.
So in the morning, I would tape my segments.
And then during lunch, I'd have to stay in my dressing room
because all these degenerates, you know, like,
midgets having sex with, you know,
you know, whatever.
It's all kinds of stuff.
It's just having sex with their mothers.
Yeah, right.
We're walking down the hallway.
And it was...
It was...
It was a traffic report.
Yeah.
That was a traffic report from the BBC.
But never.
Never.
Did I see...
See, or was I offered anything other than maybe a token
to join?
Never saw any coke.
No, I've never even done cocaine.
No.
Nothing.
All that rock and roll, you know,
stuff that may have oozed from MTV screen.
Not true.
It was horrible.
It really was just getting high and not having sex.
No, but they were...
Well, just...
No.
People weren't even really smoking pot.
It was me and Rick, the audio guy.
You were...
We were the pot fans.
Yeah.
No, the camera guys were not...
No.
Rick.
Rick's my boy.
He'll always be my boy.
It was so good.
We would share my dressing room and these audio booths.
So, you know, whenever he had to take a dump,
he'd literally come to my dressing room and sit there and read my fan mail.
Well, I was doing the audio.
And we wouldn't tell anyone.
That's a good...
That's a good way to, you know, hang out.
Well, I also learned a lot about audio.
Like, through the bathroom door, like he'd be taking a dump.
And he'd be like, dude.
No, no, because no, because I'd watch him.
How we would do the audio stuff.
Yeah.
He'd say, oh man, it's time for my dump.
Okay, Rick.
Well, you know, he had these bags.
A number of postcards before email.
Just get postcards and naked pictures.
So, I had huge postal bags full.
And, you know, just...
Whenever he had time, he opened like 20 of them.
He had no time to open all of them and read it.
And so, Rick went to help me scan the mail while he was using my bathroom.
And that'd be tracking...
I'd be opening the mics and starting the tapes and everything in the audio booth.
And the directors didn't know about it.
They'd just say, you know, alright, track 97A.
And I just opened up the track and I would start up the music.
And then sometimes I'd fuck up and be like, Rick, are you high again?
And I'm like, mmmm.
They didn't know it was me running the audio board.
And the good old days of this scene.
The good old day.
Dude, we've been at it for 31 minutes.
I think we should stop.
So I can put in 10 minutes of opening and closing things.
Yeah.
I think that's a good idea.
And I think that's a good idea.
What I would love is if you...
You should do your own podcast.
You're perfect.
I know.
If you want to see my work, you can go to my website.
Yeah.
Textploitation.com.
Textploitation.
T-E-C-H-S.
And then theploitation part.
You can work as well.
But it's not, you know, with an X.
So, yeah, I mean, I don't know about doing the podcasting thing.
I'll think about it.
I like being on your podcast.
Well, you can be on my podcast anytime you want.
You got Skype?
I have Skype, yeah.
We can try getting that working for 20 minutes on my next podcast.
See what crap we can go through.
I really appreciate you taking the time to come down and talk about, you know, whatever.
Yeah.
It was worth the jet lag.
Yeah, I was going to say, could you?
What did you get in yesterday?
Got in yesterday.
So that was my jet lag day.
Because I saw you with, I saw one yon.
That was...
I'm totally recovered.
I forced myself to stay awake all day.
Right.
So that I would be totally set.
So that way I can go tomorrow back to the day.
You're going back tomorrow?
Yeah.
Okay.
So the budget's not that big.
It wired.
You don't get anything else in London?
No, no.
I could have stayed if I wanted to.
But I need to get back.
Because, you know, my sweetie's having a performance on Saturday night.
Really?
I want to be there and, you know, support her and, you know,
What does she solo or play in a band?
So she runs a show called Writers With Drinks in San Francisco,
which is a spoken word variety show.
And she's the NFC and there's going to be a lot of great writers.
Tim Stanley Robinson is going to...
Hello, podcast.
I know.
Okay.
Saturday night.
At the makeout room in San Francisco.
730.
Tim Stanley Robinson, an awesome science fiction writer.
He's going to read.
There's going to be a bunch of other awesome readers.
And come on.
It's like three bucks to get in.
Can we...
I mean, this is the kind of stuff.
We put a link to it on your brain.
We should record this.
Oh, yeah.
We should record it.
Fuck.
This is your podcast.
Yeah.
Here's your drinks.
No, seriously.
Yeah, totally.
Love that shit.
That would be great.
I mean...
I'm going to tell Charlie.
I don't know what the, you know,
how would, you know, what people think about them being recorded and being podcast,
but shit.
What a tremendous opportunity to get this stuff out.
Yeah, really.
It's really good.
We've had a lot of fun with this.
I love spoken word type stuff.
You too.
Have you heard the spoken word revolution?
It's an audio book.
I'll send you a link.
Cool.
I can't.
So I could digital restriction management.
Exactly.
Now, but that's the kind of stuff that we need more of.
Yeah, we do.
I mean, the thing with podcasting is it's just in its infancy.
So I'm looking forward to seeing a lot more stuff like that.
Like independent artists doing spoken word.
You know, people bringing you news from underground communities that you don't normally hear from.
And that's what I think is really great.
And people broadcasting from their cars.
Hey, man.
And look at this gear.
I should take a picture of this.
I don't have a Pimp in mind.
My car is pimp.
I don't need anyone to pimp it anymore.
He's got a studio in here.
Yeah, it's pretty great.
And the BBC in constant traffic updates.
All right.
So you need me to take you back to the station?
Yeah.
Yeah, that'd be great.
Okay.
I know what we'll do.
Of course I can.
You just bear with me because you know, I'm still learning this left hand.
Side of the road.
You've got the new Pimp and ride has to have the steering wheel on the right hand side.
I think.
After the leases.
Oh.
You don't do this by yourself.
No.
Do not do this at home, kid.
Do not mod your car.
All right.
It could result in severe penalties somewhere down the line.
Yeah.
I think it's in the Ula.
All right, Emily.
Thank you very much for hanging out.
Thanks very much.
Come on back to source code anytime you can.
Thank you.