Well, howdy everybody welcome to this
It is Tuesday, September 28th, 2004.
It's Tuesday afternoons, 5...
an interesting day. On the phone a lot of people doing a lot of stuff. I kind of chilled
out yesterday and Monday and all I did basically was record a really long source code. I went
up to Breda not only for the stop off of my buddies at the Moroccan place but also went
back to a premiere last night of a musical. Let's dial down the music a little bit.
This is a musical done by a friend of ours, a big musical production that's called
Love Me Just a Little Bit More and it's based on or not really based on, it's a story that
uses all of the songs by this girl band from the 80s from Holland called The Dolly Dots.
And I've forgotten how many songs they had made. Lots of albums and it was kind of
like a grease. In the 80s you had grease which was about the 1950s. So this was pretty
much 2004, almost 2005 and we're looking back at the 80s. It was a high school and
but it was it was
funny and it made me feel old on one hand but also it you know it made me laugh
and it made me also proud of some of the leg well now I guess if you look at leg
warmers and big hair and shoulder pads as the legacy of the 80s maybe we
shouldn't be so proud but it was it was alright so I just kind of dicked around
yesterday and today had to do a bit of business take care of some stuff make
sure the empire is running right and been on the phone this morning I saw that
Dave was online and I gave him a quick instant message and he said you know
let's switch audio and so we did and I've learned by now that I've got to keep
the record button handy because of all of a sudden you know we're getting into
some interesting conversation and we'll say hey you know let's record this and
Dave wanted to record it I don't know why but we did so a new trade
secrets born a short one like 36
The good news is we get the SIP phone stuff working but it was 3 a.m. where Dave was and
he was over modulating and I knew I'd have to walk him through the mic levels and we
were talking about something else.
But it did work and all it really took on his end if you'll remember if you caught
our trade secrets where we were trying to get that system working, the problem was
Dave just had to reboot his machine.
So he rebooted and it worked.
But we got to work on the quality.
I'm sure we can get it working but the good news is if we can get the SIP phone
working I think with the free X10 Lite version I can conference three calls in
together which means we could do a call-in show because we can set up a
virtual phone number, we can set up a couple, I'll set up one in New York, in
California and in the United Kingdom and then basically you dial that number
if it's local to you which should be you know we should be able to pretty
much get local service you know that should be local to a lot of people who
listen to this and it shouldn't be too bad to call if you're someone.
in the middle. And then that'll be routed through to my SIP phone. On one hand I'll be talking
to Dave and then we can just conferencing, I guess, two more lines. And if I can't do
it with the free version, then after some testing, after I'm convinced that this is
going to work for us, then we'll do it. We'll buy a pro version or whatever. There's
also this thing called the Asterix PBX, which is a software-based PBX. You can route
calls and stuff all over the place. It's open source. It's beautiful. It also works
on OSX. But I thought it was a little bit too much overkill for what we're trying to
do. But as we progress, and as this coming Thursday, I think, we're going to try and
do a trade secrets together. So I can't be a soliloquy, I guess, if it's
together. Still word of the week, soliloquy. We're going to record a trade
secrets while we're watching the presidential debate. And is it just me
or is something wrong with Mac.com's email today? Because I think that,
all of a sudden, just stop receiving mail. I forward my email from curry.com to
adamcurry.com.
And nothing's coming in.
And the Surefire test is I went into the web browser, into the webmail, and sent an email
to myself at www.mc.com from that address and it hasn't shown up.
So I think something's wrong with Apple's email system, which bites.
Where's the announcement?
Put something on your web page.
Come on.
It can't be just my account.
I'm sure.
I hope not.
Maybe it's filled up.
Is there a way to see if your account?
No, it's only 250 messages in there.
No, it can't be filled up.
Anyway, lots of clips and bits to play for you today.
Lots of new stuff coming on the radar.
Some exciting prospects to talk about today.
And actually I wanted to just kick it off with some tunes because I haven't really
had a chance to play anything today.
And if you don't like it, skip it!
Rock and roll, Hoochie-Coo, Rick Derringer.
Thanks for watching!
I'll see you tomorrow.
Boy.
Yeah baby.
Ended up there.
All right.
I keep wondering about what I want to, you know, what kind of songs I want to play in
the source code and I always want to.
Um, actually, who was that?
I got an email about that because I'd asked, you know, do you really listen to the song
or not?
What is crypt? Crypt says, I usually always skip the songs.
By guess that's just my taste in music. Keep it up. See ya.
Crypt. So, you know, it's like that's the beauty of this.
If you don't like the song, just skip ahead.
You know, it's gonna be three or four minutes later on in the show.
Also, I've been, every single morning I scan the,
as I go through my new shows playlist on my iTunes or on my iPod,
depending where I am.
The Blog Digger Media Feeds and The Feedster MP3 Feeds.
And there's a lot of stuff that comes through there.
There's some really wacky stuff too.
And then some music shows up once in a while.
Let's see what came in today.
Some Fleetwood Mac live stuff.
You know, the odd audio blog post,
just that which is just titled as a number.
Gosh, it's so sad.
You know, there's so many really interesting things
that just no way to trace the origin,
because people don't put any kind of ID.
metadata into their files and you're just like, I wish I could find where this came from.
See what was the, there's some new IT conversations stuff came in which I haven't heard yet.
A new memory lane with Halley suit, looking forward to that.
Also something good on ITconversations.com which was open source in healthcare.
It's about a 14, 15 minutes podcast.
Interesting industry and if you're in open source definitely check that show out.
Okay, let's switch over now to a good buddy of ours who's been sending stuff into the show
and has been helping out with settings. It's our pal, Dr. Dave from Las Vegas.
Dr. Dave, surely quite an audio professional.
And he checked in again, sent us another voicemail. Here's Dr. Dave.
Hello Adam, Dr. Dave from Las Vegas. I'd like to thank you for broadcasting my previous
numerous replies and they've all been positive. It seems as though you have the ability to
reach the outermost portions of the planet, both geographically and atmospherically.
Yeah, well, and that's just with my hair, Dr. Dave. Wait until my ego comes up.
An update on my email address. I've been attacked by spam people who are using my
old email address as a return address, thus yielding
emails a day most of them
So, uh, I have changed the email address.
Please take note, Dr. Dave-USA at cox.net.
Also, Dr. Dave-USA at gmail.com.
From Las Vegas, it's Dr. Dave Clear.
Now, I love that.
Dr. Dave, from Las Vegas, it's Dr. Dave Clear.
All right, Dave, thanks very much, man.
And I'm sure that you'll get all kinds of interesting email now.
Now that we've played this on the source code.
And check in once in a while, you know.
Let us know what you're doing, what you're working on.
And I like having all kinds of different voices on the show.
And I do want to send out props to Mark Cantor for a second.
I was going to mention that during the trade secret show that Dave and I cut this morning
because something has been popping into my head for a while now.
From a conversation I had many, many years ago when I was still living in the state
and we had our company think new ideas.
And I was hanging out with Mark, which is actually where I hooked up with Dave
Weiner.
And Mark and I, we fall in and out of love all the time.
I think a lot of people do that with Mark.
But he did say at one point, he said, Adam, what we need is we need someone to introduce
this stuff, this new stuff that we're doing that we're creating.
We need a VJ for the music videos of the internet.
And when it comes to podcasting, I think that I'm fitting into some role similar to that.
I'm liking it because people are sending me links to new shows and audio bits.
I think there's so much more that we can do.
And Mark said to me today, could someone put together a podcast of dinner music?
So just basically a playlist, put together a playlist of dinner music.
Now granted that's not exactly what we're doing with podcasting but wow, if you had a
mixed list, not just something that, well yeah, really a mixed list.
Make a beautiful mix.
It could also be one podcast channel that has different songs in it.
But it could be that or it could be...
So the other thing that I heard was I had like a financial news show, you know, an analyst
doing a...
be, maybe that's only a one minute or a two minute podcast, but wow, I'd love to have that
sitting in my queue, you know, in my playlist queue.
Now, how do I come up with all that?
It doesn't matter because right along with Dr. Dave, Dr. Dave, of course, you know, I
had this visual of Dr. Dave.
He's one of these guys with this, you know, the huge gonad voice and he does all the
voice overs for the movies.
Maybe you're like in a world where men are men and women are looking scared.
You know, he just sits at home in his studio and people dial up with an ISDN and
he cuts all these recordings and he may not even know what he's really doing
him for.
He's just doing it, you know, and it's a great way to make a living because
he's basically podcasting for money.
Something else we're going to talk about today, by the way.
And I received a nice response and email from Tony Khan
from WGBH in Boston.
Remember, he's the one that sent me the 1-800 called dad.
a sound clip from the morning stories and they're putting together a podcast feed. So
he sent me a mail he said,
which is great. And he also sent me another morning stories which relates to Dr. Dave and also
the how politics work in America. I want you to listen to Fumfer Klackett for Senator.
Bill, Bill, you all warmed up in there, Bill?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, what are we doing today, Larry?
It's a last minute commercial for the Fumfer Klackett for Senator. You got this right there.
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah, right here.
Okay, good. Let's do it. Hey, rollin' on Fumfer Klackett for Senate. Take one, make it, sing, baby.
Fumfer Klackett, you know where he stands.
Yeah, actually, I don't. But where does he stand, Larry?
Uh, what difference is it?
Well, there's a long list of issues here. Larry, am I supposed to sound
former or against him?
Uh, well, take one later.
Oh, okay.
Fumfer Klackett, you know where he stands on taxes, abortion, the economy, condoms in the school.
All right. Okay, now sound.
for them. Okay.
Fumferklacket. You know where he stands. On taxes. Abortion. The economy. Condoms in
school. Beautiful. Okay now for the finish just read his name. What? Just Fumferklacket?
Yeah. Fumferklacket. Oh what's gonna be on the screen?
Well, it's early in the morning. A bird, a duck, a bus, a bus. His wife and dog are
in the background. He's got a three-piece suit and a briefcase and he's taken out.
That's beautiful Larry. So say his name. Fumferklacket.
Uh, eat something Bill. Try saying his name like it's the answer to a question.
You mean like what rhymes with the grimble gracket Fumferklacket?
The only without the question. Try and...
Who's the guy with the dbdis? Fumferklacket.
Who got indicted for tax evasion last year? Fumferklacket.
Great. What for?
Who's probably not gonna pay his campaign bills? Fumferklacket.
You...
Oh, uh, say, listen Larry?
Yeah.
He is gonna pay, isn't he?
Oh.
Fumferklagget.
Sure.
Don't see me in the election.
You later!
Larry?
Larry!
Fumferklagget.
Fumferklagget for Senator.
So, uh, some stuff to think about there, huh?
Isn't it interesting how the message changes with the tone of voice and with the music,
thanks to WGBH, soon to have their own podcasting feed of these morning stories up, I'm sure.
And I can't wait because I love them.
This is great on my walk during the day.
I don't really have a commute these days.
Once a week I go up to Amsterdam, going up tomorrow, by the way.
So I get to catch up on stuff.
But I love having that stuck in my playlist.
Okay, let's see.
Right.
Here's something that I heard Dave cut a coffee note about an interview that he did with...
with Yahoo or about Yahoo, about Yahoo's new RSS service.
And he says in the beginning of this blog post, and I have it queued up to something, honestly,
I can't quite remember what I have it queued up to.
And we'll find out in a second.
But in the beginning of this blog post, or even on his web blog,
linking to the podcast, Dave said, you know,
I just did an interview with Yahoo, and I thought, you know,
I really want to get my thoughts out there about what I was saying.
And I encourage you to listen to it because there's some important stuff
as it pertains even to podcasting.
You know, they're going to come trying to leech off of this stuff as well.
And he said, you know, I want to get my thoughts out there.
And what he really should have done is he should have recorded the interview
while the interviewer was interviewing.
I want to talk about that for a second.
But first let's just see what I had queued up here from Dave Weiner's
coffee notes for the 27.
This icon on your site.
Do they know who I am? I mean...
Why would I want to do that?
I mean, why would I want to tell my readers that...
They should favor this one aggregator over all the other aggregators.
Why would I do that before I would put an icon on my site that sent them to Net Newswire
or to even to, I would rather send them to Ampheddesk or, you know, or, you know, or
Feedster or.
So, I'm not quite sure why I queued that up.
That doesn't really make sense in the whole story, but that's kind of, that did
give you an impression of what, you know, the tone of voice that Dave was using and he recorded that at night and listen to that because you'll like it and what he's talking about and it's good to understand what Yahoo was doing and actually how opportunistic they're being right now and the stuff that we've been building.
But I wanted to touch back on what Dave said at the beginning of his podcast.
He says, you know, I should have recorded that interview and I think I've said this before.
I don't know if I wrote it on my web blog or if it wasn't in a source code.
I mean, this stuff is like, you know, life and source code and trade secrets, all kinds of runs.
It runs together.
I don't know what who else.
to what anymore. But I've done this successfully and I encourage anybody who's listening to
this show who is interviewed by the media and most likely that will happen by a telephone.
And I know that there are many of you who have been interviewed or are being interviewed
and I know how disappointed you probably have been certainly after the first interview
that you do, what really shows up in print. And I get interviewed all the time, me and
my wife and I are well known in the Netherlands, very well known.
So for some reason we're medium magnets here, go figure. But I've learned that if you say
to a journalist who wants to interview you, usually for print publication, because these
are quote the most serious, right, that if you say, okay, you know, that's fine, but
I also want to record the interview and I want to reserve the right to put that
raw data out there on the internet. And they can't really object because nine times
out of 10, the interviewer will be recording the conversation.
conversation, even when they do a phone interview, they'll record the conversation.
So if they have the right to do that, so should you.
And you know what, they're so bold over by the question that they're like, well, okay.
They say, but I want to have the right to put that source code on the internet.
And no one has rejected me so far, and I also have never put the source code of the
interview on the internet because I haven't, there was no need to.
But boy, do they really drill down on their facts and do their checking.
And right now, if you don't have a recording device, get to Skype.
You call the interview, you call him or her.
Record it with wiretap or whatever and just keep it there.
Just keep it safe.
If you don't like the interview.
This guy's full of shit.
And this is exactly what I said.
This was his question.
This is the context.
And you can check out the source code right here.
So that's something that can work very successfully.
And I suggest you give it a try.
And in fact, maybe someone will set up
a podcast feed of interviews that way.
Who knows?
Who knows what will happen?
If I were a journalist and I was getting paid for it,
I think I would want to have my source codes made available
so that people could fact check me.
Geez, what a great idea.
You write something in a magazine.
We can't fact check you with links or anything.
But if you've interviewed somebody,
put up the sound file of the interview that you did
so we can make our own decisions.
I guarantee you, I'm going to certainly
that source code to go to that source file.
Okay, we have, okay, all right,
let's talk about money for a second.
Because I heard, I remember we talked yesterday
about Dave Slusher who was wondering
should he take ads for his weblog.
And I see where all this is going is,
it's totally like weblogs.
There's really no difference.
We're using the same protocols to distribute it
and to aggregate it.
And so that's all webloggy.
And it's total freedom of speech.
You can do whatever you want.
Do it whenever you want.
It's a little different to create the content
than just using a web browser or a text editor
or a blogging client, just writing words
and sticking in the occasional image source
or something to a link.
You have to figure out how to record something.
You have to wanna record it.
So it's not for everyone.
Just like weblogging is not for everyone.
But there is a difference in the way
you experience a podcast versus a weblog.
For a weblog, first of all you have to...
to be in front of a computer. And I know you can be on a pocket PC and whatever, but you're
making a concerted effort to read something. When you're reading something, you pretty much
have to focus on that, which is why banner ads are so irritating. And I think that your
mind wraps around that. I don't see banners anymore. I just don't see them. My mind
a banner dimension size blob. I'm not just not going to look at that. That's why I think
the other day when Dave and I were looking for the obvious login to that registration
site for the Free World Dialup, the login button was a big oblong purple blob. It looked
like a banner. I think Dave's mind parsed that out. Mine does.
We've done that experiment recently. I think it's been going around the net a couple
times where it's a total dyslexic paragraph, but the first and the last letter are
in the correct spot as the correct letter and you can read it anyway even though
it's all garbled. That's because of pattern recognition. So you know that was
so far with the business model for web pages and web blogs and click-throughs
and all that. You have to sit in front of the computer. You have to make that effort.
Maybe you're at work so it's on someone else's time but still it's
You're relaxing.
You're in the obvious place where you can do only one of three things.
You're in the car.
You can do nothing.
You can listen to the radio or you can talk on the telephone.
Or of course you could talk to someone else who's with you in the car.
You usually turn to radio may be interrupted by the occasional
And that's the space, oops, use the space word, but it is literally the space that we're
coming into.
And your commute may be different.
It may be with a different type of vehicle.
You may not commute.
You may just take a daily walk.
Certainly there's a point in your day where you normally listen to radio, you're going
to flip on your podcast and you're going to get the stuff that you want and it's
going to be in the order that you want.
And it doesn't take a concerted effort.
In fact, you're in a very relaxed mode.
My belief is that traditional commercials will happen.
I think that right now I have about 1500 subscribers to the daily source code.
That's not a big number.
And if I went to Johnson and Johnson and said, hey, I'm going to sell your floor wax, these
1500 people, they're going to say, very interesting, Adam, hey, by the way, can I have your autograph?
My mom used to love watching on MTV.
So that's not going to fly.
Let me just take a very simple example here.
If I went to a conference.
organizer and I said, you know, you're making a conference and you charge people six, not
that I'm supporting conferences, etc., but just as an example.
I like the BloggerCon model myself.
But you're going to charge people three or $400 a pop to get into this conference and
you know, I think you should advertise because I have 1500 people of which many are in
the tech industry.
Many will be in the neighborhood of your conference.
Many will be interested in your conference and we know that they have
money because they have an iPod or something like it and a computer and
some type of broadband connection or access to one.
This is a desirable demographic and I want you to pay me, I don't know, $5 a week
or $500 a week.
Let's say it's $500 a week and I can convince two people or three people
a day to go to this conference because of this paid advertisement.
That's worth it.
They just made money.
So it's the niche narrow casting.
Now, of course, everyone's...
Croning saying, oh commercial commercial
Advertisement, we'll just skip past it. Yeah, if it's fucking boring you will this is something that Dave has been saying for a long time
Excuse me
Dave has been saying for a long time, make the commercials.
Interesting.
Make it more interesting.
We'll listen to them.
We'll buy products.
Of course we will.
Just make it more interesting.
We're so used to this, you know, the way you have to spit stuff on the screen and
big letters and yell, you know.
That's the old way of doing things and it's just not that valuable anymore.
It's decreasing in value, I believe, unless you're in a commoditized product.
The scrappy thing is that we're using this commoditized way of selling things to elect
a president, but that's a different conversation and discussion altogether.
So how do you make these commercials better?
More interesting.
I'm not sure.
I think what's very important is you have to know that you're being advertised to or
being marketed to.
And I always liked the way Howard Stern used to do the Snapple commercials.
He made it interesting by bringing in naked women and doing stupid games.
Whether you like that or not, that was a part of his show and his audience like that.
And so then he'd say, I think Snapple's the best drink in the world.
And he probably did.
He might not have, but then he probably would have said, it's not the best drink,
but look, we got great chicks so buy this.
And then he basically made a deal with the listeners all the time.
He would say, go and buy.
buy our sponsors' products, please, keep the show on the air.
So he's very honest about it, and that honesty I think will carry over and will work in this way.
So as an example, how it could work, I don't think this is particularly a new and interesting commercial,
but it's funny. It's funny because I know that Doug Kay, who sent it to me, who said,
the devil made me do it. I know that he meant it in jest. The echo chamber you're about to hear,
it's funny. Are we advertising a speedway or a conference here? There's an actual advertiser
in this that I'm about to play for you. I'm not getting paid for this, but it could happen.
Doug, who, in association with Lachanome.com, presents NomeDex 4.
This year will be Steve Wozniak, Woz, Robert Scoble, Chris Tabono, Jim Loderback, Dan
and Steve Gilmore will be streaming the audio all
Gilmore gang and for those who can't be there or listen to the live broadcast IT
conversations will podcast all of the sessions beginning next week so have your
iPods
Head for www.itconversations.com and look for links to NomeDex4. And thanks for listening.
The IT Conversations coverage of NomeDex4 is sponsored by Yahoo!
A limelight, networks, magnitude, music, and decision cast.
Be there, be there, be there, Sunday, Sunday, Sunday. That's great.
You know, and that was a commercial. It didn't suck. You didn't skip past it.
I know you didn't. You wanted to hear it. It'll be only interesting one time.
You're not going to listen to the next commercial sounds just like that,
but you were marketed to. You heard that Yahoo! was sponsoring the Geek Fest.
And the great thing about this, if you didn't hear it,
rewind and you got it. So,
watch out. I think there's something here. And again, and I know that people picked up on it.
NAB, they're going to show up pretty soon. They're going to have some stuff to say. I know it.
Okay, let's play something from the blog digger media feed. This is just so weird.
I don't know what it is or where it came from, but, you know, and I think if I was listening to it,
I might even skip over it. So, I'll tell you how long it is.
is in case you want to. Three minutes and thirty seconds. It came in as only called Track 17,
which is of course totally useless so I don't know where it came from. It sounds like part of
it might be from a movie, maybe it is a movie. I've titled it, you know, Just Not Enough Cowbell.
And it sounds like Christopher Walken's in some of it. But listen to it and you know,
it's just something different, something you won't hear anywhere else but on the source code.
Don't fear the reap, take one, roll. Alright, one, two, three, four.
Bruce, could you come in here for a second please?
Guys, what's the deal?
Are you sure that was sounding okay?
I'll be honest, fellas, it was sounding great, but...
I could have used a little more cowbell.
Oh, it just hit me. This is Saturday Night Live. That's what it's for.
I got to have more Cabra!
I got to have more...
I could've used a little more cowbell.
You're gonna want that cowbell!
Coward!
Guess what?
I got a fever!
And the only prescription is more cowards!
I gotta have more cowards!
The last time I checked we have a whole lot of songs that feature the Kalvass.
I guess I'm locked out.
Yes, what?
I can't believe it!
And the only question is what's happening?
So I guess that was a Saturday Night Live skit about the importance of cowbell and rock and roll.
And it just hit me while I was listening to that and I didn't have the headphones on before.
And now I'm like, oh yeah, okay, it sounds like Saturday Night Live.
So interesting how I haven't seen the skit but I can only imagine how fucked up Christopher Walken would look doing that.
He's probably some asshole record producer or some role that he would just fit perfectly so good at that.
See, while that was playing I was thinking of something else which I can't come up with right now.
Okay, then I'm going to play two more bits for you.
This first one is from a new podcast called Northwestern Noise.
And Northwestern Noise...
has, well, it's self-explanatory, but it's brand new and if you live in the northwestern region,
which I've learned is Seattle and Oregon, then this might be of interest for you because
there's some good local news for the northwestern region.
If anybody out there isn't familiar with the Northwest, I'm sorry, I plead ignorance.
Miacopa, the Northwest, is in the United States of America, encompassing the states of Oregon
and Washington.
I primarily have the called Oregon home.
My these past 23 years, I had a quick stint in Miami.
I have some interesting stories to tell you from Miami to bring up.
And I also have a musician, an artist that I won't play.
Hold on a second, where's the news part? I thought I had to cut out.
That's not what I wanted you to hear. Hold on.
Who hasn't?
I played some short excerpts.
I'll cut out.
Talk real quick about if you have a blog, this is so horrible.
This is made by Hugo.
He can do anything.
And they do Beaverton.
Any programs these pot well I feel I feel shitty now because wait maybe it's
Maybe it's after this
No, we have that bit. What happened to his northwest news yet to be born. Okay. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go
Here we go still in womb
Let me just rewind a little bit more because this is here's going into some news specific
I got messed up. Hey, I'm doing this without a producer. I'm not used to that.
You've never been there and you've never visited.
Okay, he's going to talk about him out, same hell.
Okay, here we go with Northwestern noise and the news.
1364 feet. That's amazing. Wiped out everything. All life for, I don't know, a large radius.
And if you've never been there and you've never visited Mount St. Helens, it's in Washington.
I forgot to mention that, sorry. If you haven't visited it, you should, but stay away right now because of these minor eruptions.
But at the time, which is interesting, was I wasn't even born yet. I was still in womb, yet to be born.
But I was, so I didn't get to see massive explosion and I guess I was unfortunate enough to miss the ash that covered the region like snow.
Numerous people died because of the event.
So it was very cataclysmic.
So it's still six in the mind of everybody here in the Northwest.
We all remember it if we were alive.
And so enough with the Mount St. Helens.
Let's hope it doesn't explode.
Okay.
Well, that's a good thought for the day.
Let's definitely hope it doesn't explode.
But, uh, so I missed it up there on the queue, but he really went into the whole
story about Mount St. Helens and give some background on it.
And I wouldn't have known this, you know, and so that apparently there's
been some minor earthquakes that have been registered and they're a little
bit worried about a repeat of what happened 25 years ago, which I do remember
because I was, I was 15.
So I do remember I was doing a lot of other things when I was 15, but was it
cataclysmic?
I can't really remember.
I can't really remember if it was cataclysmic or how bad it was.
It just, it's, it's even too far back for me.
I'm sure some, you know, if someone witnessed that and remembers that, you
know, record that, record that in a, in an mp3 file and point it to me or email it to
me, don't email it, mac.com still isn't working.
but you know I'll find it somehow I'll aggregate it I hope and I wanted to leave
you with one last bid here for today what are we we're 40 minutes into it
digging this I still haven't taken my walk around and let's take a couple of
podcasts this is the new tech aura show tech aura.com and with little shout out
to me and played a song for me some good hillbilly shit-kicking music but
I'm gonna let him set it up first Dave and Adam since we were talking about
also the fact that I've been working this you know solidify this system for
himself yeah my head put out another trade secrets put out another source quote
over the weekend and just it's just a kind of a funny little note Adam I have
one question for you how in the live in hell can you smoke as many bowls as
you do during a show especially for as long as you're up every day I mean I
would be going comatose maybe that's what's happening in the middle that you
go comatose. Oh dude dude dude I am comatose. Didn't you hear me cue up that last
bid? I am comatose.
those hours but it's so funny if you listen really really close when Dave
like in a trade secret when Dave is going off on his little diatrous sorry
Dave you you do like to talk when he gets going and Adam's sitting there
listening and you can hear the you know the lighter going off in the background
I just think that's absolutely hilarious but so on my first music segue I've
got a little dedication actually this is this is a great band love them to death
and I think this one is going out to Adam Curry this this one's for you dude
because you just make me laugh
Hellcat's doing I like whiskey. Actually that was a demo song so the quality was a demo tape so the quality of that wasn't that great
But awesome dude. Thank you very much for that and isn't it beautiful the way, you know, you can make a recording of
An mp3 and you just crank up the volume and it comes into my mp3 player and it's the same quality
Fantastic, even though that was a demo clearly. It was awesome. Thank you. I appreciate that what a beautiful gift to receive
And I just wanted to mention a couple things briefly about the iPod or developers list
We still got some great momentum going with developers and users all over the place
There are a couple of off-list conversations, which is all good and I threw a question out there. I said look
Where are we at with Windows and I got an answer back and probably more but as I've mentioned my email is just not working
Apparently so I don't know if more has come back but there are two Windows clients that really seem to have the installation and
The
I'm going to start making some decisions on what we're going to promote here because I
want to put on the homepage for iPodder.org.
I basically want to have download and I want to have Mac which will more than likely be
iPod or X.
Underneath that I want to put Windows with iTunes, Windows with media player and I want
to have one for each and then for other systems Linux, Pocket PC I think we have
and then I'll have links to other clients because I think there's a market here you
know and I don't want anyone to be disappointed.
I know a lot of people have given up the development of their scripts and saying
I know so I've put up my last changes I'm switching to this.
But I know that there's one or two projects out there that probably haven't gotten the attention they deserve just because I'm confused at this point about how much is going on and how many different projects there are.
And please just, you know, keep hammering me if I haven't put a link to your, your download page or whatever.
And I've put a couple more up today.
But there's a market here. There's a definite, definite market for developing iPod or functionality because it's, you know, you're talking about the organization and how stuff runs.
And when it runs and file management, and you're going to have users that in the exact same way as we did this together, they're going to want to talk with you and have you create something better.
And they're going to pay for it. They will. You know, it does work.
I pay for software all the time, not the only one. Clearly.
There are companies and small, you know, just developers by themselves who take PayPal payments for software they're making.
And there is a, there's totally a market for that. And I'll support, you know, anything. Just let me know what you do.
doing and I'll point to it and let's make something out of this industry.
Same goes for, and no one has shown up for this yet except for the Audio Hijack Pro guys,
for how we're doing this.
I'm using five different applications.
I think there's an opportunity there and it's going to be big.
This is really going to be big.
So looking forward to getting that information out there so we can get more of our Windows
proud and I'm going to leave it at that for today with the source codes for Tuesday, September
28th.
As always if you want to respond drop me an email, hopefully it will get here eventually
at adamantcurry.com or you can check out my weblog we've become a there.
The URL is live.curry.com.
All the archives and the latest shows can be found at dailysourcecode.com
podcast enabled for the iPodder. It's dailysourcecode.com
slash rss.xml. Hey, I'll talk to you tomorrow, everybody. Take care. Bye.