Hi everybody. Welcome to a very short daily source code for Thursday, December 2, 2004. I'm
a little bit pissed off. We did all day for my DSL line to be switched on, made all kinds
of other decisions and choices which did not involve going to Starbucks, thinking I have
plenty of time to do all my prepping and get all my stuff ready and have everything all
set to go for a source code. So I didn't work out and so I just decided to be almost
not online today and went analog, went out and bought some newspapers and I got the
Guardian, which I've known and I read online, I've been subscribed to their RSS feeds
for a long time. The Guardian.co.uk and picked up the paper version today and in the
G2 section, it's like a page and a half spread with a great graphic titled personal
soundtracks. Audio programming has become cheap and easy to make and has led to the rapid
spread of the podcasting phenomenon, then hammerously reports. There is an online version
and tomorrow I'll link to that. But I think it's very cool and it's just awesome to be cited
as, here it comes, Adam Curry, a London-based weblogger. Okay, almost got it right. So instead
of doing a regular source code, I want to read this one column to you from another part
of the Guardian. Actually it's a comment and analysis. So let me see, yeah, Felicity
Lauren, she's the Guardian Consumer Affairs correspondent. I did this column just really struck
me. I don't know if there is even an online version of it or not, but I enjoyed reading
this and it gave me a lot to think about and maybe it will do the same for you. So on
today's source code, I yield the floor for the distinguished gentleman, Felicity Lawrence.
This food racket just can't go on. A full-scale consumer rebellion is needed to change the
way we eat. That comes at point in most discussions about how to help people eat better
when everybody gets stuck on cheese. If you would have traffic lights on food, read for
bad, dream for good, orange for in between, what on earth would you do with cheese? This is
the point at which the absurdity of the food debate overwhelms me. It's not that I'm against
traffic lights. Actually, I think they might help a bit. It's just that when the car's
been hijacked and you're herdling in the wrong direction, I'm not sure they are up to
the job on on their own. Our food is being produced in a way that has devastating consequences
for the environment, for social justice, and for our individual health. In less than a
generation, it has been industrialized and globalized. Processed food is routinely adulterated
with artery clogging fats, a besegenic sugars and constipating starches, which are then disguised
by chemical colorings and flavorings without which they would be unpalatable. We have come
to depend on this junk food, and it is making us sick. On nutritionally depleted diet
is now kneeling on par with tobacco as the cause of ill health and premature death. Manufacturers
use these raw materials instead of good quality fresh food, because enormous subsidies
mostly paid by Western taxpayers have made them cheap. About 70% of the value of the US
soy of being comes from the US government, no wonder soy of derivatives are found in
two-thirds of all processed foods. Subsidized US corn is turned into ubiquitous corn
sweeteners and modified starches for the same reason. The money made from food is shifted
from those at the bottom of the chain, the farmers and producers. To those at the top, the
tiny number of big transnational food processors, manufacturers and retailers who control
our food as never before. Protectionist subsidies have done little to save farmers who are going
out of business everywhere. The value of agricultural commodities on which so much of the
developing world depends for its livelihood has slumped. As other barriers to trade have
been removed, inequalities in wealth have grown. Half the world now stars for lack of food
while the other half suffers from diseases of excess. The money made from these commodities
is concentrated in the hands of the cartels that control trade in them. Just five giant
coffee manufacturers control over half the world's coffee beans. Ten years ago coffee producing
countries kept 30% of the retail value of the coffee we buy. Today they keep just 10%.
When we buy a jar of instant coffee, we pay 7,000% more than the farmer got for it.
These concentrations of power are repeated across the food chain. Some 45% of grain trade is
controlled by one US company, Cargill. The power of transnational manufacturers is mirrored by
the emergence of dominant food rate retailers. In the near future, just four of five retailers
will have one global domination with a handful of others dominating regionally. Three quarters of
grocery sales in the United Kingdom are in the hands of four supermarket groups. They have a
stranglehold on how our food is made and distributed. They've created a system that is in its use
of new information technology and logistics, both miraculous and impossibly destructive.
Thanks to the barcode, food is flown around the world to meet the supermarkets requirements for
just in time ordering. Their demand for cosmetic perfection and a perpetual global summer
can be met by producers only if they use agrochemicals intensively and allow for a
big fucking word, degree of waste. A third of canyon green beans are thrown away because they are the
wrong size or shape. This new business model has made the supermarkets highly profitable,
but it depends on the extraving it use of that most politically charged and polluting of substances
crude oil for the food miles, for the pesticides, for the packaging that makes up 40% of our domestic
waste. It depends on an endless supply of cheap outsourced labor that can be turned on and off like
a tap. Hundreds of thousands of migrant workers now live in Britain in conditions that would make
Dickens blush. The way we eat is not just ecologically unsustainable, but also morally
and even biologically unsustainable. Making it better requires radical structural change.
It needs tighter competition policies, it needs reform of subsidies and trade rules,
it needs regulation of business none of which government is inclined to do. So making our food
better will also require a massive consumer rebellion. In my experience when people are well-informed
about how this globalized food is made, they no longer want to eat it, but they have no problem
with well-made cheese. And I'm going to leave it at that for the source code for today.
Tomorrow I surely do hope we have broadband. Bye.