The game is over.
Well, this is my day. September 6th, 2004.
comes to you either via download or maybe subscription through RSS and the iPodder.
I'm not on curry and it is...
we should think about breaking format right off the bat here for a second.
First of all, it's my sister-in-law, Yvonne's birthday today, so I want to play a song
for her.
And everybody could do, use a little bit of energy on a Monday morning.
And a long time ago, a couple of guys called the Easy Beats put a song together that really
sums it up and really...
if you need that boost on them.
I'm gonna grab this, it's gonna be mad, I'm gonna think it, come and choose it.
I'm gonna have to go to sleep in the city
Don't stop, don't stop.
I'm not a fan of the game.
I don't have a father who loves me
And actually, I realized that I did a very KC KC mask announcement a couple of guys
a bit long time ago, called the easy bleeds deliverable.
Anyway, sorry about that.
Oh, memo to self.
I have to find the KC KC long distance dedication, dead puppy snippet.
That's a classic.
And for those of you who know who KC KC is, I guess he's still on the air with his, what
am I doing?
He's not doing the top of the top 40 anymore.
Well, anyway, countdown radio show.
So I did a pretty good weekend.
Saturday was really nice because I went to the air show at Laylee's South here in the Netherlands.
And I was an invited guest, which meant I got to fly in.
You had a PPR number, which means you have a previous prior request or you have a permission
to land.
It was cool, you know, because they had me land and then turn in right into the main stage,
which is in front of the...
thousand people there and then flew air your hover taxi to off to us.
cool to do that. That's the moment when you like, I don't want to fuck this up. You know, let's look
good. Well, we're having a taxi. But it was really nice. It was very well organized. They had,
yeah, they really did a professional job. They were classic old planes to brand new VLAs.
These very light aircraft, which really started out as experimental crafts and are now a lot of them
are certified and very inexpensive to own and operate, but very luxurious and actually quite fast
as well. And while I was, all they said, jet fighters and aerobatics. And I actually posted a picture
of the blue eagles from the Royal Air Force in the United Kingdom who did a helicopter,
didn't demonstration with the four gazelles and one links, which was capable of doing looped
elopes, pretty intense. And then I was walking amongst the crowd at a certain point, I had to get a new
battery out of the helicopter for my camera. I heard someone call my name and I heard it was an American
accent. So I turned around and this is guy, which is himself as John.
A developer, now who had quit his job just recently so I congratulated on that.
I think he quit his job in the States and moved over here too.
Lighten, which is a big university town. And he said that he had heard about the air show on
the source code the previous day. And he decided to come to the show. He didn't even know there was
an air show on. So we chatted for a little bit and it was just really cool to see what the reaches
of a show like this. And from there, we got back home safe, which means we had a really good day.
And I ran to my email hoping that someone had picked up on Dave Winer's birthday hint and made
a template for dailysourcecode.com. No such luck, no designs, not an inkling. And then of course,
it got pretty depressing as I don't know what the coverage was in the States, but here in another
of the Russian school drama was just so intense and they just kept on going the images just kept
coming back. There was so much video footage of it all and especially as a parent it hurts so
much to think about what those kids went through and what the parents are going through and just
what everyone's going through and what was the...
It's just, and you know, what are we coming to?
You know, it's, you know, part of this was an accidental detonation at whatever bombs
they had with them.
But I understood there was also one woman who would detonate it herself.
I'm thinking, man, you know, what despair are people in this can't just be religion.
I don't believe that.
I think that there's a lot, you know, people are just driven to the edge.
And if your kids are killed and you're in Chechnya and your husband's been carted off and
you've never seen them again, maybe out of despair, you, all you can think of is, look,
I'm going to give you a taste of your own medicine.
It's just, it's crazy, you know, people are popping off all over the globe.
This is not exclusive to, to this conflict or to the Middle East, you know, to Palestine
or, or Iraq or, or anywhere for that matter, you know, Bali.
It's happening everywhere.
Suicide bombers.
This is, people are really going to desperate needs, desperate measures.
So anyway, I...
can't change that yet.
Foling could reprogram bits of the world that would feel so good.
So this is the Daily Source Code.
It's where users and developers party together and we're very proud of it.
Something we've been talking about a lot on the show is audio books.
See I made a note to myself to look at this email from a hermit in Montreal.
Who sent this to me.
He's just discovered the Daily Source Code the other day.
I think it's fascinating.
He says that he spends way too much money on audible.com as it is, but really loves the reviews.
He says they also have a lot of good free content you can download.
They actually are a really good source for NPR periodicals.
And indeed if you're a member of audible you can download a lot of that stuff for free.
He recommends the talisman by Stephen King.
There's a, he says the first version was the best with Frank Mueller as the narrator.
He also says no crash was cool.
This month we bought the dark tower part six by Stephen King.
The seventh and final book to release.
on the Stephen King's birthday, which is the 21st of September. And he also got Princess
of Ireland also recommended by Audible users. So there you go, if only I could get an
RSS feed of someone's recommendations. You know, wouldn't that be great and a little snippet
as an enclosure so I could just zap through on my iPod in the morning and see if I like
the speaker, see if the story sounds interesting, maybe listen to a little bit of a review. It
could be actually, I was thinking about that the other day, one way we could do this, developers
listen up. So let's say I'm listening to different audio books on my iPod. And I know the iPod
can do this, I have no idea how it works with other devices, I'm sure there's...
So if I'm listening to an audio book, I can give that a rating, one to five stars.
You can do that on your iPod.
It's a selection you can just thumb through and get to.
So what if I set it up?
So when I re-dock my iPod, it went in, a little program went in and said, let's take anything
that has four stars or above and create an RSS file from that and upstream it and then put
links into the pages where they can be downloaded and reviews, etc.
It would be a way to kind of do your review on the fly without too much effort.
I think it's technically possible and well, in the next few weeks to come, I'll probably
give it a whirl and see if I can get it done.
Dave Winer posted that he had taken my recommendations and purchased Snowcrash and John Stewart's book
which I'm still listening to.
I love it so much.
I only really turn it on when I know that I'm not going to be disturbed by any one or anything.
But what was interesting is I remember I told you I paid $7.95 for John Stuart's book and David
apparently got it for $4.95. So maybe Audible is really just a little bit more expensive than the rest.
I like it a lot though. It seems to work fine for me in every little online library so you can
delete files if you want to go back and download it again you can. And of course,
it's a lot of snow crash waiting in the wings to be red but haven't started that one.
That's something probably when I really take a full day off.
And I had a big oh wow experience over the weekend. The Skype client for Mac OS 10 was released.
I've heard a lot about Skype. I actually know Nicholas and Janice, who created Skype, who created
a Kaza because I met them several years ago when we were working on the Jambi stuff.
they were working on creating super nodes.
And then those guys really knew what they were talking about.
And they were really smart about this stuff.
They've created a basically a voice over IP,
well, there's a buzzword, voice over IP application program
that you can use to make telephone calls with.
And the way they do it,
they use some of the peer-to-peer concepts behind Kazaar
presumably to make it all work.
And that doesn't interest me too much because
this is available in many different forms.
And you've probably heard about the voice over IP,
buzz for maybe a couple of years now.
And I was like, yeah, sure, I can use iChat.
There's different programs that will allow me to do that.
There's some drawbacks to it.
I don't like being that people can see I'm online, so they say, he's online, so thus I can go
column up or I chat him or whatever. So not to keen on that. But it was interesting.
And this is the part that I didn't get until I actually tried it, is that you can use Skype,
and that's spelled SKYPE. By the way, so it's Skype.com, I believe it's their URL.
You can actually use this, you type in a phone number, and it will call that telephone,
so you can have a conversation from your computer over the internet to a regular phone line.
And that's when, you know, and only did I actually sit there, I was sitting with my laptop,
and I just had, I didn't have headphones or a microphone on, just using the internet.
called our Belgian number, the house line,
and Patricia picked up.
She was sitting there right next to me
and she didn't know that I was calling
and then I'd start talking to her.
And it was so, wow, this is weird.
He's talking into his laptop
and I'm talking to him on the telephone.
That was a real brain reset moment there for a second.
So I started to delve in and find out how this works.
And it turns out there's a lot of voice over IP service providers.
And what appears to be the main standard
that people are adhering to
something called SIP.
Sit, I'm not quite sure what it stands for,
but I'm sure it has to do with some standardization
of how you do voice over IP, so voice over the internet.
And what these companies do is they have local dial in numbers.
You've probably heard of J-Facts or some service
where you can basically rent or buy or rent a phone line.
And that'll go straight to a voicemail box
and so someone to you, so actually I have a number in New York.
You can call it my New York number.
And it's only a local phone.
phone call and then what it does is it takes the phone call and then it's already on the
internet. So sending the message to me is just using internet protocols and email and I have
a special web place I can go to as well to listen to my archive messages. They also do
it for fax's same thing. You can add another fax line or if I wanted to I could say, hey,
I want a local phone line in Los Angeles or I want one in Ireland. So I've used that and
that's been around for a while and that's actually works pretty well. This is the exact
same concept where you say, I want a phone line, I want a phone number in New York. So people
in New York can give me a call. Maybe I want to look like I have an office in New York
and I want one in LA and whatever. And then when people call that number at that point, it's
basically only a local call. That's why it doesn't cost very much. That's where your voice
over IP provider picks up the call and then goes out and finds your computer to say, hey,
ring ring, you've got a call and set up the call. So basically you have a phone number that
works.
like a phone can be called from any phone and you can call to any phone and you have the
same number that remains with you. And because the distance, if you're calling long distance,
is really on your local phone call, that's why they can give you incredibly cheap rates. So I could
actually call New York from my house in Belgium. It's still ours, but about to not be. And I can make
that call for, I spec'd it out. There's one service plan I could get it for 1.7 cents per minute.
Unheard of. Literally unheard of prices. Now of course, you're probably saying, yeah, but you know,
I don't want to take phone calls on my computer. And it also has a very hands-free feel to it,
which is just not nice. So a lot of these service providers are, and this is what it comes down to,
because this system, anyone can set up with your, I think they're called DID, your local dial-in number.
Any company can rent time, rent phone numbers, and set something like this up. Where they're going to
in the differentiation and the United Unique Selling Proposition, if you will, to give you a marketing
term, is in the services, so really expanded voicemail capabilities, conferencing capabilities,
anything you can think of that any service that you're getting now for your local phone company
and then some and just think of all the capabilities of being able to attach internet capabilities
to a phone call. There's a lot of richness in there. So you don't really want to be doing this on
your computer, so any service provider that's really serious about their business will also give you
what they call a SIP phone, so they'll give you a software version, which you can make calls with
from any computer in the world as long as it's connected to the internet and has some reasonable bandwidth
but even that isn't really necessary because voice is so low in data intensity.
One day to volume I should say perhaps, they give you a SIP phone which is just like a regular phone,
only you plug it into either you.
your router or your cable modem or your USB or they have all different kinds of versions
or if you can just, if it's always, I think they actually might even have a Wi-Fi version.
And it looks and feels and acts just like a real phone.
You pick it up and then it'll give you a dial tone.
It's not really giving you a dial tone.
It's giving you a fake dial tone but it sounds like a dial tone.
You dial your number and then from there it's just like the version on your PC and you're
making real calls.
And conversely when a call comes in, it'll ring.
Even better than that is a little version which is a box which sits between in between
your network so your cable modem when you're at ADSL or you know, and you're, I don't
know if they have a Wi-Fi version but presumably Wi-Fi as well.
And on the other end you plug in your existing phone and your or your existing phone system.
So then there's really no difference between picking up your phone and making calls and
receiving calls versus with a local phone company versus voice over IP.
That was like, that just blew me away because this changes the entire model of how phone companies make
money and essentially it just kills them. Home on, I'm going to take a sip here.
I've gotten into the habit of drinking Schwepp's Indian tonic during the source code.
a little bit of mother earth. So anyway, I can see this Skype thing really going places and I've
I'm determined this week to work with the the version on my computer and make my calls
that I need to make over this system and just see you know see see how the experience is.
There is seems like there's a little bit of a delay on Skype but you know I might try out different
versions of different companies. Skype by the way as far as I know does not give you an incoming
phone number that's unique but that can only be so far off. I mean it's everyone's going to be
offering the same just going to be how how how cool are your features going to be no call forwarding
and you name it there's there's going to be a lot of stuff going on. And of course you're saying well
you know is this you know I use a cell phone you know that's for me in fact that has always been my
only number is my GSM cell phone and that's what everybody reaches me on. Now granted traveling
between two countries I often wind up paying a lot of money a lot of roaming.
fees. Probably upwards of a dollar a minute when I call from Belgium to the Netherlands and I also have to pay when there's
Incoming on the roaming. So that's you know, I'm really bad
But around 2,000 euros a month, so about $23, $2200. That's a lot of money.
But I think that this, as it evolves, I think just as well basically, as Wi-Fi becomes
more free and more available. Let's look into the crystal ball for a second. Hold on a second.
Let's rub the crystal ball and let's talk about the future of Voice Over IP.
So, as Wi-Fi becomes more prevalent and available everywhere, and Dave Wein has been traveling through
the country. He's noticing that Wi-Fi is really becoming just a commodity, and then I have
to agree with him that it will be free. Wi-Fi will be just, which coffee shop you're going to go to,
which library you're going to go to, what restaurant you're going to go to, what lunchroom.
go to your choice at a certain point will come down to do they have Wi-Fi or not and they're not going to charge you for it. It's just going to be a part of the deal. There you go. There's Wi-Fi.
for being for being our guest. So if we have Wi-Fi really built out everywhere,
then I see no reason why you can't take your your handheld. So let's say it's a pocket PC or
or the cell phone manufacturers, I'm sure will do the same thing if they have Wi-Fi built in.
gadgets built into a regular phone. I mean, it can be done at your home. Then all you really need is a Wi-Fi connection.
And I think that, you know, beside the car, which, you know, maybe that's the hardest part.
And that's where you have to switch to a regular cell phone technology.
I think that, you know, your office buildings and everyone will have this capability.
And maybe you just will just like in a smaller commerce, you know, you see,
you may say, hey, we, I don't want to feel like doing business with you.
At least not at your office because you don't have Wi-Fi. My phone won't work.
But I think that as it continues to build with enough Wi-Fi, it'll be possible.
And the roaming between Wi-Fi day stations, I've found is not, you know, that groovy, certainly not if you're,
it's not going to work very well if you're made conversation. But hey, look, if it comes down to saving
a lot of money and sticking it to the man, I say it can be done. And then of course, as we get further
than that, if there's enough Wi-Fi, and I don't really understand how it works yet, but you know,
we can start to integrate meshed networks and we can have the...
Wi-Fi stations all connect to each other with different WDS I think is the protocols so they
can expand their network and I'll talk to each other and actually could become a new form of
internet backbone but oh no the crystal ball is getting cloudy. I'm clearly gone too far.
So that was my Skype experience very impressed by VoiceOver IP. Was listening to the latest IT
conversations the Gilmore gang which was from Friday the 3rd and I didn't get until last night.
I listened to a bit of it on Saturday I drove up to Abraida about a 20 minute drive, went up to
visit a couple of friends on the way back so I heard probably about half of it and listened
to the rest of it last night. As usual it's Steve Gilmore and Doc Surles and I think John Udell
and then there were some analysts who were all talking about Microsoft and Longhorn.
Now I'm going to touch on this for a second because this is
developers and users of party together on source code.
I didn't take a lot of effort, but I made a concerted effort to listen to what they were
talking about and try and understand.
Just to see if I can boil this down, apparently Microsoft has been promising a new version
of Windows.
This version of Windows is called Longhorn.
Let me just pause there for a second because this is a bad name.
I do not get any happy associations with Longhorn.
In fact, I get an association of one of those pink Cadillacs with the Longhorn on the front
coming to pick me up to take me to some horrible roadshow gig, which I will tell you about
one of these days.
So, to me, I'm eating like Longhorn.
That sounds like something from Texas.
That sounds like George Bush.
I get all kinds of weird associations.
So, Longhorn doesn't work for me.
I want something sexy like Tiger Panther.
But this seems to be just about as important for Microsoft as...
switch to OS X was for Apple. And there were a couple of things in Longhorn that people
were very excited about, but from what I understand one of the most important ones was
this Windows FS, the Windows filing system, which is, and I don't know much about filing
systems other than, you know, you've got a path to a file and somehow you're...
that when you're clicking around and dragging and dropping stuff.
But a sophisticated filing system, we much more would have a, I guess like a database
attached to it with XML so that you can address the file system in a more convenient slash
intelligent manner.
Something like that.
And this was, you know, they've delayed this.
Actually they were doing as they're releasing longhorn but not with the sophisticated filing
system in there.
And they're saying some other longhorn features which weren't supposed to come out until longhorn
comes out, which now they're saying is 2006 are going to be released before then.
So and, you know, some APIs stuff that I guess people were are supposed to be relatively happy
about.
And it was interesting.
If you're on Wall Street or you trade stocks and.
because there's some good points on what this is going to mean to Microsoft long-term,
Microsoft in terms of growth, in terms of value, in terms of cash flow.
And I find that interesting to listen to.
And to me, it seems like this is a humongous opportunity for a whole bunch of people to come in
and in fact, this is discussed on the show that open source may get some more legs on this,
and there's all kinds of reasons for that. But it was kind of fun listening to it and understanding,
really starting to understand what Microsoft's business is and how this is going to work for them
or not. And again, though, I must say that there were a lot of buzzwords being used,
you know, players, space, a play. I love that. And you use the word a play as in Google is a search play.
So what is source code to kind of play is that. It's probably a bad play.
But there was a lot of talk about developers and I do want to stop at that for-
second because when I hear people especially analysts talk about developers, you know,
and developers will do this, developers will do that. And I've had developers work for me personally.
And I didn't know anything about developers and point honestly, I not until the past few months
that I really understand why developers are the way they are. I mean, these are like speech writers.
You know how on the West Wing, that once in a while Rob Lowe's character or one of the other people,
they'll write a speech for the president and it'll be a real great,
a nice moment in the episode because there's some real patriotic feelings and what the country
stands for. It's just a really good speech. Well, that's what, you know, so then a speech writer is
in his vibe and he's pouring his heart out and putting his heart into his work. And that's the way
developers work best. If you're working on something that you really want to make and you want it to happen,
it's just writing, you know, it's not like you're tinkering with a screwdriver.
language and this language does something and it can emotionally move someone when you
write something, it can make a computer do something, but it's just language and it's writing
and I think good writing takes inspiration and you can't overlook that.
Someone has to be really into the project that they're doing otherwise.
It's just never going to be the same as they're something that they're really interested in.
So if you hire developers, try and get ones that are interested in what you're actually
doing.
At the end of the show and I was actually laying in the bathtub last night and my wife was
just walking into the bathroom and I started laughing my head off because at the very end
of the Gilmore gang, Steve Gilmore gave me this humongous plug about the source code and
it was extremely nice and I had really appreciated it.
And there you go.
That was nice.
I've learned you've get credit to take it and shut up.
Now let's talk about iPodder for a second.
iPodder has a home.
I created iPodder.org, which I did because
what to be.org because that's what open source
or open whatever seems to be registered under.
And this is totally meant as an open project.
I'm going to be real happy to maintain this website,
which is part weblog and there are two directories in there,
and one is for downloads.
And whenever if you have a new iPodder script that will work,
you can actually do a submission form under the directory.
And you can send me a URL to .2 and I'm gladly add that.
And also I've started a directory of feeds that have regular enclosures coming down the pipeline.
And again, if you have a suggestion for that, you can also click on the link.
And so I think now we've got it all official.
iPodder.org. And that's where you can point.
to point people to who want to use iPodder.
Have you have any comments about that?
Obviously, just send them to me adamantcurry.com
or comment on the weblog at live.curry.com.
And a while back, I'd also asked all of the source code listeners
where you listen to the source code.
And Steve Garfield made a video of how and where he listens
to source code and check this out.
What he's doing is he has a thing is the Iraq,
which is a little FM transmitter,
which you can plug into your into your Mac or any computer.
I think it just uses audio out.
And you can tune it to an empty frequency
and he's broadcasting that signal throughout his house.
And he showed how he was listening to source code
in his kitchen on a, it looked like a boom box up on the cabinet,
which he probably had to put up on the on the covers
because the antenna or the power was too low of his of his Iraq.
But it's true, this is, and it's wacky.
turned on that radio and hadn't told anyone where the source was coming from.
They would have said, oh wow, atoms on the radio.
And that's the kind of magic that I like, you know, the stuff that we're doing at iPod or where
it really seems like your iPod is doing all this stuff and aggregating everything where actually
it isn't it's your computer and we're just connecting all the bits. Which brings me to a thought
that Marcus Mouler, who I've been working with for a long time now, he keeps all my servers running
and developed stuff and he works with me on all kinds of fun-related projects. He lives in Pasadena,
which is great because then he can watch the servers while I'm sleeping in vice versa.
And by the way, and Marcus, I know you're listening, please put up a page and send me the
little so I can point to it of the radio user land tool that you made or scripts. I think there's
two scripts that are also 100% iPod or fodder. So send a URL to me because I want to add that to the
directory. But he's also working on a concept, which I think is quite interesting. He says,
you know, maybe we could even simply, if I get it right now, Marcus will have to set me straight if not.
What if we created a central resource that does the aggregation of feeds and creates
basically a list of just extracts the URLs, or you have a filter on it so you can say,
this is where Tivo is getting into the picture and that's why I love it Marcus, I'm totally
on to you.
So instead of having a relatively dumb aggregator that we call iPodder and just sits there and
pulls in these feeds, we could, for any different type of version, you'd have to put new logic
into the iPodder script.
We could create a central resource that you can actually address with perhaps an API
or whatever, a web interface as well.
We just say, hey, I want all links from Adam Curry and Dave Slusher and IT conversations
for the past three days and it'll just spit back a list of URLs to the content.
And that then could be used through a simplified version of iPodder.
to pull that into your iPod or your MP3 player device.
So I asked him to write that up as well.
Hold on a second, the dog is just going crazy.
Patricia's off to the...
Chrissy!
See, this is our 15 year old maltees
who was three years over life expectancy.
She is deaf and blind.
She's not dumb.
I'm curious, baby.
Come on, it's okay.
It's okay, baby.
You want to go upstairs?
See, whenever she senses that Patricia's not in the house,
then she kind of starts to freak out
and just starts to bark and bark and bark.
I take her upstairs and she can walk around there.
I'll give me exactly seven minutes
before she starts barking again.
Okay, let me get back.
Sorry about this little interlude here.
Okay.
Let me just swipe the e-book.
And let's see, listen to the recent Dave Slusher, Evil Genius Chronicles.
He says he's going to stop mentioning my name.
That's okay.
Dave, I think it's about time we all stop talking about each other and get down the business.
Although I do want to make one comment, that as a user, it's very hard for me to explain
to a developer when a piece of code is not doing what I expected it to do.
Now I've learned that the best bug report is to say, here's what I expected, and here's
what happened.
And I know that you didn't really appreciate the fact that I talked about your code on
the source code.
But really it's not your code, I think the problem is my code.
It's my Apple script.
But what I'd like, and I'm just going to do a review here.
Okay.
So here's what I expect to happen.
What I expect to happen is when the chron...
your code, get enclosure, a Pearl script. I wanted to bring everything in, put it into
appropriate playlist based upon the channel names in the feed. And it does all that.
I mean, that's exactly what I wanted to do. And that would be the end of it. I love
the caching that you've built in. I love the fact that you sport AACs. That's all fantastic.
What it does instead, and I'll talk about version 2.0, is, first of all, it brings iTunes to
the front every single time. And I know you put that in as a safety, but that's really
irritating because if it runs, if the cron job runs while I'm working, then it'll pop
it up for every new file it brings in. So I don't want it to do that. And it's creating duplicates.
Sometimes hundreds of duplicates, sometimes only one. And that's in the playlist on iTunes.
If we can fix that, it would be perfect. Everything would be just beautiful. And I love your script.
I'm not using...
using my own, I'm using yours, so I just really want to try and make it better.
So what are we at now, 35 minutes? Well, at least we've been reasonably productive.
Song of the day, I know we already had Friday on my mind, but I had something else lined
up, which I thought you'd appreciate. I always try to put a little something different on
the source code. This is by a guy called Richard Cheese, and you'll even hear his little promo
for Richard Cheese.com in the song. He's basically a Las Vegas performer who does contemporary
songs in a less contemporary way, or is that the other way around? Well, just for yourself
and check out Richard Cheese.
We'd like to do a song for you from a band from the 1970s. This is a pretty popular number,
one of the most requested songs of all time. It's about a gal who's trying to purchase something.
He's trying to purchase a means of getting from down here up to there.
We have a little mood lighting on this job. Thank you.
Let's see we swing this tonight, huh?
Hit it, baby.
I think you'll like this one.
There's a lady in shore, all that blitters is gold, and she's buying a stairway to heaven.
When she gets there she knows, those stars maybe close with the words she can't get what she came for.
Oh, Scooby-Doo-Doo-Doo-Doo, and she's buying a stairway to heaven.
When she gets there she knows, those stars...
The tree, the brood, the sun, the sea, all the thorns and all me down.
It makes me wonder if there's a puzzle in your head's roll.
It's just a sprinkling for the me, wait
Yes, there are two paths you can go by but in the long run
There's two times of changing road you're on
Reach your...
...stock up.
Hey there's that lady we all know She's standing white line once show
And if you listen very hard The tune will come to you at last
If you're watching a few
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh
And she's buying a stairway!
Thank you.
Richard Chees.
Yeah, Stairway to Heaven, I strongly suggest you check out RichardChees.com.
He does a lot of these entertaining to say the least.
And that's it for Source Code for today, September 6, 2004.
those adamant curry dot com and my web log we can do the comment is live dot curry dot com
and of course we have daily source code dot com we can check out all the archives of
the show and also subscribe to it if you're using iPodder as daily source code dot com slash
rss dot xml and that's it for today we'll be back tomorrow with another edition of the source
code take care everybody
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.