Okay, so this is the beginning of the daily source code for today, just a quick ramp up in the show.
I'm going back from the shopping center, which is about a good 40 minutes from my house.
Actually, went to two other stores and probably drove around about an hour before I decided that, you know, I probably should have gone to the shopping center to start off with.
One day, a lot of electronic stores seem to be closed on one day.
Like, geeks don't work on Monday or geeks don't eat shit on Monday?
Damn.
So, I was so frustrated over the weekend, with once again trying to group my audio properly so that I can do all the connections I want to do.
You know, do Skype calls and play np3s for a quick time or high tunes, and do whatever I want to do, basically.
Having this cold sweat always running down from the base of my neck down my spine about, you know, always wondering, is it recording, did it record properly?
And, Dave and I were doing a trade secrets yesterday, Sunday afternoon for me Sunday morning for him.
And it was, I guess I pretty much, well, Murphy's always with us, right?
And I tested a new set up for over three hours work beautifully. It was actually, it was Snaps Pro, which is a Macintosh application, by the makers of WireTap.
And WireTap, of course, is not performing very well, the 1.0 version. It turns out that WireTap 2.0 is actually built into the Snaps ProX application, whatever it is.
And that's a screen recorder. So, what that's supposed to do is record any movements that you make on your screen, and of course, it also records any audio.
And that's why they have the new version of WireTap built into it.
And I was really, really psyched. It was perfect. You know, I didn't need to record any of the screen stuff.
So, I basically just kind of disabled that. And you could happily record at a very low level apparently, because it seemed to be almost no processor load or very little processor load on recording audio.
And anything you play would just be recorded, then I would be recorded to a quick time, it would be audio only.
And then you just save it out and then save it as an AIFF and convert it to MP3 perfect.
Well, of course, the minute I started adding applications and adding Skype, even though I tested it for several hours with Skype, you got the old loops.
I'm going to freeze up your computer now and give you that, you know, mid mid mid mid mid mid mid mid mid, that's studying like a CD.
Skip things sound. And the only way to go out of it is to do a hard reset, at which point you pretty much lost your file.
Yeah, the data is still there and it's, it's findable, but it's not really usable unless you go into all kinds of, you know, I can't open or like applications to go and try and repair that.
And it sucked because I recorded half an hour with Dave when the first crash came and we just picked it up and continued from there.
And we did all kinds of cool stuff. Dave was able to come from Steve Gilmore and Vias Skype. We talked about, I mean, we didn't have a great time.
And I was just looking at my Mac and I became quieter and quieter and Dave said, you know, you don't sound like you're really into it today.
And you know, I am into it. I'm just so worried about these files and I'm worried that they're not getting recorded.
I wish, of course, was partially true. And so I decided that it's time to take action on the recording situation for my podcast and I went out and got a, was this a Samsung.
Yep, YEPP. And it's no bigger than a cigarette lighter.
It holds 256 megs of audio. So about four hours. It recorded at a reasonable quality. Well, it's a 128K. So good quality.
You could encode something from a line in. It has clearly it has a voice recorder, which I'm using right now. It has an FM tuner, which you can also record from.
And it has a USB. I think this is, it's a older model. I think it's a USB 1.1. So not a very fast USB connection, but you can basically mount it like an external hard drive even on the Mac.
And you can change a bit rate. It goes in steps, it could do 22, 32, 64, 90, 628K sample rates, which is well enough for podcasting.
Strangely enough, the microphone is recorded in way format, which probably sounds a bit shitty.
Listening to it on the, on the headphones, it sounds a bit shitty. Maybe I can enhance that as I play it back through.
It was, I opened it up on my Mac and get this ready for the podcast for today.
So, that's it. I've moved the recording function of the podcast off of the computer, so that I'm free to mess around with the computer, do whatever I want.
Applications can crash. No matter what happens, I'll still have my data safe on this external recording device, which is basically a hard drive.
It's no moving part, so in theory, let's not invite Murphy and again, but in theory, nothing can go wrong.
All right, ready to get this podcast cranking?
Well, good afternoon, what an introduction, eh?
Indeed, it did sound just kind of a little bit shitty. Hey, everybody, it's the source code from Monday, October 25, 2004, coming to you from Flanders, Belgium, from Curry Castle.
Welcome, friends, family and world leaders.
So, recorded that intro as I was on my way home in the car from the shopping mall.
And I don't know if you can tell now what we're couple hours forward in time, and I just came back from the dentist.
The left hand side of my face is numb, so I'm maybe slurring a little bit. I can't drink my tea without dribbling.
And I can't talk on the split either, I can't really get anything in, so I don't know how to do this show is going to be. It seems like we don't have all the bits in place, but we'll give it a shot.
It's your source code, where users and developers party together.
So for today, we've got some more cool bits to listen to from podcasts around the globe, also some RIA free music, which I think we just, we should just resort to calling it pod music.
Doesn't that make more sense, or maybe we should call it pod tunes, is that better or not way?
I got them all off of Garage Band.com, when they kick it off with just the fool from B hammer.
Learning everything I was told, but it doesn't seem a matter, how long I've been in school.
I'm still just a fool.
And I'm in a round world, who has a side to you.
And I stood on top of the mountain, felt the power coming down on me.
I took the walk with the wise man, and I learned the golden road.
But I'm still just a fool.
Hey, I'm just a fool.
And I'm in nothing else.
What comes in your look?
I can't help myself.
I'm just a fool.
And when I see you walking down,
I know why the cause is not made of.
So the whole wide world, watch me act as like a little third way.
With every other temptation, you know my mind already is the stubborn new.
But I'm still just a fool.
Hey, I'm just a fool.
And when I see you walking down,
I know why the cause is not made of.
So the whole wide world, who has a side to you.
And I stood on top of the mountain, felt the power coming down on me.
I took the walk with the wise man, and I learned the golden road.
So the whole wide world, watch me act as like a little third way.
With every other temptation, you know my mind already is the stubborn new.
But I'm still just a fool.
And when I see you walking down, I know why the cause is not made of.
So the whole wide world, watch me act as like a little third way.
With every other temptation, you know my mind already is the stubborn new.
And I stood on top of the mountain, felt the power coming down on me.
So the whole wide world, watch me act as like a little third way.
Watch this and you're walking by
What about me then?
Watch me be your fool
Oh
Big damn fool on your source code for October 25th it is Monday. It's 2004 and I got to tell you people friends listeners to the source code
This little MP3 recorder, which I'm now using to record and let me tell you a little bit about the setup
It is totally a a message of things yet to come because I hadn't really look past my iPod, you know
I was yeah, just kind of paying it. Hold on a second of my
Light
There we go. Hold on. I want to change the position of my mic on the way it sounds
I have a lot a lovely ear mic and if you have it stuck too far underneath your collar doesn't sound right
Okay, that's much better
So I totally think this is this is just a sign of things to come now this MP3
It's actually it falls into the category of a wearable music devices
I guess is what the fashion trend is and it's about the size of a lighter
It's really it's let me see I have a lighter right here
In fact, there's exactly the same length as my lighter. It does the same width as my lighter
And I just have a regular old big you know one of these click on Bix
It is higher. It's about two and a half times the height of a regular lighter
And it's known no moving parts. It's all solid state
There's 256 megs of ram in it and there's an FM tuner in it and there's a built-in microphone
So she heard in the intro you can record
With a memo recorder with 256 megs that gives you about 15 hours worth of recording
I'd say in a pinch, you know if I had to I would I would totally use it the way I did the intro today
But it's not a fantastic sound quality and you can't change those settings
But you can obviously load up songs
And they have some windows software which obviously didn't load being a Mac dude
But with the minute you plug in the USB cable it mounts a volume on your desktop
And you can drag the you know MP3s in or out so that works perfectly easy
So I'm sure that you know this could be eye-potted in a second right no problem
Although there's no playlist none of that is in here
So it's it has none of the sex appeal of the iPod that the iPod has for playback
But you can also record MP3s of the tuner so a radio program that you're listening to
And it has a line in and it's not the best encoder
Now mind you this only costs like 150 bucks
I cost my lip hurts
The feeling is starting to the window no vacans are wearing off and I'm starting to feel it a little bit
So I had actually I tested it a little bit and I tested it at 64 and at 96k sample a bit rates
And really had to stick with 128 because otherwise for some reason the mic just you hear that little that encoding noise
And you probably hear it rustling a little bit now
Because this is clearly it's just a cheap cheap version of things yet to come
And of the devices actually ordered two really cool ones that are similar concept
One for day one for myself although much more expanded you can really set the sample rates in the bit rates
You can move all the way up to 48 on the recording sample and you can go to 325 on the on the encoding bit sample
So there's it's a lot presumably it's going to be a lot better
But the thing that I like about this is so what I'm doing is I'm just record I think I'm using line in
Which is just a program that lets you play your your input your microphone input through your through your speakers or your headphones as I have them set up now
And then the whole headphone output Jesse can't you tell me the middle of talking about my setup here
Doesn't that impress you?
I guess not okay
Hold on though
Yeah
You have to learn to pee come in come in Jesse come in you have to learn to pee before I'm done first before I'm recording
There you go of course I want to come back in in two seconds right
So presumably the one that I've ordered is going to be have a little higher quality but
All of what I'm doing is basically just taking the output from from the headphone jack
And putting that into the line in of this MP3 recorder
Now what I like about it is that I've plugged my headphones my actually my iTunes headset
You know little earphones my iPod earphones I've plugged that into the headphones of this Samsung app
YEPP recorder so I'm actually monitoring everything that's being recorded
So I can hear that you know there's actual sound is sticking onto the solid state you know silicon or whatever it is
So that gives me good feeling and I know that nothing happens in my computer
Even if it crashes I know that the show is going to be safe because man Dave and I had some great stuff this weekend
And I could go through the whole story and tell you about you know exactly what we said and why it was so cool
But most of that has been lost and I don't ever want that to happen again
You know sure the connections can drop Skype can blow up
And you know my computer can disintegrate but it'll still and of course I'm inviting Murphy in the door here
Right, but it can still all be preserved on the on the external recorder and until you know
Until I'm convinced otherwise I think that this is this is the way to go. Let me tell you
Having done our entire reality show on Final Cut Pro
When you're reading and writing audio and video to disk shit just happens and after a while your disk just has to be like reformatted
And you have to just have to go through that stuff and
And I'm not quite sure I'm not a you know a disk drive as expert but unless you're using even pro tools
You know ask any pro tools user just to come to point where you know you reach the limit of what your computer can do and then you get skipping and
You know with all the all the software that's available for recording podcasts
I you know there's you have this risk look at Dave he has a brand new computer
Brand new this beautiful Sony with seven hour I don't know if it's a Sony
But as seven hour battery life and it's you know two gigahertz and it's fantastic and presumably he used that to record
The morning coffee note you did with a scobl or is it scobl
And even there you know three or four times during the recording you could hear that the machine just like frozen
If you didn't lose any audio with there's like a minute or a second and a half or maybe even two full seconds of silence
And then it picks up again, you know, and that's a brand new machine
Remember when Dave ran Google desktop search while he was recording will oops that doesn't work you know
So you run into all these problems with the sound you're trying to produce and all the cool shit, you know the applications
That you want to use like Skype or I chat or you know quick time or iTunes
But once that processor starts kicking and you have no idea what's going to happen to your recording
And I actually got some emails from people saying oh, you know, I run two applications
I run a backup and a dug cave from IT conversations always runs is running a CD recording backup, you know
So but looking at these little devices, you know, this is really something we're getting somewhere with these
And let me just improve the quality a little bit and put a few more functions in there
And we've got real podcasting devices that are going to be pretty exciting, you know, so maybe in fact this one
I can even even in an adapter, you can plug it almost plug it right into the USB, you know
Damn, it could be uploading stuff and doing that through Wi-Fi
Just many, many, many, many, many cool applications
Okay, um, just have a quick try to have a sip of tea here, hold on
Yeah, I know the can's getting a little bit better
Oh, man, so I had one feeling that it broke off a week and a half ago
And I was going to go see the dentist two days later and then I got this awful flu
And I didn't want to, you know, it was just disgusting
It wasn't, you know, no, no person with hygiene in mind would want to look in my open, open head at that moment
So I delayed it for a week and, um, and what he did is he took the old feeling out
Or whatever was left of it and filled it all up and bah
And you know how, you know, he doesn't want to put too much an overcane in
Because of course he knew that I had a podcast, right?
And, um, and today was bringing like the dry air and then he hits like some nerve
And just goes, boom, just like a electricity up to your head
Damn, in fact it was, oh, this is a great story
Um, was it two days ago?
Shit, there's Jesse wants to come back in
Two days ago, Patricia and I came home late
From, uh, we were visiting my niece
There you go, Jesse
Go ahead, you can leave the studio bar now, thank you
Um, so we were visiting, oh well
My niece and, uh, Rotterdam and we came back and we still had to feed the horses
Now, we, where, where the, our driveway is
Um, you can actually see the horses
You have to climb through like a little, a little ditch
And, um, and then you have to hop over
We're not really hop, you know, I can almost kind of straddle it
Over, uh, a fence, a wire fence, which is electrified fence
Um, and then, you know, that's where the horses are
And you can feed them right there, but it's real muddy
And so I, I positioned the car so I had the headlight shining
Um, and then I took the food and Patricia's standing there
Like, you know, move to the right, move to the left
You know, they want to be fed right in that spot
And the meanwhile, my, I had a bag of your pants on
Which apparently had a lot of nylon in them
And I just, as I stepped over the electric fence, you know
Oh, man!
Damn!
There was, like, all through my legs, you know,
Connecting through my groin.
It was not pretty.
All right, uh, moving right along with the Gilmore gang
Uh, hopefully you heard, uh, the episode, uh, last week's episode
That Dave and I were on it was all about podcasting
Um, uh, Steve Gilmore had arranged for, uh, three guys
From fire sign theater to beyond.
Now, uh, I'd never heard of fire sign theater
Uh, and actually was interesting.
It was, hopefully just as interesting for them to hear about podcasting
As it was for, for me to hear about what they're all about
They started in the 60s doing, um, the first, like, comedy on the radio
And, uh, and they had an enormous following
And they were just kind of like, well, in a way, very,
What they were doing is very analogous to podcasting
In fact, probably if they hadn't done what they did then
We may not be podcasting today, or it may certainly may not have been, you know,
The same type of vibe.
And so, what you do is with the, uh, the Gilmore gangs,
You call into a phone bank, right?
They give you 800 number and you call in and then when someone enters here
And you can talk with each other and then a certain point is like,
Okay, guys, let's get the recording going, right?
And then we start the show.
Uh, and I've mentioned on previous source code
That, you know, we were also free and talking about, you know,
How Bush has to get out of the White House
And none of that really came back on the show itself.
Um, which is unfortunate, but, you know,
It's, you know, when you know something's being recording
There's different energy and you think of different things
And, uh, and often the stuff you thought about, which might have been really
Interesting or very appropriate to talk about, you just forget about it
Because, you know, you already discussed it in this off your mind
Which is always the danger of, you know, radio shows,
Which is why I like keeping the mic open, you know,
Not stopping the recording and just going along
So that you hear everything fresh as it's new.
Also, you hear that, right?
That was new email that came in.
So you're going to hear all the sounds of my computer now.
In fact, if someone were to call me on Skype,
Um, we could decide whether to take that call or not.
But back to the Gilmour Gang.
So, um,
Loan behold, what shows up in my mailbox,
But a bit of MP3 from the Gilmour Gang,
October 22nd, 2004, before we started taping.
And what I want you to listen to is how I'm introduced to the surprise guests,
The Fire Scient Theater, who I have no idea who they are.
I've never heard of them, and listened to me bullshipped my way through it
Just to be polite.
I had them.
Steve, I got a surprise for you.
What's that, Mom?
We're, uh, we're going to, uh, answer Dave's questions about the birth of podcasting.
Uh, I'm, um, I've invited some special guests to join the fun, uh,
Uh, three out of four of the Fire Scient Theater.
Going to be on the call.
Okay.
So one of them is Peter Berkman.
Listen, listen to that.
Listen to that last one.
Oh, the fuck they are.
They are.
I beat them.
Oh, pretty good.
Pretty good.
Can't complain.
Excellent.
Uh, Adam, as you've heard, um,
If you listen to that, uh, nomdex, uh, panel.
Uh, I see some, uh, significant relationships between, uh, uh,
uh, uh, the first, uh, you know, stages of podcasting, and the first stages of, uh,
uh, underground radio.
And part of it.
All of that.
So now I did listen, uh, to a lot of nomdex, and I listened to,
I'm not going to share what panel, uh, Steve is referring to, but, uh,
uh, I must have missed, well, he might have mentioned underground radio.
I agree with that.
But I'd never heard of fire-scient theater.
And I just, I'm digging this whole deeper as we go along.
Totally.
Yeah.
I agree.
Very much so.
It has some of the same feeling.
Some of the conditions are similar, too.
Yeah.
Good point.
Similar war.
Somewhere.
Idiot.
Idiot presidents.
You know, I'm, you know, a lot of confusion.
A lot of denial.
You know, more of the same.
Uh-huh.
Oh, man.
I did it.
Uh-huh.
Oh, shit.
That was really bad.
You get really conscious of yourself when you listen to stuff like this.
Pretty nervous, you know.
It's like, I'm nervous about the election.
It scares the hell out of me.
I'm just, I know I don't get that upset.
But I am.
Yeah.
Well, Bush acted the way he did without a mandate.
Imagine if he thinks he has one, or other people think he has one.
Right.
Imagine what he'll do.
No stopping the bastard.
No.
Well, I'm not sure about that.
I mean, you know, Nixon thought that he was gone in two years.
Yeah, but Nixon was, Nixon did some very foolish things that, you know, he smoking guns
and all that, you know.
Yeah.
Nixon was mentally ill and Bush is more spiritually ill.
That's a good one.
Right.
Well, let's save this show.
See, exactly.
There you go.
Let, and if you say, let's save this for the show,
or don't forget to mention us on the show.
What's going to happen?
You're going to forget, of course.
Okay.
As you wish.
So Adam, did you see the mark?
All right.
So then we went into some more conversation, which probably wasn't all that interesting.
But, man.
We didn't get that good Bush comment stuff in there during the show, unfortunately.
I did find some stuff online, though, that I think you'll appreciate.
As a guy named Roy Zimmerman, who's been making some, well, I guess you'd call it
the modern day version of war protests songs.
Roy Zimmerman.com is where you can find all this stuff.
There's one that's called 90% which I'll pay it play on a later source code.
The one I'm going to play for you right now is called Burn Goodie Stewart Burn.
And that's a reference to the Salem witch hunts when the women were called Goodie.
Right?
Remember that?
You've ever seen that movie?
So, and also, you know, Goodie Stewart is like the quintessential name for a house
at the time of the Salem witch hunts who was probably being hunted for being a witch.
So check out the lyrics, particularly because it's all about the times we live in.
Roy Zimmerman.
Burn.
Goodie Stewart Burn.
We haven't caught Osama.
We spoke a bit too rashly.
He just released a video with Mary Kate and Ashley.
He's there in all the tabloins.
He's on a box of weedies.
In this war on terror, we have caught a few HVTs.
That's high value targets.
We're cracking down on cancer-stricken stoners.
And in cities independent bookstore owners.
Not to mention dangerous incliners.
And self-reliant women who are democratic donors.
Burn Goodie Stewart Burn.
You know, we love to nail them just like they did in the Salem Burn.
The prosecutor knows what a snap of the beat.
To prove you are a witch with a capitol beat.
And then there'll spirit you away to your incarceration.
What you'll be pretty to the latest insight information.
We sure when you unloaded all that stock immense.
To crumple each incriminating document.
But a person of your gender might just as well surrender.
And throw her reputation and career right in the blender.
Burn Goodie Stewart Burn.
We know which witch is witch in the oven.
Oh yes.
You're under a curse.
A curse that only witchcraft could reverse.
Because every single one of us could be charged.
But something wears thick in near us.
Behold of us.
And give us each a euras and a purse.
And yours is just another case of bait and switch.
Until we catch the one who's really Satan's witch.
We'd like to build a fire on a fire even higher.
And put away the shrillest voice in all the shrewish choir.
Burn Goodie Clinton Burn.
It's really Hillary.
We'd like to build a leader of the covenant.
We'd shove into the oven.
Roy Zimmerman Burn Goodie Stewart Burn.
Nice protest song of our times.
And I got an email about some comments made about President Bush.
And probably about John Kerry in a previous podcast.
This was posted on the day source code weblog from Bill.
Bill quotes me.
We got to get rid of Bush.
Why always says, I didn't know you were having elections in Belgium.
That you also had a candidate named Bush.
You made a conscious decision to leave the United States.
You should accept your choice.
I suggest you leave the presidential decision to those who actually be.
And who remain committed to the USA.
Well, I just want to say something here, Bill.
I'm an American citizen.
And I've voted in every single election since I was old enough to vote.
And I'm now 40.
So I've been through a couple.
When I was in overseas, I voted by proxy, which is perfectly legal.
It's very normal.
It's my privilege and it's my right to do so.
And since I can vote and since in case you didn't know, American citizens are.
Have to pay taxes, US taxes, or at least have to.
You have to file for taxes no matter where you live.
So certain the taxes that may not apply in certain countries in Europe.
I still have to pay in the United States.
And I do.
So I have every right, every right, Mr. Bill.
To say whatever I want about the guy that's running our company.
Right?
Because not just a country, it's a company.
It's a business.
And what he's doing with the cash that I am also contributing.
And I've paid millions in taxes in my lifetime.
So, so, mean or mean her.
And if you've never heard the Jimmy Jet podcast, which he calls the podcast about nothing,
Jimmy Jet is, I don't know if he still is doing radio stuff,
but he certainly has a lot of radio experiences.
He sounds really good.
He's doing a very, well, he's doing a podcast about nothing.
So he has all kinds of news bits and stuff that he puts in there.
One of my microphones sounds a little bit over-modulated.
Let me turn that down just a bit.
So he's putting all these different comedy bits in.
And he really does some research and does a lot of good show prep.
So he came up with a story about the slinky.
Was a slinky's birthday, perhaps.
Well, you listen to that story and then I'll play something that has, you know,
that is related to this story from the Jimmy Jet podcast about nothing.
Slinky, the famous spring toy invented by Richard James in 1943.
First went on sale on October 23rd in 1945.
The genuine slinky is manufactured in Pennsylvania from 80 feet of American-made steel wire.
And it's still produced on the original machines.
It was back then.
Let me see if I've got it.
Now I've got it.
Don't let I lost it.
Here we go.
Q that.
What walks downstairs?
A loner in pairs and makes the slinky sound.
A spring, a spring, a marvelous thing.
Everyone knows it's slinky.
It gives a big lift.
When raptors are gift, a very likable toy.
It's falling in place.
It's falling.
It's slinky.
But fun at the wind.
Remember that?
It's slinky.
It's fun for a girl and a boy.
I'm slinky.
So I remember there was something I found a couple of years ago.
And I went looking for it on the well-known peer-to-peer networks.
And I found it.
So keep humming that tune everybody.
And this next song is not safe for work.
What rolls downstairs?
A loner in pairs and makes the bosity sound.
It's long, a shlong, a marvelous song.
Everyone knows it's still down.
What fits in a sock feels better than a cock.
And unlike a man, it's slow.
It vibrates a bit.
It's great on a clip.
Everyone knows it's still down.
It's still down.
It's big.
It's flushy.
It's ripped.
It's still down.
Yes.
That's right.
It's ripped.
What fits in your cracks.
And even in abstracts.
The penis you don't have to blow.
They're not just for gays.
They use double rays.
Everyone knows it's still down.
A dildo dog.
A dildo plain.
Many more vibrating toys.
You turn the knob.
They buzz andæ‰ leaves.
Creating girls and boys.
Yes.
That's right, folk.
Dildo brand Dildo's aren't just for women anymore.
We also make a long line of
what a place
Weiterless,
everyone knows it's still down
a long-flushy tube
use oil they flew
not just for the neighborhood hose
for a girl on the go
with her time for about
it makes for her
fake failure
that
It's not over, hold on. It gets better.
And try new, my first deal though, for kids.
I told you it got better.
Some of those not exactly showin' batteries not included.
Not be used as a full rotation by some animal testing has occurred.
Please use a lubricant insert around it in first, not for use in the shower.
Make those choking, if you use them properly.
Bachelors, flat chillins may ensue.
If swallowed, do not induce vomiting.
This continued use, if irritation or abnormal swelling occur,
mean you're sliverin' thing in the middle.
Don't look random, it's have consequences.
Some are recurring animals.
Do not use excessive force while inserting to the low.
Make explosive place and fire.
Don't look random, it's not intended to replace the male sexual organ.
Only with a temporary substitute when a penis is not readily available.
Okay, I hope the levels are okay on the show.
It's a long second.
I hope the levels are alright on the show.
You might have to turn it up or down here and there.
And I see that we're about 36 minutes into the show today.
I had more things queued up, but you know what?
We'll just play all of that on tomorrow's source code,
because there's so many cool things just coming from left and right.
Just a reminder about a couple of things.
If you want to check out the latest episodes of all new podcasts,
that is audio.weblogs.com and look for the ping form.
If you don't know, and if you're not on that list,
and you want to be on the list, you can use the ping form.
You can use blogging tools to ping audio.weblogs.com
so that your new podcast will show up automatically.
I potted out org, new entries to the directory,
and there's a whole new slew waiting in the cache,
and if anyone wants to take over a node and wants to manage that,
let me know, send me an email.
If I don't get back to you in like 24 hours, send me another email.
Okay, because these days I've gotten almost the custom
to having to go through the junk folder, you know,
pick stuff out of there and it's just, it's a lot.
So the more nodes that can be maintained by other people, you know,
the better, so please let me know.
All you have to do is to be able to create an OPML file.
And a little plug for iPotter X, I was given a beta,
it was like beta 2, 2, 1 or something.
And right there, it was amazing to see, I fired up the application,
they've got top picks, what's new, they've got categories,
they're sucking in the entire OPML directory from iPotter.org.
They're not following all of the links yet, but that's the next step
in the next beta release.
And I'm really excited because now we'll send this application
is doing so much more for me, you know,
I can just stay with it in one place and listen to
previews of podcasts and subscribe right there.
Of course, since they have the entire directory imported
into the iPotter X application, it's real simple for them
to make the subscription process roll really smoothly.
So kudos to Ray and to August, it's really, really looking good.
Don and Drew ran out of bandwidth, but it happened,
these things always happened during the weekend.
So it shouldn't be a problem getting more bandwidth up for my offer
to host something for them, but I think they probably just,
they probably enjoyed the break anyway.
So we'll leave it at that for the source code for today.
Gonna leave you with one song that I found also from garageband.com,
which is an official pod tunes and pod music that we're allowed to play.
Dan Show, a city and me, as we roll it out on a mellow note for
the source code from 1A October 25th, 2004.
I look out my window and watch the phone ring.
It makes me feel better somehow when I'm same and though it's been so
good to know them, I know where else I
there's a rainbow somewhere out there, the one that I
from a springtime in the city for me.
North winds keep blowing on the back to my groove.
I used to feel safe there, but now I need room I wasn't
needed someone like them to share my quote on.
Now I'm growing like a flower I'm ready to start a springtime for the city and me.
So come on bread and stay and look in so great and I'm
understand and you're feeling that way, oh there's a new sun on the sky.
This way now for you, I think we better get a home now, I'm
needing it too, a springtime in the city for me.
There'll be a springtime for the city and me.
Oh man, in that pretty, unsigned band, ladies and gentlemen,
dance show, city and me, you can check out all about the band and
check out their site and everything on garageband.com, really
gotten into garageband.com because they tell you right there, you know,
you can use their music, you can download a track, actually this one I couldn't download,
so I hijacked the audio from from real audio, so I didn't really have the quality that I wanted.
I was going to wind up the show, you know, but I just I really love to test doing a sky,
let's let's be a noxious, let's make a skype call the day, hold on a second, let's
get some dialing music here, okay, here we'll play a radio trick on him.
Hey Dave Winner, Dave Winner, which is a favorite podcast?
No, what's the name of you at the favorite podcast?
Yeah, you win yourself an MP3 player down in Dave?
And that's it for the source code for Monday, October 25th, 2004.
And I'll check you tomorrow on a daily source code, we'll have more bits from podcasts
around the net and some more tunes, some more costumes for you, right here on your daily source code.
As always, you can leave your comments on my weblog live.curry.com, or you can send them to me
out of acurry.com, and you can check out the latest source code, the archives, the new ones,
and of course the podcast speed at dailysourcecode.com. I'll check it tomorrow everybody, bye-bye!