Augustine, all's live!
Adam Curry!
Yeah, everybody crank it up!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
And welcome to your daily source code!
Coming to you from the UK, this is the source code for...
Oh, man, it's Monday, November 29, 2004.
We're in studio.
Well, not actually not the it's studio A, I'm in studio A8.
Which means I'm in the Audi.
The Audi A8 is the new studio.
It's the place to be.
It had a nice weekend.
Went off to the Netherlands to do a little bit of business.
Had some friends putting together a television pilot,
which I instigated called Adams of Eagle Eye,
based around two friends of mine.
Both presenters, one legendary news guy,
who's about 55 years old and is definitely seeing a revival
that is career and man, it was a lot of fun.
I'm really even more fun was just figuring out
and actually experiencing how close the UK really is
and how easy it is to get more pretty much anywhere.
I left Saturday morning to the car picking up at 8 o'clock.
Had me at Heathrow at a quarter to nine,
I was on board the plane at 9.30.
And I was an Amsterdam, I see a quarter to an hour.
I was already in the Amsterdam bunker before noon,
I think, or just a little bit past noon.
So, not bad all things are considered.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, power up here and nothing.
All that stuff, okay.
So, let me see.
Yeah, the most important thing of the entire trip
for me personally besides, of course,
all the fun we had doing the TV show,
which was a total, what do you call it?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
One weekend in Holland and all of a sudden
I lose all my English volunteer.
All of, we basically called up all our buddies
and said, look, we need a couple camera people,
we need some producers, some sound people,
everyone chipped in and we created,
even studio was donated time.
Of course, if we actually sell this pilot
and we get it on the air, then of course,
everyone will be waiting there where they're hand out
because then they'll get paid and they'll be working
on the show, which is the way this is supposed to work.
So, it was a lot of fun.
And I'd book to hotel through,
I actually just did a Google search before I left
and said, I want to Wi-Fi,
enabled hotel in Hilversum.
And I know of some really good hotels in Hilversum,
which is kind of the Hollywood of the Netherlands.
So, you know, reason to go to hotels,
but none of them had anything that resembled Wi-Fi
or actually even broadband.
They were still talking about telephone with data ports.
So, didn't, didn't book there,
found a hotel called Revell,
excuse me, which I posted about on my weblog.
And walked in there around a 10pm,
of course, it was a late check-in.
And I think it might've been the owner
if not definitely a manager who said,
oh, you know, Adam, welcome.
I already heard on your podcast,
you're coming.
I just need your MAC address,
which is, you know, the Ethernet address
for my airport card,
which is unique to any Ethernet device.
Otherwise, I could've used the USB wireless card
from them or wireless the adapter, I guess.
So, I just get my MAC address and boom, you know,
free Wi-Fi, and it was cranking.
I downloaded hundreds of megabytes of podcasts
while I was awake, and while I was sleeping.
So, well worth the price of admission.
The room was good.
Yeah, the remote control wasn't quite bolted on to the nightstand.
So, in my book,
if you got a remote that's not bolted on,
you're in a hotel that's good enough, you know,
you got cold running water.
And you got your Wi-Fi, which is really reliable,
then it's all a good thing.
And the return journey was just as beautiful,
you know, got on the plane,
got to the airport a little bit early, had some dinner,
hopped on the plane, it left to the right on time.
It's 7, you arrive at 7, then of course,
because it's, you know, about,
actually you're at the gate getting off at 7,
because the flight itself is only about 36,
37 minutes.
Then guy waiting for me there,
hopped in the car,
and 30 minutes later I was home.
I was home before,
before was even 830.
So, perfect, absolutely perfect for the commute
back and forth to the Netherlands,
or any other part of the mainland for that reason.
So, the reason I'm coming to you from the A8 studio today
is because it's just so much going on,
and we just went to Christina's new school.
Actually, it's a school that we want to get her into,
so we had to, you know, kind of show up and say,
hey, you know, can we get this kid in?
Admissions are a tough thing here in the UK,
particularly in public schools,
because, you know, full is full,
and if they have no room,
then they just can't admit your child.
So, seem like they were going to have a space for her.
In fact, I think I heard the headmaster say,
well, you know, once we do the admissions
a little talk there,
and you feel like the paperwork,
and now it's just needs really is uniform,
and she's good to go.
It's an old request.
I didn't want to play that, our shoot.
I wanted to play,
oh, man, I totally blew that.
That's not what I want.
Here's what I wanted to play for.
Silence, silence!
I'm not that fit, but I'm afraid we'll go.org.
And you're listening to Adam Curry's Daily Source.
Bloody hell, not even.
Sheep, half of the equipment.
There we go.
There you go.
There you feel my head that's just learned some public end up.
Adam Curry's Daily Source code.
You're not ready.
I love when people send me promos,
and I love using them,
please continue to do that.
I go much, Todd.
So the reason I'm in the A.A.
is after, you know, we had to do the school thing,
and that seems all cool.
She's going to get in there.
That was really much easier than I expected.
We even dressed up.
And we made Christina dressed up to look a little bit representative,
and, you know, not her total gothic look.
That was a struggle this morning.
And so then I had to take the girls off to Sainsbury's,
which is the big shopping,
you know, the big grocery store,
mega grocery store.
And at three o'clock,
the ladies have appointments,
oops, that's my recorder.
The ladies have appointments for their nails,
and hair, and God knows what else.
And right now it's two o'clock.
So I figured,
what I do is I just bring my kit with me.
I've got my 12 volt DC to AC power converter.
I got all my stuff with me.
I just, you know,
slide the chair back a little bit.
Keep the heater on.
You can probably hear kind of humming in the background.
And I got my wireless love,
my hanging from the o' Jesus strap,
which is, you know,
the thing you hold onto when you go on a sharp corner
and say what Jesus.
And so there it is.
It's just kind of dangling in front of me.
And it's actually,
I've mentioned this before.
The car is a great place.
If you're looking for a studio,
cars are a perfect place.
You know,
to set up and get a nice quiet environment.
He let me turn off the,
turn off the,
the blower here.
There we go.
That's better.
Let's, you know,
why don't we just scan the,
the FM dial for a second.
Well, we're in the UK anyway.
We're going to start off with,
the BBC one at the top of the dial.
Okay.
So they're playing eagle eye cherry.
Isn't it?
It's like that.
Okay.
Ready or two?
Get off my line.
Uh,
that's really interesting.
Every ball day.
Okay.
And that was going to Virgin,
Virgin F.
Okay.
And that was going to Virgin F.
You know,
let's go to 96 for eagle.
Whatever that is.
The first glasshead in Secretary.
Council leaders in the south.
Are you still,
have only seen that concerns about plants about new houses.
Okay.
Let's go to BBC London.
Whatever that is.
Today's weather patch.
You may be able to dial.
It'll be bright.
The showers and the air.
BBC SCR, this we're up to news now BBC Radio 3, Classical Station
Well that's that's what we just see finale, which part of the BBC Radio 4,
leisure and news, classic, classic FM, yes they're up here, they're definitely all in news
ring now, part of the BBC Radio 4, the latest show BBC Radio 4, British underwear model
Katrina Davis is taking it off, that's the kind of news we need, the rating after winning
through to the show's last three finalists, the 23 year old originally from Cardiff is the
only woman left in the show, which ends next week and has a 200,000 pounds of price, London's
weather, writing kind of the songs that even higher, okay now kiss 100, I'm just running
on the dial here, I have no idea or, and now we have LBC 97.3, jazz FM, we are definitely top of the
hour in the news and magic FM, so there you go quick, quick scan around the FM dial here
in the UK, hello, this is top of the number of homo, some are still a dot net, music from
Germany, and you are listening to the daily source code with a podcast that he had a
curry, and have boiling, okay I wanted to make sure that you got Thomas's promo again
because last time I played something from some of the stellar dot net, I totally messed
up the URL, so now in the podcast production show notes, you can find the link to
Thomas Della dot net, which is German music, it's very cool, it's a great podcast, and
something that I think should definitely be added to the pod squad all in due time, more
about that in a second, first a little bit more about the UK, I want to thank you all so
much for responding to my call to help about television systems, power plugs, and light
sockets, let me see Dave Raven, first of all this is interesting, Dave Raven said it wasn't
until he heard Patricia talking about Iván on backing vocals, that's Patricia's sister
that he connected, he said he interviewed Iván for BFBS code in Cologne, was BF British
Forces broadcasting I guess, in the early 80s, so he says he had the world is very, very small,
he says that your local TV shop will tweak your TVs to UK standard, that I didn't
know, that's cool, also you can buy ES bulbs of all types, so you can keep your lamps,
and apparently we just didn't go to the right, do it yourself hardware store, now check
this out, he says why the funny plugs bulbs and TV, well here it comes, and this always
emases me, and I keep noticing on television and in newspapers that a lot of things
that you think might be American inventions or maybe the Germans think they invented it
or the Japanese think they invented it, British have their own thoughts about who invented
what, oh hold on that's the traffic report wailing through, here we go, low-key
bird, L-O-G-I-E, so I guess it's low-G- or low-key bird, invented the television, his
nationality was British, so I guess that's why they get to put the audio frequency wherever
they want, I did not know that, I thought it was like, you know, Mr. Xeneth, who invented
the television, Joseph Swan demonstrated the electric light a year before Edison, nationality,
British, so I guess that means he gets to put fucked up bayonet, connectors on it, if you
want, but that's amazing, I never heard about Joseph Swan, that he demonstrated the electric
light a year before Edison, then how come Edison gets all the credit or is that only in the
states that he gets all the credit? William Gilbert coined the word electricity, nationality,
British, now what I remember from my history lessons, didn't Benjamin Franklin, this is the way
Americans learned about the discovery of electricity, Benjamin Franklin was flying a kite with a
wire on it with a key at the end, and he got electrocuted when lightning struck his kite during
a storm, and that apparently is when he went, well, Boeing electricity, apparently not,
well, I have to take it from Dave that William Gilbert coined the word electricity, and then he
winds up by saying, UK Boeing over, and regards Dave, excellent Dave, thank you very much,
let me see, there's a couple more emails that got here, Mike from Holland says, hi Adam, welcome to
UK, congratulations on the culture show, peace, short of general, I love publicity for podcasting,
boo, oh, here's one about plug TV systems, here's one for you, can you explain, oh, this is a good one,
he says, can you explain, well, all electric sockets in the Netherlands are halfway up the wall,
that's always puzzling me, why not have them at floor level like over here, so they're not so obvious,
okay, very good question, that is something we noticed as well, and I believe it's twofold,
one is it was safety for children, kind of like the way I guess UK has switched next to every single
electrical outlet that they have, which is probably also a safety thing as well, but I also believe,
because most of the Netherlands is several feet under below sea level, thus underwater,
flooding certainly occurred back in the day, and yeah, when flooding occurred, you know, you want to have
a little bit of space there before it hits the electrical sockets, that's the only answer I've
ever heard, it may not be the correct one, there's something else if you ever come to the
Netherlands, you may notice that the toilets in Holland don't just have like a hole down into water,
they have a shelf, there's an actual shelf, and you know, stuff just kind of sits there until
you flush it, and I remember moving to the Netherlands and inquiring about that thinking was very
weird, and the way that happened is that the first toilets were made for hospitals, and the same
company that made the toilets for hospitals basically just continue to make them for for domestic
use for people's homes, and in a hospital it's quite handy to have a little shelf there to check
some stuff out, and that's the story behind that, hey, I'm almost as good as Patricia with
a Stevie next stuff, aren't I? Now, one more TV solutions, where do we have here, this is from Toby
Jeffy, oh yeah, he said something, okay, so here's the actual technical deal with the televisions,
reason you can't hear the UK audio on your TV is that the rest of Europe uses PAL GPH for
UHF, which is a 5.5 megahertz audio offset, whereas the UK South Africa, Ireland and the Hong Kong
used PAL I, which is a six megahertz offset for the audio, not sure what PAL does this, or PAL I does this,
but basically means that the RF reception is going to, you're going to not going to hear the audio,
one way around it, and this is something that I actually thought about myself, is if you get a free
view box, which I told you about, the stuff that pulls digital channels out of thin air,
you can use this scarred, and I do believe that the scarred is just a pure audio and video in the
start, the scarred connector when those broad, multi-prong connectors, so I'm hoping that once we
get our credit cards and either UK issued credit card to get sky, to get the sky satellite system,
and then I'll be able to connect a couple of TVs up using the set top box going directly to the
scarred to the scarred connector. So that's it about that for the, then that's also minor really
when all things considered is not bad at all, and we're fitting in quite perfectly, even with
the small, you know, these small little differences. Ross Jones sent me a link, which I actually
posted on my weblog, another link in the production show notes for today's Daily Source Code,
that the BBC is doing a show on radio six tomorrow about the ever so popular, quote, unquote,
podcasting, so I'll be sure to, hopefully get a recording of that, or at least be able to
listen to it and report back on what the BBC is doing with that. Again, the BBC is really
getting into into podcasting. I can feel it. There's no like official sanctioned, you know,
really yet, but I know the technicians are all over it, and I know a lot of the people who are
who are presenters and producers are still, you know, very interested in doing whatever they can with
podcasting. Along the lines of the culture show that aired last week, Stuart Hunter has also posted
an MPEG version of the podcasting segment for all of you who are having problems with the MP4 version,
and he's placed that as a bit torrent. Again, that URL available from the pod show production notes
for today's Daily Source Code. Let's get another little promo here. Hello everybody,
different lines, the digital man from the digital experience podcast. I want to invite all of you
to check us out. Our weekly podcast includes non-real music, news and information, podcast reviews,
and upfront political talks with Dan and Craig. We're kind of like Adam Curry,
only we never lived in a castle. We drive on the right side of the road,
and there are very few. So check out the weekly digital experience podcast,
only at lands.pfil.com. All righty. Gotta say I'm hearing more everybody's popping up every single day,
and that's actually the cover real all requests that I played by accident earlier in the show.
Check it out. Just listen to how people are saying every body. It's an all-request Sunday on cover
ville, everybody. By the way, I totally love the Beatles coverville, which was the Thanksgiving
version. Man, that kicks so much ass. It was wonderful to hear. I suggest you check that out if you
haven't yet. Great stories, great versions by other artists, and it came right after I was watching
this wonderful BBC program, which I'll also put a link to on the on the podcast show notes.
A couple of years back, someone found an old analog portable jute box that belonged to John
Lennon. I think they found it in an auction. So it's literally, it's like a case, you open this
case up, and in it is a whole mechanism, plus these 45 RPM vinyl singles, and it was his personal
jute box. And he'd filled it up with, so kind of like the the iPod of the day, right?
And it was found intact with all the original 45s that John Lennon put there in there himself,
written down a couple of been changed around. And basically what they did is they took this jute box
and went to all the people who songs were in it. And it was amazing. I mean, they also took
the people who a couple people who weren't in it, but so like sting for instance. But they,
you know, they found all these old blues artists and singers. And it was, you know, I'll put a link
to the show. I don't know if there's any video available, but it was a fabulous, fabulous show.
Again, just, and it wasn't even the BBC. I think it was ITV actually, one of the,
one of the commercial stations. It was just a great, great show. I wonder if it was, it looked like
was it was all English names on the credit. So I guess it was a UK production. I have no idea if
it's new or if it was repeat or if it's ever aired anywhere. But I was, yeah, I was totally amazed
by that. And then, but on the heels of that to hear the coverville, the coverville of the Beatles
was absolutely fantastic. Just beautiful. Let's see, what did we want to handle today? A couple
more plugs. What is this UPEI? Okay. Justin, Doran. Can't stop listening to your show. Good stuff.
Just wanted to let you know. I'm starting a new university web radio station podcasting service
over here. The University of Prince Edward Island in Canada. Your show provides a lot of inspiration
for it. And he had links to, did I just play that promo? I'll put the email in the, in the
show notes. A little discombobulated today, sitting in the car trying to do this. And also Studio Geek
another podcast you want to check out with an RIA free podcast, which I heard someone the other
day say, RIA. Maybe that's the way we should just categorize it. RIA. It's the, instead of RIA,
just say, RIA. I think that's probably the best way to go. Want to give a little attention
to the new sports node on the iPodor.org directory. And I kind of messed it up. I was talking
about the, what is it? The, the, the skinny on sports podcast. And I'd confuse it, the skinny on
sports podcast with Curtis, who is actually, does the sports pod at the sports pod.com. And Curtis
is actually the person who has been working with me for the past two weeks trying to get an
OPML file just right so that we can get it into the directory. And it was a real, I mean,
it was just like giving birth. And even though I have no idea what I'm talking about when it comes
to that, it was really painful. So we finally got it to work. It's up and running. And Curtis
is actually going to write up a little document to assist people when they get into the loop that
we got into with, with trying to get the right OPML just, you know, just perfect so that the
directory would parse it all. So apologies there. The skinny on sports is of course now listed
in the, in the directory, but it's really Curtis who's maintaining this and he's got all kinds
of sports podcasts. Check out the sports, what is it? The sports, the sports pod, sports pod.com.
Again, all information linked into the appropriate places, of course, from the iPodor.org directory.
And we're working on a lot of OPML stuff. Droo from Don and Drew has also gotten the OPML bug.
And I think what's going to happen pretty soon is this whole concept of the pod squad,
which essentially is, oh, I eight or nine podcasts that just, you know, are my favorites.
We're going to start linking those together and, and, and really having a lot of the information
flow from one to the next and also make it easy for people to subscribe to an entire,
basically a station or a network in one go. So just here's one file, drag it into your iPodor
and boom, you're subscribed. And it should also maybe put them into a separate, I'm thinking,
I don't know, maybe we should put them into a separate playlist on your MP3 player.
Not quite sure yet, but a big part of that is going to be these production notes and how we flow
things from, from one podcast to the next. And maybe how we can, you know, all together, you know,
as a, as a group, as a pod squad, maybe we can figure out how to promote certain songs together,
or who knows? But it's definitely high on the radar for getting stuff rolling.
As is the bit torrent method of distribution, boy, this has been a big thing on the mailing lists.
And unfortunately, too many private emails over the past week, which I think we've kind of
gotten out of the private email circuit by now. But Dave Winner and I co-authored,
where I think it's just going to be the simplest way to get an alternative form of distribution
for podcasters who, you know, are trying to figure out a way of distributing their podcasters,
more efficiently than just putting an MP3 up and letting everyone hammer the MP3 file directly.
So we've come up with a bit torrent name space for RSS. And it's really simple. All it solves is
one thing. And that's what I like about it. It just gives you a way to add an alternative
download location and download method specifically for a bit torrent. It's not trying to solve
anything else than that, which is why I like it because RSS is supposed to be simple. So the next
thing we'll be working on, I think, is this OPML. Of course, we're going to figure out, you know,
I don't know if there should be an OPML namespace or whatever. In fact, I've just looking at RSS
an OPML, both in an outliner. I'm trying to think how can we connect those two, but I'm not sure yet.
And hey, it's only Monday. Damn. This is the brain's work in a way too hard.
It's not often that I come across something from Andrew Grummett's feeds. I'm subscribed to a
couple of different RSS feeds that he has with the RSS 2.0 and in closures. And something finally
came across the wire off of Andrew Grummett's, I guess this is podcast feed. And it was so cute.
It took me a while that it took me two plays actually to figure out what was going on.
But this is, it's he came through as, see, was it categorized as the Grummett family players
from Andrew Grummett's audio weblog. The tune is Freddie Freeloader and I guess this
um, I'm going to kid shoot see a nine mile online here in the car. I'm thinking it's Andrew
of one kid or two. I think he has one child. So I think that the deal is Andrew is kind of doing
the melody and then his child is blowing on whatever he's blowing on.
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do
old ladies and gentlemen you heard you heard it here first on the daily source code where
users and developers party together and when we got a lot of stuff to take care of
here in the UK I have still a full afternoon right now it's shoot it's already
220 so I'm expecting the girls out here any minute now will rush the groceries
back home then I got to take them to the hairdresser nail salon and then of
course well there they are you know what I'm going to do you know what I'm
going to do you know I'm going to walk right into Starbucks and get hooked up
and upload the show that's exactly what I'm going to do and I'll be back tomorrow
with more source code for you right here from Curry College well then again
of course this is Stimio A8 I'm pretty kind of just hopefully will be tomorrow
no no broadband yet so I'm going to take I predict probably the rest of the
week before the before it's scheduled but I've got a big honking download
so I'm just coming up as always comments are welcome and you're your
audio comments or promos or whatever you have it's out of a free.com of course
I'm going to comment on my weblog of live 940.com and the source code can be found
in its archives later show at the podcast RSS feed and daily source code.com
I'll check you out tomorrow everybody take care bye bye
RSS