Before we get started, let me remind you of the following results or events predicted on these things,
namely, and materials from actual results.
The fact is that good cause actual events results to differ from expectations include
lack of growth, intense competition in our industry,
integration failures, changes in government regulations,
operational failures, or looking to England's representatives.
All right, so with fully as of today, it should not be
like common representatives in the death of any subsequent days.
While we name the like something more than we say, it's a couple in the future.
We need to not give it a leave in front of us, too.
Augustine almost lies!
Adam Curry!
Our Lord of the Lord, give it to us.
We have to do a good morning, good evening.
Whenever it's applicable to your body, the world,
everybody inside of Curry this is the daily source code.
We're Tuesday November 2nd, 2004, coming to you from Curry Castle,
Flamper's Belgium.
We're going to be for the next two and a half weeks.
Lord, give it to the movies in an imminent imminent.
It's coming up.
This time, we got much to go into about.
We are almost out of here.
Wow, what a completely fucked up day we had here in the Netherlands.
Damn, this morning everyone was kind of ready for the elections.
Every single TV show here in the Netherlands had called me and asked me to be
a guest on their show, which I had at the time, because I just did not feel like
sitting on any TV show from midnight till 6th.
I would much rather kind of watch it at home in the comfort of my own home, you know.
And so the morning started with a whole bunch of phone calls coming in around nine
o'clock people saying that a very well-known columnist television host,
interviewer, producer, director, and also filmmaker, Dale Fahol,
which you would put out as algebraic set.
Theo Van Gogh, and yes, he is a descendant of any infamous and famous Vincent Van Gogh.
Was murdered today in Amsterdam at about a quarter to nine.
He was done down by a semi-automatic fire and then hacked with a knife, stabbed.
The details are a bit sketchy still, but some eyewitness reports say his throat was cut,
and a note was left on his body.
And this happened right on the street, not far from his home.
And I think from what I could see on the TV news, it looked like the note was actually pinned to
his body with this butcher knife. It was pretty shocking. Let me tell you about Theo Fahol.
So you get a little bit of perspective on this. This is one of these people that you have in society,
usually associated with media more than with politics, that really color everything.
And make the world just a little bit more fun to live in because these people are always challenging
the edges of everything. And Theo Van Gogh's particular challenge was always his freedom of speech.
And he exercised his right continuously. And he was not very well loved, although people who knew him
knew that he was a very, very, very sweet man, a very loving father.
And in a way, he felt that this was his role and the number one issue that he'd been hammering on
for the past few years was how the multicultural integration process in the Netherlands has failed.
Country of 16 million people, little over 16 million people in an air and land mass smaller than Rhode Island.
And there's, I believe, 3 million Muslims of which a number are radical extremists.
And Theo was a guy who said, look, we've got a problem brewing here. The people know it.
The government is not responding. Something has to be done about this. This is something also,
by the way, that PIM4 times said, you'll remember the politician who was assassinated. And he wasn't assassinated
by or under the guise of some religious geod. But that was also one of his big mantras.
And this was not a racist issue. This is a pure issue of culture clash that is just not
driving within this country. I mean, I wasn't here when there's whole integration process started,
but they did not set it up right. I think if you have people who don't even speak the language
after having been here for seven or eight years, it's hard for them to integrate. Anyway,
I don't want to get down into the discussion of it all. But Theo also was very vocal.
And besides just being vocal in television programs and he wrote columns and newspapers,
he also made movies. And he recently did a movie with a Dutch minister, a senator minister.
She's a member of parliament, a Dutch parliament, here she is, and she is a Muslim woman
who is exercising her free speech rights to criticize her religion as long.
And they did a movie together, controversial movie, a short film,
which was basically about how women are treated
by or in the extremist believers of Islam. Very complicated. But there were some
very profound statements in that. And it just drove this particular guy who killed Theo,
it drove him to that point. And from by all accounts, this was totally a revenge murder for what
he had to say or his expressions in this movie. And as you can imagine in a country that speaks
a language that doesn't work anywhere else except for parts of Belgium and South Africa.
You know, we've got a very tight, closed community, which wants to be very open. And
you know, there's a lot of shit going on right now. So I didn't know Theo very well.
In fact, I met him, he invited me to be on the television show to be interviewed in a
simultaneous interview with Lowe de Valle, who's the, he's like the head of all the labor unions.
You know, they always try to get a contrast. So I guess I thought I would be the capitalist pig and he
would be the labor union guy. And we would, it turned out we had a lot more in common than we had
differences. But Theo was directing that show. And we chatted before and after the show.
And we decided to meet up. And we actually didn't meet only about four days later, I looked it
up on my weblog. And it was a great, you know, it came up to the place in Amsterdam, to the to the
bunker. And we chatted about everything from politics to, well, I was interested in getting him.
He has a website. Theo from Khach. But I wanted it really to be, you know, more like a weblog
structure. I was trying to help him get an RSS feed up and running, because he just, you know,
he needed more distribution. He had something to say. He was a blogger. And one thing we really
different on a opinion on was that he, he's a big bush supporter and thought that bush should
definitely be re-elected. And something that's interesting, because I'm looking to watching television
hearing all kinds of testimonials and he worked with a lot of actors. And they all said that he would
always say to them, you know, leave here, leave the Netherlands, go somewhere else. And it's funny
because when we had that meeting at the house, he said, what are you doing here? Leave, go, go back
to America. This place is going downhill. There's, you know, there's no saving it. Boy, you know,
how stuff can can roll. Anyway, I have a feeling you're probably going to hear about this.
It might, well, I'm sure, if it, yeah, it's probably going to get just totally buried because
of election coverage. Otherwise, it's something that would have made, and made the news in the
states. It made it around Europe because, you know, it's like show business. You know, it's a thing
this TV guy, filmmaker, getting killed and what I consider to be a pure jihadist action.
So, I was just kind of really weird. And, you know, everyone's calling each other and just,
you know, feeling really, really funny about what happened. However, we've got a show to do here,
ladies and gentlemen. So, let's play a little bit of music that is perhaps inappropriate for
today's events.
So, this is where it happened.
And, this is where he died.
This is where the sun's gone shining.
So, this is where the sun's gone shining.
And, this is where the sun's gone shining.
Therefore, the sun's gone platinum.
So, this is where the sun shines.
Bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up
bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring it up, bring
This is where it sounds to me
I'll be a party
My joans from their album diyor
Strongация
And I've played mo jones before on on the show and now in the production notes as I'm using
my still undeveloped and spiffy new pod production console, you'll be able to find a link
to the Modions website which is Modions.nl and also some information about the album.
I read something on scripting news today about Dave was talking about some blogging tools
that support enclosures and help you put enclosures which basically is an RSS 2.0 feed
which is what a podcast feed is all about and he suggested making a sub-directory on iPodor.org
in the iPodor directory which actually I think the site may be down or maybe I'm having some
DNS problems here. I'll have to check that later. I'm making a separate category which of course
is great because we want to help people make podcasts and make that as easy as possible. And
and you know thinking about that I can see that the aggregator developers so the guys who make
well as we're kind of popular aggregators are out there that are on the desktop certainly
we've got net news wire for the Mac. I hear a lot about news gator and some other
some other desktop-based aggregators. So they're getting into their waking up
and the starting to see that there's a part we go in on here on the iPodor's developer list
where users are and developers party together and that we're really achieving some awesome things
and they want to be a part of that and I think that makes a lot of sense actually but
all the notes I've gotten so far have been you know hey we we support enclosures and this is
what we do and I you know basically I think to myself oh yeah you know that's that's what we were
four or five years ago today it's about making the connection to well we're not really making the
connection to your iPodor MP3 player but we're making that connection to to mainly iTunes or the
Windows Media Center so there's a lot of intelligence a lot of knowledge on the iPodor developer list
I believe here listening to the developers podcast that Garth Kidd puts together
for the iPodor team iPodor lemons what I call it
that they're modularizing everything and you know so it's real easy I think to hop on board here
and you know we should put together some kind of checklist a day when I actually talked about this
when you check list of you know what an iPodor actually has to do and you know hurry on
up because especially you aggregator developers that support OPML there's some cool stuff happening
with directories and flows and and somehow we're going to be able to patch this pod production
console system into that and that's all going to be OPML I'm totally convinced I'm drinking the
cool aid everybody so you know you're welcome on board and you know and let's see if we can
that can help you out with with the final steps because it seems so trivial I know but it's really
it goes beyond just to get it in closure onto the desktop it has to get into iTunes or into
some other media player that will sync up with the mobile devices and I got a call today from
Jennifer Khan from wired magazine she's not she's a science writer actually writes about you know
nanotechnology and and really science geeky stuff and she's doing an article on
satellite radio which she she says she knows nothing about and I'm not quite sure because this
wasn't really an interview about pod casting although of course you know me I convinced her that
pod casting is the end all to be all but before we got to that you know she said you know
so what is this what is this satellite radio you know these guys actually have a chance of
making it will they be around and as we were talking you know and I was kind of making it up as I
went along and she was a really it turned out to be a really good discussion partner particularly
because she had no preconceived notions and and really you said she knew nothing about it so I was
able to kind of dig around in my brain and use my radio experience and we cope with a couple of
interesting angles and then as you know as relating it to pod casting all of a sudden and I don't
know if if I already had this conversation with someone if it was it it was probably with Dave I'm
not quite sure but it hit me you know because I was talking about how satellite radio basically they
have a limited spectrum as well it's just limited by money but you know so they can do 30 channels
or whatever and they're basically these channels are all specialized and this is what what Jennifer said she
said you know I don't like half the stuff that's on there this you know it's like the new wave
country crap I think is what she said and I said you know I actually I personally do like a couple
of the new wave country crap things and I realized that we're we're kind of both we're approaching
the same problem from different directions where here's the satellite radio guys who are
beaming down a very expensive signal with almost you know with very limited content or at least
the content is packers in such a way that you almost want to tevoize it you know so that you can
and in fact there are applications out there now that you record satellite radio and then you know
basically sort that and put it into a playlist and and play it on your MP3 player or play it back
through the through the digital system in your car I said well wait a minute wouldn't be really
interesting think about what what the satellite radio guys could do because they're basically
they're just using bandwidth right um they have seven megabits or whatever and they split that
up so they can get an X number of channels but it's coming down to the your receiver digitally
and these receivers are cheap you know that's that's the beauty of of what they're trying to do
is you know you can buy to the supermarket and you know you plug almost literally plug it into your
existing car stereo or you can buy the top of the line expensive you know model whatever you want
but they're just sending down digital data now what if instead of having the M&M channel which
I'm sure is wonderful but you know I'm sure there's a channel that that they could give up what if
they decided to broadcast the top podcasts you know or the top 10 podcasts it could actually be
more I think about a 24 hour period so let's say a couple of shows or an hour you know you're
probably looking at 30 30 shows a day on one channel right before you start to repeat
and you basically sell a receiver that will hook up to your iPod and your iPod will recognize
these shows coming down the pipe or shit maybe just records them all you know whatever we'll get
rid of it if we don't need it because you know it's cheap but think about if there's no difference
between getting your podcast over the internet or receiving it through a satellite radio receiver
but you know it could just be a seamless process that's running in the background anyway that so
I I told Jennifer that you know we shouldn't do this interview we should go start a company together
and she thought that was funny and then I invited a blogger con I don't know she's gonna come
moving along uh one a highlight a couple of new podcasts today and this is actually the third
installment of this podcast but it's been on my list to let you hear a little bit of it
it's from a guy named Scott Lockman he lives in Tokyo and well that's pretty apparent when you
listen to the show.
oh this is Scott Lockman and welcome to Tokyo calling for Sunday October 31st you might
call this the take to episode yes indeed I've been working for the last two hours trying to put
together an episode I had 15 minutes of good stuff recorded using the program audacity
and the thing crashed and I had not saved it beforehand so might talk this one up for podcasting
learning episode number one what a bummer it was some pretty good stuff and it is gone there
oh dude you're gonna live through so much more of that and last you listen to me and get yourself
an external recording device just for about a hundred you live in Tokyo they're probably about
50 bucks over there just a little flash based MP3 player and you know 256 megabytes is more than enough
you can connect it up via USB then every piece of sound you can produce with your computer
goes straight to the output if you can hear it you're recording it then you've got a total solution
it's a temp file somewhere and I looked at it and it's about 60 different
AU files all of them about one megabyte in there and it would take me more than another hour
why does our density do that together so it will just have to be an episode that lives in my
memory and one that is gone anyhow I still feel the need to get this out I want to do something
before I go to bed not make this time spent a total wash I've appreciated all of the
comments that have come in through the email this has been a great pleasure for me to put
Tokyo calling together okay so there you go Tokyo calling you can of course catch that through
the ipodder.org directory and I am putting in the links to it's actually it's a good idea
and it's at this time I console you need to have the subscribe here link uh wait until I automate
this thing it's going to be awesome it's going to be so easy to retrieve the source code if you
will to the daily source code yep sucking on on exhaust again oh and a member was telling
about the Gilmore gang yesterday how it totally ruined my weekend there was no Gilmore gang alone
okay Steve you win this is Doug K the host and producer of IT conversations and not just for the
sake of Steve Gilmore who has been bugging me to get an audio announcement out there explaining that
we didn't have a chance to do a Gilmore gang this past week but for all of the listeners who have
written and who have lost a lot of sleep wondering where the Gilmore gang was from Friday October 29th
the fact is that we had a cancellation we couldn't put the show together Steve did everything in his
power to get one together on Saturday a pre-election edition of the Gilmore gang but it just wasn't
meant to be so we'll do everything we can to get you on this coming Friday November 5th it will of
course be our first post-election edition of the Gilmore gang I'm Doug K the host and producer of IT
conversations and thanks for listening see that that's cool and actually I almost considered doing one
of those myself because it was so late this is actually right now it's oh shit it's three minutes
at two a.m. two minutes at two clock just switched I'm going to stay up a little bit and watch
some of the election coverage but I was considering doing the little hey guys I'm going to
watch the elections I'll catch in a moral podcast but then I said no no I've got to be there for the
gang and for people like Scott Brenner hey Adam Scott I was from Boulder Colorado I was calling to
turn you on to coverville.com this guy Brian's doing a podcast 20 minute half hour podcast
only doing cover songs pretty interesting was really interesting if you hadn't got an
ask cap license told him exactly what he's doing and they gave it to him I thought you might
cover that on your show and maybe you'd be interested in helping promote him so that ask cap feels
like oh this was smart for us to give him the license we're getting you know we're getting paid
and might help establish the license as you know reasonable that they're not going to six
months go hey that's that's not what we had in mind want to pull that license just thought
it's the Halloween edition of coverville and I promise you not once will I play the monster
mash coming up right now
happy Halloween and welcome to October 31st edition of coverville I'm Brian Abbott thank you for
listening we're going to get into some Halloween music later on but no now we'll be songs I promise
but first I want to get into a quick dedication John Peel BBC DJ extraordinaire again he was a
DJ for the BBC longer than I've been alive and longer than fans of the music that he
helped promote was alive hopefully that made sense he passed away earlier this week
very sad and and definitely very sad occasion for London because he was just huge out there
responsible for the discovery and popularity of bands like the Smiths and pulp and the
cure a lot of great great music video promote I'm in a play something that according to the
BBC's website they did a really nice piece on him on his biography apparently his favorite track
was a a single called teenage kicks by the undertones in 1978 he played it constantly
until finally Sire Records landed a deal with the undertones and and they got the music
a little more widespread I'm not going to play the original by the undertones I'm going to go ahead and play
a cover version by busted which came out just recently so there you go a little bit of cover
ville thank you very much Scott Brenner for turn me on to that and I was happy to hear the whole
piece about John Peel who we spoke about before on the daily source code and now you can hear some
of the bands you discover but also hear what you know what was being said about how he just played
these songs over and over and over again and that's exactly what we can do with podcast you know
this is this is how it works you know if records don't become hits without some kind of
infrastructure oh there you go that's another one for the list when you need a top 40 right podcast
pod tune top 40 something like that email from Dithermaster boy that I that I
fucked up on this remember yeah yeah yes I played those I trip tones to see if I could change
everyone's iPod to a different frequency so I got some feedback on that Adam if you want the
I trip tones files to actually change frequencies you have to not play the bit after the pause that's
the cancel code that makes the I trip not change frequencies it's there sort of your iPod plays the
frequency songs by accident say during the all play shuffle mode then your I trip won't change
frequency so I guess it didn't work as you would say in the programming biz so yes I shouldn't have
played the second blitz okay so that makes sense because I always wondered about that if if you're
iPod accidentally picks one of those tunes at random which has those tones in it you know will
it then start switching frequencies that's how they solve that with just little hack by putting in
the clear tone for not to change but he says please please don't send that in your podcast it
would suck for anyone using an I trip no longer packing the I trip files to change back or worse
fumbling with their iPod on traffic and crashing I used to use an I trip I would curse your
name if you did that you know what now they think about it yeah that was pretty stupid I'm sorry but
you know in case we need it we can always use it as some kind of you know emergency broadcast system
and it's good to know that it's there the latest search engine from Google could turn out to be a
privacy nightmare once installed in a computer running Windows 2000 or Windows XP the new Google tool
can find whatever's done on that machine including email sent or receive via outlook or outlook
express AOL instant messaging and web visits it won't just give you an idea it will actually show
you the physical pages and things that you've done. Pam Dixon is head of the world privacy forum
she's concerned that the beta version of a Google desktop search now available for free downloading
is not password protected so if you install it anyone with physical access to your PC has easy
access to whatever you've done machine so for example let's say you go shopping online it will
collect your credit card numbers if you do banking online collect your passwords and you're on my
thinking financial information and consider this use a computer that has Google desktop search
installed say you want to check your email from a friend's house they can see everything you did
on that computer in complete detail by the way Google is the first but other companies have similar
search engines in the works and that's today's tip i'm her voice bomb the consumer man
looking out for you on coma 1000 news i love her he's always looking out for us you should
subscribe to that if you're not already a coma 1000 news podcast you can find in the ipod.org
directory and a reminder that if you want to look for new podcast that have just been updated or just
fresh audio dot weblogs dot com is where you can check those out if you want to get on that list
there's an information ipod.org as well about how to use the ping form or use a blogging tool
that'll do that for you automatically so that when you publish your podcast everyone knows about it
and of course there's also a back end to that which can be used by developers as well you know
imagine i'm using ipod.rex currently i'm waiting for the new ipod 11 version their next release
i can't wait to try out all different pieces of software but you know already we're integrating the
directory so what if there's a new show you know it could you could have stuff high light or tune you know
just all kinds of cool things we can do and you can you know set up rules and oh boy love it
talk about blogger con for a second tomorrow will be wins day or actually it will be wins day later on i'm gonna
the in the afternoon early afternoon i'm gonna go to Amsterdam i'm gonna stay overnight there
clay fly from Amsterdam from triple airport Thursday morning around noon uh yeah just before noon
i fly by along to San Francisco and uh blogger con this is blogger con three is of course
at excuse me Stanford University on Saturday November 6 and i'm going to be a discussion leader
for podcasting session it's going to be uh i'm very excited about it um i'm on the plane i'm
going to you know kind of making out line or actually going to use now line or making out line
of you know what i want to try and get accomplished um if you have any thoughts about that
please do do email me and put it in the subject line you know blogger con you know session thoughts
or whatever because uh i'm a real mess with email right now i'm trying to get through it all
and i'm trying to prioritize but it's a mess it is just a mess there's so much email coming in
and i've learned from the past that the less email you send the less you receive but even that's
not really helping right now uh so in preparing for my flight i'm also uh stocking up on on podcast
it's really hard i'm forcing myself not to listen um there's uh uh let's see uh IT conversations
behind the mic uh uh interview with it with my uh my partner and crime Dave Winner um and i've
listened to a little bit of it but you know i want to save it i want to save that for the for the plane
there's also uh Doug K was on a web talk radio uh we're also podcasting now and i want to listen to
that uh what i do catch uh and i'm so happy Dave uh um at this i think this is for the first time
and i talked to him about it he is now uh morning coffee notes is now officially a podcast and it was
in you know about time we still we still need to get an opening tune for him but now he's he's put
some structure into the show and what the couple things i really like about uh about uh the morning
coffee notes uh one is the into just that even the title suggests such an intimacy you know you know
here we are and of course i come from the written port the written version of morning coffee notes uh
which is kind of you know Dave's brain dump uh uh you know that that he has with his morning coffee
but they don't necessarily have to be done in the morning they can be done at any time but there's a
real intimacy and uh i got to find out what microphone is using because it sounds really clean you know
it's just a very clean uh audio in fact if i'm listening on the on the iPod sometimes i can
hear i think it's a refrigerator or something that's kind of humming in the background and when that
kicks off then you really realize how quiet it is um and uh so i wanted to play a little piece
about uh the food this whole this whole podcast is great because there's stuff in there about
how to make money on the internet with web logs with podcasts and um and and Dave goes into some
some good detail about that i really suggest you listen to it if you're interested in making money
you may not be um but as it relates to blogger con um he did a little piece about the Saturday
food for thought dinners uh and i'm hosting one table i think there's a whole bunch of tables um
and it's actually two i think two podcasting tables and dawn and drew will be hosting a second
table so what a hood um but the thought behind the the food for thought dinners is uh there's a
couple of different thoughts behind it but the one that i that i really like the most is comes from
some personal experience that Dave has with uh with conferences which i find to be exactly like mine
care to talk about what you you know what you signed up for but also it's okay to wander a little bit
it's a it's a it's a social event and that leads to the second reason why uh we do these dinners
is so that there can be a Saturday evening social event for basically that's open to everybody
and this is one of the nicest i went to uh the world economic form conference in uh
in Dallas uh Switzerland uh in 2000 and um this was one of the nicest things that they did there
now had i relied on you know making dinner plans with uh people that i knew uh at the conference
i would have eaten dinner alone every night um as i had in the early years of my career in the
computer industry where you know i wasn't necessarily you know i for many years i wasn't an 18
you know and people didn't necessarily want to eat dinner with me they were always kissing up and
trying to eat dinner with you know more famous or richer people and uh more influential people
and so very often i would be at these conferences um um you know first or second nights and have
absolutely nothing to do you know which was really ridiculous because um you know those are the
people that pay for the conference by the way the people who don't have anything to do on the
and of course buttercon is a is a free conference you don't have to pay to come to it but the
principles still stands in fact you know we we for more or less codified this we tried to
discourage people from having private events at the conference uh they do happen people will get
invited to uh you know sort of like invite only sorts of things uh and they don't invite me to
them anymore because i tell them forget it don't do it i won't go you know because i feel that
i'm trying to in in doing this conference to create um something that's kind of like the
blogged sphere where um anybody can set up a blog you don't need to be um sort of an industry
insider or an influential person or anything like it and as a result many of the really if you did
didn't many of the good blogs wouldn't exist um mine sure wouldn't exist i mean i'm not the kind
of guy the industry you know likes to turn to for um insider advice they they more or less like to
forget about me and um no which is why i played it don't come easy it's getting over it all right so
that's a bit from morning coffee notes and you'll be hearing a lot more uh on multiple podcast about
blogger con i'm sure of it i let a new podcast now it's the gator jug podcast
good morning this is Mike Levin this is your podcast from the swamp and uh we are here in beautiful
winter park florida on monday november first it's about six forty five a.m. the sun is just coming up
we don't have much debris left from the uh the um hurricanes that have hit but there's still a bit
in the streets it's the day before election day and uh i'm just back from beautiful Switzerland
my wife ran the double in marathon last week this is from the the poor brethren of the podcast
you've ever just gone monday that was a a lifelong dream of hers and i decided to meet her in Zurich
on Wednesday and then we had lunch in Milan for the weekend uh from florida to Switzerland and uh
enjoy a change of pace and uh climate and et cetera for a couple of days okay that's right
of the gator jug podcast there just want to let you know that there's all kinds of different voices
out there do a different things and of course now that i've got the production notes together you'll
be able to find the podcast feed directly uh from the post and uh this was it uh the some other
stuff we're working on uh uh uh that's too early to talk about that i don't know how to explain it yet
hit when that happens uh another promo uh people using openpodcast.org to uh to promote
their stuff which i think is a great idea i really like this open podcast idea of you know just a
place where you can either phone in uh or you can email a file i think it also email a url and point
to a file um very cool concept because it's kind of like the PR engine of podcasting uh and
i think there's room for many different ones you know there should be a podcast feed
that's for certain types of announcements you know it should it should be short things which
these openpodcast.org pieces are really interesting uh particularly uh when it came across uh
this promotional announcement hello world introducing some instale.net a place where you can find
music from Germany where your club can find informations about bands from Germany and we can find
some stuff from the internet check it out some estale.net it's spelled as a mm-e-l-s-t-e-l-l-e
uh fine German podcast with German music and i gotta tell you that the German
rock scene was always tripping out a little bit you know the just a whole the whole culture and the
whole vibe is a little bit different from uh from the states or maybe even any other year
you can definitely know cool little jingle there at the end actually i should look this up
uh because um i hung out with the scorpions uh remember they were really big uh uh what was uh
was the wind the river or what was it uh i can't remember the name of the song um but they did
something called the mascom music piece festival i should talk about a couple stories because i
went along with that that was an 88 i think um actually i i i'd put up a site one time uh which is
at mtv.curry.com where i had started uh this is when uh David first introduced me to directories and
i started putting a directory together um and i started you know just an alphabetical directory
there's some missing spaces but i was writing all the stories codifying what happened in the
at the mtv days and that you hear it is i'm i'm gonna read the story to you oh this is funny okay
holy shit um okay many a story this was posted um uh on oh wow how about this this was posted
on november second 2001 at 1259 p.m. damn so that was you know a year ago exactly whoa okay
i don't know this that there's a reason for that obviously let me read this to you many a story
must be told about the mascom music piece festival among the many attendees like aziyahs born
and bunjilvi were German rock gods scorpions shenker swans it my tale of aziyahs born you can read
parts of the incredible journey we made from Newark to Moscow you made a quick stop in Frankfurt to
pick up claustmina and the rest of the scorpions the scorpions were semi retired by then the drummer
was even living on a mountain top and monkey carlow so these guys were pretty used to the star
treatment star treatment was a far cry from the accommodations we were given in Moscow yes it was
the best hotel on town but they still had to turn on the hot water facility and that part of town
especially for us the beds were mattresses filled with straw though each room did have a tiny
black and white set with one channel running that I suppose with some government propaganda
this is before the wall came down so we were in the heart of communist russia in another story
i'll delve into how skid rose Sebastian Bach and i wound up hanging out with the masco chapter
the hell's angels a telephone was not a service considered standard in russian those days
there was one phone per floor on the hotel and operator physically sat by the phone and if a
call came in she would knock on your door to inform you that there was a call you take the call out
in the hallway at her at her little station subsequently making a phone call was even worse
you give the number to the phone lady who would schedule the call to be made the lag time between
scheduling the call and getting place was about six hours i guess the kgb wanted to ensure their
taps were in place later i hooked up with some cool guys from the westward one radio satellite
truck who would link their stuff so they had an actual 516 area code dial tone in the truck for
which let me use whenever i wanted to call home for those without such geek contact she
really had to stay in the neighborhood of the phone lady since she called might be put through
after only four hours of waiting time last thing you want was to miss her knock and have to
reschedule the call so i mean the hallway on the way to pick up a can of tuna fish from my room
one of the items on the list for everyone to bring when i noticed the phone lady is trying to
figure out where root off shanker is because it's called been placed and was waiting for him
now since the scourps axman wasn't in his room i figured i'd be a good dooby and try to find him
so i knocked on his brother's door which wasn't closed properly it's one open upon my knuckle
wrap to reveal root off sitting in a chair receiving a blow job from some germ if from some
Russian girl whoops phone call for you i closed the door and decided i didn't want the tuna fish
and that's it for the source code for today and her body
as i told you so if you're hearing this before you voted i'm sorry one more time please
go out and vote for John Kerry and uh i will bring you another dating source code tomorrow
from uh amceband at the end of the day and of course on Thursday probably when i land in
sentences now as always your comments and welcome i love the audio comments as much as you
can track over and look so i'm sure with it so send that to atomacore.com
or leave a comment on my weblog live.curry.com i'll post all of it
archives and the most recent shows available at dailysourcecode.com
and the podcast fingers there as well dating source code.com slash RSS.
action out.