Hey everybody, who listens to the Daily Source Code?
The Daily Source Code podcast.
It's for everybody.
Testing.
All's live.
Adam Curry.
Yeah.
Monday, everybody good afternoon.
I you're doing and welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Today is Monday.
It's December 6, 2004.
I'm out of curry coming to you from Curry Cottage in the United Kingdom.
That's right.
With a brand new set of new sounds.
And lots of reverb by special requests.
I'm not even going to get into the entire set up and exactly what I've changed.
But boy, a lot of thought went into it.
In fact, Patricia actually spent a lot of time with me coming up with the microphone sound.
It's pretty good.
In fact, it could be a hell of a lot worse.
You know, I could be at Starbucks right now.
That's how bad it could be.
That's interesting.
Still kind of working on the entire set up.
All the pieces and bits.
Everything that goes together.
It's all right here.
This is where users and developers party together.
And I kind of feel like a little bit of a developer.
If you look at the setup that I've got going here.
And part of the reason for this entire setup is
I've been catching some some flack about the sound.
The, you know, basically the big room that I had at the castle.
Some folks seem to actually miss the kind of echoey reverb thing.
And sometimes they even are pretty vocal about it.
Listen to this that came in on my iPod or just over the weekend.
Hey.
How are you?
Okay, how are you?
Very well.
So are we recording?
We are.
Okay.
So.
Oh, this is the sound of excitement in the background.
Yeah, exactly.
So what do you want to say?
Uh, I don't know.
I'm not a podcaster, you know.
So here we are.
You're not?
No.
Are you a podcaster?
Okay.
So we're not good at this off the coast all the way.
No.
We're not going to sit there and do a David Adam.
And did that our way?
No.
Okay.
So are we here?
Because Adam insists upon having some sort of a seat for his iPod or network.
Right.
All right.
So Adam.
This will have to do.
All right.
So, you know, one of those of you who haven't heard the last week show down low that one.
That was a show with Jonathan Schwartz, right?
Yeah.
It got a lot of good reviews except for people like, you know, who are concerned about,
how am I, big ego or HP?
Well, those complaints happen no matter what.
Yeah.
So I think it was a good show and I hope people will listen to all the way through because some of the stuff towards the end of some of the best as well.
All right.
The point about me, come on.
Get to me.
That's what the second I am.
Stephen, I'm great except.
Right.
Yeah.
Well.
Okay.
So what are we going to do next week?
We're going to try and do the full show next week, right?
Yeah.
We're going to try and record it on Monday.
But we'll have to leave that one for perhaps another little down low.
Okay.
We're good.
All right.
So let's hope everybody does go back.
Listen to last week's Gilmour Gang with Jonathan Schwartz, great show.
I know I will.
You know, I will too.
Okay.
When Friday rolls around, that's what I'm going to do.
Get to the part about me.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Let's hope he gets his broadband as of noon here on Thursday, which is when we're recording this.
Adam just said email that the British telecom people have not, no, whoever it is is not come through with his DSL line.
Not as this saying because, you know, there's just something different about the sound of this voice when he's got dial up.
Not the attention here.
It's the bit.
You know, he needs more reverb.
Yeah.
That's it.
There's something about that Mike changed that he's done.
It's just not right.
We missed the castle.
Well, I, you know, when the jury's out on the cottage.
But it doesn't really matter.
It's what, uh, Adam thinks.
That's true.
Oh.
Okay.
Steve, have a great weekend.
And we'll talk to you on Monday.
Okay.
Thanks for that.
So nice of you guys to be thinking of me.
And so nice to say that it sounds like shit now that I'm in the cottage.
So I've cranked up the reverb.
Make sure you guys got plenty of it.
Oops.
Sorry about that.
Still don't have the windscreen happening on the new microphone.
So I think we kind of got this vibe going.
You know, I've got the drum cadence now on the background.
This is the last time I played that drum drum line, the drum cadence.
I got so many responses that actually started up an email thread with Joel Hawksley.
He said, uh, actually I'll read this email to you.
Because I said it was really awesome.
A lot of people had commented on these cadences.
And I said, you know, how did you record it?
He says it turns out the file.
I sent you a record a while ago.
My friend Sony microphone and Sony mini disc recorder.
And, uh, what it is, he sent me another one.
And this is of our shoot.
What was this?
I think this is the Michigan Michigan State drum band.
Hold on, I'm trying to get my show notes to scroll up,
which apparently is going to be a problem today.
Let's see.
Yeah.
Come on everybody.
Oh, there we go. Okay.
Um, right.
So of course, doesn't tell me anything about that in the show notes.
Uh, before that, uh, as we opened up, you heard a little bit of, uh,
Steve Gilmore and Doug K.
Apparently there was no Gilmore gang to be recorded this week.
And, uh, so that you don't go running off and start checking your, uh,
your iPodder and, uh, your scripts to see if something broke.
You know, there actually just was no show recorded.
So hopefully they'll have one, uh, one up pretty soon.
Um, okay.
So this, oh, there we go.
Uh, street beats.
It's Florida State.
Florida State drum line.
The license is non-R-I-A-A.
Why did these cats crank?
Check it out.
I love that.
No, I used to love it.
I really used to love it when, um, when they'd be doing a, um, a parade.
And then they'd walk by and they'd do, um,
the theme from entertainment tonight.
Have you ever heard of a high school or college drum band
or the theme to entertainment?
Uh, anyway, I'm kind of getting into drum, uh, drum band.
Uh, should we be concerned about me?
Possibly.
Good morning and welcome to today's podcast for December 3rd, 2004.
This is a brief daily offering of words for the wise and the other wise.
Today's words from an article Adam Curry read on his abbreviated daily source code.
The article by Felicity Lawrence is a wake-up call for the Western world's food
humorous.
The way we eat is not just ecologically unsustainable,
but also morally and even biologically unsustainable.
The word is profligate.
Let's listen.
Food is flown around the world to meet the supermarkets requirements for just in time ordering.
Their demand for cosmetic perfection and a perpetual glow.
In case you had noticed, this is, uh, basically me, um,
fucking up the read that I did on, uh, what was it, um,
what was I supposed to get my broadband? Was that, um, on the first of December?
So that was, was that Wednesday, I think?
When I, when was I really pissed off?
Yeah, something like that.
And then instead of doing a daily source code,
I'd read this article from the Guardian,
which I've actually linked to on ipodder.org.
And I couldn't get this, this word right.
Well, you'll, you'll hear it.
We'll summer can be met by producers only if they use agrochemicals intensively
and allow for a, uh, prof, uh, a big fucking word,
degree of waste.
A third of Kenyan green beans are thrown away because they are the wrong size or shape.
Prophligate.
PRO, FLI, G-A-T-E.
Volume is an adjective that, in this context,
means recklessly wasteful, wildly extravagant.
It can also be used as a noun to describe a profligate person.
Adam, I want to thank you for reading this editorial to us.
I think you and Felicity draw much needed attention to the very serious problem.
Um, hope all of your listeners read this article and hope a few of mine do too.
You can find a link to this article as well as Adam's reading of it at today's podcast.com.
Please email me with questions.
Scott at today's podcast.com or send me a voice mail at 435-514-4859.
Thanks for listening and please tell your friends about podcast.
Yeah, right on.
Okay.
Thank you very much Scott.
Send me straight there.
Profligate.
I can do that.
And it's good to know what words mean once in a while.
Profligate.
So we're sitting here in my new office in the castle.
A couple things still wrong with it.
I've got this beautiful desk that's antique desk that's Louis the 14th desk.
But my chair doesn't fit under it.
I guess the Louis guys were really small back in the Louis the 14th day.
So I kind of like my knees are banging against the bottom of the desk.
So we've got to figure a way to raise that up to give me a little more.
A little more breathing room perhaps would be good.
And as you can hear, I'm still using the new mega mic, the the sure SM7.
I've got my reverb set up, Steve, and Doug, hope you like that.
So I get a little bit of that castle vibe regardless of the size of the room these days.
And even though I still don't have my broadband and you know,
I'm so past the pissed off stage.
I'm just kind of rolling with the flow on all of that.
I've kind of relearned how much I love the concept of enclosures.
And the whole iPod or concept because basically what I've done now is I've thrown out all my subscriptions completely.
All I have is just basically the pod squad that I subscribe to.
And of course link to the pod squad is on the production notes for today's show.
And I only have that download the minute I go to bed.
So actually the computer wakes up at 2 a.m. at 2 a.m. at wakes up.
And the first thing it does, it fires up iPodder.
And it goes off and downloads the pod squad.
So pretty much every single day I've been lucky enough to have all of the all the files sitting there waiting for me.
Because it's not so much that the bandwidth is slow.
Because you know, some some podcasts really because they're so crunched just by so many people
requesting the MP3 files. They come in pretty slow as is.
The problem with not having the bandwidth is that you can't multitask.
You can't download two things at the same time.
Because that really of course is just no bandwidth.
So it's not so much that's about the speed of stuff coming in.
But it's about being able to do multiple simultaneous parallel processes.
Like get your email at the same time check a web page.
So I'm shifting all that stuff off into the middle of the night.
So actually where I was telling you to please send me just a link to an MP3 file instead of an attachment.
I'm back now to attachments.
Please, if you're sending me something, if you're sending me a promo to your podcast and I love playing people's promos.
Send it to me as an attachment.
As long as it fits within, I think it's three or five megs that my email server allows in.
Because that, you know, basically I just look at the headers and look at the body of the messages.
And at night once again, I say go out and cash all of all of the attachments.
So by the time I'm up and we're going to bed late, you know,
I'm we're going to bed around 1 a.m. for some reason.
Of course, we're seeing a still isn't in school.
Hopefully this coming week looks like she'll be able to start and boy,
she really wants to start.
This is a great kid.
She's like, I want to go to school.
I'm so bored.
So I then will obviously be going to bed a little bit more in a more timely fashion.
Probably before midnight.
So there's a good nine hours, you know, of just time for the computer to do what's work.
And it's really not that bad.
What sucks, of course, is when someone says, hey, check this out.
And I can't do that in real time.
I can't really do Skype calls.
I can, but the Skype calls like four or five second delay.
So, in fact, what I'm going to suggest today,
if now that he more or less has his voice back,
I'm going to ask if he'll do a trade secrets with me later this week.
And what we're going to do is we're going to do a double ender,
the way Don and Drew taught us.
So Dave will basically record on his end.
I'll record on my end.
We'll have a communication like a phone.
Probably, I think that'll be the best one,
phone to communicate.
And we'll both record our individual sides.
We'll slap those two bits together.
And we'll have a trade secrets and boys time for one.
So much has happened.
A lot of email, a lot of cool links to non-RIA-based music,
which, of course, is what we try to play most of here on the daily source code.
For instance, and again, all of these emails that I'm reading to you,
all that information is in the podcast show notes,
email from Joshua.
Josh on the train, actually, who's listened to the source code on the train
and it's called me about that before.
He says, a thought here.
Non-RIA music should be freer, freer, freer,
F-R-E-F-R-I-A-A,
which stands for F-R-I-A-A, freer, freer,
I don't know Josh.
I think we've got to work on that.
I don't know if that's going to work.
Some freer music that we have been playing,
that I played a couple times, is the lascivious bitis.
Bittisforever.com is their website.
Excuse me, and I've had kind of an ongoing email conversation
with Leanne from the lascivious bitis.
And what was really nice is, she sent me an email,
and she said, I want you to know,
we've sold a ton of CDs,
and have gotten much more fan mail than usual
after your podcast of the list of these bitis.
We've done plenty of radio and TV,
and I think the only other thing that got people going
like that was when we did the Bobby Flasho
on the Food Network.
All right, we're up there.
Podcasting equals Food Network.
Hey, the Food Network's all right.
And I haven't had the courage actually
to ask what a ton of CDs means,
but just the fact that by playing someone's band
on the daily source code that people are going out
and buying that CD.
They're probably buying it from the website.
I cannot tell you how good that makes me feel.
It's the same thing with Leanne Wilkins,
who we'll talk about later on in the show.
And Jenny, they're two dogs.
You've probably heard this from the Friday podcast,
where I basically had him on the show,
and he's trying to get his dogs out of jail.
In Atlanta, I total fuck up,
and he's really just too much money for them to cough up.
I spoke to him this morning,
already they had like $700,
and it was so incredibly cool that people don't know.
I mean, people are doing $10,
$20, $25 to help them out.
And really, I cannot tell you how much I appreciate that.
And most people really understood the,
the issue and really understood what it means to have
your dogs in jail, basically.
And the people really understood it donated quite generously,
and that's so incredibly nice.
And what it tells me is that,
hey, wait a minute, we have a business model.
We have an absolute fucking business model for podcasting.
I know how to make other people money.
That's what I know.
I know how to make those serious bitties money.
I know how to make money for worthy causes.
That's a real serious business model that we cannot overlook.
And quite honestly, I'm pretty fucking proud.
I was sitting to Adam Curry show last week,
the Tuesday show,
and I was surprised to hear him play Battalica.
Battalica are a band that take Battalica as a sort of a style,
and then take the riffs and the backing music of the Beatles,
in this case it was, hey, Jude,
and sort of mash them together.
He introduced it as a mashup,
although mashups are usually working with a crawled at works.
And in this case, I would call it more of a live mashup.
So I thought it'd be interesting to play a band that I know of in San Francisco,
called Smashup Derby, who are actually doing live mashups.
They're doing these actually live,
and actually playing events,
whereas Battalica, a very secretive,
and friends I know only do recordings.
So, here they are taking Franz Ferdinand,
mixing it with talking heads. I'll see what you think.
By the way, this is pretty fucked up, chef.
But I think you're like it.
This is not my people house,
make a good show, this is not my people house,
make a good show,
make a good show, make a good show,
make a really good show,
make a good show,
making a good show,
Too dramatic to jump
I'm back for a bit, let it get out
Burn it down the house for a tight
We're doing the party cover, hold tight
We're in for a naps, you wear those
Let us go to the party
Burn it down the house
So we should keep your fact to pass
It's times for jumping over the board
Trust me, tasty and secure
Closing up but not too far
Maybe you know as you are
Fight your fire required
Oh, hey, you might need a break down, shake down
Keep up in rockin' light, free, hunt, train, stay by the breeze
Burn it down out, not out, so I don't want to hear it
Next life, don't wanna hurt them all, it's something sure
Can't be me, all five feet
Burn it down the house
I don't wanna believe in you
I know I won't believe in you
With you
Same as it ever goes
Burn it down the house
That was talking friends by SmashUp Derby
Now if you want to find out more about SmashUp Derby
They have their websites, which is at www. SmashUp Derby.com
That's Derby or the need Derby as in Derby and Joan
Now I love that song, I love the idea of sort of mashing things
That were live, because so often I'm messing around in acid
Or not on acid, I mean in acid the problem
And actually trying to get things to work
And you can do so much more with a real band
And of course Adrian and Matti C are both involved with
The club in San Francisco
So they're quite heavily involved in the bootleg scene
And it's really nice to sort of hear something that's sort of live
And something that's quite dynamic like that
And I would love to see them alive at some point
Shit
Let me just explain what happened
Can you take this question there?
Oh, cool
But I want that, I don't want a free mouse pad, I want my mouse
By mouse and Matt
Okay, so I was so enthusiastic about that live mashup
That essentially in my entire cup of tea
Spilled all over the desk, all over the Louis 14
The Louis Qatar's
Shit
And Christina was nice enough to get me a big roll of paper towel
It didn't spill on the keyboard
Fuck, all over the desk, all over the breakout box
Over the mouse pad
Christina
Okay
All right
Okay, so sometimes shit just sucks
Let me see what can I do with like continue to clean up here
Listen to the sports pod, okay?
Yeah, you'll enjoy that
Oh, it's fun, who goes crazy
Down goes crazy
Oh, it's fun
I don't believe what I just thought
And check the ball
Oh, it's fun
You believe in miracles
Yeah
Okay, we're going to the sports pod for Friday
December 2,000 and four
Sports pod on demand through pod task technology
I'm good, it's talking to you at 9
Yeah, yeah, it's just a good time
And I want to hear from you
Tech that voice emails
Go to
Curtis
At these sports pod
Okay, so basically I just wanted to give you a little
Just a little bit of promo there about the sports pod
I didn't want to play the whole thing for you. Okay
Hold on, let me just reset the microphone
Okay, that's better
There we go
Shoot
I hate that
So rocking, man
I was like totally jamming out to that mashup
And then it's like this huge cup
It's not like a little teensy weeny
You know, a little wanky tea cup
It's a big, I love my pony coffee cup
You know, and the whole thing
I just like, I think my headphone
Wire caught on it or something
Oh, man, totally sucked
Okay, you're still tuned into the daily source code
Madam Curry coming to you from the United Kingdom
We're in Guildford
And it disclosed cottage location
And
I'm still getting lots of email about
You know, UK culture and who invented what?
Another email here from
Let's see
I would this email come from
Oh man, it's a long email
That's for sure
Okay, well, can I even tell who the email is from
But the gist of the email is
Inventors of the TV
Remember we were talking about this on a previous source code
Well, it's a tie
Okay, Adam, you won't remember me
But I love when people start off the emails to me like that
Adam, you won't remember me
However
Oh, a number of years ago
When you needed assistance with your power book
At Media Plaza
I was the new Mac headed American webmaster there
Of course I remember
So whoever said that low-key barred was the inventor of the television
Only told you part of the truth apparently
You see it's a little more complicated than that
Barred invented a technique for television
Referred to his mechanical television
And publicly display that in 1924
Now what it is, it used huge hungs of wood
And a spinning disk kind of like a flat
Zoatrop to collect the image
Oh, there's all kinds of links to this shit
So at the same time in 1923
In 1923
A first up towards electronic television
Developed into today's cathode rate
Toot patented in 1924
And he called it at the time
The kinoscope
Meanwhile in 22 in the town of Rigby, Idaho
Philo T. Farnsworth, the high school science teacher
With no history of electronics
Engineering sketched his design
For electrical engineering
Toot and the high school science teacher
With no history of electronics
Engineering sketched his design
For electrical engineering
Design for electronic television
The model we used today
So you've got to go through this email
It's in the podcast show notes
It's just it continues to bugle my mind
How you grow up
Depending on where you grow up
Thinking that certain people
Usually of your own country, origin and culture
Discovered certain things
And when you really get down to it
There seems to be some dispute about stuff
Some people say, well
Yeah, it depends on how you look at it
So check that out in the podcast show notes for today's
DailySource Code
Which can find on dailySourcecode.com
Hey Adam, hope you're settled in at the Prairie Cottage
Well, yeah kind of
Patricia said yesterday
She said, we finally unpacked
It doesn't mean we're completely settled
But we're unpacked
I just wanted to go and tell you a few things
One struggle comments
Love in your show
You can work ass
Maybe back in MTV
Didn't see her for a while
And I'll get them not seen you now
But definitely hearing a loud and clear
Thanks
Number two
I got a little behind on my podcasts
And so I thought I'd just listen to them
Oh man, this sounds kind of crappy
What are you using?
On the plane ride
Well, I was listening to one of your podcast
And it was you on a plane
On your way to Amsterdam
And that's where I was headed to
Just a little funny deja vu
I guess that's the word for it
And number three
I've seen one of you talking about
The idea of being able to do podcasts
From like your iPod
Thought I'd let you know
That there is a non iPod alternative
Okay
Hard to I've played
Not like the little yups
It's the I River
I HP
So
And I'm doing it from that
Actually, I think I ordered one of those
And are you recording it on the on the I River?
Damn
I hope it's
I wonder what the is it like
32k or is it 64k?
You need to
Wait, that maybe I can see that
From the info on the file
Let's see
Oh
Data rate
4.8k
Bites per second
Ah
Okay
That explains the quality
So
If you think it sounds like crap
Maybe it's not good for you to use
But does have a digital
And a analog
Lines and line out
It's pretty nice tool
Okay, that's it
Just wanted to go
And main point was
Thank you for the killer cast
Oh man
Degadise
No, you don't have to thank me
Thank you
Boy or only
Thank you all so very much
More on the source code now
Um
Let's listen to the latest Don and Drew
Uh show
And a couple things
First of all, it turns out
They're banned in Finland
Apparently
Uh one or multiple
Finish ISPs no longer
Allow access to the Donandrew.com
Man those fins, you know
There's there
They're so politically correct
Don't try and show a nipple in Finland
Either everybody
But Dons get really pissed about all this press
That they're getting
And basically, and this happens all the time
With people who are married
You know, they'll kind of
Assume or presume
Certainly the press will assume that you have
Your husband's last name
So
So she's being quoted as
Don Dunkus
So it's Drew
Dunkus
And Don Miss Sally
And she's getting pissed
And we got to watch out, you know
Journalists out there
Because you know she's going to stop
She's getting into a half
And then you show a puff off
And she
And she won't want to do any more podcast
So we got to be careful
Don Miss Sally
It's Don Miss Sally
Everybody
And
There's something else that I don't
Don't have a queue up for you
But there's something that Don says
In, uh, let's see
That is the December second podcast
So the Don and Drew show
Where she says something
There's been haunting my mind
For the longest time
Because it works
You know in order to stop smoking
And I'm talking about evil smoke
Right cigarette smoke
Let's just forget all other types of smoke
For the time being
You have to have some kind of incentive
Death is a good one
That works for a lot of people
It's really hard to stay off smoking
And I guess for me
The worst part is
In the Netherlands
If you go by a
Prefabricated split
They basically mix the
Marijuana with tobacco
And that's not good
It tastes really good
I got to tell you that
It tastes wonderful
And I can dream about that
But I can't have it
I can't have it
Because I'm an addict
I am a
Nicotine addict
And if I have one of those
Then I basically fall off the wagon
And then I want to smoke again
And Don said something to me
At a blogger con
Hey, hon
Hello
Can I help you?
No, no, no
It only spilled on the Louis Cetsware desk
Oh, shit
It did spill on the carpet
Yes
Fuck
It was this whole thing spilled
I'm sorry
I didn't even see it on that
Yeah, that was a bonfire
It's just a little bit
Will that come out?
A T
No, a T won't come
It's like pain
Hold on
We can't hear you
We used to die
Are underwear in there
In T
You're underwear?
Yeah, if you want to have sort of
Well, who's going to see underwear?
Skin collar underwear
Well, sometimes you need it under
Under something that's a little bit
Yeah, see you
See you through
So you wear something
Wait everybody
Here's clothing tips from Patricia
You put it in the T
Well
You can now wear my carpet
You can steep it a little bit
And then after we're afterwards
You got beautiful skin color
Underwear
But it's not good on the carpet
No
That's not good
That's not going to come out
Is it?
That's going to suck
Ah
It's probably already in there
Oh yeah, it's already leaking
Down towards the very good
I did a good job, huh?
Yeah
I did a good job
Stepping on it with my big boots
You know, and I was in the shower
I took a nice and relaxed shower
I didn't do anything
Nothing
Nothing, dear
Okay, thank you
I'll continue with my show now
Love you, mean it
Bye
So Dawn
Let's get back to Dawn for a second
My other wife
She
She said something that haunted me
And it just works so well as an incentive
And I've been to Amsterdam in the meantime
She said
Smoking cigarettes
Smoking tobacco
Is like sucking on
The man's dick
The man being the man
Not a man, but the man
And she says it again in that podcast
December 2nd podcast
I'm going to have to drag that up
Because it's going to work for other people
I really will
When you hear the way she says it, it's just like
Whoa, you know, and it makes so much sense
Because totally, you know, like you're being addicted
And it's, you know, and it's
They're putting shit in there to keep you addicted
Okay, so anyway, just want to
Just want to say hi to my other wife Dawn
And more helpful hints from around town
People trying to help me out
With my ADSL problems
I actually posted it pretty long
Outline of
What's gone wrong and what my options are
And it will get fixed obviously, but it's just
It's a pain, you know, two weeks without
Any type of real connectivity sucks
People who have been there can feel my pain
But I got a great comment
Again on the podcast show notes
Here's all you have to do
Step one, get a shovel
Step two, dig around until you find a trunk line
Step three, tap into the green blue yellow
And move white stripe wires
Number four, run those to an RJ 45
On pins 1, 2, 3, 6
And then plug into your switch
Plug into your switch in the house
And then cover everything with dirt
Maybe a couple of ferns
And you're good to go
I'm like, uh-huh
Yeah, I want to dry that
Seriously, there are some of those options
That are pretty similar, there's the SDSL
I mean, I'm getting a real education
Different ways you can get connected to the internet
When I'm hoping most will happen
Just for a short interim is this WDSL
Which is wireless DSL
Which is should be hearing about today
So perhaps more on the podcast tomorrow
And see a gaff
Which means a fuck up on my part high Adam
Says Tim Biedle
Really enjoying your show
Especially your experiences adjusting to UK life
So many things we take for granted
And also I'm sorry I do that again
Take on new meaning when we see it through the eyes of a stranger
There you go
Just one thing though
BBC SCR does not stand for South Coast radio
As I said, I was really in my American mode
I guess it stands for Southern Counties radio
Love your cockney accent
Better than Dick Van Dykes
I feel so incredibly special
Time for another promo
If you have any promos that you want to air it on a daily source code
Which basically just kind of promotes your podcast
Happy to play them
The more creative, the better obviously
Just email them to atamercurry.com
Hey podcast world, this is Greg
And Lisa
And we want to tell you about a great new podcast
Coming to you from the Deserts of New Mexico
It's called Viva podcast
So for more information visit us
at vivapodcast.com
That's vivapodcast.com
Adios
Right on
The vivapodcast vivapodcast.com
I don't know if you know who a peeper del is
Pete is actually the guy who I think I don't
And Drew started on podcasting
It's all his fault
He responded to the guardian article
Actually he talked about a lot about
I call him produce Pete now
About how he cooks
A lot of people took this article to heart
They were really thinking about
What are we stuffing into our face these days
And what are we eating and where is it coming from
And how is it being produced and how is it being processed
And shoot, it's kind of scary
Just food is basic
If we can get past this idea of putting
Burning tobacco in our face
We should certainly look at
At all the other things we stuff in there
Dawn
No, what I mean girl
Here's Pete with the rastery body
This is rastery body of four
Well, oh two
So why did the British guy
Bring two of hookers into his robot
Someone told him he needed a pair of arms
He said
Thank you
And good night
People are living
Rastery body
That is the show for December 2nd 2004
This is the daily source code
I'm out of curry coming to you from the curry cottage in the UK and lovely
Guildford and sorry
And not far from here
Todd Maffin was in Berlin
Looking for the Berlin Wall
I've got to play a bit of this because this is like the tower of
Where
And you have to listen to this whole thing
I've put a link to the show
Well, just listen to a bit of it
And then we'll explain what happens
Hi, I'm Todd Maffin
Thanks for tuning into the iLoveReadyow.org podcast
Today we are coming to you from Berlin Germany
And my goal today is to find
The Wall
Or what's left of the Berlin Wall anyway
Which I understand is not very much
But I'm
Basically in the wander around the streets
The Concierge is pointed me toward the right
Which
Good as the instructions as he was able to give me
So I'm going to walk along here and
Follow along as we try and find the wall
So besides I'm the kick-in
John Lymus
He listened to the cab driver
I think this is it
Oh, who is this English?
We're going to terminate
Do you speak English?
Hello
No, but I'm going to kick your ass
You fucking American
Can you tell me how to find the wall?
I wonder if did the
Todd, you have to let us know
Did you have like a big fucking microphone while you're doing this?
Hi, I'm a fucking American tourist
Do you know where the fucking wall is?
The wall, what's left of the wall?
The wall? What's left of the wall?
The wall?
It's not here.
Okay, we're in food
And
You see the mirror?
Is he the mirror right here?
He's 50 meters here
How many euros is that for you to take me?
Okay, now this is the beautiful part
The cab driver says
And I'm good at this
Because I've lived in Europe
Most of my life
The cab driver is having a real hard time explaining
But he's saying it's only like 50 meters from here
And Todd says, how many euros will it cost to get me there?
Now, 50 meters is about, you know, 55 yards
Basically
So this whole podcast and you have to listen to this
Because it's hilarious
And I can just imagine him walking around
With this big ass microphone
Asking people where the wall are
And they're like, oh, the fucker
It's like right there
That's where it was
So of course he finds out
In the end that he really only had to walk
Like, you know, half a football field to get there
But an excellent podcast
And I'm considering moving
I love radio
The podcast into the comedy section
Because it's just really, really good
All right, time for some free music
This, let's see, I played
Something a while ago
From, let's see, what was it?
From chosen
I think it was chosen
And I got a whole email
Going on with
The manager
Or the actually the management and marketing guy
Who does this for these bands
And you just have to read the email
To get all the background on it
Sent me another song
And I think this is the right one
I don't know if I have the right track queue
I'm so frazzled now with all this tea
Spilling all over the carpet
Here's a track from
Remained to one, our artist
He says, let me know what you think
The track is called I Candy
I was blessed with an angel from the heavens above
But like cooling a gang
I cherished the love
I thought the grass was green
We was like Rick James and Tina
So we let things come between us
Look how you ended it
Little friends were friends better fits
So chill west was so innocent
I ain't going shed no tears
Can't get my money back on top
Spin all those years
Wasn't home all the time
But always there
Not a picture that you painted
It's crystal clear
Same looks as deceiving
You left without a reason
Quickly change like the season
Now I'm still breathing
You can't break me
You'll make me never do things
Was they shaky
Clear the take me quite some time
Cause everybody knows how I can find
I want nothing fancy
Just a piece of eye candy
Can I get a glimpse of that
I'll kiss you Spanish
Wait a black just one
He said, I can't
I want nothing fancy
Just a piece of eye candy
Can I get a glimpse of that
I'll kiss you Spanish
Wait a black
Just one little taste of that
I can't
What would it not give for
One more taste
One more shot
I'm talking about
One more chase
And I ain't blind
Could up on your lies
How you should grow
Friends is you have the boss
Which we could go to distance
To get chance to try to listen
Now we knocked out a position
My heart would lower you
You was just for you
Get some stuff into
That's why I never told you
Don't let this damn me
I can't be
We could have both been a family
I'm not sure what's going on
I'm going to let you play
For another time
It keeps crapping out
That's no good
I don't know what's up with that
I've heard that her up on a couple of times
Was it with MP3's
Okay
I can't you will get to that
Another time in the source code
Hope you didn't put the automatic
Three minutes skip in there
Because now you probably missed this
Bit and you're already off into
Something else
I got to remember
What was this?
Was this the last Starbucks podcast
I guess that must have been
Must have been Fridays
I was trying to get a hold of Lee Wilkins
Wilkins to talk about his dogs
And I was looking for some
Dialing music and I just basically hit the first thing
That came up in iTunes
And it was a king of the road
By was it Roger Miller
And I came up with this
With a little lyric
Which was Prince of the pod
And of course you got to figure
Someone wrote lyrics to it
Kim Black did a great job
She says
I'm no songwriter
But here it is
And and I for a long time I thought
You know what I'm going to do with this
I should maybe I should
Maybe I should try and do something
Do a song
Patricia hates it when I sing
And she's right
Because you know it's like I can't sing
I really cannot sing
I suck at singing
And if you really do know how to sing
Like she does then
You know that's like painful
And by the way I think most
These jockeys
Really are frustrated singers
Or performers
And whenever
You'll notice this
Whenever DJs
Radio DJs
Have a chance
To sing
They jump right in boy
They love singing
And I have to admit
I have some of that
Not what's not a frustration
But I don't know what to do
I think
Most of it's just the whole process
Of putting a song together
That is fascinating
Because when you're DJ
You're already into sound
You're into
Into mixing boards
You know just put
Really your it's in life
It's performance art
It's just what podcasting is
So
When I saw the lyrics
I said well you know all I really need
And I have garage band
And you know I should be able to
I thought no I can't do that
Because I don't know how to
Fucking play
Yeah
I studied piano for two years
But no way
Am I going to be able to
Even figure out how to do
King of the Road
By the way the piano
Was still sitting in the empty castle
Life
If you want a piano
Let me know
I need to sell it
Or I have to send it somewhere
Within two weeks
So it's going to be safe
Anyway so
Why not
And Google for
For a MIDI version of King of the Road
And I actually found something
That was
Let me see
Sequenced
By
Here comes
I'm playing for you now
Harry Todd
I put a link to these original
Page in there as well
And I listen to this
So yeah
That's kind of like
Harps Accord
Like
I like that
If I'm going to do this
I'm going to do it right
Now what I found is
There's a way to
Take a MIDI file
And through another little program
Which I forget what it's called
Montemedi
Something like that
I mean you could just
Search Google for
Import MIDI into Garage Band
Because Garage Band
Doesn't do it natively
For some reason
So you take this MIDI file
Drag it onto this application
And it does all kinds of magic
And it creates a folder for you
And in that folder
Is all the instruments in separate files
And you drag that into a Garage Band
Song and new project
And low and behold
It gives you all these tracks
In this case it had like ten tracks
And it gave me the opportunity
To then go and select
Different instruments
Because I wanted to
I already had the score
Right
But I needed
I just needed a little more
And just some kick and stuff
A little heavier bass
And some guitars in there
And I'll shut up
And you know
Well, see for yourself
Cast your phone
See your rent
Cut it just left
For 50 cents
No Wi-Fi
And almost no mess
And John
Look, girl
No cigarettes
So that
Two hours of
And whatever money
Makes me a podcast
The personality of a man
A means by no means
Friends of the park
Podcasting
Not show
Destination
How the hell should I?
Don't go now
For the jokes
I'm paying my empty views
I smoke
All sinkies
A one or two
If I can quit
Hey, boy
A silken
You're one of
My enemies
By no means
Friends of the park
I know everything
Podcasting
Everybody
All of them girls
And some other
And other
So other
And...
Anyone
They
And on Christmas
Andboy
Two hours of head to the weather up all night. It makes me a podcast of personality
Okay, Prince of the Pod, everybody. This will never air again and no, I'm not going to put up an MP3
No
Just did it because people were so nice to do the lyrics and
And basically so nice to put a MIDI file up there and share and so I thought I'd share something back. Don't you love it?
Good and interesting comment came in from Bill Kennedy from
Indianapolis who of course followed the Lee will Lee and Jenny
Story of their of their two, you know, they're two beautiful little doggies who have been caught up in the airline and quarantine
Hell and he had an interesting idea. I said
Couldn't a podcast listener in Atlanta get the dogs out of the kennel hold them for
For Lee and Jenny until they get all the money
To get them back to United Kingdom
In fact, they also could you know if they could find like a really good you have family
Because he has the way it works basically you have to the animals have to have a rabies shot
Forget all the other stuff the passport and the chip and the neck but they have a rabies shot and then they have to wait for
Six months before they can enter the United Kingdom. So six months after the rabies shot
I presume they've probably had that rabies shot by now and they've probably so it's about like a week or two
Maybe just a full week
But they would have to stay in the states for another six months. Maybe there's a really great family who would want to
You know take care of them instead of
Bring them over to the United Kingdom and curing huge costs. I think it's for two dogs
It'll probably be about five thousand dollars for the six months. They have to stay in quarantine. I'm not kidding you about this
And you know sure you can visit them, but they're basically in jail. You know, so it's just a thought anyway
But again really cool that everyone has helping out on at least getting something going and getting it back
to the UK
If it all possible within the next way have another ten days to go or something
Another email I wanted to share with you. Hi Adam. I've been listening to the daily source code for a few weeks
I've been following the growth of podcasting
My addiction to podcast will have to stop cold turkey for a while since I was strong armed and my
iPod was stolen this evening while yes, indeed listening to your star-bucky and Skype adventures on the daily source code
Incidentally says this occurred on a quiet street in Residential Menlo Park about two miles away from the blogger
on three location at Stanford University. This is freaking me out
It goes into explaining exactly how this happened. This is will by the way
And it's horrible. He was walking along with his iPod
He said actually a realize later must have been following me because I was unaware
And couldn't hear anything over the exciting beat of the rockman enough, which of course is the power of your intellect
And they basically grabbed the iPod ripped you know ripped it right off of right off of them
Kind of ripping the headphones out and boom took off with that. So, you know
Menlo Park
Sox
Sorry about that dude. I'm really sorry. Oh good news
The new Jay Potter is out. Jay Potter is an iPod are variant. It's based on Java, so it works
On anything that will run Java, at least that's the promise of Java, right?
Couple of new features in that though, and the thing that I like the most is
The vacation switch
Oh, so I'm just trying to look at a different email here. I was talking about this
On the source code. I might even post it something about it on on my weblog is
When you have a loss of connection for a couple days. You could be on vacation or
Like me you could be without bandwidth when you go to start you know syncing up with your shows
iPod or is going to bring in everything. Every single iPod has done this to date
It'll go and try and bring in every single show that that you've missed and what we need is some more
Intelligent content management and Jay Potter as well as
What is that the bottom feeder something that I found
Through email
Actually, it's on Apple's website Apple was had a link to it
If then soft.com
Also has this feature and you know, it's it's great to see that
You know, we're we're helping me help and a brother out need who has like no fucking bandwidth
What's this in the daily source code comment?
What are we? We're like 55 minutes shoot. It's gonna be an hour long show
That's for sure. Let's check out the comment
Yeah, this is Kurt from Minnesota first off. Thank you for podcasting in the daily source code
I really enjoyed listening to it well just about every day
Right now I had downloaded it onto my i-book and I'm sitting in a car in a parking ramp in herndon Virginia
And what you would talked about with regards to
All nations which I'm like right please. Please tell me
You have your pants on
Rank true in my situation. I have no bandwidth during the day and then I've got great bandwidth at night
And I thought would really be great as a feature instead of having you have a vacation switch
Is have a bandwidth slider
So you can slide it all over do. I've got nothing no net to I've got dial up in which case it'll prioritize what it downloads up to
I've got my normal full net set up so just a thought
I thought I'd voice it as a as a sound file here. I'm using garage band for the first time and it's kind of an interesting experience
Turning off like the metronome and some other things, but anyway, it was just my thought up for a feature
I thought that would be more useful than something that just toggles on and off for vacation
Anyway again, thanks for daily source code and keep at it. It sounds great. Yeah, that's a good idea
So that's actually a very good interface
So oh, yeah, just say okay, right now I have X bandwidth and it's gonna make decisions based upon your bandwidth
What to do that would be really cool. I don't know how you set it up if that's a
Pre-determined matrix that we come up with or if that's something you can you should always be able to configure it yourself
But good idea
very cool very cool
It's I was like he's sitting in this in the parking lot in the car
You know, what is he doing there? Is he hijacking someone's Wi-Fi or jacking something else?
You know, we got to get out of here. It's almost time it's almost an hour for this show and and I'm
I have so much to do well tomorrow
I already have tomorrow show almost planned and when I look at it this way
I'm gonna leave you with a little piece that was sent to me by
Well, I can't tell you who sent it to me because he basically broke the wall by sharing this with me
And it's definitely I'm breaking the law too. I'm gonna play it play it for you. It's a classic
I'm gonna end the show with this so don't wait for the rock money off power up your intellect
I'm just gonna play the last minute of this song
Please listen to the foresight that these genius musicians had and I what I mean songwriters producers musicians
Genius when they wrote this and they recorded this they knew that one day
podcasting would be for ever body