How are you, everybody? Good afternoon. Welcome to the Daily Source Code for Dan. Thursday, October
14th, 2004. This is the low bandwidth edition of the show because I've been cut off by
my provider. I'm back to 56K so I'll probably upload it at a gas station somewhere.
Either that or I've waited until past midnight when my bandwidth quota drops down below
it's 30 to eight, 30 gig levels. So the show is no problem. Creating the show is pretty
easy today but actually getting it up on the server and getting everything published is a
little bit more challenging. Regardless today, thank god I was able to get some stuff
with iPod overnight before the bandwidth cut off and I'll talk about that a little bit later on.
We got a viewer's final listener response from Australia. We've got some news about
St. Helens. We've got listener response from Japan and a history of the commercial internet.
And because I've been so low on on pipe in the past, it was the past 10 hours. It's now three
in the afternoon. This is coming to you from Curry Castle in Flanders. I had a lot more chance
to catch up on email and check out some core respondents and I really have to say,
it's been so nice. All of the work that we've done together, developers and people who are just
podcasting. So here's a song for you guys for everyone who's been helping out with this really fun
movement. Thank you for being a friend. Travel down a road and back again. Your heart is true.
You're a pal and a confidence. I'm not ashamed to sing. I hope it always was day to sway.
My head is all focused and up and take a bow.
And get you through a party invited everyone you knew. We you won't see the biggest difference
for me and the card attached would say thank you for being a friend. Thank you for being a friend.
Thank you for being a friend. Thank you for being a friend.
If it's a car you lack, I truly buy you a car lack. Whatever you need in a time of the day
and night. I'm not ashamed to sing. I hope it always was day to sway. My head is all focused and up and
take a bow. And when we both get older, with walking keys and hair away, I'm your fear even though
it's hard to hear. I will stay in your clothes and say thank you for being a friend.
Thank you for being a friend. Thank you for being a friend.
And when we go and come away into the night, when we'll be late, you'll be gone
as we get to sway. Thank you for being a friend.
Thank you for being a friend. Thank you for being a friend.
Thank you for being a friend.
Thank you. Thank you for being a friend.
Andrew Gold, for all the iPod or developers and all the podcasters parting with us today on
the source code. Thank you for being a friend. Isn't that just a sweet song?
So this is the source code for Thursday, October 14, 2004. You probably saw the posting on my
weblog if not. Here's what happened or what has happened in the past and I thought I was over this
with my internet provider here in Belgium. The good news about living in a castle is that you live
far away from everybody and you've got just nature surrounding you. And of course that's also
the bad news because that means that ADSL is not possible. We're too far from the head office.
Now we do have cable mode from tailonet.be and oops. It's me wifey poo. Hold on a sec, I got to take
this. Hello. Hi. Yeah. Yeah. My happy-happy passport, though. No need, I'm going to
walk the new. Okay. Jamie Nayser. Okay. Exhibit in the show. This is like a shelterous bella.
Okay. Rusta Khan. Love you. Bye. Right. So that was my wife. She's in Brussels right now.
That's about an hour's drive from from our house from the castle.
Because Christina's passport actually expires in what like five days or something like that.
So seeing as we're moving to the UK, she had to go get the passport taken care of.
I have jobs too. Obviously, I'll get her on to the bandwidth in a second. Let's see.
The getting the new bed that job was taken away from me. I'm looking at the note on the wall here.
I'm supposed to look for schools. Found a lot of schools. Here's a problem. If you want to put
your kid into a public school in the UK, you can't apply until you actually are living in the UK.
So I'm making good friends with Audrey, who happens at the same birth date as Christina.
And we'll probably be able to smuggle maybe a week or two. But it's also very, very full.
All the schools are full. And so it's going to be interesting to get Christina in midterm.
But I'm sure we'll work that out. Another thing I was supposed to take care of was the piano.
We have a discleaveer. DSC was it three or something like that from Yamaha. It's a baby grand piano.
A midsize baby grand piano. It's white, which there's only like three of them in the entire world.
It's one of these pianos that plays itself. You can also record your playing and it'll play it back.
And it doesn't play it back as a recording. It plays it back. Really playing it on the keys.
And we decided that now that we're moving, time to get rid of some stuff.
And this is one of those pieces of stuff that we haven't used. No one plays anymore.
Christina and I took lessons for two years and then we said, hey, screw it. She wanted to ride horses.
And I wanted to fly out like copters. So I'm trying to get rid of that.
I found a place that will put it up for consignment in their showroom. But it's, oh man, I'm moved like this.
An international move is not easy. So anyway, back to the bandwidth. I've had this with this provider before.
So I've cable. And what happens is they have a limit. They have a total bandwidth limit and an upstream limit.
Now I've surpassed the upstream limit before because, of course, in their asynchronous money-making scam,
they let you upload only a third of what you can download. So that's part of the big scam. The man has over us.
And I said, look, I've said this many times. Just let me buy whatever ban with, you'll sell me.
Just give it to me. And so finally they found that I have like now the top level account,
which is the super duper gamers account. I have 30 gigs. You can't get more. There's no business account.
They can get you more. You can only get more IP addresses or email addresses or something like that or more web space.
Whatever. Let me see how my battery is doing here all on. Now we look to be doing okay.
So with all this podcasting, and it's not the upstream bandwidth because I didn't even come near
to half of that, it's the download bandwidth. You know, I've subscribed to everything I'm putting into the
directories to check it out, listen to it, listen to bits. And of course I have to listen to every single
dawn and drew show now that I know that dawn doesn't love with me. Right, Dawn?
So I exceeded my maximum. That what happens is automatically they cut down your modem speed
to from a cable modem literally to like 56k. And they do it in a really nasty way by destroying
about 40% of your packets, which makes all kinds of applications not work reliably. And just really
crappy. And the thing is, they will not sell me more bandwidth. I'm sitting here saying tell me
what it costs, give me another 30 gigs, give me another three terabytes, whatever. Now I'm sorry.
We just, we don't have the application to sell you more. And this is like, it's like the electric company
saying, oh, we're sorry, Mr. Curry. You have used too much electricity this month already. We're
cutting you down. In fact, you can only leave half your lights on from now on until the end of the month.
You know, so it sucks. It's just really fucking blows. So what I will probably wind up doing
is driving, well, people have been very helpful. They've given me all kinds of hotspot lists.
Now, I installed a couple of Wi-Fi base stations and four computers in the local grade school.
When Christina will still go into that school and I donated all this MAC stuff, all the new
e-max. So I'm going to drive by there because I did leave it open on purpose. I'm going to drive
by there, see if that's still open. Otherwise, I left to go to a gas station on the highway,
which has an official hotspot operated by Bellhacom. And I'll probably upload from there.
So I'm probably going to encode a little lower bit rate than normal, just to lower the
file size a bit more because even, you know, if I'm on a good line, it can still take quite a while
to upload the show. And I also want to be downloading. So I'm going to be sitting the parking
lot for about an hour and a half watching, you know, half go up and watching stuff come in.
It should be very entertaining. And if that doesn't work out, then somewhere around,
well, somewhere after one AM, I'll be able to get my bandwidth back. And then, of course, it'll
still be limited. So it sucks. It just sucks. Oh, look at my, looking at my list here. I also have
to figure out the stables. Stabiling for the horse. Oh, man, my life. Okay. Let's see. One of the
things that's been circling around on the net for the past few days is this theory that
George W. Bush during the debates had an earpiece in and was being tutored or coached throughout
the debate. Now, I've talked about this before. I think we've even talked about it on trade
secrets, not necessarily related to the debates, but just in general. So it's so often seems
like George W. He's sitting there and these long pauses, like he's listening to someone, you know,
prompting him and giving him the, you know, the next line that he should say. And it's sometimes
he just comes across that way. So now, of course, and I'm going to play the piece that Dave
Winer pointed to first, because I got, you know, it's so easy to do this. That's why I'm sure
that there's more than just the two that are going to play for you. But here's some actual audio
from the prompting of George Bush. Not doing the debate. I have that for you in a second. I have
a secret audio recorded from the, from his prompting service in his earpiece. First, this
is just from a general speech. Mr. Chairman, delegates, foul citizens, farmers, fellow citizens,
Americans have been given hills to climb and found the strength to climb them to climb them.
When I, when I said those words 26 years ago, four years ago, four years ago,
now we can see the valley below. My father surveyed years at the side of another great American,
Laura Bush. Ronald Reagan. Ronald Reagan. Pinching plans, worker training. We're created for the
world of yesterday. Tomorrow. Not tomorrow. Not tomorrow. Yesterday. Yesterday. Oh, I give up.
I could listen to that over and over again. I think this one's even better. And I haven't heard
it seen this one around on the night yet. So I think you'll appreciate it. Here's actual recorded footage
recorded tape of the president's earpiece during the second presidential debate.
He said he was $487 billion and voted against it right before he voted for it. voted for confusing.
But it works. That's since they confusing single people. He said he thought Saddam Hussein was a great
threat. Now said it was a mistake to remove Saddam Hussein from power. Now, I can't see why
that. Because he got that. He changed his position quite often because he does. Now you don't find George.
You know, for a while, he was a strong supporter of getting the Saddam Hussein. No, it's not a god.
There is a system until the Democrat primary came along.
How are they? They don't like him any. And how are they in the anti-war can it began to gain on him?
He changed positions. I don't say you can leave this country in a time of war, in a time of
uncertainty. You change your mind because of politics. He just brought up the tax. There you go.
You remember that? We preached that child credit by $1,000.
We reduced the marriage penalty. You spent a little bit of a 10% tax bracket for the low-income
Americans. That's right at the middle class. There you go. He voted against it. And he tells you
he's for middle class tax customers. You've got to be consistent. There's a lot of pressures.
You've got to be firm. This president, I would follow up.
We have a series of questions on Iraq. And so I would turn to the next questioner.
It's a question to President Bush. And the questioner is Robin?
Just not. We practiced it.
Can you get him like a water or something?
Just drink water or something. George, it's just water.
Just a president. Yes, he is. Don't. We'll get more. He's not asking the question. Look at the
audience. Master structure. Just like we practiced it. But just apply to the
education by stating, I think you have a real hard question in the knowledge. We'll
carry out our needs. That is down to reduce weapons of mass destruction.
Booting could have passed this knowledge to our Dutch enemies.
Okay. That blank is just not believe. This to be a reasonable justification for being
yourself. I'll charge you to. For invasion. When this statement applies to so many of the
centuries, including North Korea. Each situation is different. Each situation is different,
Robin. And obviously we hope that diplomacy works before you ever use
a position. Hardest decision for those who make his paper to use force.
I don't know about it. 9-11. 9-11. There you go.
Well, differently. 9-11. We had to recognize, we saw threat.
I'm going to let you go here and get my notes. We must take a series of
graphic. I don't know if it's 5 days. We'll see a threat.
Oh, man. 9-11 bullshit. No, yeah. Just think about your favorite salad dressing.
Please vote for John Kerry. Believe me. It's the best thing to do.
We've been along with a source code for today. As we're about 18 minutes into the show,
I was listening to a fine IT Conversations podcast, memory lane with Halle suit. By the way,
got a mail from Doug K, who told me that there is a way to get just the feeds that you want.
You don't have to subscribe to the main feed. I just didn't look closely enough at the website.
And quite honestly, I like subscribing to everything that comes from IT Conversations.
Oh, there was one thing. During this particular interview, Doug, I could hear your hybrid,
your phone hybrid bleeding over and you were talking to someone else and you could just
barely hear it in the background, but I had it really loud on the iPod. In this particular
memory lane with Halle suit, what Halle does she talks to, you know, pioneers of our industry,
of technology, of networking, of computers. And she interviewed Len Kleinrock, in that inventor of
packet switching. So arguably, one of the guys who founded the internet. And I've mentioned before
in both trade secrets. And I think also on the source code that I was, you know, without a doubt,
partially responsible for the commercial internet. And there was so much pushback at the time
when the commercial internet started, people hated us for doing that. And I was interested to hear
what Len Kleinrock's take would be on that. And I was probably even more surprised by what
his actual take was. He's going to explain it a little bit. He's going to kind of set it up
as we drop into the story after the Arpenads already been founded. And NSF comes into the picture.
National Science Foundation was now governing who could use the network. They had an acceptable
use policy. And it was a very liberal policy. They allowed all of their constituents in
the biologist, the physicist, the chemist, the meteorologist, the geologist, the oceanographers,
all manner of science when else don't see the network. So it's great to expand it the user's
base. Now, again, it was researcher oriented. But many of these research organizations
lived inside large corporations. For example, the research group that IBM, the research group
at major chemical companies, all exploration companies. And what were these guys doing with the
net besides moving down to the data back and forth? You said it before, Hally, they would do an email.
An email was a terrific application. What you have to realize that those researchers inside this
large corporation couldn't keep the secret of email from the others in the organization. So the
production people saw it, development people, the sales folks, top management, pretty soon,
the internet usability and applications leaked out from the research organization
into the entire commercial organization. And that's when the dot com's began to appear.
Right. And I know that was the big issue at that time, is the net should the net be commercialized.
And the academic community had a lot of different ideas about it. Right. Can you tell me about that?
Well, as I said in the very early days, we were small community of people who trusted each other.
We didn't put in restrictions as to how the network would be used or what would travel over the
network. Because there was an unwritten rule of engagement that we all adhere to among which were
this network was for scientific purposes and not for commercial purposes. As these dot com's came
on, we didn't see a problem with them using the network. In fact, to look forward,
I'm very pleased that dot com's came in because it never would not have grown to reach out
in all the applications and all the people in all the countries of the world had not the dot com's
come in and begun to provide some commercial services, commercial applications, and deploying
infrastructure that the open net at that time could not afford to do. But getting back to the
approach of these dot com people in 1988, the first worm appeared came from Robert Morris.
He launched the worm and it totally took down a large portion of the network. We were very
unhappy about that. But that seemed to be an isolated incident until in 1994, the two most hated
people on the internet, Canton, Seagull, who were running a small, small legal firm,
sent out the first spam. They sent out an advertisement to all the news groups offering to help
users get green cards if they were not citizens. Now, this went out, it's flooded the network.
Now, those on the other side, people like myself said, what the heck was that? The network
is not supposed to be used for advertising purposes. So we'd launched email back to the Canton
Seagull saying, you can't do that, that's wrong. And everybody without being coordinated sent
these information back, these emails back, as it was full. We created the first denial of service
of that network. I like that. It is hard to imagine what it's even looked like in those days
and when it switched. Actually, well, you get the idea there. And there's even a piece of the
end where he goes in a little bit more about the dot coms. Really good to hear Len Klein-Rofka talk
that way, because I do think it was good. The commercialization of the internet did bring it
to every single corner of the world, or at least close to it. And still, we're only like what,
you know, 6% of the entire population that has access to the internet. Good show to subscribe to
great podcast. It's memory lane with Halle Suit. You can find it at IT Conversations.com.
Today, the source code, I'm Adam Curry reaching out to the far corners of the earth myself,
including Australia. Hi, Adam. This is Les Pose and Melbourne of Australia. Thanks for the great
work that you and Dave and the others are doing with podcasting. There was something that happened
in yesterday's trade secrets for the 12th, where Dave spoke about a friend of his Les Williams,
talking about blogs and by extension podcasts, being like Chinese meals, small tidbits,
who delicately eat them with chopsticks, rather than just having a big meal in front of you.
Can I send that metaphor a little further to get some extra meaning out of that?
Sort of bad metaphor, because it reminds of what happens when you go to Chinese yam chat.
Very popular in Australia, and I'm sure in Europe. And of course, in any good China town in
the United States, yam chat doors is where the waiters serve you every couple of minutes,
something you pop out on the trolley and you have a choice. Could be Chinese broccoli,
could be fish, could be seafood. There's usually something for everybody and it's usually in
serves for three people. And this way, it reminds you of podcasts, because if you don't like something,
you just say, no, I'll wait for something better comes along. That's really good. Well,
all have that, or no, any summers will have that, will have something else. So that's how
reminds you of podcasting. Just a little bit for everything. You're happy to, they're happy if you
reject. There's always something coming along. And that's going to be better than what you had just
before. So look, guys, keep it up and really enjoying it here in Melbourne, Australia. Bye for now.
All right, Les, thank you very much. And I'm noticing that there are a lot of podcasts coming
out of Australia currently. I don't know. You guys must be star for good radio for good entertainment.
It's just those Mad Max movies. That's all you see on TV. And then, you know, I can only imagine
it's, it's Molly, whatever, who's no longer doing the countdown shows on every, every radio station.
You must be so starved. And of course, it's so much so vast. You know, it's only the cities,
I guess, that really have radio stations. And if you're not anywhere near a city, it's going to
it's old, the coat hanger antenna time. And something that Les was talking about triggered,
well, it's like, I mean, just bring him my email here for a second, triggered something that I found
which as it relates to podcasting. Oh, my second. Let me see why this is.
I have to look at my scent box. At least my setup is going to be able to handle
handle me doing this or it should be able to handle me doing this. Okay, let me see. Here we go.
Yeah, I got this from in Karta. That's MSN's encyclopedia. And I was looking, because I was interested
in the total market that radio is in the United States. That's all I have as US numbers. So,
because I think that what we're doing here is no different from radio broadcasting. So, I wanted to
see, what's the size of this market and what can we do with it? Radio attracted about 8% or 17.2
billion of all US advertising dollars making it the fourth largest advertising medium in 1999.
Although national advertisers can buy national network radio time, here it comes. 90% of all radio
advertising is local. Unlike television, which reaches abroad audience, the specialized
programming of radio stations enables advertisers to reach a narrow, highly specific audience,
such as people who like sports or urban teenagers who listen to the latest styles of popular music.
Because many people listen to radio while in their cars, radio also enables advertisers to reach
prospects just before they go shopping. But because people listen to the radio while doing something
else, such as driving or working, radio commercials can be easily misunderstood. As a result,
radio ads work best when the messages are relatively simple ones for familiar, easily understood
products or, and I'll add to this, which it was a wiki, or if you can just rewind and listen to
the commercial again, because you're actually interested in the advertisement, or maybe because
it was actually entertaining. So I'm quite sure I can't be too far off pace with that theory.
Okay, even though I'm living here in Belgium at the castle, we still have the house in Amsterdam,
my mind is already left in Netherlands and left Belgium. I mean, I'm barely skimming the front
page of the newspaper these days. It's just like, you know, why bother? I'm already gone. Although
certainly, my mind have not yet arrived in the UK. In fact, for the past three days, I've probably
been living more in the northeastern part of America, or northwestern corner of America, mainly
because Dave Winner lives in Seattle now. Let's see, I've been listening to Northwest Noise, which is
a great podcast. You can get it from the iPod.org directory. It's, I mean, there's lots of history
about the logging industry and how tech came in and saved stuff and about coffee history.
It's really, it's just fun to listen to and all the local news. And I'm also listening to Koma 1000.
And of course, they have a podcast, which you can also subscribe to with iPod or.
And, you know, Mount St. Helens has been in the news. I heard about it before it was mainstream
on the northwest noise, because it was of course local news. And it may have drawn to a little bit
out of the mainstream now, I think as well, except on the local Seattle station, who,
you know, they picked up a nice human interstory about Mount St. Helens. Meet Billy Jonas,
singer, songwriter, and musician. He loves to entertain kids. And 15 years ago, he wrote a song
about the 1980 eruption of Mount St. Helens. 1990, I was hiking on Mount St. Helens with a group
of campers. He says it was like the song just came from the mountain.
The kids that were walking with me at the time immediately just started dancing and
popping along. Ever since it's been part of his show, who's year Billy decided to put the song
on his new CD before the volcano began burping again. When I heard about it, I just said,
oh, that's funny. What do you know?
Truman lived by Spirit Lake. Oh, St. Helens. They told him to leave. He said,
give me a break. Oh, St. Helens says he's working on a new verse for old St. Helens.
Now she's gone on blow again. Old St. Helens. If this is a proud election, old St. Helens,
maybe she'll shed light on this election. Old St. Helens. Billy, I'm not sure you can't
shoot the true spirit of things. I mean, the volcano has just been belching up steam. You know,
burping. Think of the kids, man. I hereby pledge that burping belts will be in the next
verse. I personally can't wait to hear a Brian Kelp, a couple of 1000 names.
All right. Some light entertainment on your source code. And from the north,
western part of the United States, we go to the other side of the globe to West,
nowhere, Japan. Greetings from West, nowhere, Japan. I don't know. My name is Steve
Henryburn. I've been tuning into your podcast for more for a little while now. And I think you're
doing a fantastic job. Your work is really building a strong foundation. I got to blow in our podcast
and community and kind of organized around in really to grow on. So, tears to you. Thank you.
Thank you. Wait, but do you think that Steve being in West, nowhere, Japan, that he's actually
he's actually in a pod? Could he be in one of those pods? You know, where you can only lie down and
you've got just light and a mirror and a bed. And then he's really pod casting from a pod?
I was especially happy to see the directory that you've been focusing on lately. And it's
really, it's increasing the exposure and the availability of all the pod casts that are out there.
I took a look through there here the day and added a bunch to my list. And it was great help.
Okay, so Steve is talking about the ipodder.org directory. And I am amazed about this.
This is an OPML directory, which stands for Outline Processor Markup Language.
I thought this was going to be difficult, but I am amazed at how many people know what OPML is,
have an application that outputs OPML. And how many people are, frankly, just willing to
write it up by hand in VI or text that. It's great. And we have now, I think 11 people maintaining
their own nodes. We even have a documentation node being set up as we speak. And it's blowing
my mind because there's no single entry point. You know, anyone could make their own top level
and link in my nodes. It's a complete world outline, if you will. One thing is right now.
Adding new feeds is a bit of a hidden mis situation. You really have only the category
and the title of the feed itself to go on. So it's hard to really get a good idea of what the
pod casts is about. Okay, so this is true. What we're doing now is we're the links that you see
in the ipodder.org directory are links to the pod casts feed itself to the RSS feed. So it's not
really easy for newbies who come along and click on that. And then maybe their browser parses
it and they see an XML outline or maybe it doesn't. They just see some letters at the top.
Luckily a lot of people are used to seeing this because that's how we're currently still
kind of doing RSS except for some aggregators, some centralized one like blog lines. And if you
have a blog lines little button on your homepage, people can click and automatically subscribe to
it and you know, coffee cup for radio user land. But we don't have all the stuff, all the
groovy stuff you'd want in there. And I'm sure that's what Steve's about to mention.
I would like to see a brief description of each feed just to get a better idea of what the feed
is actually about, what the pod casts is actually about. Now that info is usually right in the source
code of the RSS feed itself. For example, in your own RSS feed, the description reads
a daily audio blog post by Adam Curry in mp3. That's a daily audio podcast in mp3
Now, this certainly is not all inclusive, but it at least gives me the who's and for how often.
So I've got that to work on. Now, as the description is right in the source code, shouldn't
be a way to parse that data out? Absolutely. And Steve, I'm really glad you brought that up.
And Steve's audio comment goes on for at least another two minutes. But it's really important
to stuff that you're saying here. And we do have that. And in fact last night, day one or
night, we had a very historic moment together. It was last night for me yesterday,
I early afternoon for him, maybe even still morning. And we both simultaneously bought a new
server. You know, that's kind of like what women do when they go shoe shopping, we're like,
oh, that's go buy a server. And we, you know, we, I'm going to look at all the options.
And it's an IDE drive on IDE, raid one, and which, like, get and how many how big should the
hard drives be? And we're kind of bandwidth. And what are we going to name the machines? And it's just
porn, you know, it's total porn the way women love shoe shopping. Some women, most women,
lots of women love shoe shopping. And we're going to really get, get serious on attacking these
issues. And one of the things that is high priority on the list is for the directory, the submit
links should be a lot easier. If you're maintaining a node, you should basically just receive an email
and you click somewhere and all the fields are filled in. It pulls in that data from the RSS
feed, you're right for the channel title and description. Even the logo, and that should automatically
be posted to the iPod.org homepage, totally right there. And we're working on it. So everyone's
thinking about the same thing. And I'm so happy to see this come together. And anyone who wants to
help with this outline stuff, you're more than welcome to contribute. There's a link on the iPod.org
directory right there under podcasts. How you can contribute and how you can maintain a node or
multiple nodes of branches of this entire tree that we're making right now. All right, one more
bushism. It's a topic we've discussed before. Repetition works. If I say to you, buy this soap,
it's better than all the rest. And I say it really loudly and with big orange and yellow colors
and white colors. And I tell you, over and over and over and over again, you're going to buy it.
I promise you. And that is part of the Republican strategy. So here it is. Once again,
prepare for a mine control. Repetition becomes truth. In the heart of this great city,
we saw tragedy arrive. In the heart of this great city, we saw tragedy arrive.
September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September
September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, October 11th, March 11th, September 11th, September 11th, healthy health outcomes, December 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 9th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th and September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 27th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September 11th, September
very caring oil or framing very very very critical of a triedising murder
That's what you're laughing at.
Terrible.
That's what you're talking about.
What you're talking about.
When I snap by fingers,
fingers, you'll wake up and vote for John Kerry.
And, wake, wake, wake, wake, wake, wake.
Yes, Stella, everybody, welcome back.
You listen to the Daily Source Code.
I'm Adam Curry.
We have one more song to play for you before I
have to go off and find the gas station or the hot spot somewhere
to go and upload all this stuff.
It is by popular request, Droma Douchy.
This is Here You Are, The World Fingers, the Lumisol.
So, one must have slipped the old Stella, me too, y'all, mommy,
cause here you are.
In the back, she left some old Stella, below, got sloppy,
and here you are.
You're not just a dream that financials in the midst.
It's bliss to know simply that you exist.
I'm happy that your happy give the misses, likes of yourself,
cause here you are.
I am afraid to do the same because I'll keep it made me stupid,
so that you are.
Would you care for a touch of material for my smile?
Is that when you are here?
Yes, it is you are.
You're not just a dream that financials in the midst.
It's bliss to know simply that you exist.
I'm happy because that came of how the weary made that teeny little dear you are.
No kinder than to cheat us on the sweetest little fetus, baby here you are.
Would you please have some sharing and sharing a while for my smile?
Don't worry, do shade here you are.
It's a lot of me song, and I've got to thank Ivan Roxy for turning me on to do her
do shade.
I ripped the CD off of them, but if you like what you hear, there's a whole CD full
of it, so go out and buy it.
And that's it for the source code for today, Thursday, October 14th, 2004, and I'm
off.
I'm going to see if I can upload this puppy for dinner time as always you can respond.
That was interesting.
You can respond by sending email to Adam at curie.com or leaving a comment on my weblog live.cure.com
and of course the archives available at dailystoresco.com.
In the podcast feed, RSS 2.0 at dailystoresco.com slash RSS.xml.
All right, everybody see you tomorrow for the thank God it's Friday edition.
Bye-bye.