Delta Sierra Charlie, 8-1-9.
This is the worst moment of my entire life.
Who am I, everybody?
Are you ready for this?
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass,
then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
I want my bail out money.
Keep the bills coming.
Sweep, grin, crash, just drippin' like honey.
I'm a new cutter cog with the watching to buzz.
Cause feelin' that bitch better than real drugs.
What do you think's gonna happen when they double the money supply?
A $4 dollar makes it harder for you to survive.
And take those billions of trains and give it to their old clients.
Hope it's all mine.
Feelin' right by it.
We got runaway credit.
Ain't nothing going down unless the cooks is marching for less.
I live as great, but it still doesn't get it.
Cause the economy is crashous or bad.
It leaves a parallel valley.
I want my bail out money.
Sweep, grin, crash, just drippin' like honey.
You've got to keep this economy running.
I need another hit.
I'm a bail out money.
What could you say?
It's like a mad dash for the cash.
I got the tax payer taken.
It's in the ass.
I see yours.
They are having the blast.
Why the work and ball trying to make a paycheck mass?
The bail out money is created with new debts.
But why they're growing in the middle of a strategist.
All the work is on the streets.
Sip and sweat.
But my car don't have to lose, I'll take it.
Everything that can wreck.
This was the nation on a hyper-reficion track.
The residential administration can take it back.
And now the tax payers pickin' up the sign.
I like to put a high dollar big brother, monkey on your back.
I want my bail out money.
Sweep, grin, crash, just drippin' like honey.
You've got to keep this economy running.
I need another hit.
bail out money.
Sweep, grin, just drippin' like honey.
Sweep, grin, crash, just drippin' like honey.
Sweep, grin, angry, pues' curtin me.
Sweep, grin,rab, kotin' like honey.
But it's in the red.
It got a mini dance.
The politician said that we're going to be
all in the red.
Paying by a friend.
The people are being blessed.
But get it through your head that we're going to be.
The bankers got to stay ahead.
Got to make more bread.
That's when they said, bro.
More money.
Ha ha ha.
Yeah.
Give me some of my bailout money.
Everybody how you doing?
It's a silly source code episode number 81.
Niner.
We are rocking into the weekend with a food bar Friday.
Totally loaded up.
We've got the top share chat room filled.
The stream is running and a phone number for you to call within the next hour.
You can't even ask ice cream or a kid's a screamer.
But the cool song real is who you gotta be.
Love and community laughter is a turn of your choice real.
You can't go now.
You can't go.
It's successful so you can't keep taking pictures.
Medic on it more urgently, mostly for such a romantic story.
And then see you guys soon.
You can't go.
You can't even go.
You can't go 好 there.
It is impossible to find the location.
You know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you
know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you're all little you know, you know, you know, you know, no, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you are His last wife, You know, you know, you know. you know, you know, you know, you, know, you know, you know. you, know, ya. you know, you, know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you, know, you know, you, know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you yeah, see, what you know, you know, what you know, you know, you know, do what you know, you know, how I just, yeah, that captain
Let me in the soul, let me in the soul, let me in the soul, let me in the soul.
Special thanks to a good buddy Ray for sending me a whole bunch of songs to play on the Charlie for today.
You too, get on your boots. It should be downloadable from their side, on February 15th.
And of course, you legally play right now on Daddy's Source code every one night.
Screw up, man. If they can steal from us in Washington, it should be able to steal at least one song and share with my friends,
especially for me too.
It's Friday. It is January 23rd, 2009 currently 714 pm in the United Kingdom coming to you from the
Curry Terrace in Southwest London. Yeah, I'm kind of getting used to saying that the Curry Terrace, which relates
totally to the address that we're at. I'm not going to help you in finding that.
But I've done a lot of studying about this particular area.
And this house, in fact, some very interesting people have lived here, famous sculptor.
But more importantly, this entire area, which is kind of the Clapham
Battersea and almost a little bit of the bricks in area, very significant historically.
And now I know why I'm feeling so incredibly at home here.
You know, if you're lucky enough, you've moved into a house where you just feel everything's right.
And man, all three of us have this here. And you know, I guess we're old souls, no regardless.
So we kind of fit in, particularly with the Victorian style.
I think the Lady Patricia in this life was dates back to the Victorian era.
She can't hear me obviously.
A couple of things that are interesting. One, this is the exact area that in 19...
And I'm sorry, in 1660 to about 1666.
The famous diarist Samuel Peppy lived in this area. If you've never seen this online
go to Peppy's diary, p-y-s-d-i-a-r-y, Peppy's diary.com.
You can subscribe to a feed in every single day. You'll get what he wrote in 1660 or whatever.
I think they do multiple entries for each day.
But I've been following his writing, which is very different from the way we speak these days,
for a couple of years at least. And I've always enjoyed kind of reading what some guy was,
you know, essentially one of the first webloggers was writing about 300 years ago.
And it turns out he lived in this very area. In fact, he retired here at the end of his career
and passed away a happy man. This was also the time.
I've just got to run some history by in 1666 people in London,
because we're right on the other side of the Thames.
So sometimes not considered to be London.
Of course, it is a burrow of London, the burrow of Lambeth.
The black plague, the black death, was rampant in London with thousands of people dying on a daily basis.
And what people were doing is running away. They actually locked off London
up until the Thames. And you could buy passes on the black market to get out of London.
And people moved to this very area to be safe.
It's an interesting side note. The government at the time blamed dogs and cats for spreading the black death.
And they killed tens of thousands of pets, dogs and cats,
which of course only made the problem worse because dogs and cats actually
stop rodents like rats who were the trooper portrayed or something problem.
So that only accelerated everything. And then to add on top of all that.
So I'm feeling good. This is a place where people would flee from the city when peril was there.
And you know, I'm feeling some perilous times are ahead of us.
I love the fact that Peppies lived in this area.
And so I did, that's a very creative vibe.
But I also discovered that in Clapham, one of the two remaining unused, deep level shelters
is located here.
100 feet under the earth.
No, not Churchill Eisenhower.
Used one of the, one of the other deep level shelters during the second world war as a communication center.
And this thing literally, it can house 8,000 people.
And they've tried to flog it off to nightclub owners.
And it's always been bounced off because of zoning regulations and health and safety concerns.
And you know, people want to make a nightclub in it, which would be really cool.
So it's just kind of nice to know that within not exactly walking, but within running distance,
there's a deep level shelter.
So when the shit really hits the fan, would it all really really comes down?
I know that, uh, well, kind of be safe.
I got a phone number for you guys to call and see if we can get that work in today.
And of course, the talk tube bridge is over.
With all the shitty sound you're used to over there.
Yeah.
I don't worry.
One more song from Ray is from Dutch Band.
And so nice to hear this one again.
You don't hear this stuff made in Holland anymore.
This is, uh, I think it's early 80s.
Fatal flowers, younger days, on the Charlie 819.
I've been through the time until this guy, I used to know him.
And he's been telling me all the story.
By the long time ago,
makes you want to come back to those places.
You used to struggle all night.
Makes you realize that these are times long gone by.
You're young today that's still with time.
There's no use fighting a whole room to a feeling, feeling change in time
Well time will pass you by
Your young days that sail with a child
All your young days that sail with a child
Ah the days of the good old Dutch bands
Fate of flowers as younger days
All right, so here's how I want to run it for today
I'm thinking I'm going very very long
Of course the last show I did I believe was on Monday
At the last show I did we had a different president
It was George Bush
Gotta say I watched of course all of the coverage
And we were covering it ourselves as well on my view
Which was kind of fun
To do it in it's almost like I'm looking at what was the John C. to work
We call that a fractal
It's almost like I'm seeing a fractal of MTV being recreated
But yet it's not exactly the same
It's a little bit differently
But so many similarities and seeing how much better we can do
And everyone recognizing that annoying that will do better
And it's exciting
It's cool to see a whole group of people just coming together
And getting stuff out there
Boy I almost don't know where to begin
Because so much as so much has taken place
I'm just looking at my story list of stuff that I saved
To talk about most of this of course comes from the drop
If you've never been there before please
Point your web browser to drop.io slash daily source code
It is a fantastic
Jumble mashup of
Mainly mainstream stories
That really hit home when you think about what's what's going on in the world
Things you just don't see
Often enough and airgo don't really exist
I finally convinced the lady Patricia
I've really been complaining a lot lately
And you know what man she really must love me
Because every single day you know now that I'm a Londoner
Now that I'm a city boy
I walk out I go pick up a newspaper
I pick up a paper for her
She usually wants the daily mirror which is a piece of crap
I pick up the financial times
And then I'll come back
Pick up a capuccino
And the official capuccino with the official Italian place
Not a chain
Right around the corner
Nice little walk back to the curry square
And then she'll do my hair
Because I'm on a six day week schedule now with the video production
Seven days a week of full-on production
Really if you look at if you take Saturday into account with the no agenda
So it's kind of nonstop
And she's always done my hair
As far as long as we've been married
Whenever I have to do something that is
Because if not then it just looks you know
I just I don't shave or do anything
Now it's a whole new life for me
Shaving my god what a concept
Every day no less
Getting my hair made up done per day every day
I've learned to do my own makeup now by now
But I'm also doing my own
My own production, my own writing, my own camera work, my own lighting, my own sound
Engineering, my own editing
It's been quite an experience
But I'm in a pretty good vibe
And just need
Well I've gotten things I've gotten a lot faster
You have no idea by the way
I still don't have the virgin 50 megabit
Or even the 20 megabit that they've promised me in yet
But just having BT which I think is five megabits five or eight
Something like that
Oh
Your life goes so much faster
I can multitask
I mean at this moment I'm actually
I'm watching
CNBC on the sling box from my buddy in
In Chicago
You're just gonna just turn it on for a second
Unfortunately
Aaron Burnett is not on today
Which is kind of a bummer
I have a bet riding by February 14th
I expect the stock market the Dow Jones to be at 7286
And it's been all over the place
If we have two down days
The way we've seen them right now
The mark is up a little bit
If we have two down days
Then I'll make my hundred bucks
Of course that won't be worth much anymore
Although
A hundred bucks in British pounds
It's starting to get pretty interesting
It's now at 137
Unbelievable
The country
The United Kingdom is on its way
To bankruptcy
They're talking about
Turning to the IMF for support
Can you believe this is actually happening
Well I'll tell you
I've learned some things
This is fantastic program on the BBC
It's called Question Time
It's a live program
I think it's a live program
And they have a panel of politician
Sometimes they'll have a
Political comedian on
And they'll pick a topic
And of course it's been a lot
As been about the bailout
The exact same thing that has been taking place
The United States is happening here
And the government here has now said
Oh we're just going to create a bad bank
Which is the same that's happening in the States
And that means that bad bank will buy up all the assets
Of the banks
In effect nationalizing the banking business
But what people get really pissed off about
And rightly so is when you have a bank like Northern Rock
Which if you've been listening to the show for a year
You know that that was effectively nationalized a year ago
They just gave
All those fuckers over there bonuses
By the way
For the people who work there
I understand you get a bonus
I'm not really angry at you
I'm angry at the government for allowing that to happen
I do pay taxes here
Income taxes as well
Not just
Municipality or council tax but actual income taxes
And they're just giving it away
They're giving it away to the same people who created the entire problem
Very much like
Well this is the fantastic thing that I've been watching
These confirmation hearings of Timothy Geitner
Who has been in the treasury
Has been an actual part of handing out the first
$350 billion to banks
Which the treasury
Will not tell us where it went
Who received it
And now they're going to bring this guy in
And he's going to hand out the next 350 billion
It's the stupidest thing I've ever seen in my life
And we're just kind of sitting there and let it pass by
Because we don't have
And this is what I've really come to
Conclude we don't have the type of media system
They have any knighted kingdom
Where it's pretty much BBC 1 and BBC 2
Channel 4
Yeah sure we got big brother
And I'm a celebrity get me out of here
But Channel 4 is effectively bankrupt
They're going to fold that into
More of a public broadcaster
And the rest numbers wise really just doesn't matter
And there isn't just a show where
Normal people get on on a live show
And say hey screw that you guys are fucking with us
Stop it
So that gives me more of his own death
Hey let me try something
Since the talk show
Conference bridge thing
I think pretty much
A failure
As far as I can tell
You know and for a number of reasons
Not necessarily talk shoes fault
One is that has you know the chat is okay
You know there's there's much better chat clients out there
I'm kind of using this chat right now
But there's you know there's no direct number to call into
It's it's not really efficient
And of course a lot of people will call in
With Skype which you know I just can't
Skype nine times out of ten sounds like shit
Because I'm dialing into talk shoe with Skype
So the experience you're getting on talk shoe is crappy sound
I urge you to listen to the stream
Yeah, I know there's a delay
It's just a little bit
But something I've
I have not been able to try out
Which I'd like to do now
Is to see how many incoming lines I can receive on Skype
Am I Skype in number now home on a second I've got to set this up
So I say receive calls your online number from anyone
So that means anyone should be able to call me here's the number
It's a new jersey number
It only if you have something to say
Okay, and this is meant to be called with a regular phone or a cell phone
If you want to start a conversation
If you want to start a topic if you want it we could even do requests
Oh, yeah, it's the all request Charlie everybody
2 0 1 7 9 3 8 3 3 2
So if you're dialing from overseas plus 1 2 0 1 7 9 3 8 3 3 2
And I'm very curious to see if if that actually works
And if I can what happens if I'm talking to one person and another call comes in
I would presume that it will just it will give me the opportunity to accept another line
If it doesn't do that or if it does that will it will allow me to receive a third line
I don't know I'm pretty sure though if I if I take a call
That the people listening on the talk shoe system
We'll be put on hold automatically and won't be able to hear what's going on
So you know you're best listening to the stream for sure
201 7 9 3 8 3 3 2
I'll give you this song
If you want to call and if you got anything you want to talk about
You know otherwise just get into some news we'll take in a reverse chronological order and man there's a whole shit load of it
This is hello down
Hi
I lived in the same place now for six or seven years
See drink I smoke what I want
It doesn't matter to the folks around here
I just live my life when no need to hurry
No need to worry
Down here in Bimani
So to put it in a way to make a long story short
When to the store of all the bullets and some more
Put it in the harbor and watch me and in a rope my boat
A thousand miles back to Bimani
I wrote my boat back
You're a little one day what happened
I made a girl from New York City
She was so so pretty
I fell hit all my heels
She said come home with me to hand watch me
So I left my home
I left my beach in Bimani
So to put it in a way to make a long story short
When to the store of all the bullets and some more
Put it in the harbor and watch me and I wrote my boat
A thousand miles back to Bimani
But I've been there and you're sitting
It turned out that she wasn't quite so pretty
She found out I wasn't too rich
But I've been there and you're sitting
It turned out that she wasn't nearly that pretty
It turned out to be such a bitch
Oh
I went to the store of all the bullets
More than one canteen
Three cans of two to through the rough rough waters
The shark heavy harbors
I wrote my boat a thousand miles back to Bimani
From hello Dave
One of the guys the bands that meet the song
And said if you don't like it
I'll just walk around and say
If you don't like it
But if you don't like it, I'll send you a dollar.
I'm like, give out my address.
I'd rather play the song.
I like it though.
Give me any sounds like a place I'd like to be.
Where you can smoke anything.
People don't care.
I wrote my feedback, signed it out to you.
Yeah, we'll leave back home.
All right, so as predicted, I got a call in,
which means the people on talk show are screwed.
So they can't hear it.
Really, the place to be is listening to the stream.
But of course, the majority of listeners are listening to this on the podcast.
I would presume.
201, 7, 9, 3, 8, 3, 3, 2, Chris from Philly, of course.
How are you doing, man?
Do you know it yourself?
Yeah.
Are you on a regular phone?
I'm on an iPhone.
iPhone, Skype, but all sounds crap.
You know, the iPhone, I must say they've never really
sounded good to me.
Particularly when you have to talk slower.
Yeah, that's the way Apple, a cup of tea, no one's going to talk slower.
It works much better on the iPhone.
What's on your mind, Chris?
It's one of the ways we think about the last present home,
we're going to be closing this one's on a little bit of TV.
All right.
Are you walking outside, man?
Because it's really windy.
I am outside.
I'm trying to stay still.
That's okay.
Well, this is interesting.
I'm glad you brought that up because I did save a number of stories
about it.
So, here's the danger in what has taken place where there were a couple
of executive orders the day before yesterday, which were actual executive orders
to do actual things.
The way the press has spun the Guantanamo Bay executive order is exactly the way
you perceived it.
The president closed Guantanamo Bay, not true.
What, and I've read the executive order, which is it's a lot of legalese, okay?
Which I always find interesting.
You really got to be careful when it comes to little, you know, the fine print.
Because this is not about Guantanamo Bay.
I think we've kind of forgotten what was going on there.
Can you recall Chris, what the actual issue of Gitmo was?
I just got a, probably the torch, I mean, that and the people just kind of sitting there
without any charges.
It's not actual legal, you know, the abuse court brings evidence, but they just, yeah,
you can bring it to evidence, but they don't want to see it.
Right.
So this is about, so the torture part, that's a separate issue, which I want to talk
about in a moment.
But, Habius Corpus is, as I believe it's even written, the God given right, that you have
right to a fair trial, and you can't just be locked up forever.
The way the Bush administration got around this is by doing it in a different country
where jurisdiction, you know, is basically military jurisdiction.
So the issue is that there are people in there, and they've already let hundreds go
who were innocent after a year, two years, three years of detention.
So now there's, I believe the reports are 245 people left, and really this executive
reporter from President Obama was about, which is kind of, it's nasty to read it, about
the disposal of these prisoners.
And so the problem here is, and this is why it's kind of crazy, you know, as a part
of the executive order, it says, yeah, within one year, no longer than one year, Gitmo
has to be closed.
So apparently they're going to need to, you know, a year to figure out what to do with
245 people.
Now, if you bring them to the United States, then, you know, you have to, you have only
a set amount of time, and you have to, you know, basically charge them with something
or let them go.
And I would presume that the people who are sitting there, oh, man, Chris, that's real
noisy.
I would presume that the people, that's all right, man, the people who are sitting there
have been sitting long enough to have either been proven innocent or guilty.
And this is, it's a big conversation I was watching, C. Span, this morning, and people
were calling in and saying, hey, look, if these people committed crimes in the United States
against United States citizens, they should be tried here.
We should not be afraid.
We've been taught by the Bush administration to be so afraid of everything.
And I think it's time that we say, all right, look, if there's something we think you
did, we're going to bring you over here, we're going to put your ass in jail, and
we're going to put you through a proper process and trial.
And already, you know, people saying, well, you know, because, you know, they may be terrorists
and so we'll have to do like an alcohol thing, we'll have to try them on something else.
And or how about, let's have other countries take them.
And it's funny, because I'm literally reading in the news that all of that, the United Kingdom
is very happy to take some of these prisoners, that's not true.
Not true.
There's everyone over here saying, oh, we don't want terrorists.
Bad for our security, look, these people could be innocent, in fact, most likely, most
of them are innocent.
And I believe we should bring that they should be out of their immediate lease.
So I don't understand why this has to take an entire year to figure this out.
And let me get the article here.
I'm going to click on it.
Yeah, I have a co-workers who's from Yemen, and you were always talking about, you know,
stuff happened in the world.
It says a lot of times, people get convicted of these terror crimes and get extra died
back to the country.
But then, you know, countries like, oh, well, you did, you know, two years worth of time
on an 80-year sentence.
Let's go take a vacation.
I went out to worry about it.
And I don't know what exactly he was talking about for the, what kind of, like, convictions,
but it was very interesting that, you know, we had this horrible feeling about these supposed
terrorists in the Western world, like, probably that they could deal.
Well, you know, look, if any of these people are convicted and they're, and they're sent
back to their countries, I'm sorry, I would have to say not if they're convicted, but if
they are exonerated and they're let go, and their countries don't want them, that shouldn't
be our problem.
You know, I'm sorry, I'm just sorry, it's not my problem.
That is if they committed a crime in the United States, and they have been exonerated from
any crime of the United States.
They put it on a plane, drop them off, and not our problem.
I'm really sorry.
Nothing.
We can do about it.
Then it's a shit country that they came from.
We have no compassion for these people as an American public.
That's clear.
We view them all as terrorists, where as far as I know, you're still innocent until proven
guilty.
Most of these people have been sitting there for years without any trial or process whatsoever.
A human rights group, and of course, these links are in the show notes.
This is from the Washington Post.
I'm just going to read this for a second, because this comes down to the interrogation
process, which is another big sticking point.
So the question here is asked, did President Obama's executive order today banning
torture leave wiggle room for the possibility of reverting two coercive techniques that
the current executive order outlaws?
Michael Ratner president for the Center of Constitutional Rights says he thinks the answer
is yes.
And it comes down to wording.
And again, this is all legalese.
We can't just gloss over this shit.
You got to go to Whitehouse.gov, which is pretty big disappointment at the moment.
It's not really as transparent and certainly up to date as I would expect.
And read these things.
So Obama strongly repudiated torture as he signed today's executive order, which mandates
that the Army Field Manual will be strictly adhered to during interrogations.
You should read that, by the way.
But Ratner point to the following lines in the executive order that he says provides
a possible loophole by creating a task force to study the issue.
And I have to agree, this whole thing is filled with task force.
I do not like task force.
I don't like them in business.
I don't like them in government.
Whenever someone in my company says, we're going to start a task force.
I'm like, no, you're not.
Because task force are shit.
They net, that's like a steering committee.
That's another one.
I love steering committees because everyone's grabbing the wheel and you usually crash.
So the mission of the task force, the special task force, according to the executive
order shall be one, to study and evaluate whether the interrogation practices and techniques
in Army Field Manual to dash 22.31 employed by departments or agencies outside.
The military provided an appropriate means of acquiring the intelligence necessary to
protect the nation.
And if warranted to recommend any additional or different guidance for other departments
or agencies.
So the key ratiner says is that the executive order appears to follow for an evaluation
as to whether a keyword here, whether the Army Field Manual techniques are sufficient to
protect the nation.
He says that allows the task force to find after studying the issue that there may
be cases where it's acceptable to go beyond the Army Field Manual.
And quite honestly, I agree.
I really think that this has been constructed by lawyers and it's put together very,
very carefully.
And we're all still in such a state of euphoria that we're willing to overlook some
things that just may be hidden in their Chris your thoughts.
Jeez, I don't know if you've got the field manual, but did you see the boiling
one close to about the guy who's detained, I think it's a kid actually for owning a
capsule watch.
Now, if you can take a part and it can be a timer for a bomb.
So that's like the evidence they have to hold him for years.
Right.
Well, so we've got this watch.
So it, right.
So that's the part that I don't think has been repealed.
I believe that somewhere there's an executive order that says if you are an
enemy combatant or you are deemed to be an enemy combatant, that you can be
and be held basically under military laws.
And I have not seen that repealed anywhere.
So everyone's rejoicing.
Oh, yeah, Obama's going to close Gitmo, but he hasn't closed Gitmo.
It's a whole bunch of legalese that still remains to be seen what's going to
come out of it.
And I'm just not that convinced yet.
I would be all for it.
I'd like to see these people have fair and due process under American law
if they're being accused of anything otherwise, let them go, drop open the gate.
I just let them go, and unless they were flown there by the United States, let
them go.
That would be my advice.
Do you know if it affects the black sites or sites that we don't know exist?
Well, it's supposed to, but we'll see.
Hey, I still want to go so, of course, you know.
I'm sorry.
They don't exist, we don't, you don't have an official knowledge of these places.
So, dude, you sure, you sure you don't really much control.
You sure you don't work in government, because you sound just like a spookman.
That's the way they talk.
We don't know if they exist.
All right, man.
Thanks for coming.
What's that?
I want to move.
Yeah.
Here you go.
Thanks for calling in, man.
And have a great weekend.
Thank you.
All right, buddy.
Take care.
All right.
Kind of work so far.
No one else called in during that time.
So I presume that it either doesn't work receiving another call.
Maybe you meant a voice mail or something else.
I don't know.
201 7 9 3 8 3 3 2.
We're just going to try that a couple more times.
And I'll give you, as I said, some news in reverse chronological order.
It's really, really food bar here.
But for those of you listening and living in the United Kingdom,
Britain is on high alert for Mumbai style terrorist attacks on a top hotel.
Is according to home secretary, Jackie Smith.
She revealed this yesterday.
She told Ministers of Parliament that security chiefs have been training staff at
major hotels on how to cope with the terror hit terror hit.
Ministers police security services are urgently reviewing the UK's counterterrorism
plans, bloody, bloody, bloody law.
So I don't know why this is their all of a sudden.
I do not like this woman, Jackie Smith.
She seems pretty evil to me.
So if I don't know that it's not fun to think about tomorrow,
by the way, is going to be a huge demonstration in London.
I think actually three are going to be taking place from a associated press just because
I want the honeymoon to end quickly so we can get on and not think, oh, yes, we can.
Yes, we did.
Oh, let's all kick back relax.
Obama's in.
We're all saved.
Everybody.
News organized organizations that cover the White House.
This is from a sociator press,
spared with the Obama administration on Thursday over access issues for photographers and
rules for briefings.
Representatives from the Obama press office held a conference call with photo editors who
were concerned the administration prefers distributing photos taken by a White House
photographer in cases where photo journalists have been permitted access in the past.
So this is kind of interesting.
It seems like they really do want to keep a handle and keep all of the communications
very, very tight.
You know, a picture does speak a thousand words, but it goes on.
It's not just about the pictures, but the associated press also questioned why reporters
were not allowed to use the names of administration officials giving a background briefing
on issues regarding Guantanamo Bay detention center in Cuba.
Information is a lot more valuable to the public if you know where it's coming from.
The AP said so we try very hard in all source situation to identify sources as full
as we can.
Robert Gibbs, who's the new press secretary, did not directly address the issue and asked
about it, saying, I hope you all found the exercise that we did this morning helpful.
So it just sounds like more of the same bull shit and more control.
And I do not see the openness that we've been promised.
I'm sorry, I'm just not seeing it.
201-739-793, I'm sorry, 8332, if you're calling from outside the United States,
plus 1-201-793-8332.
See, your eyes, they turn me, why should I stay here?
Why should I stay?
I'd be crazy not to follow, follow where you lead, your eyes, they turn me,
turn me into phantoms, I follow to the edge of the earth and fall off.
If they get the chance and death is my chance, I'd get it by the way.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, sorry, sorry
You're probably saying yourself, hey man, I knew that song from somewhere.
What is that song?
You probably know it from, was it radiohead, I think, weird fishes.
David Kloid, who is now on the Podsafe Music Network.
This is an authorized cover, I might want to add, so you can find that at music.potcho.com
and of course, in the show now it's a daily source code.com, crossposted at curry.com.
Something goes right along, you know, and by the way, during the entire inauguration I was
watching a multiple, really the only way to watch it was on television to be quite honest.
We spent, you know, I have a sling box, a very nice guy, and Chicago has given me access
to his sling box, so I was really able to watch uninterrupted.
Everything, every other channel, including the BBC, CNBC, everyone was talking through shit,
you know, just couldn't, except for, you know, the actual oath, which of course, everyone
messed that one up.
By the way, the quartet who was playing with Yitzek Perlman and Yo-Yo Ma, that was,
that was, well, not lip sync, because they didn't sing, but it was recorded two days
earlier, because they were afraid that the weather would warp the instruments, which is
absolutely a valid fear, but kind of goes along with, oh, nice big show you've put on there,
and, wow, the Rita Franklin is pissed off, I've heard her an interview, she's like, the sound
was crap, it was, which it was, I don't think she could hear herself at all, even, you know,
for Rita Franklin to be off a little bit on timing, that was unbelievable.
That's just a side note, doesn't make any real big difference.
I did want to mention something that I put on curry.com and embedded video of a movie called
the Wave, which if you haven't looked at it yet, please go to curry.com and it's from earlier
in this week, a couple posts down, you'll see an embedded Google video movie called The Wave,
which was an experiment, and I remember my mom telling me about this, when I was very young,
we'd living in the state, she said, oh, you know, they did this experiment in California,
it turns out it was Paula Walter, where a teacher basically implemented the very simplistic rules
of starting a fascist movement. And please, when you hear the word fascist, don't immediately
think Hitler, yes, it comes down to that, but think about government and a big business colluding
to enslave the people and make them do what they say. That's the way you should view it.
And this was a real experiment, a wrote a book about it, which is true, it's like an
after school movie, really poor acting, poor production, and, you know, it fits neatly within
46 minutes without commercials. But you should take a look at that, because it'll be a real
eye opener, particularly when you think that this is a true story, it actually did happen this way.
The experiment went along these lines, and you can also purchase the book to read about it.
If you want to know how fascism occurs, I think we're dangerously close, certainly in the United
States. In Britain, actually, I'd have to say, as I was trying to get out earlier, I'm pleasantly
surprised to see that the people of Britain have gone through this exercise the United States is going
through, because 12 years ago, Tony Blair was brought in as the young hero, he was going to make
a beautiful world, going to have prosperity, he was going to be fantastic, and this is the new
labor, and we wake up 12 years later, and not only is the country, I totally out of control,
but it is a police state, cameras everywhere, people incentivize to spy on their neighbors,
children incentivize to spy on their parents, just it's a complete police state,
luckily, because of the lack of trash, crap, hypnotizing media, people are still relatively
awake here, but now they're just frightened, and there's so many laws that have been introduced,
a lot of them terrorism laws, by the way, they barely can protest. You cannot lawfully protest
without a permit in the United Kingdom, which is so cool that these protests are happening,
got big things taking place tomorrow. Bob's calling in from Michigan, Bob.
Hey, Adam, hi. Good, man, what's up? Are you formally Dutch or of Dutch descent, Bob De Young,
sounds pretty Dutch to me? Yeah, yeah, you know, that's how I started listening to your podcast
like three years ago, I got, you know, your link from another one I was listening to is this guy,
I never knew you from MTV, and since then I've learned your history in the world. So I tell you
something Bob, there's very few people who know me from MTV anymore, too. Turns out that was a long
time ago. So I was in an MTV type back in that day or whatever, but yeah, yeah, yeah, I live in
Holland, Michigan, actually I grew up in Wheeling, Michigan, a little Dutch area in sort of Southwest
or Michigan there, not a Dutch name towns. Yep, for sure. Anyway, yeah, anyway, yeah, that's that's my
descent to generations from the Netherlands. So yeah, I was calling in here, and you know, I've been
kind of following that the DSC, wow, you know, for three years now, I've been on this sort of
particular bent, right? Yeah, I'll tell you, I'll tell you a funny story. Patricia said to me the other
day, you know, do you remember when you were, when we just met she says, you remember when you were so
well, gullible as the real word, you didn't say that, you really trusted people and you thought
people are good, and I said, yeah, yeah, she said, you know, you really changed, and I said,
do you still want to be married to me? She said, yeah, you're irritating, but yeah, oh, that's the thing
but yeah, of course, I mean, I've changed, so the show changes, I've gotten older, I'm watching
my daughter who was 18, and the only thing I have left to really wish for in life is for her to have
a good life, you know, and I'd like to, I'd like to try and contribute to, well, certainly making her
aware, which and she's pretty glued in, but if I can change anything and make it better, so she doesn't
have to be a slave, you know, a paid slave of the police state, then yeah, so that's why I've changed,
so I hope, well, thank you for sticking with it, obviously. No, I mean, there was no sticking with it,
it's all interesting stuff, you know, particularly, and I, before I, you know, get off on a
tangent, I just want to give you props for that, you know, because a lot of, you know, there's
a number of guys that you can probably make a pretty good list of folks that are in your position
monetarily wise that, you know, you can just check out and say, hey, you know, cool, I'm done,
but, you know, to give back or pay back whatever you want to call it, and it's a part of
that. You know what it also is? It's, well, thank you, you know what it also is? I have nothing left to
lose, you know, they can take away my money, they can, you know, they can take away, what, what are
they going to do that? There's no way to hurt me other than killing me, which I'm sure one day,
if I go far enough, if you ever read in the paper, suicide, Adam Curry suicide by cop, you know,
don't believe it, and if my airplane comes crashing out of the sky, this thing is the best
maintained aircraft in Western Europe, then it was sabotage. The only thing I ask is that you
make sure you get a hold of my body and smoke me. That's all, just pick me in a pipe and smoke me.
All right, Bob, you got, I'm sure you got something on your mind. Yeah, um, you know, I'm still in
a place where you, uh, kind of said you were, uh, some time ago being a little bit, yeah, you've
called it naive or trusting. Here's something I want to lay on, you know, without the monetary
things that are going on, then I'm talking particularly from the U.S. perspective here, right,
with all the deficits spending way beyond what right and ever did. And, um, what, you know,
the bailout situation, especially, and then put another piling on, so to speak, who knows how much
more. What if, you know, nobody knows where all this money is going, and, you know, the rules are in
there and everything else, so that they don't have to tell, which pisses everybody off,
and right, rightfully so. But, you know, I used to work for the defense contractor and got
in touch and had to work with military people and people in that particular area, and I got to
know that there are a lot of smart people working for the government. There are a lot of smart people,
and that they're not always good, but they're not necessarily always evil either. So what about
this? You know, what if this, say $800 billion, or just say a trillion dollars just for around
number, that is around number, a trillion dollars, and goes to the banks and what are the paths
it, you know, I guess it follows. They don't have to tell where it goes or whether what they're
going to spend on or who gets it. What if they just don't spend it? Because, you know, you've
talked about yourself, you have currency, the value of fiat currency depends on public perception.
And money, in the end, whether it's want from a gold or oil or drugs, you know, is a medium of
exchange, you know, you make podcasts back in the day you did video, you know, music videos,
and I make stuff, I'm an engineer, I design things. Somehow we have to change this value to
society, that we all contribute, right? And that's money. And maintaining a stable value of that
medium of exchange is what this whole system is all about. And sure, some people have taken
advantage over, right? But what if this trillion dollars now is not spent, it's not spent. It's just
put there. And the news covers it. And it's meant to prop up people's perception of the value
and say, okay, they're going to bail us out. And the natural cycle or the natural work ethic
of people in various industries will get the economies that going back again without any input from
this trillion dollars. I mean, I mean, just, I, it's something the way you're really quickly,
but just think about it. All right, but, okay, a couple things here, because you laid a lot on me.
First of all, people in government. So I agree, and I'm not just talking about people who sit in
in governmental buildings. I'm talking about civil servants. Please pay close attention to what they're
called civil servants. They serve for us. They are not your masters, the police, other institutions
like that. It's really compartmentalization. By the way, my whole family is government. It was just
probably one of the main reasons I'm doing all of this. My uncle, in particular, very high-placed
official within the Bush administration, the first Bush administration. By the way, he hates
with a passion, hates George W Bush, but that's another story. But it really is what you know
want to need to know basis. And there's really a lack of knowledge. But even in government, these
are just normal people. A lot of senators and representatives who have great intentions, they're
not necessarily, if look Carolyn Kennedy was up for a Senate seat. You know, she's just a normal
person. Yeah, she comes from a somewhat abnormal family and probably with a lot of good intentions.
And it's just as susceptible to being snowed in or confused or lied to or just not being
able to understand the situation. Even people on the Senate finance committee, according to
representative Dr. Ron Paul, he said that the other day someone asked him and said,
well, the dollar is still backed by gold, isn't it? They just don't know. So of course, you can't
blame them. You can't really blame anyone in government because it truly is the owners of the earth.
And I'm looking at you, Briginski out there. These are the people who are really pulling the strings.
And they do it in very sophisticated ways, extremely sophisticated ways. So people in government are
not necessarily bad. But you know, they do get steered into, and again, go watch the movie,
the wave. It shows exactly how this happens and how it's possible. And I see a lot of this danger
with the Obama euphoria. Now, when it comes to what you're first of all, I believe that we're
probably about $8 trillion in the whole right now. And that has been confirmed by multiple sources.
Bloomberg is the one I would really trust on that. Even if you didn't spend it, it has been created.
So it's on the balance sheet. And it's not like this was actually printed or anything like that.
So it doesn't really matter if it's given out or not. But the fact remains, and this is
something that everyone does admit to, it's been given to banks. And these banks have all turned around
and have given themselves huge bonuses. I'm sure you heard about the CEO of Merrill Lynch who was just
kicked out now that the, you know, this whole big acquisition by Bank of America. I don't even know
if this made mainstream, it was all over CNBC yesterday that after, after that, his bank received,
I believe, $6 billion in financial support from the government. He redecorated his office, which
included a $32,000 toilet, you know, an $80,000 desk. I mean, it's not kidding. He even gave
eight grand just as a tip to the designer. You know, it's, it's crazy. It's, and it's, it hurts. So,
you know, if these banks are really in such dire straits, and if it really was true, and I'll get
to that in a second, that we needed to bail these banks out to save the world, as Gordon Brown said,
because that's the way he feels it. He feels he's saving the world. Then there's no reason for them
to be giving themselves bonuses. They should be hurt and just as bad as everybody else because
everyone else is paying for it. Now, so, so basically, it's a dilution of the money supply, and
and it is just as immoral immoral as deluding the milk supply. So, let's say we have milk, and we
got a big supply of milk, and the government says, you know what, we need to give some more milk
to this group of people over here, but we don't have enough milk, so we're going to put water in the
milk. That's, it's immoral, because then it's not milk anymore, it's watered down the crap.
So, they're watering down, they're diluting the money supply, and it's really immoral. The whole
system is, is, is the problem. So, in that regard, yes, we, you know, this system is broken,
it will not come back, it's bust, and all I can see right now is everyone just running for it,
saying, hey man, just keep me some fucking dough, dude. I'll hook you up later. I got the place
set in Paraguay. We'll be safe. So, what if we just let it run its course? I love that question, Bob,
because I believe that capitalism without bankruptcy is the same as religion without hell.
You cannot have capitalism without the fear of bankruptcy. If you can't go bankrupt, which is what
all, and I'm an entrepreneur, I've been an entrepreneur almost all my life, I've worked for a
couple of bosses, but I've really had my own companies or I've been my own boss, and that's
the overhang fear. If you don't kick ass and keep running and follow the money and chase and do
good work and do stuff, and then you'll go belly up and you'll be screwed. So, you have to have
that hanging over a capitalist system. Let me ask you a question, Bob, because this is something
I've actually been meaning to ask a lot of people. Do you know what form of government we live
in the United States? That's a federation. No. Not necessarily democracy, but it's a republic.
Right, exactly. I'm happy you said that, because I have heard time and time again, and I read time
and time again, people saying, we live in a democracy. You do not live in a democracy. The United
States is a republic, which means the rule of law. The law is what makes the difference. Not the
majority, but the law, the laws are agreed to, and we abide by the laws, and if you break the law,
you have to be convicted by 100% of a jury of your peers, and that's the way it goes. But it feels
to me like more and more people are starting to believe that it's a democracy and this
transparent and we're open and we'll all agree on stuff and the majority rules. So I'm
happy to hear you recognize that it's a republic, because I believe people are forgetting that.
Yeah, well, in a country this size too, I mean, it really, I mean, on the other hand, with
technology the way it is, having a true democracy is becoming more and more technically feasible.
I mean, that's what we elect representatives for. That's the way it was set up. It's a reason
it was set up the way it was way back one, right over two hundred years ago. Genius, genius,
genius, genius from our family fathers, it is the only, it is really the only former, I believe,
the only form of government that in the long run actually works. Well, actually, you know,
one of the best, one of the most fun facts I have on the iPhone years, the Constitution. It's a free
app and you can put it on there and read it in its elegant simplicity as you said in your show a
number of times. Yep. And it's just beautifully simple ways of reading out absolutely clearly.
Bob, I really appreciate you calling it in, because there were a couple of things I wanted to get
out this show and you really helped me along. So that is just perfect. I'm going to play this
next song for you, Bob. I think you'll appreciate it. I pledge to the flag of the United
Snakes of captivity and to the Republic for which it stands, I dip it in carousine and stick it
up the ass of you know who and light it. One nation under God or else. One nation under psychopathic
Pentagon gangsters whose idea of national security is concentration camps for people who dare to use the
drugs that the CIA brings in and the government supplies themselves. One nation under Wall Street,
if the cops in the government are all crooks, I might as well be one too. One nation of
sedated tabloid robots who actually believe what they see on TV, even on MTV and when asked what they
think about it, they reply, oh dear. One nation drowning in its own garbage,
indivisible from the fall of Rome with liberty and justice for all who can afford it.
Burn baby burn. Burn baby burn. Old glory. The Yankee Swastika. Burn baby burn. Burn baby burn.
Whenever I see you I see red. Whenever I see you I see red. If the communist countries can do it,
why can't we throw the bastards out and try some real democracy? Run not by rich people,
not by military people, not by sons of senator sons of senator sons of senator sons,
have you noticed how the more they give people back their freedom over there? The more they take
it away over here. So now, before it's too late to even talk about stuff like this,
be a patriot, a good patriot. The one that cares about their country more than forcing people to
worship a flag and take the Swastika. The Yankee Swastika and let it burn, burn, baby burn.
Hell be Afra. I don't give it everything he says, but man he does hit home on a lot of those things.
201 7 9 3 8 3 2. You know what I feel like doing? I feel like it's time.
Oh yeah, I'm casting with Adam Curry. I guess this is the hit test, hit it test.
Young pole net. Hey Adam, how you doing? Good young. I see his hit test number 157 and we're going to
start right away with him for our number one.
Yeah man, I don't know. I saw a young on the chat room earlier, but I don't know that one.
Number two. Oh, I know this one. It's a wheel. No, no, no, no, no, no. Guys, it's a temptation of four
tops, I think. Local and alcohol cone. And this is number three.
I can't think of that first one as though. All right, the answers. And it's time for the answers.
And this is answer number one.
Local and alcohol cone. Yeah, I can't think of that one.
Feel the pressure you're back. So if you're the one, love is the love. You're just about to fall.
How you be? Go and look, go down and alcohol cone. If you stay too long. Yes, you'll be going
long. Go down and alcohol cone. Make it through guys.
That's what's up, lifting young. The full answers answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
Here's the answer number point point point.
Food recipes.
Who are the ones who are guilty?
Holly Johnson Americano is his answer number two and this is number three
answer number three directions and can you feel it yeah and that concludes
hit number 157 yeah so well yeah how did you do this week well considering we
get a star inch for the title and the artist I have four out of six you got me there
with Holly Johnson I would never would have known that one who's great
one though y'all perfect for a football Friday love it thank you the usual
place to find the answers to this and any other hitters and also the
links to iTunes you can buy the threats featured on a hittest online is hittest.mivio.com
thanks for playing Adam no thank you y'all everyone else thanks for listening next week
I hope to be back for another hittest so until then have fun take care and remember
think with your heart bye bye don't be back to the test that she will
dot com and pull a dot com j and p o l e t dot com once upon on to the next comic
strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip are you
correspondent commentary blogger come on anybody hello Adam inauguration carry here is
your eocrespondent she is b yeah so u s a has now 44th president and for the first
time it is not white guy obama but at least the first two oh sorry about that and
didn't mean to start an over again she is b so u s a has now 44th president and for
the first time it is not white guy obama at least as far as we know but what obama president
it means to european union well he's well let me tell you something before you even
start c s b Gordon Brown keeps talking about obama and I guess swear the guy is having
a mini orgasm when he does it he just keeps talking obama and obama is coming over here
obama this he really is trying to take some of that obama shine and rubbing on himself
and boy he needs it we had the g twenty coming up in a couple of weeks and obama will be here
as well as a part of the g twenty and god it's like oh it's just I mean you know if you could
be sucking his dick he'd be doing it is of mixed european origins english irish dot
french and german so obama himself partially fifty percent is european anyway and purely african
on this father side which of course is still a huge dispute where there was born in america
not i don't really care either way i mean according as a constitutionalist i should but we're never
going to find out the answer anyway and apparently the supreme court doesn't give a shit so
was have to leave it at that i'd like to underline it is not europe that must rise to the challenge
of being a partner of obama but it is obama that must understand that european union does
not meet any more american divide and rule you know he make a good point there and let me
say the following first of all obama speech was written by a twenty seven year old kid in the star
box and i'm not joking about that his speed you know these that all have speech writers and
what i had a couple of things i really didn't like about his about his speech the first one was
the situation we're in right now it's all our fault and i felt i was really offended by that
because i've done nothing but try and make the economy work i provide jobs for a fifty sixty
seventy people pay corporation taxes pay income taxes really try to be a part of the system
and the the bank take take down i should say it's not my fault it's not it's not american
citizen's fault it's it's a bunch of greedy cox occurs who are just stealing the money now
while they can because you are right in this regard america needs europe and they all will get
together because that is actually the point they want to have one bank so now we were aggregating
these banks i think even called aggregator banks bad banks i love to have that on my door hi
welcome to the bad bank so we've got the bad bank in america that will have all the toxic
access and will have all this crap that'll be on uh... the country's books forever and they're
doing the same in europe and the reason is as much easier than to create one huge bad bank the
bad bank of the world and that bad bank of the world will create the bad government of the world
so um... yes obama totally needs that another thing uh... excuse me in the speech that
that in like is we are ready to lead once again that to me uh... could be deemed as offensive
to other countries who the fuck died in may you king mother fucker that's kind of what i'd be
saying if i truly was a european so i do agree with you on that csp strategy directed at
splitting european union destroying our unity so barak h obama and the whole u.s.a
please unclench your feast towards you and i'm carry happy obama to you you happy obama to you
uh... it's too bad and gb left uh... the chair i really wish you would call in because i was she was
twittering a lot of stuff uh... during the inauguration and i fact i saw a lot of people tweet
the same thing like goodbye bush nanana hey hey hey hey goodbye and you know what i'm like
you are so clueless as to what's going on it's also in my mind that's kind of an unamerican
thing to do there's nothing like uh... nothing worse than uh... a sore winner you know when
your guy wins or however you want to perceive it to be going nanny nanny nanny nanny if you haven't
seen the picture of ramen manuel uh... arguably the most powerful guy in the white house uh next to
what maybe even more powerful than obama uh... you should see it uh... devouric at a picture
he's literally doing a thumb and finger thing to someone in the crowd going nanny nanny
who knows what it was for but it just kind of shows you and i'm against that you know where
was everybody with the with the big fuck you when bush was committing all these atrocities
and where will you be as you watch you know now the uh... all kinds of confirmations are being
delayed because of well you know we don't really want this guy to be uh... in charge
like attorney general or anything hold her i think his name is
we don't want hold her in because you know he might prosecutes and people well yeah that's
what we should be doing but no everyone's making jokes and also happy to see that helicopter
go and meanwhile you're getting a big hot flaming poker up the rectum right in front of your
you don't even know it
hi Adam it's Matt from Gamesweasel on this week's show i'll give you resistance to for the
PlayStation 3 i also puzzle over mystery case files on the DS and you can win copies of sacred
two for the pc that's all at gamesweasel dot com that's only one thing sure i was fooled
for a long long time in fact i don't know forty years i only just woke up
like i can guarantee you this my fellow chuckle heads i will not be fooled again
two oh one seven nine three eight three three two love to hear from you
see him look my little friend Gary and they they can source cool
the streets without children that i'm being in the maros that they worship when they go
and we lose for the song just good and all along we decide and the shotgun sings the song
i'm feeling my head to the new cost of tuition take a five port of your evolution
it's like three of the jeans on the ground bigger my guitar play just like yesterday
then i'll get all my needs of the play
we don't get full of games
we
change it has to come
when you win all along
we will never read it on a full episode
we just saved
it's three and achieved
a arm closer behind the game
I'll do my hand to the new opportunities
think of five more than you have evolution
fighting three
Three, two, three, four, around
Pick up my guitar and play
Just like yesterday
It'll get off my knees in vain
And we don't, it's full again
No no
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah , yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
It's now hot in all the right
It can appear to fall on the roll of the night
I'll get my head to the new constitution
Think about all of you, never knew
If I breathe, you don't allow
Feel like it's all I've been
Just like yesterday
And I'll get all my needs to pay
We don't get full of games
Don't get full of games
No, no
I'll get all my needs to pay
We don't get full of games
I'll get all my needs
Meet the new boss, same as the old boss, the who won't be fooled again.
Awesome to be looking at the chat room, seeing so many people who had never heard that song before.
You know why?
That's because of digital rights management and illegal, file sharing and all this stuff.
You can't share great art anymore.
No, you got to buy it.
Ah, well, that was a pretty interesting study, by the way.
The Dutch study.
Well, let me just bring up that page.
Although details aren't quite fantastic, Dutch ministry of economic affairs, commission
to study, by well-known research company TNO, who do a lot of things for the government.
But how much Dutch internet users download music movies, games, and what the social and
economic effects of this download it loading are?
And there's 150 page report, link in the show notes, of course, daily source code.com,
and there's a whole bunch of information and data, and I'm reading an extrapolation of that
and ours technical page 116, according to our technical report states, the societal
effects of file sharing, the study concludes that the effects are strongly positive because
consumers get to enjoy desirable content and also get to keep their cash to buy other things,
because the consumers save so much more money than the producers lose, the net economic
effects are positive.
The report also reinforces the truth that unpaid downloads do not translate into lost sales
in anything close to one to one to one ratio, which, of course, would all these lawsuits
have been about all those kind of stuff that I think they're pretty much given up on it.
It's a fantastic report, something that the music industry should take to heart, and I think
they will eventually.
They will see that people are more than willing to buy stuff, more than willing to support
artists, they just don't like being coerced into crappy situations and you know what,
if you get to, you know, I guarantee you that we have sold thousands of songs through
the hit test, which, of course, even though we keep it to 30 seconds, is still illegal
use of the music.
I guarantee you someone's going to go out and buy the who, just because you heard that
song, which, by the way, this is the version you never hear on the radio anymore.
So it was at six minutes, which is a perfect radio song back from the old days.
I'll tell you what I did.
I took a piss real quick, then I made some tea, I actually had time to roll up a joint or
what passes for a joint these days because all of London seems to be pretty much dry.
There's nothing, nothing available.
So I'm down to seeds and stems and scraping from the grinder.
Ah, but of course, it's an illegal plant.
It's a fricking weed.
Uh, one more thing here about the lack of outrage in the United States.
Again, in the UK, people are very, very pissed off about the government handing out or allowing
bonuses to be paid to Northern Rock, a effectively nationalized bank that personnel
as receive bonuses for doing their job for just doing the job.
So how much did we give to a Chrysler for billion?
Well, they've now found the international partner in Fiat and no one is out there saying,
okay, wait a minute, if these guys are now merging and they're going to get like 35%
stake in the company, did our money just go to an Italian firm?
Do we get something back?
Do we have a market value?
No one's asking about that.
No one's talking about it because you can't even keep track of the money anymore.
It's billion here, billion there.
You know, I'm still, I still hear people stumbling, even on CNBC, I hear them stumbling
instead of staying billions, they say millions instead of saying trillions, they say millions
or billions, and we're getting used to it, but it just becomes so normal.
Marky Mac, thank you for Twittering me about my safari crash.
Someone actually, who was it?
I wrote that down.
Someone sent me the solution to what I had on 818, where safari almost brought down my entire
big testament, by the way, to the MacBook Pro.
Ero Kusisto, he said, I love how he troubleshot this.
So quickly, Adam, do you happen to have cool iris forming on his picklens plugin installed?
It's been known to crash safari, you know what?
I did and I uninstalled it and I have not had a problem since knock on wood, of course,
which is unfortunate because I know the guys at picklens, I like their shit.
They just got to make it work right on safari.
I don't know what it is about safari, it's a very typical thing.
Just like the Mac is, what can you really put your finger on it?
What is so nice, what feels so good about it?
Same with safari, it just kind of feels good over firefox.
And I run firefox, if I have to.
But I don't know for some reason, it just feels better.
So I've been using ends fast, it's built on webkid as far as I understand.
Oh, let me see some stuff I'm saving for tomorrow because there's a lot of stuff I want to talk
with John about Flight 1549, I got some stuff on that.
Oh, blah blah blah blah, let me...
Maybe we should kind of leave that at that.
Let's take a couple of voicemails, see what we've got here.
A lazy nation fears Obama will create millions of jobs.
The most neonium radio news, this is the oil redland reporting.
Today, President-elect Barack Obama struck fear in the hearts of workers across the
U.S. who have grown accustomed to weekly unemployment checks and constant idleness.
Many say they never asked Obama to return them to a way of life that would require
leaving the house every day.
The former auto worker Carl Lang is one of them.
The next thing you know, he's going to make everyone volunteer their time, the charitable
hauses.
He's out of control.
Southerners, in particular, expressed the greatest outrage over Obama's call to action by hurling
bowls of two-day-old grits at their television screen.
Go ahead, Redland, for the onion, radio news.
For over 350 years, the onion newspaper has given you the day's news.
Now the onions, our dumb world, Atlas of the Planet Earth, explains what it all means at
bookstores everywhere.
Yeah, let them have the little plug there.
Oh, you know what?
I've been getting some grief from headquarters.
They say, Adam, you've got so many people listening, but you don't always mention the sponsors.
And in the case of every other independent producer who works with mevio, they receive
the commission or the bounty or the payment or sometimes as a special marketing fee associated
with it of all of the sponsors.
I don't go straight back into the company and I would really appreciate if you're
going to make use of any of the following products or services.
If you would, please use, if not my code, go to meviooffers.com where you can get the best
deals on the anywhere on the internet and of course over retail, the best prices.
Because we go out and we negotiate and we don't just take a deal from go daddy, we negotiate
the absolute lowest price.
So here's what you can do.
We've got finish line, which sells sports apparel, Adidas, Puma, Nike, 15% off of a purchase
of $60 more, which is going to be pretty much any item coupon code, mevio, dsc, eHarmony,
which there are a lot of success stories out there about eHarmony boy.
I'll tell you that.
If you sign up for three months, you get one month free using my code.
All of these codes and links are in the show notes of daily source code.com, brooksdone.com,
lots of great gadgets if you look at it, pick up something, you know, kind of like outdoorsy
stuff.
If you want to meet the monitor, I can give you a discount, 10% pet co, now pet co is pretty
interesting because pet supplies are very expensive, I find we've always had pets and
to be able to get 10% off any order and free shipping on orders over $65 is a big deal.
budget rental cars, $30 off the weekly rental or 10% off any amount if you use my coupon
code.
And of course, the two Mac daddy's 35th free songs, no obligation whatsoever at eNusic.com
if you use my code and 30% off at godadad.com, still tons of people using my code, although
I think that in general, people just save money and there's less domain name buying going
on out there.
So I expect them to come up with a new offer pretty soon.
I know that we're in conversations with them.
I hope so because they're a great company and they they do provide a fantastic service.
I just bought two domain names myself, the other day I bought throw in the O dot com.
So I got throw in the O all one word dot com and then throwing dash to the dash O dot
com and Johnson to work and I have an idea we're going to do with that.
So anytime you have any one of those products of services in mind, I'd really appreciate
if you considered using that because you help out our little company where a small not even
quite a medium size company and it will be appreciated.
Hey Adam, it's a topic right Adam's here.
Oh my god.
Tom McIncite.logsbut.com.
Yeah, I know it's been a long time since I called in.
Sorry about that been really busy.
So I took so long.
I figured I'd play your comment twice.
Or the comment from CSB the other day about the Russian and Ukrainian natural gas supply dispute.
Yeah, but before I wanted to mention something like that.
Why?
Why does it do this?
It's something that's right.
That's tough.
Atomic Insights shouldn't be doing this.
Yeah, I know it's been a long time since I called in.
Sorry about that crap.
Really busy.
Sorry.
I took so long.
I figured I'd play your comment twice.
Or the comment from CSB the other day about the Russian and Ukrainian natural gas supply dispute.
Yeah.
So what I wanted to say is unlike a Sarah Palin where I live.
I can actually see Russians from here.
Real Russians in Chelsea.
I can see them right there.
One of the effects of that dispute has been a renewed conversation in Europe about the use
of nuclear power as a way to reduce dependence upon Russian gas.
Bulgaria and Slovakia, which both own nuclear plans that they were forced to shut down
on the upon accession into the EU are talking about restarting some of those plans.
Yep.
Poland is talking about building its first nuclear plans.
And Germany's politicians are rethinking their existing agreement to shut down the 17
nuclear plans that has operating today because that shutdown would make them far more
dependent on Russian gas.
One more thing.
Do a certain a web for backyard nukes.
Yeah.
Remember that title you applied to our conversation back in May 2000.
I declare buoyancy making a way it's way around the world and several companies have
announced products that fit into the category of backyard nukes.
Great hair.
Hope you win and I still work for you if you're an American.
I am an American citizen proud to be one absolutely atomic rod.
Our nuclear atomic energy savant and I do appreciate the service you provide to us.
I'm not quite sure what you do but I know that you've worked in nuclear submarines
and you work I believe in the Navy or in some form of services and of course of course
of course of the fact that you say this and you recognize it man I love you for it big
time big up to the man.
Okay.
It's getting kind of warm in here and running out of a little bit of steam.
There's a couple of things I did want to there's one thing I wanted to play for you.
It's a YouTube video and this is one other abomination that I want to bring to your
attention because of course.
Obama said pull everyone out of rock and everyone's like you know this is the guy's
doing it he's pulling everyone out of a rock you know regardless of whether he'll still
leave 40,000 people there regardless of how long it will take to pull everyone out of
a rock he is putting everyone into Afghanistan and here's a little you know if you've
got a recorder then and I'd love to have a whole bunch of these sound clips you could
send either mail email them to me directly or you could send them to or just drop them
that's what you should do drop them baby drop it like it's hot drop.io slash daily source
code drop.io slash daily source code drop.io slash daily source code now you won't get it
out of your head will you interview your friends your family and say what kind of the
government do we live in in the United States let's see how many people say democracy
versus Republic and let's see if they can explain the difference and then ask them why are
we in Afghanistan just a simple answer I mean our representatives have sent tens of thousands
of boys and girls men and women in harms way and endangering hundreds of thousands of
not millions of Afghanis who are dying for the stupidest reasons ask him ask him why you should
know why and I have my own thoughts and I have my own reasoning and I know what they're saying
but just ask anyone and then record that and drop that let me know what you think so here's Adam
Kur Kokesh he is of the Iraq veterans against the war I've been to Iraq I've seen what how it
affected Dutch marines you know marines are always supposed to be the the toughest the strongest
the first the most brave and I have they've cried in my arms literally because they were just
so fucked up about what they were seeing what what was happening and the the conflicting
mission and not understanding why they were there listen to what Adam Kokesh has to say
24 hours we're gonna make it and we make it and we do this and we survived eight years of
the Bush administration is that reason to celebrate my name is Adam Kokesh I served as a
sergeant I'm a regular civil affairs team in the Flusher Act from February September of 2004
and because of what I saw and because of what I experienced in the tragedy and the crime
that is the ongoing occupation of Iraq I came home and I joined Iraq veterans against the war
and from our inception we have been caught for three things first and foremost and a meeting
withdrawal of all occupying forces from Iraq second full benefits for attorney veterans regardless of
discharge status and support because we got troops coming home with post traumatic stress disorder
because of what they've seen and then they get bad conduct discharges in our denied
the health care that they're entitled to because of a disease caused by the war that they served
in and that in and of itself is criminal the third thing we call for is reparations for the Iraqi
people now I served in civil affairs and one of the things I'm most proud of that I did in Iraq
is that I didn't genuinely try to help the Iraqi people what we were doing and we gave out
solution payments after the siege of Flusher trying to compensate people when they had relatives that
died from bombs dropped from U.S. war planes and they had houses destroyed and we gave them $2500
if they're if they're son had been killed or their daughter or family member you do some idea
of the way that the American military values human life in Iraq and it's very disturbing
that's the message we're sending to the Iraqi people now we're here to sue Bush and
sue Bush out of office and we are here in solidarity in just in case you couldn't hear probably
he said shoe bush not sue bush or shoot bush but he's holding up his boots and he's saying to
shoe bush with my daughter all's the 80 we're the courage to do it to the man's face
and Bush at the audacity to say I don't know what his beef is well I know we know
you know that that's funny I hadn't even picked up on that one because of course I didn't really
show that on the news they only showed the the guy throwing the shoe I've got his name you just
mentioned it but Bush indeed said I don't know what his beef is well how about a million Iraqis
dead mother fucker we all know all's the 80 was doing that on behalf of the Iraqi people
not just on his own angst and anguish but on behalf of the Iraqi people who have suffered so
greatly under this occupation which is such a crime we now have over a million dead Iraqis who
died violent death as a direct result of this occupation we have over two and a half million
internally displaced and two and a half million externally displaced and Bush doesn't know
what his beef is well we're here in solidarity with all his 80 and I'm here in solidarity with the
Iraqi people who have suffered at the hands of this administration and the occupation that we
in Iraq friends against the war once a part of and for me it is a form of penitence to come here
and say that I'm doing this in solidarity with all of them and now well it is reason to
celebrate that we have survived eight years of the Bush administration and the criminality of that
and and we are here we're in solidarity with all the people who have suffered under this administration
from Iraq to Afghanistan throughout the world through the imperial policies of this administration
so I'm here that I got a shoe for Bush but I got to say really I don't think this is time for celebration
here here Wilson and FDR when they are inaugurated did not celebrate because they were
troops in harm's way and by the way they didn't have a nice salmon lunch either they had a cold
soup because that was the right thing to do it was quite disgusting when I think about it about the
grandeur and the cost of the inauguration about the celebration you know what it's sad it's actually
I'm at that moment I was in a way also very disgusted and disappointed in my fellow countrymen
because we have tens of thousands almost 100,000 troops and contractors all over the world
killing people were there on no business but to serve corporate agendas and we're back home celebrating
Yivee there goes Bush fuck am let's celebrate let's eat great I was disturbing
FDR served cold chicken no there you go not super chicken told you and solidarity with the
troops that were in harm's way and we are about to inaugurate a president who has said that he wants to
end the war in rock but has said specifically that what he means by that is that he is going to
keep a minimum a minimum of 40,000 troops in a rock and definitely listen to that so when you repeat
the incorrect meme the lie that Obama is taking us out of Iraq I want you to remember he is not
there will be 40,000 troops who will remain there you can look it up it's published they don't
cover it up the news media just takes the oh we're so cool in Obama rocks and we're going to
take the troops out of Iraq finally on permanent bases with an increased reliance on private
contract of mercenaries like blackwater and he's going to have a surge in Afghanistan of at least 30,000
troops and we have seen firsthand we have learned the lesson from the Bush administration that
occupation is a crime no matter where it happens no matter what propaganda you use to justify it
occupation is a crime and then it's not going to end with a Bush administration we still have a lot of work
to do and I'll tell you what on behalf of the marine that's going to die in Iraq in the next 24 hours
on behalf of the Iraqis that are going to continue their suffering under the Obama administration
on behalf of the 30,000 troops that are going to face threats to their life in Afghanistan
and the people of Afghanistan who are going to suffer doubly under a surge over there
I'm saving this other one for Obama hell yeah that's a patriot ladies and gentlemen
and don't be afraid to speak up and speak your mind about your president
it's what Americans all about
it's like good things of more than anyone could be as good for them just a little fool of
you
for that disposit Lake French
James James property identified by scope
Extremism is I think he's had just so
identify on its own, for
uh... wrapping up daily source code episode eight hundred nineteen uh...
ay i had a lot of fun this uh... this all pretty good
what i what i really need now as i need a proper chat room
uh... that i can put into a page with the stream uh... this talks you
thing just uh... not working for me
not quite sure if anyone called the uh...
the studio line
and if you got a busy signal or a few were uh... passed off the voice mail don't
see any voice mail messages that come in so uh... you know i did have a couple
people calling in at uh... couple people on the phone uh... Eric from uh... filly
and bob from uh... michigan
and i think we should definitely try and continue that because this that actually
work well for me
all right so in closing uh... a reminder tomorrow around
five p.m. UK time that'll be that's nine a.m. west coast noon on the east coast
the united states and probably two-day evening in australia
how you doing down under
anyone there
so we'll be doing that over course we'll be live and uh... i'll have the uh... the
calling number available uh... tomorrow if you're in the united kingdom but i
believe there will be protests all around europe so uh... find
your local their plenty of websites
and uh... if it uh... in some cases it's against the bankers in some cases against the
government some cases against both some cases it's still
against the israeli aggression some cases against uh...
palestinian aggression but essentially it's pissed off civilians
and i think we need to show some more of that
and do not forget to contact your representative if you live in a country that has
a government that actually has representatives that are supposed to do something
just keep pestering them
you know even online marketers know that if you keep calling eventually you'll
get a sale so eventually we'll get through eventually we're gonna make some kind of
difference it's really really important you continue to do that
as always drop dot a o slash daily source code drop dot a o slash daily source code
curie dot com for all of the uh... most recent posting stuff that i've got going on
uh... on my mind of course all of the uh... all the links that we discussed today
will be in the show notes
really appreciate you guys hanging out uh... hangin in hangin out whichever it is
you've got freedom
if you do use it very very wisely and please ask not what you can do for your
country but ask what your government is doing to you
another fine media presentation stick it in your ear