Delta Sierra Charlie, 816.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
To the next generation video contenting my ears.
I don't need lost eating greens.
I like to think I'm flying into this church.
I'm guessing it's a battle curry.
For our Monday!
Oh, all the times I've come.
We're here for time, let it go.
Season's don't fear the reason.
Not to the wind, the sun of the rain.
We could be like this.
Come on, baby.
We'll take my head.
We'll be able to fly.
Don't fear the reason.
Not to the wind, the sun of the rain.
Oh, all the times I've come.
Come on, baby.
Call the time, let it go.
We're here for time, let it go.
Come on, baby.
Call the time, let it go.
We'll be able to fly.
Don't fear the reason.
Not to the wind, the sun of the rain.
Oh, all the times I've come.
Season's don't fear the reason.
Not to the wind, the sun of the rain.
Go!
We're here for time, let it go.
Go, we're here for time, let it go.
Give the last night I said yes, and if you stay as you can long,
Don't lose all the night away in the face,
If you can't lose one of his feelings,
But then you still want to meet me,
And I'll be fine.
Come on, let it be, let's not let it be.
She ran through it,
And I'll be fine.
They're the fact that you said it,
Keep that night,
I'll be fine.
Come on, let it be.
And just a little bit more cowbell.
Daily source code episode number eight hundred and sixteen,
Coming new from the curry terrace in southwest London,
In the United Kingdom,
In the eastern part of Gitmo Nation,
The bluer is to call,
Don't fear the repart.
I don't really fear him,
But he's out there, that's for sure.
You know, the past two weeks have been so full barred,
When it comes down to production and getting stuff done,
I just felt I really needed to do a full on full bar show.
Just couldn't eat it out on Friday.
I had to work ahead as I mentioned on eight hundred fifteen,
Which was one was that Tuesday, Wednesday last week.
I had to work one day ahead in the production schedule,
And I've successfully done that over the weekend.
Of course, a couple other things going wrong with the new set up,
Including, well, the biggest problem that just really,
I didn't understand how, how was happening.
I'm now recording on audio hijack pro,
Instead of recording everything multi track in Ableton Live,
And then usually, you know, that records either wave or AFF,
Whatever it is.
And then I'd, you know, just spin it, I think it was wave.
No, AFF.
And it's been that down to MP3 using iTunes.
I was just using audio hijack pro.
I've tried constant bit rate, tried all different versions,
And too many problems.
People literally could not listen to the entire show
Because of the timecode problems that have been all messed up.
So now I'm recording this in high quality AFF.
It's about 10 megs a minute.
And, and I'll use iTunes to add the show notes,
album art, and to compress it down to MP3.
Brand new music from the pretenders.
Mine have seen this on the video today over the weekend.
Got some free tickets for the pretenders for you.
Just keep it here on the source code.
Now you're home and gank your boot of please.
Pretty happy little resonance begging on a knees.
Illusion fills my head like an empty can.
That's been a million items living the same name.
Well, yeah, everything dry.
They're up on through the vein.
Whoa, it's making way back to the hot again.
By the way, look fantastic.
Can you hold boots of Chinese birthday?
I have written Krishna, I have written vomit too.
Going there, I'm still in love with you.
I see you in the birds and in the trees.
That's why they call me Krishna Mai.
They're everywhere.
Whoa, everyone through the vein.
Whoa, it's making way back to the hot again.
I'm found.
Look fantastic.
Can you hold boots of Chinese birthday?
Woo-hoo!
Yeah, hey, hey, hey.
Woo, dang it!
Fuck it, Thomas, we should tolerate the people and the things that make me want to hate
All I have I live must must be on me There's season begins human pageantry
Jesus Christ came down here as a living man If you can live a life of virtue, then I hope I can
One, two others, you would have a turn I'm back here and repeat until you learn
Under, oh, yeah, the red dot Time comes through the veins, oh, it's made the twain
Back in the heart again, and ever it does That living's life of a change, goes with its life
One, ten, for nothing, and proud of the way you look fantastic in your boots of Johnny's place
Oh, oh, brand new from the pretenders boots of Chinese plastic
We just got the video from their record label, Shangrelong music along with the MP3
I believe it's going up on the pod save music network, at least I sure hope so
Because it's just awesome and they're hitting the road the end of this month
I think US tour and the record label has given me a couple of tickets to give away
Now I've also promoted this on the video today
But we're keeping it real honest and fair doesn't matter where you
Where you caught the information to enter if you want to pair those tickets
Send it to join the show at neveo.com
Join the show at neveo.com for free pretenders tickets
courtesy of neveo and Shangrelong music
Hey Adam, Eric's a Portland
Your show has really been sucking ass back
Thank you
The comment thing is not working
You know, I know you're experimenting and that's cool
The one thing I didn't want to
That's what my mom always said. It's okay to experiment honey. Don't worry about it
Say that that is different and and cool about about the shows
Even though they are a little scattered
Is your compassion for the people that are writing and getting hurt
Really comes through when it's less staged
Podcast and you're your passion for for the issues you're talking about
Really come through so in that regard
I would say it's a plus plus but
For a whole man the production body is down
So thank thanks
Take care I'll be waiting for season
Alright, yeah, thank you
Yeah, I'm not quite sure how to work with the phone yet
I mean what I've done now is I've just unmuted everyone in the conference bridge
And I'm not sending the music back only my voice
So people can talk amongst themselves and I'd much much
Much more prefer you listen to the
Listen to the stream because the quality is much better
And of course if you log in to talk shoe then you also have a chat room there
Which people are using and
And you know, I could see who's on and I could of course I could call it you in any moment
So be prepared
It's the football Monday and it's in 1816
How about a little bit of water sound everybody
Some feel specter
I think it's a good idea
To the soul
And if I had to get in the car
Never let you go
So once you say you love me
I'll make you show
We'll make the turn there pick
Every place we go
So fun to play
We'll make the turn there pick
We'll make the turns there pick
Baby, now, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
Baby, now, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, beautiful love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love,
Gilling her on a mistrial hung jury 10 the two. We don't know if it was 10 who wanted to convict him or 10 who thought he should go
Scott free, but still got honor the man's work. What an amazing sound. That is Ron. That's me, my baby
Daily source code 816 where food bar, which means they'll be kind of low on talking about oh
You know the typical things how the new world order wants to kill us off and
And roll out some tunes. I like him hope you do
The radio the other day. I thought I got to share this with a chuckle. I didn't say Madison Lighthouse
From like the 60s I think
Talks kind of easy and people say she's crazy and had lots of missed the read
Oh
And nobody knows
Something about it and all in mine
It's a feeling that's fine and I just gotta say hey
Really gotta make it this well, and it's working so well
I'm a lucky fella and I just gotta tell her that I love her and let's meet
Because love proves when I'm almost there it goes and nobody knows
What an amazing light
There's something about it and all in mine
It's a feeling that's fine and I just gotta say hey
Really gotta make it this well, and it's working so well
And I can't get away
I'm a lucky fella and I just gotta tell her that I love her and let's meet
Because love proves when I'm almost there it goes and nobody knows
And the cool thing about those songs from back in the days
This is short, can play 10 of them, play five new ones
Yeah, I'll put that in the show now, is that it's in Lighthouse, my love rose when my rose married goes
My love is growing as my speed
All right, again, I'm not sending the music into the conference bridge
If anyone wants that change, I'm certainly happy to listen to a vote on that one
A couple of interesting articles that I did run across that I do want to share with you
And I love it when mainstream articles come out with the stuff that we've been talking about here
And just kind of confirms the thinking of the chuckleheads
This is from Bloomberg, and of course, you're seeing a lot, or I'm seeing a lot of articles
And I'm seeing many of them on the drop.au slash daily source code about the change
That President-elect Obama has promised us and well, this is a very tongue-in-cheek article
But interesting on the less Obama at the headline reads, Obama to maintain practice of naming donors to ambassador posts
So, and donors is kind of a misnomer, because there were several hundred, but a couple of really big what we call bundlers
And the way these guys work, and they did do it for all campaigns, by the way, for all political parties
Is they gather all of the individual checks from hundreds, thousands, sometimes thousands of people
And then they hand them in, and here's a bundle of money
And as a reward, it appears, and this is something that's been going on for many, many years
In fact, there was a time in the Netherlands when a new government was coming in, where I actually thought to myself, hey, this is a cool opportunity
If I help to get this party elected, you know, I can get an ambassador ship out of it
I think ambassador curry has a nice ring to it
And of course, well anyway, so here's a bit of the article, President-elect Obama will uphold at least one of Washington's old ways
The appointment of campaign donors to plum ambassador ships
And it goes on to tell you more about some of these bundlers or these donors, and of course, which, which other presidents have done this
And which is just about every single one of them, and the cool thing, of course, is that
I mean, there's some awesome ambassador, I should have gotten into this game, man
Ambassador ships to Rome and the Vatican are highly sought by Italian American and Catholic donors
And of course, the Bahamas is always a popular one
Yeah, that's some change for you, right there
Very happy to see over the weekend that the shoe throwing name has really, really caught on globally
Tons of protests, we're talking hundreds of thousands
Friends, France, I should say, and not even too far from here
SW6 Southwest London in Kensington, on the Kensington High Street
Thousands of protesters
Throwing shoes, protesting outside the Israeli embassy, which apparently is on the Kensington High Street or nearby
Unfortunately, a Starbucks was a, was a, a trashed in the process
But people are pissed off, they are very pissed off, and what's interesting is that
It's coming from two sides, we have the pro Israeli and the anti Israeli fractions
But I think everyone is kind of saying the same thing, this has to stop, this is ludicrous
Children dying, sitting in dirt with their dead parents around them, it's just, it's, ah, you, you want to talk about football
That's massively football, and really, really, I'm so happy that the protesters are catching on
But there's not a lot of pre-information about them, I wish I could tap in and help organize
And, and shit, if I knew when these things were taking place, I'd be out there myself
I'd love to go out with my eye river and get some, you know, get some impressions for you, play them on the Charlie
And I think I got a shoe or two, I'd like to send in someone's direction as well
I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I
could send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in something's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's turn, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like to send in someone's turn outside, I'd like to send in someone's direction, I'd like
Attention number one
Let me pause. I was gonna say Tina Turner
Since we've been together
You forever
You were the one
You were the best
Hi, Tina Turner. Let's stay together. It's answer number one
Yeah, it's came out
No, wait. This is answer number two
Is it?
We'll head party right
I want to know, can we feel it too?
Answer number two, cameo and candy
And this
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I've got it
But I keep those things
Last night, did you say my life?
Oh, the rap is great
From the song
Here comes
Oh, that's a problem
I can't say
Because I can do it in the mix
And if your man gives you trouble, then you will go down the level
No, you don't say
I say my life has answered number three
And that concludes
It says number 155
Yo
So Adam
Yeah
How did you do this week?
Well, worse than I expected actually
I was sure to have said Tina Turner and missed those two
I got half right on Camille
And so three stars on total including indeed last night of DJ's
Save my life
That's the best way to play
To find the answers to this and any other hits
And also the links to iTunes, you can buy
That's right, feature on the hittest
Online is hittest.mevio.com
Thank you for playing Adam
Yeah, man, thank you
Everyone else, thanks for listening
Next week I'll be back for another hittest
So until then, have fun
Take care and remember to try to think with your heart
Bye-bye
Hittest.mevio.com
In Ho Young Pulla.com
J-N-P-O-L-C-T-D-A-C-A
Fantastic
Unfortunately, no one participated on the phone
I, you know, and now that I think about it
There's no way you could
Because I forgot to turn the music up
And the music came too late on the screen
It's like a 15 or 20 second delay
Duh
All right
Next time
Let me see
What does Melmo say here?
Cannot listen to the stream
And being the chat room
Because there's too much delay
Between the two
So I, you know, why don't I just turn up
The, I'm just going to turn up the music
On the, on the chat room
So you guys have that
Might as well
And thank you very much
On Pulla.com
Who I see is also on, on the conference
You should put the whole rap in, y'all
I know the whole thing
It's like, and there's a problem that I can't fix
Because I can do it in the mix
And if you manage to treble
then you move it and the doubling
you don't let it treble
you brain
Because away, go, the treble
down the drain
I said away, goes
It's like Engage
It's like
I don't care about nothing
Man
Rolling on the front
ży
complet
You're allowed to sing a wrong if you want I was gonna clean my room
I was gonna get up and find the room but then I got up
I'm taking the next semester and I know why I couldn't cheat it and I could have passed
But I got up
I'm taking the next semester and I know why I couldn't cheat it because I got up
Because I got up because I got up
I was gonna go to work but then I got up
I just got a new promotion but I got up
Because I got up because I got up
I was gonna go to work but I got up
I was gonna pay my child support but then I got up
And I know why I couldn't cheat it because I got up
Because I got up because I got up
I wasn't gonna run from the cops but I was high
I'm serious man I was gonna pull right over and stop but I was high
I was gonna pay my child support but then I got up
Because I got up because I got up
I was gonna make love to you
I was gonna get up
Because I got up
I don't know why, why man, yeah, hey, cuz I'm high, cuz I'm high, cuz I'm high, cuz I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high,
cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm higher, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm high, cause I'm
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ah ah, hey, ah, hey, gee, oh, hey, hey, oh, hey, hey,auth, and sometimes
we go to look at the nickma fucking house to let's go back to сегодня with Hart Shell Marcia dabroool and sunglasses
Afroman world
God
Hi guy hi. I haven't feeling that that was pretty much the original oficial recording
Yeah, I did turn into a mow. I hear the girls next door. You know, I'm on the ground floor now
Which is the room with the bars in front of the window at the front of the house? Very typical for Victorian
And the only other room on this floor is the kitchen which is actually phenomenal because I can just walk right next door
It's almost like a commissary for the studio complex just just fucking love it
Hey, I got some feedback. I want to share with you on this
Fubar Monday edition of the source code. Yeah, I just it's Gaza Strip thing
Yeah, I went to hear King of Jordan speak at the commonwealth club a while ago and
He said to understand the middle east
You must first understand the God's strip
So you know, I don't know who cast the first stone in this whole turmoil and the me you know
By now it doesn't really matter
But when I find the lying corporate media lettuce, you know, speed and spewing this prop again to be yes
I find myself going back and just counting how many times the mindless drone reading the you know the telecom drone at TV
Saying the words Israel the words
Well, how much and the word Palestine and you know and after I do that it becomes so
Clear
What's life? I'm supposed to be on at least in this country
Anyway, so yeah, just just some thoughts I was having but no
I still don't as a king of doll Abdullah whatever his name was told media to do
I have no idea what's really going on in the fertile crescent region, but you know what?
I'm still researching it. I'm still trying to figure it out. All right man happy new year
Great. Oh my hope you went peace. Yeah, love you to
Yeah, it's so there's a couple things going on here what I've that I've been able to see first of all
the United Nations Security Council which consists of I believe 15 members
signed a resolution which called for an immediate ceasefire
And he just got a love it. This has not been widely reported
So they take all this time in trouble
Condolisa Rice who is still the secretary of state
Of course, soon to be replaced by Hillary Clinton what what an abortion that's going to be what a disaster
She is a disaster
All right, so she'll be even Patricia said she said what is this? Why is this club always in all these positions? And the reason why you know
What I do I have that here? Yeah, hold on a second. I got to grab the newspaper. You're going to you got to freak out when you hear this all up
This is
Front of the financial times today. Yeah, this is great
Little picture there of Tony Blair former prime minister Tony Blair above
Is reemerging as a possible choice to be the European Union's first full-time president after four crisis
Reinforce the argument for having a high profile personality in the job
According to officials and diplomats the performance of Nicholas or cozy Francis president during
It's his spell in charge of the you last year has strengthened the hand of those
I want a big name so the deal is they really want to get this
Lisbon treaty pushed through and they're going to do another vote September October in Ireland because no doesn't mean no in the European Union
Oh, no, you just got to go back and ask them again
So when the time comes I'll be
Promoting the no again and also the Czech Republic as far as I understand is not ratified the Lisbon treaty
But if it does pass then you will have an unelected president that will be appointed somehow through some mystery Starfleet command council
And they want to put Tony Blair in that spot
The guy who were sat together with the Gordon Brown fucked everything up in the United Kingdom
Anyway
It's clear that
This is being used as a proxy against Iran you watch and of course the United States did not
Sign the resolution as the only member of the security council
It goes because what if they know this what you think you can
Don't say
Where you're going to regret
Don't let fire rush to your hand
I thought the accusation before
And now who got to take any more
Believe me, the sudden you're right
It's some of the lies worth believing
I am behind the sky looking at you
I can read your mind
I am the maker of rules dealing with fools
I can keep you blind
And I don't need to see any more to know that
I can read your mind
Don't be false and you should be high
Don't cry, I am changing my mind
So find a new fool like before
Because I ain't got a little bit of a belief
So not the lies worth all of the signs are to see me
I am behind the sky looking at you
I can read your mind
I am the maker of rules dealing with fools
I can keep you blind
And I don't need to see any more to know that
I can read your mind
I am the maker of rules dealing with fools
I can keep you blind
I can see any more to know that
I can read your mind
Alan Parsons projects the eye and the sky
Which is exactly how this war is being fought in Gaza
By the way, they got drones
Running overhead there was a link on the drop
Drop.io slash daily source code
Which had a live webcam from Gaza
You could hear the booms and the distance of the explosions
And you could hear the drones flying overhead
And the IDF, the Israeli Defense Forces
Has a YouTube channel
Believe it or not, something else
Everything I do is source from the drop
Every song, everything, it's all coming from the audience out there
And you look at this IDF and it's just so discouraging
And so they see a rocket launcher
Which is pretty much a PVC tube
With some welded pieces of metal being shot out
Not saying that this is good
But man, they do take pride in showing how they destroy stuff
Don't they?
It's a very American thing as well, by the way
It's just disgusting
Just talking about that takes the wind out of me a little bit
But of course, it's a footballer Monday, so that's kind of part for the course
So if there's more demonstrations planned
What I would like you to do is as soon as possible
Put those on the drop
So that I can promote them and let people know what's going on
Drop.io slash daily source code
Please, I'm looking forward to as much help as I can possibly get
And as much help as I can possibly get
This is the daily source code
And I'm Gary
We are all keeping
Absolutely
I want to see you here
I want you to see me
I...
Fashi so I love to jump just like me
Get a plunger
You know, I think I saw you, I watched that, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw
I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I saw you, I
I'm not that I want to play any kind of music that would invite you to a protest and write it
or anything.
It's time to testify MC5 on the Charlie 6-1-8-1-6.
Oh.
Nice fade out.
Crap.
Crap drop stuff.
Just looking through the drop and reading some of the articles that are feature that are
been posted there by the charcoal heads.
The photographer arrested in London for so-called terrorist activities.
You can't go around photographing everything.
God forbid.
Let me click on this order.
I know I read it before.
I might as well take a look at this from Boeing Boeing.
Let's see what the article says because there's so much dumb stuff going on.
I can't believe the Brits are standing for this.
Here it is.
Photographing and painting around this home neighborhood of elephant and castle in
London was arrested under anti-terror laws and jailed.
His DNA in fingerprints taken released after five hours once his member of Parliament
intervened.
It took some actual intervention there under current policies as DNA will remain on file
forever of course.
You're getting a donation though the EU was ordered Britain to cease this practice.
Yeah sure.
I'd like the UN Resolution to cease fire between Hamas and the IDF please.
Here's a studio near the 19th of December.
Let me see if I can get this here.
The studio near the 1960 shopping center at the heart of this area in South London again
near where I am.
These are familiar figures regularly seen snapping and sketching the people and buildings
around this home.
Currently the site of Europe's largest regeneration project but to police officers who
arrested him last week, his photographing of the old HMSO print works close to the local
police station, posed an unacceptable security risk.
You slave.
The car skidded to a halt like something out of star skiing hutch in this officer
jumped out very dramatically and said what are you doing?
What are you?
What are you doing?
I told him I was photographing the building and he said he was going to search
me under the anti-terrorism act and this happens all the time and I want you to delete
your photos.
It's crazy.
It's absolutely nuts.
We should stop this and if that means we got to start the stopping by throwing shoes
and protesting.
Yeah, that's a good start I'd say again use that drop.au slash daily source code to get
the word out.
Let's see we got some feedback here, a good friend Ross, what does he have to say?
Hey, Curry, Russian Washington, just a little feedback for you here in 2009.
Notice that the first DSC of this week was cut off right as an hour.
Yeah, so actually I think the show was exactly one hour the first DSC of 2009 but this
is going back to people who've just joined the stream but maybe you weren't paying attention
at the beginning of the podcast and you didn't hear it but I'm changing the way I'm going
back to the way I used to bake the MP3s because audio hijack pro for whatever reason
is screwing up all kinds of listening experiences on iTunes and iPhones.
I'm surprised that a top shoe did not go into kind of an archive.
I know that blog talk does have that but I can't say if talk shoe does might want to look
into that otherwise the bike you cut it off for this time right with the second one.
So that worked.
I've also noticed that Noah Jen knows about 40, 43 minutes longer than it cuts.
Nah, I see that.
This is really way that.
Ah, it makes me so angry.
I don't understand is this not some kind of uniform thing?
Hey, printing time code and again, I was very careful not to select variable bit right but
constant bit right and still didn't work.
Also found that interesting site that seems to be reporting reasonably well.
It's called the first post and it's actually a mainstream publication.
It's owned by Dennis Felix.
This is a guy who owns many media properties in the United Kingdom and you can find it at
the firstpost.co.uk.
I see people in the chat room were talking about daily mail and different publications,
Guardian, BBC and how bias they may or may not be well, they are biased and they're
biased not because they're biased, they're biased because this is the culture, this
is the DNA of mainstream broadcasting.
I've been in this myself.
I've never made a joke about Madonna when you're on MTV.
It was just not done.
They didn't have to write down the rules, I knew it.
And of course now everything that goes out on the airways in the BBC must be cleared
by at least two people.
So how can you ever get any information out?
How?
And the two pieces of the most disappointing pieces of news that the European Union and certainly
Britain right up front there, starting in 2010, will ban the sale of plasma screens.
So I have to get my new TV's quick, I guess, but more interesting, something we talked
about on no agenda, John C. DeVorek and I is the new light bulbs, the energy-efficient
light bulbs.
Now granted they use a lot less wattage, air-go less energy consumption.
Although I have to say we use dimmers throughout our entire dwelling and that significantly
reduces the draw as well, I mean, we have light bulbs that have been going for 10, 15 years
because we keep them dimmed all the time.
But you won't be able to buy light bulbs anymore, though, with the incandescent light,
it'll have to be these mercury-filled pieces of crap, which of course you're supposed
to recycle great article that I found on the drop as well, that there's a Minister of Parliament
in the United Kingdom who is going to benefit somewhat from this.
We just started, just in time, started a mercury-light bulb energy-efficient savings-piece
of crap recycling system, so he's going to make tons of dough off of that.
It's all a scam.
These guys are all in for the scams and the schemes, and the people who are true and really
trying to change things that just get snowed under, but our time is coming.
I want to, before I play this next song, this came in on, let me see if I can find it here.
Ah, excuse me, here we go.
This was from Ernie in Zurich, Switzerland.
He sent us on Friday when I sent out the call for potential Fruber Friday songs, and of
course it didn't get to play it on Friday since we didn't do a Fruber, but wow, this
is the kind of song that really makes you feel kind of happy.
Just kind of get your feet tapping, and lift and lift up your heart and make sure you're
so open up and feel good inside.
I never told the second place, I know I got what it takes for you, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
It's never been stolen
One that I needed on to share
That's from me
Love is magic
We need a special place
We need a house based for you
They're not fake us
Two land of brothers, guys
One land that I reside
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Baby, fuck it
I'm burning in theelijk
I need a power with now
I'll win it
It's nah
Laaו
Yeah me
I'm burning in theetera
Laaו
No need power
That dishonoured
Which will be the best I can steal.
Your emotions are so sad
Oh, I feel a belly. He sings so beautifully, don't you agree?
Earth wind and fire. The speed of love.
What is this? Oh, man. I don't know if they're freaking conference call. Okay. That means I gotta wind it up at about five or ten minutes.
But it's been good kind of an energy release here to do a football Monday.
Let me just, I was looking through that side. I just told you about the first post.co.uk.
Here's some of the headlines for today. This is the 12th of January.
Israel sends reserveists into Gaza. Israeli armus reserveists were sending to Gaza last night.
Is fighting intensified in the strips towns and cities. However, it was unclear if the move signaled the start of the third phase of the conflict.
It doesn't sound good. Hey, don't Skype me. Okay. God, that's so annoying.
If you know him, if I don't do one to show, don't Skype me. Use Twitter or use the chat room.
Like I just talked about Obama pledges new approach with Iran. President-elect Barack Obama has vowed to act immediately on the US economy in the Middle East crisis in his most wide-ranging television interview.
Since election, you have to watch this ABCs this week. A lot of, oh, we have to make tough choices.
It means you're going to fuck somebody and I don't think it's just rich people. Oh, no. When it comes to health care, well, we're going to have to make some tough choices.
One of the fuck people, lying cock-sucking son of a bitch.
It's okay. He's just following the script. So I can't be angry at him because he's a charismatic guy and he reads the prompter well.
But, oh, man, we're getting so close to no change.
Britain's alien car industry could be the next in line to receive a government bailout package.
Well, that would be good for me because I've been trying to sell my Jaguar because I don't need it anymore.
I want to buy Jaguars because the company Jaguar Land Rover is so broke.
They're asking for a billion pounds to help them. So that would help me. I'd be happy with it.
But I'm also happy and content to just keep it in storage.
Keep that hydroxy booster on it because when I need it, it'll be there.
Big frack over Prince Harry, some tape surface from, I think, was two or three years ago.
And on this tape, he's talking about his buddies.
You know, the way you talk about your buddies on home video footage.
You know, it's South Jersey. We had chat the leaning mule. It was this crippled guy.
He was chat the leaning mule and it was okay. That's what we called him.
You know, it was cool.
People call me, you know, all kinds of names, which are nicknames.
But of course, it's politically incorrect to call someone who's from Pakistan.
Pakistani Paki, although all of the United Kingdom calls him Paki's.
I mean, who are you fucking kidding?
And so another buddy you called Raghead.
So they sold this to, I think, the screws, the news of the world.
And they made a big deal out of it. Poor guy.
It's so stupid. And then, of course, dominates the news while children are being killed.
This is also horrible.
Fears are growing for the 249 people still missing after an Indonesian ferry,
sank in heavy seas early on Sunday.
Geez.
Ah, that sucks.
Hey, interesting site. Although it can bummed you out.
It definitely is definitely worth checking out.
Alright, little promo from my buddy, Matt Cotto.
With Matt Cotto.
Hi, Adam, it's Matt from Games Weasel on this week's show.
I reviewed low-co-roco 2 on the PSP.
Far Cry 2 on the Xbox 360.
I round up the latest party games for your Wii.
And you can win copies of football manager 2009 for the PC and the PSP.
That's all at gamesweasel.com.
You know, the more things change the more they stay the same.
And you could just go back to songs from the 60s when everyone was pissed off about
Vietnam and Nixon and their crappy ass government.
The history world.
Here it is exploding.
Violence flaring.
Boy, it's loading.
Here old enough to kill.
But not for fun.
You don't believe in war.
But what's that gun you took.
And even the Jordan River.
Has bodies broken.
But yeah.
Tell me over and over and over again, my friend.
I you don't believe.
Where I'll be above discretion.
I don't you understand what I'm trying to say.
And can't you feel the fears that I'm feeling today.
If the button is pushed.
There's no running away.
There'll be no one to say.
With the world in a grey.
Take a look around your boy.
It's found a scarier boy.
And yeah.
Tell me over and over and over again, my friend.
I you don't believe.
Where I'll be above discretion.
Think of all the hate.
There isn't red China.
Then take a look around.
To sell my Alabama.
You may leave here.
Before it isn't space.
But when you return.
It's the same old place.
The pound of the drums.
The pride and disgrace.
You can bury it dead.
But don't leave a trace.
H-a-next door, niva.
But don't forget to say gray sand.
Tell me over and over and over.
I get in my friend.
You don't believe.
Where I'll be above discretion.
I know no you don't believe.
Yeah.
Nice stereo effect.
From the 60s.
To say word to same stuff.
Nothing has changed.
But why don't I go to the 80s?
You say Africa.
We are the world.
Band-A.
Do they know it's Christmas time?
Nothing changes.
It's futile.
We have to take a different approach.
That's for sure.
And that would probably start with taking back government.
Very interesting.
We can't looking at all the new shows coming out of America.
Meet the press and George Stephanopolis's show.
Again, President elect Obama on the program.
And it's almost like he's still campaigning.
But look, he keeps saying.
But look, there's going to be lots of tough choices.
Which means it's not going to be, you know, there's another thing.
This would be the last thing before I shut down dinner is actually waiting for me.
I saw Dave Weiner had posted something very interesting on his blog, which I want to read to you.
And which I will respond to.
I don't even think there were even any comments on it on his blog.
No, zero comments.
The blog post is titled, I'm not an economist.
I'll read this to you.
Even though by the way, Dave Weiner, huge Obama supporter.
mega.
Even though I'm not an economist, I'm sure that the US government can print money.
Yes, that's true.
I'll, I'll editorialize here.
So if we have a one trillion dollar deficit this year, that does not imply that someone has to lend us one trillion.
And does not imply that therefore that someone will have to pay someone back that money at some date in the future.
If there's an economist listening who thinks that it's not true, please say so.
And everyone else ignore what I'm about to say.
Well, first of all, the US deficit this year is over eight trillion.
Not one trillion, eight trillion dollars.
This includes all the money the treasury has lent.
Forget the 350 billion of tarp.
That's just a drop in the bucket.
And of course, it's really 700 billion, but they spend half.
But in total, buying assets through the treasury with help of Goldman Sachs.
That is our treasury secretary's old haunt, old stomping grounds.
As many of those guys look at Larry Summers coming in.
It's eight point four trillion dollars, which is about ten times the deficit from last year.
In fact, it almost equals the entire deficit of the United States.
So that's incorrect to start off with.
He continues.
So now why does the discussion on meet the press in this week revolve around how much better the private sector could spend money or how we're passing on the problem to future generations?
That seems like who he.
They have these discussions based on a make-believe premise that there are only two ways for the US government to pay for something.
Taxation or borrowing.
There's a third way.
The one they're taking, they just invent the money.
Well, this is really good.
I'm glad that Dave understands that they are inventing the money.
They're just making it up.
They're not even really printing it.
They're just adding it in it to a spreadsheet.
Just add a couple numbers with tons of zeros and you've got the money.
You continue because you know it's coming next.
Now in normal times, you pay for this invention with inflation.
Well, yes, you do.
You absolutely pay for it by inflation, which is what I call a hidden tax.
And Dave says inflation isn't a problem.
Quite the opposite.
The world economy is having a massive going out of business sale.
You're going down.
Think they're low this week.
Wait until next week, they'll be even lower.
And wait is what people do.
And that drives the prices lower.
I agree with that.
It's like inflation in reverse.
Wearing about inflation now is like starving a man.
Wearing about getting fat if he eats too much.
You'll take your calories anyway.
You can get him.
But you can't make up calories if you're starving.
You can't think yourself extra calories.
Anything that makes people want to buy things now is good for the economy.
One way to do that is to give the money by hiring them.
Oh, yes.
We're not giving the money to them.
We're giving it to large corporations who will take on people at slave wages to build
roads, which is probably not what most people went to school for.
So forgive me.
Dave finishes here.
Before thinking the analysis on TV, the analysts, sorry, on TV are either corrupt or
idiots or whatever.
And of course, please forgive me if I'm wrong.
And the government isn't going to print money to get out of this whole.
Okay.
Well, first of all, I forgive you.
But it's really important because this shows you the thinking of the people who nominated
a voted for Obama.
It doesn't matter if you'd voted for McCain.
It would have been the same result.
But the misinformation that is now coming out of this man's mouth, present Alexa mouth,
gives this impression that, oh, no problem.
We can just print the money.
Well, let me explain.
It's dilution.
Okay.
So let's say we have a company with 100 shares.
And Dave, you have 10 shares of my company, which you've always wanted.
Now let's say I'm just going to make 400 shares.
Are your shares still worth the same amount?
No, it's been diluted.
That is exactly what inflation is about.
When you hear inflation, don't think old prices are just rising.
That takes a little while.
And it is stealing from our children's future.
And it's to the tune of $8 trillion.
And they're going to have more Senate hearings.
They're going to give away another 350 billion of tarp money.
And it is a complete scam.
Did the 350 billion they gave away before?
Just a piece of the $8 trillion that it helped anyone get any mortgage.
Just now, mortgage is to let six or seven percent.
It is a complete rip off.
What we think we understand where we came from.
What we think we're doing.
The more you begin to see, we've had lied to them.
They lied that lied to them and lied to everybody.
Every year she wants to make sure that the mortgage is in the institution.
That's the only one that's never been told.
I'm thinking now I can lay down.
Put a pack of lots of paper.
We can go told it's all we see.
I don't think you ever want to step inside the chamber.
I don't think you want to see inside the eyes of Vader.
Put a drop right in the force that I bring.
I'm like rock, you want Seattle when you walk in the ring.
I'm stalking the ring.
You couch down the soul when you sing.
But I'm a Zachary.
It's the motherfuckers caught in the bang.
It's all for the thing.
But I'm a woman who was standing tall.
And I ain't stopping like the habit.
And it's really war.
I'm so broke, motherfuckers, you can barely fall.
I'm making my family because we can share it all.
Money, the world of all evil.
I don't care at all.
Now we can just respect together.
We get it all.
We've got to do it all.
But like it's not enough.
Don't put a rock the more in.
When they can do it.
All the last days.
Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks
Blacks, Black, Blacks, Blacks, Black, Blacks, Black. Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Black, Black, Black, Black, Black- Awлattan Man, Blacks, Blacks, Black Sanchester, Blacks, Black Finn, Blackfax, Blacks, Blacks, Black's on his side, Black s拿, Blacks, Blacks, Styl Mixed, Black B plots, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks, Blacks 00, P-T-B B Dolsonoker, Blacks Chances Ma Little girls, Bill West, Black First only his good própria, Blacks
When I'm robbing your floor drops, making everyone eat the floor stuff, I'm going for y'all a wrestlein' over four chops
That whole hatchin' thinkin' we was down with that board drop, I ain't goin' front, I was strapped with the doors
Like, have a walk around this motherfuckin' with fours, I'm picking up the foot of fucking hole in the floor
I've got to eat something that you wanna explore, unless you want the army comin' kickin' your door
Unless you wanna end up bloody and wet
Fuck China's cover man, what they done to fat
We're fully wet, it's somethin' sad
Where the motherfuckers rob you, where they're gunnin' connect
Where you showed my fuckers, where they come to the fat
Where you toldin' gettin' fix, when you're comin' to sad
Dwecker up cops, where the fuck is gunnin' your vassal
We retaliate by puttin' fuckin' one and they just
Goin' on my feet, y'all I'm goin' on
Where the motherfuckers rob you, where they're gunnin' connect
As with just about everything on today's program source from the drop.io slash daily source code
Jedi mind-trick's monolith, my history of violence
All I gotta wind it up because I have an eatin' since this morning
And Patricia's made me a fantastic suit
I've been keepin' my eye on the chat room, yep
Blood Sugar's low, you're right, I'm gettin' grumpy
I also think the problem is I'm out of weed
Oh, no, no, no, time to panic
Thank y'all for participating everybody on the conference call
Should you wanna say goodbye now as the time, because I've got the phone lines
Open thanks for being a part of the chat
No, all right, yeah, who's that?
Hey, Jamaican New York man, haven't heard you in a long time
How you doin' my brother?
I've been hiding, you know the economy, but I know everything, you know
So we have to reload some time
I hear you, man, I hear you, you gotta send me some voicemail comment again
Jamaican New York, I missed you
Oh, good, I missed you too
Yeah, man, and send me some tunes to play
I'm really into reggae these days, I don't know what it is, but I'm just digging it
For sure, for sure, no problem
No problem
All right, everybody, thanks a lot. This was DailySourceCode episode 816
I'll be back later in the week, maybe tomorrow depends on the schedule
But I am ahead, so I'm looking forward to more of the chuckle, Charlie, Chacha
You still got some freedom, post that shite on the drop
Check the show notes, the DailySourceCode.com, crossposts that are curried.com
And whatever you do, live your life with passion
Another fine, medial presentation, stick it in your ear