Delta Sierra Charlie, 820.
I don't got a wreath.
Take your sauce cold.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio coach, any of my years.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Oh, fantastic.
It's a battle, curry.
The feeling.
See it.
But today, if you can't think that doesn't matter any way,
you will never understand because it happens to bang.
And it feels so good inside, working the glass.
So good, so good, so hip at somebody.
It's so good.
It's at a sight.
You could touch it.
It's so good.
It's just so sweet.
But it makes me feel good.
I couldn't actually touch it.
Wow.
It's so good.
Time.
Even a light in the macro, so good.
They don't understand what's in both.
It's so good.
So good, so good.
That sounds so good.
Right here.
Dream's are nice and full.
Once again for a daily source code episode 820 coming to you from the Curry Terrace in Southwest London everybody
How you doing good to talk to y'all's been a while
Totally my fault
Mowcare
Oh
Let's see what is today today is Wednesday February 4th 2009
And it's been over a week since the last source code
Not notice I left a daily off there because that's just the way it's gonna be from now on
It's just too much happening. It was in San Francisco and it was actually a
Pretty good time. We had beautiful weather all week long everyone was even talking about it
They loved it so much they even forgot that they were in the midst of a severe drought and actually need water
But so I kind of took the week off from mevio today. I took the week. Well
Essentially I really didn't have any time to do a source code
Considering just how much time goes into it because I I don't know I just can't do those short shows and I've also had an
minor epiphany
That we talked about on Noah gender. I want to do more Noah genders and so if that means it's gonna take up the spot
of a daily source code and I can keep that at least to one make it a weekly source code
I think that's what I want to do because it just
It's uh, I've always worked a lot better with a partner in any type of
Actually in any type of venture now. I think about it
So that just seems to be working that's getting a lot of traction huge audience
Yeah, lots of reaction and I got to tell you man
The hate is here
I don't know what it is but in the last maybe it's just the last couple of shows that
That I've been doing with John and and the source code all of a sudden there's people sending me emails and
Twitter's that are you know hammering me for hammering the president like I'm against Obama like it's only Obama that I don't care about it
Like where were these people when Bush was president? Please
Then of course, you know, I think Barack Obama is an adorable guy
And I can tell that he's sweating because
There's a new script and a change of storyline every single day is they they basically try to keep it all together
They being I guess the military industrial complex the people the shadow government
Whatever you want to call it the people really running the show
Who are writing legislation and look at the transparency. It's so little
Whitehouse dot gov. I check it every single day so really behind
On executive orders and member and a member and I my member and that
That the president is which doesn't really mean anything. It's not a not a legal enforced
Statement. It's more just exactly that it's a statement and then all these confirmations and tax
I don't want to call a tax evasion but back tax is not paid which hey I've been there
And through no fun of my own in fact
And I didn't get treated the same way. Let me tell you that
But now there's a how man. I feel so bad for the president nice to go on all of these wonky talk shows
It's a talk to Katy Curric and has to explain to her why oh well, you know
Maybe this guy wasn't so good and he withdrew his name and yet we can't have two standards and yeah, you know
We got to we got to put limits in place for
For executive salary for banks people who accept tart money and buy American, but I don't really mean buy American because I don't want to upset
Like the whole rest of the world with protectionism
It's coming apart at the seams. That's that's what I'm seeing
So I'm jolly happy to talk to you guys about it. I have the Skype in phone number available if you want to call in
2 0 1 7 9 3 8 3 2
I'm gonna get a UK number for the next show. So it's a plus 1 2 0 1 7 9 3 8 3 3 2
That's the direct studio line everybody. I think I can handle exactly two lines with my Skype in number
But that's it seems to be more than sufficient
So lady Patricia's off. She's in the Netherlands doing her judging thing for Holland love losers
Of course, I mean Holland's got talent and
So she's been real busy with that these are the you know the pre-selection rounds
So there's basically she has to look at
Hundreds of people over the course of a couple of days. She almost didn't make it out. She was she had to go out Monday
I returned from San Francisco Sunday
You know, I was kind of rushing back so I could still see your own basically hand off of the keys because there's you know
Still work going on here in the terrace as we bring it up to lady Patricia like standards
And so you know
She took off Monday morning just as I mean the snow had been falling all night and it and it was just
Rages we had 20 inches of snow in London and I knew there was a car company who would get me a good eggnuch bloke
In a good sturdy car and he got her there all right and I've been checking the website because she loves easy jet
As does the entire curry family
And I was checking the website and I was looking all the cancellations
But not a single cancellation for London Amsterdam. She got to the airport and of course all flights canceled even though the website didn't reflect it even too
Ourly updates later. It still didn't reflect it
She was able to hop on a BA flight
So she got lucky and she got out because after that the country just shut down schools closed
But Christina hasn't been to school for three days
Trash is piling up outside because
It hasn't been collected
It's just that the whole place is a shambles and they expect another 10 to 15 inches tonight now this may not hit London
But it's certainly affecting other areas of the UK which people often forget you haven't
Doesn't happen in London, but then it's not really happening
The so I'm here with the kids
The children's being a Christina and boyfriend Dexter
And Dexter is doing some kind of movie in in
Canary Warf so even though he lives in Gilford he's been staying over here because it's much easier to get to the set
In the morning
Actually he's staying with Christina out back in the in the apartment and
So it's been fun, you know hanging out with the kids watching
DVDs
Kids do buy DVDs. I'll tell you they don't you know they don't really like to rip off movies to watch him on the computer
Seems like they really want the quality or at least some quality and get it on the screen
Which is good that boats well for the yeah for the film industry
At least they still care about what they're seeing
Think about how horrible it is how much information you're actually missing listening to MP3s
I mean it's a 10 to one compression so
You're just not getting the same amount of information and then when you actually that's why it may be concerts are so
You know so much in the upswing and that's where all the money is being made is because you actually hear real
Real sounds for the first time in your life probably if it's the first time you go to a concert
They're the sort of episode 8 to 0 got a lot of shit to go through and all of it's fun
Hit me up 2017 938332 the animals on the Charlie the rooms was so much cold
of them
My father was
So you're then at times for very hard when I was young
I was young
I spoke my first sickle at 10 and for girls
I had a bed in and I had quite a fall when I was young
Hey
When I was young it was more important
Me and more pain but a lot from much now to yeah
When I was young
I met my first love at 13
She was brown and I was pretty green and I learned quite a lot when I was young
When I was young
When I was young it was more important
Pain more pain but a lot from much now to yeah
When I was young
My faith was so much stronger than
I believed in fellow men and I was so much older than
When I was young
These guys had a number one hit on the day I was born September 3, 1964
Wasn't this song? That was actually house the rising sun there
More famous song the animals with Eric Burton
When I was young
On the daily source code I forgot to tell you about the children
So we had all that snow so Christina actually did get up in the morning to see if she could get to school
It was like a ghost town outside
The tube wasn't running trains weren't running everything was at a complete standstill
So she came back home and then she indexed her spent about four and a half maybe five hours outside
And they built an enormous snowcock right on the steps leading up to the lovely
Curry terrace
I'm talking I put it on my flicker site and I also posted it on curry.com
It was huge and I must say anatomically interestingly correct
You know not built a scale of course and
You know they worked so hard on it. They were so proud of it now. I know Patricia would be horrified if she knew about this
So of course we took lots of pictures and I couldn't bring myself to knock it down
So it's been up for two days now
And yesterday I think one of the neighbors and I I actually expected someone to break it down
Out of anger
Someone put a trash bag
For the top which makes it actually even funnier
uh
So
It will it's
I check it every day to make sure it hasn't become one big block of ice that I actually can destroy it because it has to be gone by the time the lady p gets home
She will be utterly horrified
Plus one two oh one seven nine three eight three three two if there's something you want to talk about today
I also on Twitter
Follow me Adam Curry on Twitter. I see a Jeff Ridgeway just tweeted
Ha salt ban weapon HR 45 proposed build to require licensing and registration for all firearms
Yeah, I don't know too much about that because I'm not a gun not myself. Yeah, I do believe in the the right to bear arms and I think it's extremely important
But I don't follow that as much but I do understand that there's maybe not just this HR 45
But there's a couple of bills in the house right now. There even have
Impressive co-sponsors
That essentially are meant to get rid of all guns and it makes sense because these guys they're not stupid
They know what's going on. They know that just like every other country in in the world
unrest is a foot
And people are getting pissed off and it's for a variety of reasons witness the United Kingdom just had wildcat strikes
Because they they want British jobs for or UK jobs for British workers which is a direct quote from
Hair Gordon Brown
Who promised this in it's far back as 2007 and of course that goes contra to any
rule that is
comprised of the
Trade agreements of the European Union which specifically states that you can do this they all agreed to it
They agreed that foreign companies would be allowed to bring in their workers from their country to work on projects if they bid cross
Country or I should say state lines
And yeah, so now that doesn't seem like such a good idea before when everyone was getting money and the back
channels on the take pass and all this shit which has now been proven
Certainly in the in the government in the UK
Lord's taking money for
Favorable votes on bills and adjustment actual amendments to bills
fitting the the laws
or fitting
Fitting the mission and motives of companies who they are befriended with
That's a nice way to put it
So they know that the that shit is gonna hit the fan pretty soon and it of course it will happen in the United States as well
It has to because people are gonna start getting very hungry right now. We're all still kind of
Hoping
Man, what's I should play that song wishing and hoping and hoping and wishing
That's one
Is that dusty
Sandy Shaw, maybe let me see let me see if I can find it home on oh that will be perfect wouldn't it
Sandy Shaw. I think it's Andy Shaw. I didn't want on the chat no
Let me see
wishing and hoping and hoping and hoping no pop it on the string no
crap, maybe it's
wishing
and hoping
crap
Okay
That was a fun idea. Let's not do it
So
That's it. We're all just kind of wishing and hoping and hanging in there and companies are
Holding on to staff as long as they can because you know the stimulus bill is coming and there's a lot of confusion about that
Is it going to be is it stimulant enough
Is our tax cuts with the way to go or are is spending the way to go? Oh, I don't know the answer
But it seems to me like I'm hearing the same thing over and over again. It's just new faces saying it and it hasn't
worked so far and the only people who seem to be making out are the people receiving the money and it's not small business
It's big business
And now uh talking about a bad bank that's back on again
oh
Man and the worst thing. This is absolutely the worst thing now dusty springfield
How can I be such an idiot
That's what it was hold on dusty springfield
It was an enormous diek by the way, which kind of makes her hotter even though she was it wasn't really hot
I
Can't find it wishing and hoping and to boom
What's the title that song that's and and I thought it was wishing and hoping that
crap
Does anyone know
Hope you don't mind, but I just have to
Get this out of my system
uh crap
All right
You know what it is we got that 20 second delay on the stream so it takes a while before people hear what I'm asking for all right so maybe that'll pop up in a second
And I'll play that song. This is it's a golden idi
So this is really really disturbing to me
And I'm I've become incredibly
downtrodden and
downcast
Um, and I'll put this link in the show notes of course at
DailySourceco.com crossposted at curie.com common dreams dot org
Posted
YouTube video and some editorial title of this
Of this post is NBC has an Aaron Burnett problem
And basically what it uh what this video and what the associated editorial
actually is a transcript
kind of says is that Aaron is
evil
And and and looking at it this is from now she was on
Ocean the Sunday meet the press
As a panless you know being interviewed she looks so stunningly beautiful
I'm gonna read the words the captions that are put over this video while we listen to it together for a second
So Aaron Burnett CNBC's embedded journalist on Wall Street is how it starts on
bonuses or private jet use or or also just that they're not lending none of these things really are
Are the real issue here? Why isn't populism though has been amazing? I mean just the rhetoric out of
Barack Obama and Joe Biden this week that they talk use the word shameful and outrageous to refer to Wall Street
Practices that that that isn't choosing mean street versus Wall Street that is a completely false
Toys that is being put out
All right so let's go these people are idiots
You can't use another cut to Senator McCasco billion dollars in bonuses
What planet are these people on fair question here? I understand the outrage
Okay, do you is the caption that then pops up understand the populism silly populism that's just what the public wants
There are though
Well the house so we say this
Please say it slowly the public's kind of dumb Aaron. I'm just reading the the captions here
It's so hurtful to have to do this
The taxpayer money's not being used to pay the bonuses
I think people could understand if you work for a company right if the three of us work for a company your guests
And I lost ten billion dollars but Steve over there
He made a billion dollars so overall the company actually loses money
But Steve went and did his very darned us for that company and he made money
So should he be paid for his work that's essentially what we're talking about here and reasonable people could argue about this
But many reasonable people would conclude yes, he should be paid for that
So now the title says Aaron Pailin Burnett Wall Street execs did their darnedist and I'm and at this point when I first saw this video
I'm thinking well
You know she's really just
There is a degree of truth in what she's saying
Although man you look at those bonuses. They seem to go one for one ten million dollars and tarp ten billion dollars and tarp money
Ten billion dollars and bonuses
But of course, you know there is some degree of business that has to be conducted at a certain level if you believe in the the whole concept of a bailout and so at this point
I'm thinking you know, maybe she's really just
playing the devil's advocate and
Getting away with it doing a pretty good job, but God, it's really hurt to God. She's so pretty
Oh, man
Feel so horrible
She's one of them
She really is
And I think David you've raised a fair point which is maybe it's the whole use of the word bonus if you
Explained to people this is how they are compensated that might make a difference
Exactly a bonus is not a bonus silly public is the caption
But there's also a fundamental misunderstanding the tax pair of money isn't being taken and paid out in the form of bonuses
It goes in a separate pool, so we say a separate account
So maybe people don't care about that distinction, but it is there
Bro companies used a magic separate pool of money for bonuses. Yes, he's digging a hole. Hopefully his Aaron don't do this
Please stop stop
Tell Aaron Bernat stop being an apologies for Wall Street, so now it's basically telling you to email her
And I'm looking through the comments and if you look at her
Where is it?
Somewhere there was a
Bio
She's from council and foreign relations
She worked a Goldman Sachs. I mean all the death stars Aaron
Oh no
Can she really be one of them? Maybe she's just dumb
Please please make it be that I still I still would love her even if she was just not smart
Damn
This is what happens in times of
Hey, Adam this is hit us number 158 so you have to start right away with intro number one
That would have to be men at work and down under
I think yarn is even in the chat, so you can no follow along number two
I want six
And 10 to 10 George Michael
But easy and number three
Don't listen food listen to your heart
This crazy rock set. Yes, under the air
This is answer number one men at work
I never understood the lyrics this
Answer number one men at work down under
And this is answer number two
Where's that George man bring him back
What the old George
George Michael. I want your sex is answer number two
Yes, and this is answer number three
I don't know where you go in and I don't know
Listen to your
Rock set
As answer number three listen to your heart
I'll do to hit that number 158
So Adam yeah, young how did you do this week? Well
There's more cowboy everybody
Six out of six yarn and I better hurry up and do another show because I think you have one fifty nine standing by thank you so much
It was fun. I'm a winner baby
If you want to know more about the answer to Disney any other hitters or if you want to download the tracks
Buy the tracks and I choose you can go to hittest.mevio.com
Because they will find all the links and info
All right, Adam thanks for playing thank you young everyone else thanks for listening next week
I'll be back for another hit there so until then have fun take care and remember to think with your heart
Bye bye
Oh, yo
There we go. Thank you so much young
Okay, so actually I found the dusty springfield song but doesn't work anymore now
crap aroma
Now let's see what's going on in the news a couple of wacky stories that I've been following I hate it when the CDC
This Center for Disease Control and Prevention does this
They put out a
report warning
APB
widespread outbreak of flu has been reported in Virginia according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is the first state to
Report an outbreak which the CDC observed was on a slow start but CDC epidemiologist Anthony Fiori warned the U.S. might be hit by the chronic winter ailment within the next two weeks
Since say oh
Aside from Virginia the CDC reported localized flu outbreaks in Maryland and the District of Columbia
How conveniently located to our government
Where was I based on it's weekly polls what are they doing telephone research now Virginia Department of Health epidemiologist Laura and Nikolai forecast high incidents of flu cases in the state for the next six to eight weeks
With the ailment running into March April even into May
Flu symptoms include fever aching muscles headache dry throat sore throat dry cough sore throat and lack of energy
According to the CDC flu vaccine manufacturers have shipped in lots of the shots for the 2008-2009 flu season is earliest August
2008 they estimate 143 to 146 million doses of flu vaccine will be available for the current influenza season
Holy moly well I'm just gonna tell you this I am not getting a flu shot I recommend you do some research and perhaps you won't
Either I'd rather just stick it out because even if you take the shot it's only for one strain of the flu
Which apparently they have hence the antidote and
Fuck it, you know you need to be sick once in a while when it comes to flu take the flu
It'll make you a man
Or woman oh
Yes
Aaron
I'll bring in your chip chicken soup. I'll make you feel good
I feel so torn about that
Okay, let me see
Point clip penetrates super bowl broadcast. No, that's no fun
This was a funny story
Residents in northern Australia you know it's a mess in Australia. If anyone is from Australia. It's listening right now
Give me a call plus one two one seven nine three eight three three two
Because they're you know they're having a very very hot summer of course that is summer in in that part of the world right now
And so there's all kinds of crap going down floods and
Residents in northern Australia have now been warned to be where
Of large crocodiles and snakes as the floods sweep the area and
You know, it's it's true. They're like crocodiles floating by
And so
That's scary, but what I liked was this quote
from
I believe the owner of
The pub on the manager of the Albion hotel Donna Smith
Said that a four meter crocodile had been four meter four meters
Yeah, it's a 13-foot crocodile
Had been stalking residents and dogs in the flooded Main Street
She also warned the town was expected to run out of beer in two days now that's what I call a crisis now
Now we're in real trouble. I don't care about four meter crocks with man. We're out of beer
You have feelings of inadequacy
Do you suffer from shyness?
The use sometimes wish you were more assertive if you answered yes to any of these questions
Ask your doctor or pharmacist about tequila
Tequila is the safe natural way to feel better and more confident about yourself and your actions
Tequila can help ease you out of your shyness and let you tell the world that you're ready and willing to do just about anything
You'll notice the benefits of tequila almost immediately and with a regiment of regular doses
You can overcome any obstacles that prevent you from living the life you want to live
shyness and awkwardness will be a thing of the past and you'll discover many talents you've never knew you had
Stop hiding and start living with tequila tequila may not be right for everyone
When the poor pregnant are nursing should not use tequila however women who wouldn't mind nursing or becoming pregnant are encouraged to try and side effects may include
Dizziness nausea vomiting and incarceration erotic lessfulness loss of motor control loss of clothing
loss of money loss of virginity delusions of grander table dancing headache dehydration dry mouth and a desire to sink
Cariokia play all night rounds a strip oak or fruit or dare and make it twisted or warning the consumption of alcohol
They make you think you're whispering when you're not is a major factor in dancing like a retard
They cause you to tell your friends over and over again that you're in love with them also may cause you to think you can sing alcohol
They lead you believe that ex-lovers are really dying for you to telephone them at four in the morning alcohol
They make you think you can logically convert with members of the opposite sex without spitting it may create the illusion that you are tough or smarter
Faster and better looking than most people and it may lead you to think people are laughing with you alcohol may cause pregnancy and it also may be a major factor in getting your
Ask it, so what are you waiting for?
Stop hiding and start living with tequila
That was good straight from the drop
By giving you no time instead of at all
Till a pain is so big you feel nothing at all
Working class hero is something to be
They hurt you at home and they did do it school
They hate you if you're clever and they despise a fool
Till you're so fucking crazy you can't follow their rules
Working class hero is something to be
When the tortured and scared him for 20 odd years
Then they expect you to pick a career
When you can't really function yourself for the fear
Working class hero is something to be
Keep your dope with religion and sex and TV
And you think you're so clever and classless and free
But you're still fucking peasants as far as I can see
Working class hero is something to be
This room at the top they are telling you still
But first you must learn how to smile as you kill
If you want to be like the folks on the hill
Working class hero is something to be
If you want to be hero with just follow me
Plan up on the granddaddy's knee here kids I'll tell you some about the songs
All these songs were made in the 60s man because
It was a rough time then too
So I'm glad that we're doing that in hip hop and metal and
Too bad about the top 40 charts
George Michael did give it a good try and I give him massive props for that
Man, do you remember what everyone was bitching and pissing all over him for doing that video with
Tony Blair acting as a or depicted as a
little lap dog jumping all over George Bush and it was like whoa, it's horrible. He was awake
In Patricia who was a young woman yeah at the time this song was released
Of course she was very my in fact when the Beatles did that
Worldwide love fest she was a part of that she was a part of that satellite telecast in the Netherlands if you go back and look at the footage
You can see her there with a golden earring hangin out being all love
Very very hippy
But she often says she said a man if the if John Lennon were alive said you would have loved each other
To he was saying the same stuff talking the same way
And then of course now I understand why why he had Yoko because she probably didn't understand what he was talking about
But you got to have a real messed up chick you know if you if you're if you're if you go on the rabbit hole from time to time or
Open your eyes and really pay attention to what's going on around you and not just see it as another story on a web page or something in the newspaper or a little flash on TV
But actually get into it and find out what's happening
whoa
So God bless my darling wife of 22 years
I'll give an example here. This is from Mary Claire magazine. Why should we do a show with Mary Claire?
Called the mast head. It's a good show. It's said we're just a
Re-sign for our third season with those guys sponsored by Unilever
Dove
But it's cool. It's a ugly beddy meets Delaware's product. You should watch that show the masthead dot mevio.com
or just go to Mary Claire.com. They put a embed version up there
so this is from
The sex and relationship articles
Love lessons desperately seeking approval. I just got to read this to you because it's
It's so sad it's funny
So these are letters sent in by women with love problems
When my boyfriend suddenly decided that the US government had planned 9-11 to justify a war in the mid-East
I was alarmed but not enough to ditch him out right after all. I told myself his pension for questioning
Everything in his path was one of the things I loved about him. Surely he'd regain his senses soon
So I refrained from rolling my eyeballs when he'd say things like
I'm not sure the Pentagon was even hit by a plane. Those photos could have been doctored
And I kept my mouth shut when he'd futs around on the internet all night studying bushes family ties to the
Saudis and the melting temperature of steel. I even started attending weekly truth meetings in a dusty
church basement pretending to be very interested as he'd mutter. Yes exactly to people's rambling diet tribes.
Yes, I know it was nuts
But it wasn't the first time I'd faint interest in a subject in order to please a guy ever since high school
When I studied up on third level or junior dwarfs
So I could converse with my dungeon and dragons obsessed boyfriend. I've adopted a variety of interests that were not my own
I've taken carve maga classes. I've thrown batches of toast at screen during repeated viewings of the rocky horror picture show
I've gone to the death cab for cutie concerts. I've hosted marathons of movies made by the obscure Danish actors
I once seriously considered spending a week in the desert un-showered for burning man and the already pot smoking dude
I was dating at the time
I know it sounds a little pathetic, but I guess I wanted whatever guy I was dating to like me
If he peeked my interest, I wanted to peek his. I wanted to be the woman who got all his pop culture references
One carefully researched conquest and thus when I mentioned the band Genesis
I wanted to be a gal. His friends thought was awesome
Someone who inhabited his private world as comfortably as they did
That's when I decided enough was enough listening to death cab for cutie was one thing pretending that nine eleven was an inside job was another
Finally, I told my boyfriend. I thought his theories were insane
After accused me of betraying him and the people we broke up now. I just need to get rid of that prog rock collection
So that could have been me
I am a lucky bastard
But if there's a lot of people doing it maybe it's time to question if there's something going on with all that stuff
Here's someone who's going through the exact same process right now
I had and this is New York there
Hey, you're there
And I offer my table and the process of Obama
And you know, I'd probably replied to a Z-mail by the way
I do tend to do that these days particularly if John and I are both on the email that sometimes we even have a little thread going on
I just
Missed to your current episode
The very source code and I just
It's so much for me
It's a
But even what you're saying I mean I understand
That that you've been for for four years and
You know you don't need to be fought again, but you know this is really by the way
I really appreciate E. Arthur's comments here because he's calling up and he's really laying a sole bear easy
Target for ridicule which of course
Don't I don't like
Especially this me
But I understand you know people say that there's this awakening when you start to figure things out
It's not really like you wake up one morning and you're like
Yeah, I see now
It's a process it took me about a year and
Gradually you start seeing things and you start paying attention really because you aren't you are in a way jolted
It starts with a jolt, but that that's really the beginning of
Figuring things out and we just spend a little bit of time moving beyond the headlines that everyone
accepts as the truth and the news and what's going on and it's become a
Disgardable product products, you know what's on the news tonight? What's on it tomorrow?
We even speak that way
Yeah, there was nothing on the news
Once you go a little bit farther and you listen to what people are saying my favorite one by the way is
The stimulus package
Here is the quote from the president and the administration really from everybody
Everyone's just parroting the same thing, but it's a brilliant structure of words and I do think take things quite literally
When someone says that the stimulus package is meant to
Save or create three to four million jobs so
Again, save or create three to four million jobs everyone keeps repeating that it is meant to save or create three to four million jobs
Sometimes it's three sometimes it's four, but it's always save and save or create not save and create save or create now
if I was the
President of
The country if I was the boss of everybody and was a business deal the first thing I'd say is what is it three million or four million?
Is there a variable in there? What's the variable for that's 25% difference and then I'd say what is it
Save or create because there's a big difference between saving three million jobs and creating three million jobs
Because if you create three million jobs apparently you've already saved three million
So is it six million or
Could it have been a hundred million that we're gonna lose?
It's not a good and fair proposition because we're talking about eight hundred billion dollars that is supposed to save and create
What is it just tell me which one it is if it means save that okay then we can accept that or not
But it's it's a it's a huge hedge because you can always go back and say what we save three million jobs
They didn't go away did they well, yeah, we lost 10
But it would have been 13 maybe even more it's nasty
It's just not good business and we shouldn't accept it as taxpayers because it is our money
So these are the things that you start to see my friend
I just it's hard for me, you know
Tyler saying and
And you know especially when I see other people like you know David believe I mean what
And her
For him on the show who in a while and
You know when I look at this what say talk about how
I mean what even say about how
You know most you pour
Or like you know
There's a glad that he's you know that Obama's
You know that inauguration he's in the White House. I mean yes, like Jersey Todd
Who supported Obama people who people like that. He's he chapter for masks and hash yeah hotcast
I mean well, you know what
Both of us guys and many other people are really warm
Loveable loving caring people
As far as I know them
and very personable and
They are very positive people and
That's exactly what's being played to right here
So I'm not you know
I don't have to go around telling everybody oh the sky is falling because it is it's just a fact and when the jobs are gone and when
We have all kinds of trade restrictions which means less choice of food
All kinds of crap that is that is likely to happen. It's not just me saying it it's experts
Other experts real experts
I saw Nancy Pelosi
The speaker of the house and she was talking about 500 million jobs will be lost 500 million there's only 300 million people in the country
I should look for that it was very funny
500 million
Like I can probably get that for you
This this so much stuff
Well, I'll me grab that that's worth it here. It is I just got a copy it over from I was gonna put that on me via today
Here we go
Yes
The economic recovery package is going too fast and maybe it won't be ready by the president's day recess
Every month you do not have an economic recovery package 500 million Americans lose their jobs. I don't let's hear that one again
Bob how many Americans lose their job economic recovery package 500 million Americans lose their jobs
Now I'm sure I'm sure it wasn't oversight
I'm sure she meant 500,000 which is not a small number either, but
She stands there with how many flags is she have she's got four flags. She's a four flag woman
Four flags three inputs Nancy Pelosi brings you the fact package 500 million Americans lose their jobs. I don't
Dork
All right, Arthur. He Arthur
to me
It just seems like
I
It's so much it's just so much
me to believe and maybe because I'm
Not 42 45 or whatever and dude and I haven't you heard more
You know I know the kind of experiences that you've had out of but you know I'll tell let me tell you man
There were friends of mine who were older significantly older when I was a young man
My late 20s Ben Cohen. I'll never forget
Um
George Bush senior became president and this guy basically raised me since I was 19
He had a restaurant and you know that's kind of where I went to eat because I was out of the house when I was working when I was 19
And I remember him his head whipped around when I said oh it looks like a pretty good president
And you all probably vote for him and he went like this is one of the biggest crux in the world and I'm talking about eighties, right?
1980s
One of the biggest crux in the world this this guy is it's all for his own benefit and he was going off on all this shit and I was like
Angry as Rayleigh is what I thought I had no idea
And some of a lot of that comes back I have to say I said oh man I remember when he told me about that crap
You know and I just wasn't paying attention and these are these are pre-internet days really
Bulletin board stuff, you know, we had modems, but it was not like it is today
And so now all that shit's flying back at me, so it's okay, you know
I think that we have enough communication now that the
That process will accelerate and you'll see so don't worry about it, you know, you don't have to
It's what I think what they call duality
You know where you're kind of one foot in you know in that side one foot's on the other side come on over son to the dark side
We've been waiting for you
I just
I don't know maybe it's just gonna take me time
It's a preview of everything you're saying
Maybe
Maybe it is but you know
Anyways
Thank you guys for the show and keep up
What shit, sorry about that
All right, man. Thank you so much for calling. I appreciate it. Yeah
I think uh I think yon sent this to me. It was Raymond
When I did the food bar I kept it and I want to play it for you baby
God, I love this song
I've not heard of live version
Because of course radio won't play that
Crazy I would break format that would be horrible
How long is this been going on and say so Chuck eat you sir
Just blues
often
Your friend with a fan says where is
Know the men that it's part of weekly
I can't ever have my suspicious
So I need what is the most as they
No, you said you're never too late
To break up I seen in this way
Well, they're ain't any use you're too late
It could happen to us any day
Oh, how long
There's been no way long
Oh, and your friends, with a fancy persuasion
No, no, no, that is part of a scheme
I can't ever have my suspicion
I think what is dumb as I say
No, you said you're never too late
To break up I seen in this way
Ain't any use pretending
It could happen to us any day
Oh, how long
There's been no way long
How long
How long is this before and long
There's been no way long
People singing for me now
Oh, how long
There's been no way long
Yeah
Oh, how long
There's been no way long
Everybody love me
Singin' out
Yeah
Oh, how long
There's been no way long
How long
How long is this before and long
Oh, how long
There's been no way long
Yeah, beautiful
You know, come on
Everybody, come on
There's been no way long
I don't...
Thank you very much.
Thank you, people. Fantastic.
Yeah.
Hey, live. How long has this been going on?
Of course, Paul Carrick.
Who is Paul Carrick on vocals?
Fantastic, shit.
Alright, so it's kind of messed up because I'm just seeing the chat
is starting to perk up a little bit.
We got folks waking up in Australia.
We've got someone on from Milan, the stream is jam packed.
You know what I'm thinking?
Because Christina, as you know, is here with the boyfriend.
And she just cooked dinner and it smells fantastic.
And she cleaned up the kitchen.
And she's really made a job of it.
So what I'd like to do is I'd like to stop the,
the DSC recording and pick it up after dinner.
What I'll do is I'll turn on some music.
So y'all can enjoy it on the stream or not.
And come back in, I don't know, like 40, 45 minutes.
And I'll continue.
Cause I do have more to talk about.
So keep the stream alive.
I'm going to pause the recording right now.
Alright, we're back.
Those of you listening to the recorded version of Debbie source code 820.
Well, you missed a good dinner.
Oh, yeah.
And played some tunes.
Played a lot of who.
I had to ring out the mission control is next to the kitchen in the curry terrace.
So I can just keep the doors open.
I could hear the music going like, okay.
Maybe a little bit too much.
Who?
But I can't say.
It was on shuffle.
There you go.
Chicken.
Actually is what she made.
Chicken mashed potatoes, peas, wonderful salad.
Dexter brought over some wine.
Which I think he bought with my money.
Okay.
Let's see.
Oh, I want to play this because this is one of our.
True.
Chuck listeners who's calling in reports.
Adam here at Fortland.
I am back from my trip to Pakistan and I wanted to.
Provided note on the GSA the global security agency.
I have continued to Google this.
Oh, yeah.
This is.
So Eric when he went to Pakistan.
He was questioned.
I believe.
I think he said it was questioned or.
At least the security at the airport was the GSA, which.
No one could find it.
There was some.
He like private security companies that do have worldwide services.
But it didn't seem like that was it because it would.
You would have to think it's a homeland security department or division.
So here's the update.
Cannot find it.
But I know what I saw.
But what I did not see.
Was a badge.
There was no badge on the uniform.
It was a blue uniform with a embroidered logo that's in GSA and the left breast.
Pocket and on the back and said global security.
Either agency or administration.
I'm not exactly sure.
Yeah.
That's.
That was in the JFK.
Check in area.
At the Pakistan PIA Airlines.
The person who checked my passport, essentially.
Hey, two points about Pakistan.
First of all, Pakistan is a police state.
Yeah.
It's amazing.
There are military police everywhere.
You can't drive 20 K without going through some kind of a guard check point.
If you want to go into certain shopping areas.
They're looking with mirrors underneath your car.
There.
You know, I'd like to have that job.
Look with mirrors underneath your dress.
There are metal detectors at shopping malls.
It is a police state.
And we do not want that in the United States.
No, sir.
And then lastly, I also thought it was interesting.
The people I was staying with.
They are the lead of the country.
And you know what they have.
They have really high quality food.
They control their food source.
So much so that they didn't like the milk.
They were getting from the local market.
They bought their own cow.
With the codex, Elmatera is coming down.
It's interesting to see the elite in all countries.
Really taking care to feed themselves and their families.
Yeah.
Only the best.
Except.
Well, that's it for today.
Big hair.
Hope you win.
I had to be back in the USA.
Welcome.
Hi, buddy.
Welcome home.
Thank you so much.
Appreciate the update.
So maybe it is that global security agency that people sent me the link to, which has.
It has different offices.
I think the Netherlands is one of the main offices.
G.
Ah, the stranger things seem.
The more they seem like.
Serendipity.
So here's a, here's a link that I think bears.
Worthiness of discussing.
Or report, I should say.
Now, I don't know much about bribar dot com.
So I have no idea.
And I'm not sure about the sources on this.
But if it took place at Davos or devil.
I'm hoping there's video of it.
Check President.
Vuckloff Claus took aim at climate change campaigner.
El Gore on Saturday in Davos.
In a frontal attack on the science of global warming.
This is highly interesting.
I don't think there's any global warming to the 67 year old liberal who's country holds the rotating presidency of the European Union.
I don't see this statistical data for that.
I'm starting to like the gentleman from the Czech Republic.
Referring to the former US vice president who attended Davos this year.
He added, I'm very sorry that some people like El Gore are not ready to listen to the competing theories.
I do listen to them.
Hallelujah.
My ball brother.
Environmentalism and the global warming alarmism is challenging our freedom.
El Gore is an important person in this movement.
Yes.
And I think that this guy is on a very good track with the way he's choosing his words.
I hope that these are verbatim quotes.
Because if anything, we need to stop the the.
The exactly what he says, the challenges to our freedom because of this,
which is exactly where this is headed.
And which is really my main gripe about against all this.
People say, oh, you know, you talk bad about greenies that greenies are terrorists.
I've never said that.
I don't even think I've used the word greenies.
John Devore, I use the word greenies.
Go, go, pastor him, go Twitter him.
I'm just being logical.
I'm all for making the world a better place and doing more for the environment.
But I don't think I should be taxed for everything.
That involves CO2.
Speaking on the sidelines of the World Economic Forum, he said that there was that he was more worried about the reaction to the perceived dangers than the consequences.
I'm afraid that the current crisis will be misused for radically constraining the functioning of the markets and market economy all around the world.
Exactly right, which is exactly what the stimulus package is all about.
All this green stuff that's in there.
Which surely we need, but I don't think it's the way to solve the financial economic crisis.
I read somewhere that there's $2 billion in there to find out if capping and storing CO2 was possible.
I thought people were doing it already.
They don't even know if it works yet.
That's pretty outrageous.
Class makes no secret of his climate change skepticism.
He is also a fierce critic of the European Union.
And as branded the world's top panel of climate experts, the UN's IPCC, a smug monopoly.
Oh man, 67 years old.
I hope he lives to see 68 because they're going to kill him if he keeps talking like that.
Here's a guy that matters.
Maybe they're just going to belittle him.
Crazy Czech president who happens to have the presidency, the Czech Republic,
now the presidency of the European Union.
Good thing.
Well, keep your eye on this guy.
It's certainly something that is worthy of some research.
Don't you agree.
Let me just check through this.
What are we doing now?
We'll over an hour.
Okay.
It should be just about time.
She's okay.
That's a critic hunch.
What's next for the world?
It was the first post.
Oh man.
I don't want to just reject this story.
I don't want to go out on a bummer.
This first post.co.uk.
That's pretty good.
They got some good writers there.
Hold on.
Tuner is twittering me with more Czech love with a link.
Ah, okay.
I can see the title already as the page is loading and building the lower house of the Czech parliament.
I guess this has is as of today.
Has postponed a vote on the European Union's reform treaty.
Excellent.
The Czech Republic, which holds the EU rotating presidency is the last country to vote on
the so-called Lisbon Treaty.
Well, let's see what this article says.
The vote was delayed at the request of law makers from Prime Minister Mirick
Topalonix, conservative civic democratic party, which is split over the issue.
The Lisbon Treaty document seeks to streamline decision making in the block.
All member states need to approve it to take effect.
So far, 24 of the EU's 27 nations have ratified the document.
Irish voters dealt it a blow when they rejected it in a referendum last June.
A second poll is planned for later this year.
How does this bullshit?
They have to have this thing done because that's how their new banking system,
their new financial, one world bank and eventually one world government.
That's how it.
It's all in those documents.
That's all the shit that that's why they needed this.
That's why they pushed for it so hard.
And that's why they rammed it through 24 of the 27 member state parliaments.
And got it ratified.
The Polish parliament has approved the treaty, but the president has yet to sign it.
So that's a game he's playing there.
I'm sure that has to do with it.
Oh, they're going to drag president Obama into this for sure.
Because they're going to say, well, man, get rid of those missiles in Poland.
And then maybe the guy will sign up.
This is just a bunch of gangs and thugs.
And it's not against you and I.
I don't hate Iranians.
They're paying into beautiful fucking people.
And they got iPods.
But more do you want?
Now it's the idiot to run the place.
And we've got the idiots in the UK.
British people are lovely, fantastic.
They drink a lot.
Good on them.
But they're completely ruled by
this bunch of dickheads.
And you notice that no one's complaining about the issues they're complaining about.
We're complaining about the shit that they've made wrong.
Just thugs and bullies worldwide, global bullies.
And every single one of them's got some kind of finance here behind them.
And you think that the doctor evil concept is wrong?
No, man.
I bet you they even have the white pussycat.
Okay, what should we do?
I don't have time to play a home.
I'll play one more song.
We'll get out of here.
All right, hold on.
I'm going to play this one just because it's such an incredibly pretty song.
Oh, man.
They don't make music like this anymore.
Ah.
Dennis, the young and sticks.
Babe.
Oh, man.
Oh, whera.
Oh.
Oh, man.
Give me the courage and the strength I need
Please believe that it's true
Baby, I love you
You know it's you, babe
Whenever I get weary and I've had enough
Feel like it may go, you know it's you, babe
Give me the courage and the strength I need
Please believe that it's true
Baby, I love you
Baby, I believe in I'll say it once again
Somehow try to smile
I know the feeling we're trying to forget
If only for a while
You'll be lonely without you
And I'll need your love to see me through
Please believe me
My heart is in your hands
I'll be missing you
Oh, Aaron Burnett
Aaron
Baby, come back
Baby, please
We've got a saver
I know I'm in a melancholy
Sad mood
We must save Aaron Burnett
From the evil elites
We must bring her over to the good side
Bring her to the light
Bring her towards the white
Please help me save Aaron
Oh, all right
I'm going to try and do tomorrow
No agenda taping with John CD
And then Friday of Fubar Friday
Which will the timing will be very dependent upon the travel plans of the lady Patricia
And wrote in weather conditions may affect your your mileage and performance
As you can understand
So until then my friends use your freedom very, very wisely
Save Aaron Burnett from the evil elites
And live your life with passion
Another fine medial presentation
Stick it in your ear