Delta Sierra Charlie eight one five
sixteen million dollars worth of airplane
strapped by us
to the next generation where you
content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying to the
shore.
Fantastic.
It's out of curry.
Hit me now.
It's out of the night.
Oh.
Imagine waking up.
Solid everything is evident.
Home any rules.
Thomas a relevant.
People to places.
The message racing.
From race fist to cities.
Recyst to change.
Speak the scenario.
With a future drop in 2020.
Some number a year ago.
People rose up.
Up a man's closer.
World wide block party.
Everybody shows up.
Up on who stops.
Gettles and hotspots.
People celebrate.
No more souls ride.
No more blush in.
On the first deficit.
Keep in hip hop.
The face lift.
The latest fashion.
Stockwalk is crashing.
It's out of date.
Time to get the party crack in.
And it's the time.
And the day is right.
The revolution will begin.
It's out of the night.
Time to get the party crack.
the grease minus zero so it's freezing in Holland and we got a lot of water you know
we're the lower territory so we got a lot to do here man it's really warm the
foot to see everyone's planting on the ice so I'm going to skate today and
what I say thanks for everyone who comment on the DSE Overview 2008 it was really
a pleasure for me to create a stop you know it's like a painting or something
it was kind of sucked into the project but I really love it thanks and talk to
you later this year but happy new year you know how to go now Ray thanks again man
it was a fantastic overview I know exactly what you're talking about with
it being almost like a painting I feel like my shows are that every single day
and the mevio today show I put together actually put together like a painting like
paint by the numbers no less B.C. Smith apparently is in California let's see
if we can get them on the phone hey I don't know the gun hey is this B.C. stands for a
watt bulb actually it's been this is actually been from Oakland your old time
economics advanced hey Ben how you doing man good to talk to you that's a bad
yourself yeah I hang it in there so what's what's the situation like in Oakland
right now well for what I could tell it was interesting because you know I live in
Oakland and just kind of watching you know last time I'm going to sleep for probably
about three or four helicopters flying over downtown and didn't really know what
we're going on then but you know this morning you wake up here is a news report
and from what you know we've seen locally here there are about 200 people but
started off at a rally at the barge station where they got a shot just kind of a
peaceful you know gathering there in the afternoon kind of a memorial that
same and then from there kind of a group broke off and started walking you know
feel like they're marching downtown in Moscow the mob mentality I think
took over right and just let you like you were saying I mean you know one person
throws a brick for a window in there and so it's chaos they tried flipping a few
cop cars over broke a bunch of car windows that some cars on fire the cops
and right gear showed up and then your guests are flying right you know what
happened you know kind of one of those things where you get that work yeah they
should be marching and they should be saying that you shouldn't be
doing this on station turning brick through windows of random
shots downtown but you know they're pissed off yeah now they should be
some very very pissed off he was speaking of tear gas I was reading that the
cops in in Athens were with the writing has been going on for for weeks now
that they actually ran out of tear gas and they bought more from Israel of
course well Israel doesn't need tear gas they have thanks yeah but but they
got tear gas apparently and they're selling a cheap bunny bait so Ben is there
any media coverage it sounds like like it's 200 people well although I
wouldn't like to see an angry mob of 200 people it's certainly not thousands
is there any coverage of this is is mainstream picking it up or not you're
definitely seeing you like the San Francisco I call out a store in the front page
this morning right yeah that's the one that I read last night so that was there
I mean that's you know if that's mainstream I'm sure the network news stations
probably had stories this morning I don't want the network news because it's
usually pointless so you can't comment on that I mean you're seeing stuff I mean
it's definitely if you go to the Chronicles website today it's the lead story
there they've got a lot of pictures I think for people there last night taking
pictures in the Chronicle to their credit as a pretty good job of letting the
public submit pictures to them yeah the publish on their website so there's a
lot of good pictures I think it's probably the best one they have on there is
a car burning in the background with the cops and right here in front of it right
it's kind of those ominous shots well I would say and I would plead to to all
chuckle heads that you know the the best thing you can do to help the
situation is whenever you see a good article and I agree I thought the
thought the Chronicle article was at least it seemed detailed and I presume
accurate is send that to people you know it's just show it around because it's
the reason that people really don't know this stuff is you know I have to see
something three times before it sinks in I've learned this because my wife
for 22 freaking years repeats everything three times to make sure that I have
heard her and understand it and she's right of course usually I want to say oh yeah
I got it okay and if you don't see news about something at least three
time is not going to sink in it's like this morning I picked up the the financial
times was sold out I got to talk to my guys and my new news agents the headline
looking for it is something that I I told Patricia just the other day I said you
know what these guys are doing I'm going to do what these bastards are going to
do is the same thing they've done in the States is they're going to want to
protect themselves for deflation because you know you can't make any money when
there's no interest on on loans oh I can't I find the fun of the paper so I
said they're going to start to inflate stuff and it says right on the crap I can't
haha I know what it said I just wanted to make sure I read it exactly right
it says treasury to print more money to to beat inflation that's essentially it
as that's what Alistair Darling said oh we got to create some more money to come back
more money in inflation it doesn't necessarily inflation no no they want to increase
inflation okay so that's like it's delusion of our money so I mean that that is
Ron Paul said and I think he said it correctly it's it's immoral as like saying here's
this milk we have but you know what we're going to dilute it a little bit by adding more water
to it it's it's immoral and it messes up a lot of stuff so you know when you start to
print money your money devalues inflation rises and prices go up your wages won't
necessarily go up immediately that's when the real ride is going to happen because
people will want more will need more money to get by so the interesting because I think
what you're going to see this year is they're going to a lot of companies are going to
give me this to their employees because of poor economic times but inflation's going to happen
and it's going to take a while for people to kind of catch up to that and that's that's where
it all goes horribly wrong I'm still looking up here it is finally got the front of the paper
Chancellor set to print more cash as rates hit record low and I should have underline this I should
have kept this but essentially as interest rates appear certain to fall to an historic low today
interest rates essentially sure you know you're getting screwed as if you're saving money because
you're getting very little interest but more interestingly guys who lend money aren't going to
get a lot of interest either so the chancellor and that's Alice Darling and Merven King I'm
talking about the UK obviously the governor of the Bank of England the central bank of England the
Federal Reserve of England are looking at expanding the money supply by billions and using the
extra cash to buy assets ranging from government or commercial debt to private equities exactly the
same thing that the tarp program was all about big bailout big printing of money the people get
screwed or people who are pretty much in the lower middle class I'm sorry I'm sorry I know you
would you well well the said doing all the time the banks are doing I think they need to do
the second act they're going to need the pump money to the economy people they all need to do
isn't a year's time to take all that extra money back out and the hard thing is the set has a
really hard time taking me out of the system very easy to put money into this everyone's good
right so it's your money slot and around and if it was only a temporary thing
It would actually benefit, but the problem is that the Fed hadn't taken money out of the
system until the early 80s when inflation was so bad and Volcker came in and did all that,
but it stopped for about two years while he was doing that. But it was great. It's 60
economy. It did what it was supposed to do and it was a good thing. Probably I don't think
that's going to do that this time. And here's going to have this math inflation. I think those
unfortunately could sweep into the system. Well, the countdown has begun. We'll keep our eye on it.
Down there. Ben, thanks for calling me, man. I appreciate it.
Hey, that's a lot, thank you. Bye bye.
Oh, lot, they're don'ts. While robbers laugh and steal.
They're going to watch them eat their meals.
Oh, lot, they're gonna eat their meals.
Rock on glass is everywhere. It's a bloody scene.
Can't make the citizens as they own the news.
Children play with mustard cards.
Those cover their hands.
Palaces are laughing and drink.
Drunk to all their memories.
Family's buying dog food now. Starvation runs the street.
They've decided before the one infected by the green.
Now some folks say that we should be blessed.
For what we have, tell me what you'd be happy.
Oh, man, be incomparable in the bowl.
The music a genius at our steve wonder.
And village ghetto land from songs in the key of life.
I love that song.
And I love the way it sounds on the new set of everything sounds.
Let me see, this is a pretty big story over here in Europe.
That Russia has effectively turned off the gas supply running to the Ukraine.
This seems to happen just about every single winter.
This, of course, there's a lot of history between Russia and the Ukraine.
And this really, I would have to say, is pretty much a business deal gone bad from what I understand.
And what I've been able to gather, 640 million, I believe it's dollars is owed by the Ukraine to Russia.
And Russia said, hey, man, if you're not going to pay up, we're going to turn off the supply, which, of course, is obviously,
is not Russia, is Gazprom, but let's just say it effectively, that's Putin, Ergo Russia.
We're just going to turn off. If you don't want to pay, now, the slight problem is that the gas that flows through the Ukraine also
supplies, I believe, about a third, if not somewhat more of all the natural gas to Europe,
including many Western Europe countries.
So I'm looking at this map here.
Everything from Romania, Bulgaria, Macedonia, Greece, like Greece needed this shit.
Bosnia, Croatia, Hungary, Slovakia, Poland, the Czech Republic, Austria, Slovenia, Italy, Germany, France, all of them
affected from badly to severely due to the shortage coming through the Ukraine.
Now, if it weren't for the fact that this is one of the coldest winters we've witnessed in many, many years.
You heard Ray call in. In fact, a guy I know in Holland, he was kind of a whacked out Tony Robbins,
type guy, celebrity, NLP, dude. He gets an unfair rap, his name is Emiel Dattelbaum.
I like the guy very much, he's very smart, but he messes up his public,
he messes up his public stuff and people think he's a, you know, basically he took it one step too far,
and it's hard to erase that image from people. He's a very, very smart guy. He called me up.
He said, dude, let's do the 11 city skating competition, which hasn't taken place in
God knows how many decades, which is a huge thing in Holland.
All the canals for his over, it's a natural ice and you skate through 11 different cities.
And I don't know, it's hundreds of kilometers long and, you know, people died doing it.
But it hasn't happened so long because of course, well, that's a global warming and climate change has brought all this upon us.
And well, now we have people who are going to freeze to death in their homes.
And if you don't think it happens, pay attention, pay attention to the news and spread it around and try and help people out.
And, um, where was that I was reading about this? It was, um, I believe in Rome.
Maybe it wasn't, I think it must have been either Romania or Bulgaria of the schools are closed.
And they're chopping up wood to heat the children.
So, uh, there's a lot of crazy things going on.
Let me see what else is in the news, uh, interesting.
And of course, all of these links in the show notes, a daily source code dot com crossposts that are curry dot com.
Uh, Reuters article.
I love this.
Uh, John Taylor, who was the undersecretary of the treasury for international affairs from 2001 to 2005, said the explosive growth of the feds balance sheet.
That's, uh, the money that, uh, we have effectively lent out the bankers and given away in some cases.
Since September, this balance sheet, according to John Taylor, has been, quote, unbelievable.
He goes on to say, this doesn't really seem like quantitative easing in the sense of finding a growth rate in the money supply told a panel discussion.
At the American Economic Association, what you're looking at now is really being determined by other considerations.
How much should we buy of mortgage back securities?
How much should we loan to foreign central banks?
This is really more like an industrial policy. Read this article.
It's from Reuters. It's mainstream.
And it really does, uh, give you some insights into how some people are thinking about what's going on.
I'll just turn on CNBC.
Man, there are a lot of people freaking out about about what's going on.
Uh, I'll just run through this list and stop anything that, uh, that hits our fancy.
This is, uh, New Zealand is now picking up on the Gardasil, uh, profit freight train.
They now want to offer this, uh, or they're, it's being made available free to girls age 12 to 18 in New Zealand.
It's free, maybe, to those, the victims who are taking it.
It's being paid for by your tax, uh, tax money.
At the bottom of the article, thank God, at least it's in there.
Family first national director, Bob McCowskree said,
The vaccination is unproven.
Yes. I think we've, uh, safely established that.
And I'm not against, uh, vaccinations. I'm not again. You know, there's, we,
Look, I'm sure that I'm very happy I got my polio and, uh,
What other, what other, um, vaccinations I've received as a child.
But when it comes to the amount that kids are being inoculated with these days.
Like 36 different, in these cocktail, 36 different versions.
And there are traces of mercury. And there is all kinds of bad shit in there.
And it's hurting our kids, but this stuff, this HPV.
Human, papal, mal, what is it? Papal, mal virus.
Papal mal virus.
Which is supposed to prevent cervical cancer is indeed unproven, even by scientific methods.
We've had doctors on this show explain that to us.
Um, this was kind of fun, particularly because it came from a daily tech.com,
which I read from time to time, uh, more for tech than for anything else that you can imagine.
Headlines, sea ice ends the year at the same level as 1979.
I'm sure you will be reading about this.
Make sure people see it because it's important to know that this is data being reported by the
University of Illinois's Arctic Climate Research Center.
And it's derived from satellite observations of the northern and southern hemisphere polar regions.
And right now, uh, according to them, the sea ice this year or 2008 ended at the same level as in 1979.
And they, they go on to say that, you know, this stuff does, uh, thaw and freeze quite a bit.
It's not like the, uh, like the permafrost, permafrost.
Um, but in May, and this is the point that I think is important,
concerns over disappearing sea ice lead to the United States officially listing their polar bear as a threatened species.
Even over objections from experts who claim the animals numbers were actually increasing.
So, uh, someone's full of shit somewhere.
That's for sure.
This is a really cool one, uh, from CES, of course, to the consumer electronics show taking place in Vegas.
So, be great if someone was out there.
And, uh, I could call in if you were in Vegas, uh, because I'd love to see this device for real.
Blau-punked.
And company called me rumor, I think is how you pronounce it.
We'll be announcing the first in-internet radio receiver.
I love this.
So you get streaming radio stations.
Um, here's actually, well, this is a very, it's, this is from autoblog.com link in the show notes.
Uh, a lot of a lot of information about it, but users of the new head units will be able to tune into
Internet radio stations offered by me, rumor, okay?
As well as add stations of their choosing by simply inputting the URL.
So I'm hoping that they have some form of, um, RSS parsing mechanism in this software as well,
because I'm, you know, pretty much like you listen to a podcast that has been pre-recorded.
Um, as long as you can access the MP3 file and you can, you know, you can play it progressively as it downloads,
kind of a version of streaming works perfectly over, uh, GPRS and, uh, and, and, uh, 3G.
That would be very awesome.
Oh, man.
What I'd buy, I'd buy them for every single cut.
Well, actually, I get rid of my cars.
Hey, if anyone wants to buy a car, by the way, I'm getting rid of a couple in the UK,
cheap.
I'm getting rid of the jag and I'm getting rid of the, uh, the smart roadster,
but we don't need a car anymore.
I want to keep one car, Christina's, um,
but, uh, the others that they gotta go.
It's just, it's cost me like 120 pounds just to keep them near the house.
Who needs to get rid of these cars?
I'm going green, baby.
Alright, let's, uh, play another song.
If you got anything, talk about throw it up on, uh, talk to you.
Chat room.
Stand up for your right.
Or Twitter me.
Stand up.
Stand up for your right.
Don't give up the fight.
Pretty.
Come and don't tell me.
Heaven is on the gear.
I know you don't know, what life is really worth.
Here's a call that needs a reward.
I've just told you I've never been told.
So now you see the right thing.
Stand up for your right.
Come on, get up, set up.
Get up, set up.
Don't give up the fight.
Stand up for your right.
Get up, set up.
Don't give up the fight.
Most people think,
Break our little come from the sky.
Take away everything,
And make a heavy body feel high.
With this and all, with life is worth.
You will look for yours on earth.
And now will you see the right.
Just stand up for your right.
Get up, set up.
Stand up, set up.
Stand up for your right.
Get up, set up.
Don't give up the fight.
Let's see, we've got you for Bob.
Yeah, I'm Norea.
Good man, what's your name? Bob?
Yeah, Bob's young and little dad boy.
Hey, Bob.
So I saw you chatting away there about about the sea ice,
which apparently is not melting away.
Yeah, that was a good story.
I don't have to do a Google on that.
That was a catch by your dad dialing for that.
Because, you know, I've been following your most, you know,
your recent DSAs.
They're nearly on the trail of, you know,
the BS story about the climate change.
You know, we're used to be called global warming.
Definitely got, you got also that pretty straight.
Yeah, it's, uh, it's pretty amazing, you know,
there's so much evidence coming out about, uh,
about global warming at this very moment.
And, you know, by the way, just look around you.
Look, and, you know, what is the perfect temperature for the world?
I know that it's kind of cold here.
And I wouldn't mind it being a little bit warmer.
But, you know, it's, it's so amazing when you talk to people about this.
There is an immediate, whoa, you're crazy, man.
We're, we're burning up the world.
We're, we're killing ourselves.
We've got to change.
Like, yeah, obviously we've always got to be careful with our planet.
But I take huge offense at the, at all the laws and restrictions that are being placed.
And as far as I can tell, monetary system that's going to be put in place based upon
what I can see is nothing but a farce.
It just doesn't add up, you know, all the charts and all the beautiful power point presentations
and the movies and the Oscars and the Grammys and the Nobel Prize.
Still makes it very cold here.
Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
They see the same sort of spinning planet by our old friend out there.
And that's great.
It's kind of scary.
It's kind of a potential at least, you know, in very kind of like we're potential for this carbon-based
monetary policy.
You know, I'm not, I mean, in any position to get influence anything.
I like to use hope to hope that does.
Well, well, Bob, that's where I disagree.
I think we're all in a position to do something about it.
And all it takes is that look, you're forwarding stupid YouTube clips to your buddies all day
long anyway.
We're twittering all over the place.
We're doing blog posts.
You know, if you see something like this, but you don't,
it does not have to be a nian, a nian, a nian, a nian, which I do enough of.
But just, just send it along.
Hey, look at this.
That's kind of interesting.
Didn't know that.
Everyone sent around all the word dying emails and power points and links and webpages
and graphs and charts.
So, you know, it's, and if it's, and this is what I like about mainstream reporting
because there is a lot of good reporting being done.
It's out there.
All you have to do is catch it.
And you've got to share it amongst people.
So I think everyone can do something, just help educate your fellow man.
If they see something three times, it'll start to dawn on him.
That's really all that it takes.
Yes, good thing.
All right, Bob, I appreciate you calling him, man.
It's a very kind of you.
I just want to hit Philly real quick because he's been hanging on since the
moment we started the show.
Yeah.
Hey, man, who's this?
This is Alex.
I think it's a little bit.
First of all, are you on Skype?
Sounds like it.
Now I'm on time.
I just want to have a time.
I'll see if we'll dare.
You know, this phone technology.
We really got to find something better.
It's just not cutting it.
It's like the weakest link in the chain.
I just want to say, hey, since since you've been hanging on so long,
I appreciate you listening and appreciate you hanging in there.
Okay.
All right.
Let's go down to, well, actually, let's go straight down under to our
buddy, Claugwag, Tom Scooting, sent me an audio comment.
It's Tom.
Tom speaking from Australia.
Um.
All right.
Let's go down to, well, actually, let's go straight down under to our
buddy, Claugwag, Tom Scooting sent me an audio comment.
It's Tom, Tom speaking from Australia.
Um.
The first of all, the reason why I called got them cracked off and I thought I
have to send you something straight away.
I also forget.
Um.
This is the sound.
Oh, that we's going to do the SLR reflex debunking.
Excellent Tom.
But why are you calling from the toilet bowl?
Of a very cheap digital SLR.
They all make that sound.
The more expensive they are, the more notice they make.
And so let's, yeah, some sort of debunking one of your theories.
And he's, I've got a few other ones.
Uh, the FEMA camps all over America.
There's, uh, there's a good list out there with, um, with geo tagging.
I had to look at quite a few of them.
Uh, that, that don't look more like, um,
storage building, single story storage buildings.
They don't look like camps to me.
Um.
So I'm going to drop in a whole price.
Oops, sorry about that.
You know, the, um, those FEMA camps.
Obviously I've been reading about those.
I've seen the YouTube videos.
I've seen the pictures of, uh, of the so-called plastic coffins.
Hard for me to say either way.
Um, I, you know, and I think people look at it and they say,
I'll only shit.
This is for real.
And, uh, other people look at it and say it doesn't seem like it's real at all.
Um, I, I go by the official government documentation.
Um, pretty sure that there are indeed FEMA camps that maybe not, you know,
the hundreds that people apparently have cited, um,
but they're definitely our camps.
Uh, no doubt about it.
There, there, there are, uh, FEMA owned enclosures that could pretty much be used as a camp.
You don't need much except some bar wire and some huts.
And I seem to go hand in hand with a lack of volume if the oil prices manipulate it.
It's the, um, the same volume or,
Let me, let me tell you, the oil price, it gets manipulated when it's on the tankers.
That's when it happens. Okay.
It's the, listen, oil has to flow and it gets loaded onto tankers.
And that's where the price gets manipulated.
Even more volume, um, got a tiny URL.com forward slash oil price too for, uh,
for a bit of a graph on that.
Um, then some of the good news, uh,
Oh, maybe agrees with something.
You know, how do, how you said things get less and less, um,
um, a more and more restrictive, um,
in a year and a straight year, they've just recently, um,
allowed, uh, Dutch unpasteurized, um, milk cheese, um,
to come in, so it's not all bad.
And, uh, a link, um, that you might be interested in,
it's called What's Up With That with WAA,
WTS UpWithThat.com.
This guy has, uh, got a warming debunker.
Uh-huh.
Um, yeah, that was it, mate.
Sorry, dude.
Let's just, just get into me.
There's too much conspiracy theory stuff going on.
Yeah.
It's not all that bad.
All right.
Well, I don't know, man.
Uh, you're down there in Australia, where they're, uh,
shutting off your internet.
So, uh, I don't know what's bad in your book,
but I think that's pretty bad.
I love the fact that, um, I put this in that mevio today.
Um,
uh, who is it, uh, Larry Flint and Jo, uh,
what's his name?
Not Jo, not Jo Fraser, obviously.
Jo Francis.
They, uh, they say, oh, we're going to go, uh, to the, to the,
to the Congress and, uh,
we want $5 billion for a bailout of the adult entertainment industry.
Ha ha ha.
Those guys are funny.
I do appreciate a good joke.
Although I know they're pretty damn serious.
I don't think they're kidding about it.
It is.
It's in, it's in huge trouble.
Mainly because people copy stuff,
although I pay for my porn and I'm quite proud of it.
And in fact, they got an email from Bobby Eden.
Who turns out is a pretty well-known porn star, actually.
This is the, um, the girl, the young woman that Patricia flew on, uh,
the place she was on the same flight from, uh, Amsterdam to London.
And they got the chatten and she was going over to do some, uh,
productions in her adult film industry job.
And, uh, we've kind of kept in touch.
And, uh, she sent me an email this morning and said, hey, man,
uh, we're, we're looking at ways to, to make money.
And it's, uh, you know, times are hard and it's podcasting anything.
And I can just see Bobby Eden doing a pitch for Go Daddy.
Ha ha ha.
I bet you they'd be into it, too.
That one actually could happen.
But I got to, I got to figure out.
I'm gonna take a meeting with her, her, her people regardless.
Because that's just gonna be fun.
Oh, by the way, oh, man.
This, this will trip you out.
I got to get this from the other side.
Hold on.
Just, uh.
It's an envelope.
This will trip you out.
Let me read this.
You guys are going to love it.
The reptilians are out to get me.
Okay, so it's a very nice heavy bond envelope paper and inside a number of different sheets,
which I'll explain in a moment.
And a card, you can hear it's very thick.
Probably that's a good millimeter thick.
It has a gold embossed edge, completely, that's probably real gold.
And at the top it has the emblem of Queen Elizabeth.
And I will show you this to you.
The master of the household has received her Majesty's command to invite Mr. Adam Curry
to a reception to be given at Buckingham Palace by the Queen to relaunch the monarchy website
www.royal.gov.uk on Thursday, 12th of February, 2009 at noon.
A reply is requested to the master of the household, Buckingham Palace, London S-W-1-A-1-A-A.
Email Master.household at royal.gsx.gov.uk.
How interesting is that?
I'm going in.
And of course, all recording devices are strictly prohibited, but, boy, I got to tell you,
I feel that maybe I got to pull that old MP3 player recorder out and I might have to get
the wireless set rigged up because you know I'm going to go, you know I'm going to,
because who knows, maybe they just want to trap me.
Throw me in the tower.
Ah, so that shall be fun.
Let me see, how long are we on time here about it?
I want to keep this under an hour just a couple more, I actually should scan this thing.
I will.
I'll scan that and I'll put it up on Curry.com.
Great article about the pirates, the Somali and pirates.
Please read this.
It's in the show notes.
It's from the independent and when you read this article and you first understand the background
about pirates as we think of Johnny Depp Pirates of the Caribbean and what the romanticism
of pirates and irony may be.
But then the background of the dumping of toxic waste, the illegal fishing of Somali's
waters, the illegal toxic waste dumping, by the way, of course, done by the West.
These people are extremely desperate and this is pretty much the last resort, the last
thing they can do.
It's working for them because you don't read a lot about what's going on there in the
mainstream media and when all you hear is pirate, you think, oh man, crappy pirates, kill
them, get rid of them.
But there's a lot more to the story and I encourage you to read that.
That's definitely worth the conversation in the near future.
Just some other things I just wanted to mention.
This was just horrible.
I always say your government doesn't love you.
Well, the proof is in the pudding from CNN, the United States Army is apologizing to thousands
of Army families who have received letters beginning with Dear John Doe after losing a loved
one in Iraq or Afghanistan, not just a couple, 7,000 letters were sent in late December
to notify families of services or gifts surviving family members can receive from non-profit
organizations that help families of fallen soldiers.
These are the people that want to keep the ID database.
Better yet in the United Kingdom, they want to hand this over to commercial entities.
You can't even keep track of people who fought for our country and died for our country.
Shitheads, government doesn't love you, leave me, they do not love you.
And then what is this?
Oh, I'm a very happy note, like this.
The power beam company, power beam preparing to deliver us wireless electricity, now it's
not like they're doing big transfers yet, but they do say that it could start off quite
nicely where you'd never have to hook up your cell phone, your iPhone or any other, you're
iPod ever again.
You just walk into the house and it starts charging.
Of course, Tesla knew how to do this 100 years ago and all of the information on his
wireless power tower, which he actually built in New York, go ahead Google it, you'll see
it.
That's gone missing, been destroyed.
It's been suppressed, but he certainly was on to something really big.
And then, oh, yes, I should add this to the Gardezill Merck, the company that makes
Gardezill, this horrible drug, which is paralyzing and killing children, filed last month
for approval from the FDA, the Food and Drug Administration, the same people who passed
this dangerous drug in just six, under six months of testing.
That's for approval for males, give it to the boys now, ages 29 to 26, CNBC confirms
it.
Yeah, give it to the boys.
We haven't killed enough children, holy crap, a reminder or actually a notification
for this weekend on mevio today and probably I'll somehow get a food bar Friday out tomorrow.
I've got a new song by the pretenders and I've also got three tickets to give away to
their tour from the record label, who apparently someone over there listens to the show
likes a lot.
And we say, hey, would you mind spitting the record so I'm getting the MP3, it's good
song by the way, Chrissy Hight, a little bit of her anti-social behavior, love that.
And of course, tickets for one of the gigs on the tour.
Here's the news.
A cute, deep found, a good old rabbit light.
Someone left the light behind and plastic bag.
There's no rules.
There's no rule.
scratch, which she tends to do almost every single day. I really appreciate you guys
listening. I got a couple of calls in there. That was good. I wish I could make
it sound better on the talk show system. Unfortunately, well, the biggest problem is
that the new version of Skype, in fact, it may even be the beta versions or
maybe you have to downgrade. It has automatic gain control turned on by default
because I can literally see the max input volume changing, but there's no
apparent place. I've looked in all the settings and all the options. There's
no place to turn it off. They used to be as far as I can recall, so I might
have to downgrade that because that is the biggest source of the sound
problems. And otherwise, well, you know, it's back to trying to figure out the
tip protocol and hack and then God knows what, but at least some version of it
is working. Okay. Let me just hold on. Open up all the phones for everybody.
Just want to say thank you all if you want to say something now is the time
because we're going to shut her down. Yeah, thanks for the thing I love
telling in there. All right, Bob. Thank you. Appreciate it. Thank you. And everyone
else seems to be hanging up. Okay. That's it for now. Back with you tomorrow for
the food bar of how I'm already food bar. The food bar Friday festivities. I'll
scan that to invitation. You'll get a hood out of it when you see that from the
queen herself. I hope the gold shows up perfectly on the on the scan. You still
got some freedom, exercise it, use it, stand up for your right and whatever
you do. Live your life with passion. Another fine, medium presentation. Stick it in
your ear.