Delta Sierra Charlie 817 Fubar Friday
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying with you to the future
No Christina's got the body
She really lacks the spin and fur
But when she's flirting with the camera
She's just a little girl
Now pink is cute but still a baby
And she talks with attitude
She has some scum for a young lady
But what I'd be like to do
I'd rather do it with my tongue
She is what's the woman's face
All the time I want to get to meet me
When Britney sings a sound of music
Like a belly and a bird
But how would you let's be with her
She's always hanging with them all
I'd rather do it with my tongue
She's what a woman's supposed to be
The only girl I ever need
But I'd rather do it with me
I'd rather do it with my tongue
She really got me on her knees
The only girl I ever need
But I'd rather do it with me
I'd rather do it with my tongue
I'd really like to be with Kylie
She's feeling really hard
I wonder if I can get Kylie
I'd rather do it with my tongue
She's really got me on my knees
All my tongue won't you do it with me
I'd rather do it with my tongue
She's what a woman's supposed to be
The only girl I ever need
But I'd rather do it with my tongue
She's feeling really hard
I'd rather do it with my tongue
I don't know if I'd want to do it with Madonna anymore
There was a time perhaps
From their longer
Food bar Friday everybody, welcome to the Daily Source Code episode
One, seven coming to you from the Curry Terrace in Southwest London.
It's been way too long once again, and I apologize profusely.
Life got in the way is usual.
Actually, with the, with the preview today stuff that I'm getting better at it,
and I'm working really hard, and I'm doing everything.
Editor, producer, writer, cameraman, audio guy, and oh yeah, asshole talent.
Very different, all very challenging to get everything right.
One thing goes wrong, and it could be hours and hours of extra work, but I think I've kind of got it under control.
And almost had to show out yesterday, but it was nine o'clock by the time I was finally done with dinner,
and I wanted to sit with the girls, Patricia Kristina, and Dex, by the way, was pretty much now a full fledged member of the family.
Kristina's bow.
Good kid, man, he's sure's helping me out. Oh, what? He's a final cut wizard.
Got to love it.
So, I've got a whole week's worth of news, which is really too much to go through even for a food bar,
or maybe even particular for a food bar show.
So I'm going to try and work through my list and reverse alphabetical reverse chronological order, I should say.
With yesterday, last night, as I went upstairs, we were going to watch celebrity Big Brother,
which, once again, is I'm loving the show so much.
My favorites have got to be Coolio, who's in the Big Brother house here in the United Kingdom,
Verne, known as Minini, from Austin Powers, he's in.
And, uh, Latoya Jackson, who is just a really, she's very nice.
My favorite right now, just because she's smoking hot is Michelle.
I actually from some dinky girl group, I don't know, S club seven or steps or something like that.
I have no idea what she's from, but man, she's hot.
So, I'm ready to watch that.
And I glance over my screen where I have CNBC streaming on the sling box from my good friend, in Detroit.
I think it's Detroit or Chicago. I don't know, we do so many shows in the row.
And I see an airbus in the Hudson River and like, oh my god, check that out.
And, uh, look like a very successful ditch attempt by the pilot.
So, just phenomenal job on, on getting that plane down.
There's a whole bunch of data points that I've been collecting.
One is a flight track from, what does that mean?
Maybe that's flighttracker.com or something, a flight aware, there you go.
You can literally see the plane do a dog leg and head back towards LaGuardia.
And you see the track end right there in the Hudson River.
What's funny about it though on flight, flight aware, this flight tracker.
It has data. So, departure, scheduled 304 p.m.
Eastern, actual, or estimated 326 p.m. Eastern.
Arrival time, scheduled 438 p.m.
It was on its way to, uh, where's it going to?
I forget KCLT.
Doesn't make, it wasn't going to Tempe, was it?
I think it was going to Tempe Arizona.
But anyway, the actual arrival time, remember, actual departure time 326, actual arrival time 332.
Unfortunately, got short change on your ticket.
You landed up in the Hudson, didn't get that far.
But wow, phenomenal. And I'm so disappointed that no one has this ditch landing on video tape.
Maybe it still has the surface. I've also been surfing around a lot of the aviation boards.
I'm not just a pilot. I play one on the podcast as well.
And I was looking for the, so there's really two data points that I'm interested in.
One is I'd like to hear the air traffic control report where the captain calls in and says,
Look, we've flown through a flock of geese and we have, we're losing power.
So we're turning back. That would be really nice to catch that. I can't seem to find it.
I did find this piece though, and I listened to this.
This is from, this is actually from JFK, and they do reference what's going on at LaGuardia.
Hello, my aunt, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie,
auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie, auntie
So, these questions still to be answered, but very, very happy that everyone made it out and everyone made it out safe, and still hoping I can, I would have fantastic landing that must be to watch, so I'm really hoping that I get a video of that somewhere.
All right, Fubar Friday, the festivities should begin, let's begin them in style, and we have the hit test, 156 coming up, a little bit of phone lines for that.
People can participate, I know the sound is still kind of shitty, I'm talking to you, but, be fine if you guess one or two.
Time to kick back for three and a half minutes, you know what I'm going to do, man.
Just a tradition on Friday, you know.
To be hardworking, man.
My mama, she wants to be something who's who the best you can.
But then one day, I met a man who came from me and said,
Hard work, good, and hard work, fine.
But first take care of him, so now I smoke to judge, when I get up, in the car I smoke to judge.
I smoke to judge, when I get a video game, and then every 10,000 points I smoke to judge.
I smoke to judge, in time of peace, and two in time of war.
I smoke to judge, before I smoke to judge, and there I smoke to more.
I'm a daddy, he wants to listen, he'll be hard working now, my mama, he wants to listen, he'll do the best you can
But say no one day, I met him, I gave you me a day, a hot one good, and a hot one fine, so take care of it
That's why I spoke to you this city morning, I spoke to you this night, I spoke to you this city afternoon, it makes me feel alright
I spoke to you this city morning, I spoke to you this city morning, I spoke to you this city afternoon, it makes me think that this city morning, it makes me feel alright
I spoke to you this city morning, it makes me feel alright, so take care of me
Cause you're gonna come as for the joy With me and my morning
Oh
Cuz you're gonna come as for the joy With me and my afternoon
Yeah
Oh
cuz you're gonna switch the other and some brand
cuz you're gonna hop on
Yeah, homework
Oh theong
Thanks
Oh
That's
as usual all stories and music source from the drop drop.io slash daily source code and
it's much appreciated you know I've gotten a lot of response about the drop people say well
you know we should we you know we should lock it down editorial access you know because
of course we had the penis poster come by and from time to time this via grads that
show up and I do look at the drop obviously several times a day and I work on
you know removing stuff that is just lame irrelevant etc. I don't really remove
so much but there's people seem that you know they want to make it into like a
community type thing like a dig rating etc and I'm against that and let me
tell you why because I've seen this time and time again whenever you pull a community
together and you put them into some form of space where someone has power over that
space or more than one person from the community has any form of power it just
turns into crap every it with any type of list whether it's you know it doesn't
really matter what the topic is about even engineering stuff it just turns into
a mosh pit of bullshit in fact I feel that this whole thing about Steve Jobs
which everyone just jumped on that it's like you know for some reason communities
online have a really good way of self-destructing and I'm actually going to blame a
lot of these problems that Jobs has not the health problems necessarily but just
the company problems on you know the very own community that he's in charge of
because you know they they are very restricted they keep news close to the chest
and somehow communities just seem to self-destruct so I like the idea of having
well of course we have a community we're all chuckle heads but I I want it to be
free form free flow and just keep it going you know there's ups and downs and
the drop sometimes sucks and other times it's brilliant and I don't mind that people
double post things it's in fact you know whenever I see something I immediately
grab it and you can also do some interesting things with drop.io you can start
your own drop and if you see a story an article or something has been uploaded you
like you can send it to your own drops you can have your own little personal archive
you can create derivatives of the of the source code drop there's just tons of
things you can do and I would actually like to ask you for the listeners around the
world we're doing some coverage inaugural coverage of president elect Barack Obama on Monday
and Tuesday Monday is also pretty important day in in in context of in inauguration
day and Tuesday Monday is Martin Luther King Day and what I'd like to do is on Nivia
today I'd like to show little snippets of people around the world and what they expect
from the new president you know what their feelings are and if you feel like recording
something going out to your favorite bar on the street whatever maybe there's an inauguration
party you're going to if you just upload it to a drop I think each drop gets 100
100 megabytes free by default so that should be more than enough just upload it send me the link
and if you email it to Adam and Nivia.com I put uh Barack clip in the subject so I don't have to
go sorting through everything and I don't miss it if it's you know if it's arable and it's good
then I'd love to use some of that because I think it'll be fun to show this stuff around the globe
and I'll I'm perfectly happy Monday and Tuesday to create you know new episodes every you know
every couple of hours to update those clips and I will I guess I'll post something about this on
couried.com perhaps I'll put it in the show notes at the dailysourcecode.com all right let's see
what we've got going on hit a couple audio comments here for a second Adam here at the Portland
Eric and bankers are in basal yes the basal Switzerland fed chairman Ben Bernanke and his central
banking counterparts have all met this week in uh basal Switzerland yeah you know I know about that
and I actually um Ben Bernanke was in London at the London School of Economics and he did this whole
big thing about uh how they need to spend more of our money to bail out his buddies
there was uh I'm seeing if I can find it somewhere there was an excellent um let me see there was a
just a fantastic youtube video where someone asked him point blank and said hey you know
this shit you're doing it working um you know how can you say that this is the way to go
Mr. expert on the great depression and he gave like a 15 minute answer that said absolutely nothing
let me see maybe it was part of the tarp uh financial services hearing let me just see you know that's
Ron Paul we'll save that when I'll play that in a second anyway yeah so they were in basal this
bank of international settlements very very uh very um shady type of operation it feels like but
international settlement this is basically where all the gangs from all the different countries who
rule the world um settle their money I presume but that's just my presumption.
I get this it's called the bank of international settlements sounds very serious there is no news
in the mainstream media on this I wonder if you had any insight or European news on that
on a personal note I will be heading to Pakistan next week on a business trip and if I
earn anything new there from the people I talked to I'll be sure to drop a comment.
Okay right now I'm listening to the uh to the comment at the same time I'm looking at the
comments in the in the chat room it talks you people are saying the stream is over modulate other
people say it isn't over modulate I just hope the recording is okay I did test it before I went
on air so doesn't seem like audio silly is it okay so young poet is uh is saying audio
still over modulated please specify if this is um on the stream or if it's in talks you
because that's what I need to know you know I'm gonna play another song real quick I got to open
up the door and post some some reports that I can really work where if you don't mind post those
in the talks you chat will I'll be right back. similarly in India I'm not hundreds but
millions of us would be ashamed and offended if we weren't anyway implicated with the present
Indian government's fastest policies which apart from the perpetration or state terrorism
in the valley of Kashmir in the name of fighting terrorism have also turned a blind eye to the recent
state supervised program against Muslims in good job it would be absurd to think that those who criticize
the Indian government are anti-Indian although the government itself never hesitates to take that
line it is dangerous to seed to the Indian government or the American government or anyone for that
matter the right to define what India or America are or to be to cause someone anti-American
indeed to be anti-American or for that matter anti-Indian or anti-Tingled Tune is not just racist
it's a failure of the imagination then inability to see a world in terms other than those the
establishment has set out for you if you're not a bushy you're a Taliban if you don't love us
you hate us if you're not good you're evil like many others I too made the mistake of scoffing
at this post September 11 rhetoric this missing it as foolish and arrogant but I realize that it's
not foolish at all it's actually a canny recruitment drive for a misconceived dangerous world
every day I'm taking a back at how many people believe that opposing the war in Afghanistan
amounts to supporting terrorism or voting for the Taliban now that the initial aim of the war
capturing Osama bin Laden dead or alive seems to have run into bad weather the gold posts have been moved
it's been made out the whole point of the war was to tap topple the Taliban regime and liberate
of gun women from their burqas we are being asked to believe that the US Marines are actually on a feminist
mission if so if so will the next stop be America's military allies Saudi Arabia think of it
this way in India there are some pretty reprehensible social practices against untouchables against
Christians and Muslims against women Pakistan and Bangladesh have even worse ways of dealing with
minority communities and women should they be bombed should Delhi Islamabad and Dakar be destroyed
is it possible to bomb bigotry out of India kick kick kick kick kick kick can we bomb our way to a feminist
paradise
I'm not quite sure what that is but I thought it was freaky enough to play for you Roy versus DJ Spooky
on Delta Sheriff Charlie 817 see wonderful fade out I knew someone was going to be messed up with
that all right so I've adjusted whatever I could on on the on the stream and talk to you
and that's all I can do now the tough shit that we just have to live with it now don't we
all right let me get into uh get us some uh into some stories here this is actually quite
interesting that now why is my uh hmm now actually the sound of my headphones is actually lower
oh well I don't know food bard makes total sense doesn't it
tomorrow uh January 17th 2009 there's going to be a huge protest in London protesting the conflict
in the Gaza Strip I do not believe it is necessarily anti-Israeli or for that matter anti-Hamas
but it will start at Trafalgar Square not far from the curry terrace and I've already announced to
the children to Christina and Dexter 18 and 19 years old respectively that I am taking them with me to
the demonstration I want them to see it because um it's just these kids you know most of them
they'll just see shit on television they're on another protest a lot of people showed up
I want them to witness it I want them to see uh anger and uh and witness and understand why people are
angry and uh they actually are quite excited about going and Dexter was immediately saying oh man let's
let's do some video I'm like no we're going to be concentrating on what's going on I might
record some audio it's easy just take along a little record but I don't want to do video because I
also know that I'm sure that I'll be the guy that the cost come up to and say you got to
turn off your camera and then they'll say delete your uh your footage and I'll say no and I'll be
arrested and I'm not looking forward to that so that is tomorrow January 17th 2009 in London
kicking off at Trafalgar Square and there's all kinds of links as a fantastic site that someone gave me
anything I think it's called uh the global day of action dot org yeah global day of action dot org
now they've got another one scheduled for January 24th and the assembly there will be at the BBC
broadcasting house as uh we're now looking at uh thousand dead and of course you saw the the news
about the bombing of the UN building it's just it's despicable and I'm still really just
reeling from the fact that the United States as the only member of the 15 member security council
the United Nations which of course clearly is a fricking scam declined to vote against uh
uh what do you call it the resolution that the United Nations calls for an immediate ceasefire
oh man it's disgusting really is hmm let's run through a couple of articles again in reverse
chronological order in which they came in and when I think something's too old they'll just stop
but this first post dot code i UK has been entertaining me with a lot of their writing remember
this is still kind of a mainstream publication and what's interesting about this article written
by David Cox titled it could come to this a calamitous recession could lead to public unrest
and uh he lays out in some very great detail the reason why we're not seeing any of these riots
a reported widely on television and why the government's uh particularly Gordon Brown is just
spewing bold for bold-faced lies is they're very worried that the populace will become upset
and take to the streets every day you see companies laying off thousands of people it's coming
to ahead i think that they're at uh six to seven percent unemployment now they're expecting 11 to 12 percent
unemployment rate in the United Kingdom this is just a small last island man it's could be very
very complicated it's a great article i suggest you read that a little bit of homework uh link
in the drop uh link in the show notes at the daily source code dot com cross posted
at uh korea dot com great new invention you know i'm always on the lookout for some new type of
energy this uh link comes from technobob dot com the nopopo battery this is great of course
it comes from japan their little uh batteries now what they're showing here are penlights double
a batteries and there's a little applicator you can actually recharge these things with urine
like what you're having to recharge as you get out of it but it said the aqua power system
and you can uh well i say urine but you can recharge it with fluids such as beer, apple juice,
cola, saliva and yes indeed urine and uh i'm not sure where they're called nopopo it's kind of
shitty ass name but the packaging is great you see two penlight batteries two double ains and
little like applicator thingy with the you stick into the battery and there's actually a picture
of some like yellow goo in it yeah that's marketing for you man i love that
i posted this on korea dot com yesterday just out of sheer glee it's uh from cnn
done by Glenn Beck it is a youtube video you should be passing on to all of your friends far and
wide and i'm gonna play a little bit of it because it really it just repeats everything we've
been talking about here when it comes to uh climate change it's called the global warming hoax
listen to a little bit you'll get the idea pretty quickly severe storms
devastating hurricanes and massive walls of sea pummeling into major cities these are the kind of
extremes that movies like the day after tomorrow propagate about global warming even take
gillet all is it safe this grace you know it's vague what you can get similar stories from
convincing actors and no cool special effects but you're still getting all the trouble so the whole piece
is really about the about the news organizations which uh correctly identified art now businesses
have to make money it's been going on since the first uh desert storm the original invasion in the
early 90s it's a big money profit profitable money making business and it works based upon fear
and hype and drama and man it's so easy to do that with images just look what i'm doing all by
myself on that media today stuff you can do quite a bit and manipulation is quite easy you just got
to show the images have the right voice over and boom you're done and it really goes into great
detail um it's about nine nine and a half minutes you must watch this clip you will not be disappointed
guarantee it all right vaccination time see what this is i had a bit of it just just called up to
you on last week's episode of private practice and why would you be interested in that why
because last week's episode was all about vaccinating your children after recent criticisms of vaccines
by parents big farmer has fired back with the latest episode of private practice i'm particularly
interested in this debate being the father of a two and a half year old son on the autism spectrum
personally i'm not totally comfortable with the chemicals injected into our children today
and i believe it should be the parents decision after proper discussion of the risks and benefits
of each vaccination right on doctors in my experience treat these procedures far too lightly
under the orders of public health officials although i do not believe our sons of
vaccinations cause is autism i do take offense to the latest episode of private practice last week
a mother refused to vaccinate the younger brothers her her artistic son due to the risk of the
injections and due to the mother refusing these vaccinations one of her sons contracts and
eventually dies of measles the show could not have put it more clearly vaccinate your children
or they will die i can't begin to think of what i would do if i had to make the decision again
all i do know is that the show definitely forms a negative public opinion of parents who choose
not to have the children vaccinated thank you for furthering awareness of the risks of vaccinations
it's something every parent should at least be aware of love you mean it and wouldn't it be nice if
they worked for us we got a reminder man i was on i went into town to the west end
earlier this morning i'd pick up a battery charger and some some batteries for the for the camera
and there were guys in the tree outside of the ministry of defense protesting hanging in the
tree it's starting it's starting everywhere people are on the streets and you can see that the
the police are ready for it if got to barricades all over the place and has definitely
enhanced security going on rightfully so i would say but i'm hoping that everything can be quite
calm tomorrow but probably it just doesn't take much and what's crazy about these protests and
these are happening still worldwide what's crazy about them is people going after big globalist companies
like Starbucks McDonald's from Coca-Cola and that kind of destruction does get attention for sure
so we'll have to see where it leads but we're just i guess the best thing we could do right now is just
keep our eyes on it and see what's coming strip comic strip comic strip comic strip comic strip
comic strip go you'll see us be come on in my body hello there hello how are you at the
I'm good man here is csb your eucor espondent Adam yes you obviously were born with a silver spoon in the
earth this is what so many people think no man i'm pretty lower middle class my friends so you don't
so i don't know if you know if you ever were bullied in your life are you kidding me in 1972
as an american moving to europe americans were universally hated for vietnam at the time
we were taking over jobs a Texas instruments was moving in 70s was a very very difficult time
and and america was severely understood we're talking about nixon you know we were evil people
i was yelled at i was shot at with paper darts and and berries from pbc piping i was called names
yeah i think i know what it's like to be bullied csb have you been but these days your opinion is
being bullied by russia who is using proxy here you're creating to bully you in our blame game
you can't is by cutting off gas supply whether more nobody can do anything to consume rations because
they have 30 year contracts with various countries so screw global warming i mean climate change
it is bullshit and that is of the issue of energy where is this fucking code fusion generator
or something and congratulations to you on becoming alone on our other yeah thank you you thank you very
much csb it was uh let's see if i can find this uh it was article and uh an associated youtube
video here we go saltwater burns dot com i've i've i've i remember looking at this probably a
year ago and it really trips me out every single time i watch it this is a guy who was um originally
looking for a cure for cancer guys a doctor so he has a little bit of a lab
and what his search led him to an accidental discovery is that by sending a certain frequency
onto saltwater plain saltwater right out of the sea or any other saltwater you know natural saltwater
source he can actually light and make the saltwater burn so i believe and from what i understand
from these videos somehow he's creating hydrogen from the water but not doing it through the typical
means of electrolysis by actually sticking electrodes into the water with a current running through
it but he's doing it externally with frequencies and he doesn't in this youtube video and i can't
say otherwise that it looks damaged it now of course the implication of being able to
you saltwater as a fuel source i mean that boggles the mind because you know once once it
heats something well then you can you can create a turbine you can go back to old fashion steam
engine you know there's a million different ways you can use it but wow burning saltwater i can
see people laughing about it in the in the chat room but it's true and you should watch these
youtube videos saltwater burns dot com is where you can see it it's it's extremely trippy there's a
couple other resources on that site it's been featured on sixty minutes popular science i've got
to catch up on what this guy is doing i guess the trick is to understand what frequency he's been
into this water and i mean that's getting very close to removing all the problems of the world
which of course means we're probably never here from the good doctor again because he'll be killed
because this one's way too good i mean i've seen the magnet engines and i like those a lot and
you know there's a lot of questions about how those operate but this looks really clean and
can you imagine if all you had to do was had some kind of box with you that you could just
set next to a glass of saltwater and that would be fuel and you could light that and you could
not mean that just imagine the things we can create if we have that type of power i gotta say
that just be spectacular so that's what i'd be looking for csb got to tell you i feel good
about being in the Londoner actually i really do and i feel very involved in the city and it's
good you know i'm kind of a new yorker although i really didn't live in new york city that long but
both Patricia and i feel were urbanites and we're here in southwest London so we're not not in
Chelsea which is just a little bit up the road because that's where your neighbors essentially are
just all rushons and you got to get in a car to go somewhere interesting and here we just walk
out and turn left and turn right and then your boom you're right in the middle of the action
and uh really am enjoying that i was going to start a new mission on the the source code i was going
to start up every show with where's all summer been ladden where is he because of course
with all this fighting in the gaza strip you'd expect him to be out there and say no i had this
got to stop we need to kill americans and kill all the westerners and we have to do away with
everybody and well so then they i guess they finally thought it was time they did something as well so
apparently there's some audio tape that came out you know how lame is that and it's no longer
top priority for our president elect to kill him that's what i found most interesting so not only
and i'm just gonna say it you know this is fabrication you know why don't we on one hand
lower the expectations very buddy yeah we don't have to go and kill the guy anymore he's incapacitated
and the other hand let's uh make sure that he still appears to be alive and i just can't believe he is
brock obama suggested last night removing us out and been ladden from the battlefield was no
longer essential in that america security goals could be achieved nearly by keeping alchita on the run
even though at the top of his list is obliterate alchita kill or capture been ladden so he's
already breaking his promises the top of the list my preference obviously would be to capture or kill
him obama said but if we have so tightened the news that he's in a cave somewhere and can't even
communicate with his operatives then we will meet our goal of protecting america excuse me
what the f are you talking about so okay so now we know he's in the cave and he can't communicate he
can just barely get out little MP3 file they're posted on the website and where is that file
there's never a link to it on these mainstream sites that you never hear it on the news uh oh
well they got another tape interview uh no tape was released and you never hear it
and it's never verified yeah by some pentagon official sure that's who we have verifies it
pisses me off liars just the lies it's just becoming too much let's see uh what else do we have
obama and uh Biden visited the supreme court because of course they'll have some say over the
justices there I call it casing the joint not a visit they're getting ready because the big
hijack is about to take place and I've also been watching these confirmation hearings
Timothy Geitner's fantastic uh this is who president elect obama would like to have in as I believe
treasury secretary let me just double check on that I thought it was treasury secretary
he's no stranger by the way to the position uh little problem there uh didn't pay as taxes
in 2006 two years he forgot to pay let me tell you something
when we started our company in the United States you know I've been filing taxes you don't
have to pay taxes in multiple countries you pay it in the country you work in and where you get paid
so I've been paying all kinds of taxes out of my butt all the time in the Netherlands and partially
in the UK for a good portion of the eight nine years so we start this company and my name shows
up somewhere the IRS came into our offices with their hands on their weapons okay hands on their guns
we want curried of course it wasn't even in the country and for this guy uh you'll get confirmed
didn't pay as taxes here's something else that happened yesterday this this is uh for those
even the United Kingdom you will you will really should have brick when you hear this so I still have
a rental property there's a couple more payments you know in this transition to the new home
and it's through foxtons foxtons is the real estate agent anyway they manage that property for the owner
and uh I read about a week and a half ago that foxtons wasn't financial trouble
and that's understandable because houses are not moving they still got the overhead so they're
firing people left and right there's all kinds of shit going on but they're in financial trouble
but when you send your your rent check you send it to them and they then uh take whatever
management fee and anything else that needs to be deducted and they send it off to the owner
the remainder of the balance so normally this is paid on the 29th of the month and uh there was
you know payment going out final payment on the 29th of January and it was transferred uh on the
14th and I just I just saw it by uh by accident really and I'm looking at him like that's strange
so I call him up and the first thing the guy said I know of course I'm a dick I should have recorded it
but the first thing the guy said was all of me uh let me talk to uh let me talk to some of
you right back and comes back as well yeah it looks like that happened by mistake um you know and
by the way my bank for this particular transaction is Barclays Bank it's important for the story
do you mind if you just consider that the payment and we will make sure no payment goes on
on the 29th and I said no that's unacceptable we have a contract it's a standing order is what
it's called so it's automatically transferred on the 29th of each month I said we have a legal
document I had to sign this it couldn't even do it over the internet I had to confirm with my signature
that this money can be transferred once a month from this account to that account it doesn't mean
on the 14th so you're breaking our agreement well yes hold on a second and guy comes back well
Mr. Curry we have two options one is uh you can call um you can call them you can call uh
Foxdons and have them transfer the money back to you because the alternative really will take seven to eight
weeks as we have to go through all these procedures and I said no you're misunderstanding something okay
I believe that something very fishy is going on is what I said and I know you're recording this
call because all of them are so listen very carefully I said Foxdons isn't deep financial trouble
do you think it's possible that the bank made a kind of a decision or a deal to help them out
by transferring some or maybe all of these standing orders two weeks in advance is that possible do you
think maybe you should get me a supervisor so get the supervisor go through the whole rap
and uh and I and I'm getting really annoyed you know the guys well we well we can't do this and you
know this is the unfortunate mistake I said look do you know who John Gages now so he's the editor
of the sun he's my next phone call with this exact same story call on a second Mr. Curry call
back we're going to credit your account in five minutes so I'm calm bullshit on Barkley's bank
and I will no longer do business with him because that's just just a complete outrage but they
would do something like that and it's fun to yell at bank managers hello fellow DSC chuckleheads
it's Tim Binder from the Century Media podcast are you a rocker who likes to bang your head
well if so check out the Century Media podcast that's right the Century Media podcast
where this month you can find new music from the likes of Napalm Dad
the haunted in this moment
all
and more check out the Sentry Media podcast over at iTunes and also at
media.
It's sentrymediapodcast.media.com, rock on atom and rock on chuckle heads.
All right, let's do a little check there.
How you guys doing on the Talkshoot conference, everyone alive and well?
Yep.
Okay.
Hey, have the Chelsea drugstore still there?
The Chelsea drugstore, you know, I'm looking for a dealer, but I haven't been looking
for that kind of drugstore.
You're stupid.
All right, topless dance bar right there in that chat.
Oh, hold on a second.
Let me write that down.
Hold on.
This is getting important.
How does it?
Chelsea drugstore.
Okay.
Yes.
Real son of a place.
Excellent.
Actually, I'm going to go see my buddy Michelle tonight.
Michelle Harper in Guilford at the, at the Lion's Dead, which is, yeah, that's
his, his pole dancing joint.
It was birthday yesterday, so I'm going to go over and stop by.
Which I love it because the lady Patricia says, oh, that's no, that's cool.
I'm a lot to do that, man.
That, I love that.
Quick note.
Parker, uh, Parker London sent me this and I see a Twitter tweet from Fargo.
That, uh, Zimbabwe has now released a $1 trillion note.
I had the $100 billion one, which I scanned and put on flicker a while back.
But now they have a $100 trillion note.
This is the direction that we, of course, are headed in.
And I'm, you know, I've been watching CNBC almost every single morning.
And you just, you know, they're, they're literally yelling at the government on, on this,
watch squat box in the morning.
They're so angry because already in the first, you know, two weeks.
The, the deficit is already in the hundreds of billions.
Bank of America, $138 billion of our money.
We're printing it.
The printing presses are in high gear.
It's just, it's out of control.
All right.
So we've got a number of people on, uh, who are dialed in.
Um, I know the sound is all messed up, but, you know, just to stay in the,
to stay in the habit of doing it.
Let's see if we can do, uh, this week's hit test.
All together.
What's that?
Are you able to hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you fun.
All right.
Awesome.
Okay.
That's groomsy, right?
All right.
Okay.
Guys.
Let's see if we can, uh, figure out what the songs are in today's hit test.
All right.
I've heard a rumor.
I know that one.
All right.
Anybody on the, talks you know?
Okay.
All right.
I've heard a rumor.
I know that one.
All right.
Anybody on the, talks you know?
I think I look at it.
Yeah.
Banana Rama.
Number two.
Oh, that's an easy one.
All right.
Talks you people?
It really hurt.
Yeah.
Breaking up the bad on my phone.
It's Duran Duran Reflex.
And number three.
Got it.
Yeah.
This is like,
John's given it away with that one, then.
Pride in the name of love.
And it's time for the answer.
Sorry.
And this is answer number one.
You may sing along.
But not a Rama.
It's my duty.
Seven.
Who's friends?
You never show.
I'll tell you what you want to know.
I love a girl.
They say you got a broken heart.
I'll let her roam her.
Yes.
I'll tell you what you want to know.
Number one.
Banana Rama.
I heard a rumor.
And this is number two.
Man.
You've got some fun this time.
But I've never been on the bad line.
You've never been on the bad line.
And we've made a way in the reflex.
Does.
Do.
Flat.
Flex.
The reflex.
Your answer.
Number two.
Oh.
The answer.
Number three.
Three.
Four.
You never come in the middle of love.
One man.
And the.
My love.
And.
That's number three.
Try it in the name of love.
You too.
And that concludes.
It has number one.
Fifty six.
Yeah.
So Adam.
Well.
You have to do this week.
Dude.
Six out of six.
Kind of me.
Nailed it.
Got to fix the audio on this talk shoot thing.
It's pissing me off.
I know people would have fun playing.
If only they could actually hear it.
Right.
The answer.
To this hit this.
And also the iTunes link.
So you can buy this right.
Featured on the hit test online.
To be found.
The hit test that mevio.com.
Thanks for playing Adam.
Thank you.
Everyone else.
Thanks for listening.
Next week.
I'll be back for another hit test.
So until then.
Have fun.
Take care.
And remember to try to think with your hearts.
Bye-bye.
Keep back.
Test that she will.com.
Y'all pull a dot com.
J-N-P-O-L-C-T-D-A-C-O-N.
I really got to figure something out.
Maybe I...
They actually, they do have a VoIP dialing, which is interesting.
So I got to put the other router on because I can't use my gizmo VoIP setup.
I've tried port forwarding everything.
They may be doing something nasty or their BT.
And I still don't have the version 20 megabit line in.
I don't think I can get the 50 megabit here.
Just this got to sound better.
It's got to make it better.
And I've got to figure out what this distortion is coming from.
Because I'm really doing everything by the book and on the meters.
And still is...
God knows how it's going to sound.
Once I play back the recording.
God, I hope it's not over much.
It sounds so bad.
Okay.
What do I got here?
I want to wrap it up pretty quickly.
Here's some very good and interesting data points.
Because you're not going to hear about this in mainstream news.
Well, actually, this is a mainstream article,
but I don't think people understand the significance of the shipping rates.
So when you ship something, of course these days,
just about everything is sent via standard size container.
And you ship it from typically China, of course.
There's a cost involves.
Well, freight rates for container ship from Asia to Europe have fallen to zero.
For the first time since records began,
underscoring the dramatic collapse in trades
since the world economy buckled in October.
And there's all kinds of experts in this article saying
that they've never witnessed this before.
Imagine that.
It's like, this is like Federal Express or DHL doing free shipping,
except for containers, for huge containers.
This really shows that there's some dire circumstances
and desperate situations going on.
Let me just check my email for a second.
I was, oh, man.
Oh, wow.
I was planning on that.
You know what? I'm going to do this right now.
I'm just planning on talking with Maggie from our office
and because she's going to the inauguration.
Now, Maggie is African-American and I don't want to say
exactly how old she is because that would be extremely rude.
But I sent her an email.
I said, you know, Maggie, you have such an amazing story,
which really starts with desegregation because,
okay, so I'm giving away part of her age.
I don't know, I'm just finding a number here for a second.
And, you know, even, I believe she's got like front row tickets
or something for the inauguration.
And even though I disagree with Obama and while the whole system
really, I thought she would have a very interesting story.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to,
I'm going to have to put the talk she was going to have to go on
and hold, I think.
I don't think, can I start a conference?
Can I add another call to this?
Probably not.
Damn.
Because I want you guys to hear it and maybe even chime in.
Oh, if only I had a,
okay, I got to work on that.
Hold on, let me see if I can get a hold of Maggie.
Let me, uh, get her number here.
Uh, tell you what, I'm going to play a song and then I'll get her on the phone.
And we'll, uh, we'll finish the show with her.
It really, I think, I think you'll enjoy it.
It should be interesting.
By the way, the song that I'm going to play for you is such a beautiful tune.
It's the new one from Skinny.
You know, the guys from Holland.
But this is holiday.
But this is where we saved our money for all year.
So this is the sun.
This is a good, good life.
This is where everybody wants to be without their wives.
This is where I won't be flying.
I'll be on the moon on the moon.
Hallelujah.
I really got it made.
I got two cars on the driveway ready to take me anywhere.
Glory, glory.
Who wrote a beautiful place?
All the water and the mountains.
I want the people look the same.
This is where I won't be flying too.
My heart beats on the moon.
On the moon.
You're a little bit submitted.
My heart feels like you're drunk.
I'm ready to leave this planet.
If I can find you here.
I look done every corner.
Every leaf I turn around.
Stop my engines.
I'm gonna leave this town.
I've been west.
I've been used.
I travel everywhere to find my news.
But the only place I found in
wasn't my news.
I woke up at the sun.
I lost everything before I reached the moon.
Now I'm still trying.
Getting over you.
And I know where I'll be flying too.
I go anywhere.
You're a little bit too.
My heart beats on the moon.
On the moon.
16 needs a minute.
Easy like this summer sun.
On the moon.
I heart beats on the moon.
As the title, my heart beats on the moon.
It's skinny.
You know, from Mod Jones,
you can find all this shite.
It's skinny.
I know what a beautiful, beautiful song.
And I got to hold a Maggie's
and I'm going to see if I can call her.
I believe that it'll put the
a talk shoot client on hold.
But at least to me.
Morning.
Hey, Maggie.
Good morning.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
We're already recording.
And I really appreciate you coming on the show.
Because I really just want to talk with you for five or ten minutes.
Because you have such an extraordinary story.
And I really appreciate taking the time.
Because you're actually your off today, right?
You're getting ready for your big trip.
Yes.
I am very much so.
So just to put into context,
Maggie is executive assistant to three of the biggest
egos in the world.
To myself.
To Ron Bloom and our CEO Jeff Carpe.
Is anyone else your executive assistant for Maggie?
Or did I summon up there?
Anybody that needs any assistant
from always willing to lend a hand?
So I've been really, I've been very considerate.
And I haven't mentioned your age,
although to put it in context,
you're a little bit older than I am.
Just a tad.
African American.
And would you born in the South Maggie?
No, born and raised in San Francisco, California.
Wow.
Somehow I thought you were from the South San Francisco.
Okay.
Would you mind my parents are from the South?
Right.
Okay.
That was it.
Now, let me just frame this up.
Maggie is a fantastic debater.
We love going at each other,
particularly when it comes to politics and policy.
And you got another line coming in?
No, that's okay.
All right.
If you got to pick it up, no problem.
No, that's okay.
They'll call me back.
All right.
We go back and forth.
But it's all in good fun.
And we get our emotions out.
And we yell on the screen.
But we enjoy that.
Right, Maggie?
You would have to say that.
Yes, we do.
Yeah.
Now, I enjoy it.
You're smart.
You're bright.
You're articulate.
It's always good.
But of course, I don't support.
Or I didn't support our President regardless.
Give him a fair shot.
I was, of course, an ardent, ardently against Obama.
And you are one of the largest, it was just most magnificent supporters of Obama.
I've ever met.
And I just wanted to understand a little bit about the story from your perspective.
Being African-American.
Being a little bit older than I am.
You literally witnessed desegregation.
Yes.
Can you tell me, and I don't know if you can put it into words.
But what has taken place now and what has about to happen?
Can you even describe how that feels for you?
Well, for me, it's just so phenomenal.
It's, and for most, I'm not going to say it only African-Americans.
But all people of color who are witnessed over the years,
the struggle, the hardship, the, I guess, just the overall,
of us becoming equal, it's so to speak.
In terms of Martin Luther King's, I mean, just that whole generation of civil rights leaders
and movements that we're going on.
And therefore quite a few before Martin Luther King came along quite a few leaders
that sort of paid the way in the 20s and the 30s.
But it became really, really important when Martin Luther King started fighting for the cause,
because it was televised.
It was on the radio.
You could see it.
You could hear it.
You could feel it.
Before the North and the South's were a little separated, we knew there was Jim Crow
in the South going on.
And most people who had migrated, migrated from the South, like my parents,
that came here in the late 30s, early 40s, to get away from that situation.
And just to see it unravel and unfold after 45 or 50 years, just to say, okay,
now that we have made it, because we've always been here, our contributions
to the overall history of this country have been phenomenal.
And you only hear about it during one month of year, and that's February.
Right.
Or when Chris Rock has a new DVD out.
Exactly.
I'll hear you going to get John and says something really ugly about it.
What's going on in the world?
I guess.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
It's just the long, hard struggle at him.
And for this particular time in history, for this to happen, for this man of African and American
descent, to just hold for overwhelmingly went an election in this country.
I mean, it's beyond imagination.
I can understand that.
Was it the same feeling?
Because what you said there was really important Martin Luther King, because it was on television,
it was on the radio.
So here, you know, that was a huge step.
Is it the same type of feeling, do you think, with Obama now, where he is?
Oh, it is even more so.
You're talking about the dream.
Martin Luther King was the dreamer.
The dream has unfolded.
Barack Obama, the 44th president of the United States of America, a man of color.
Did you ever think that would happen at it?
Well, you know, I grew up in Amsterdam, Maggie.
You know, so for me, it's, I don't see color really that way.
Or men or women, you know, because leaders in Europe,
have been many women, Margaret Thatcher.
Right now, Angela Merkel, you know, and no one ever, although the jury's out of
she's actually a woman.
But it's.
Because so that's a different, yeah, I would say that's, that's just a different environment.
But you and I have spoken many times about racism, and you feel the racism is still rampant in the United States.
It's still there.
It's, you know, and I, I don't want to say that, I don't, let me put it this way.
There is something awful and hidden in the United States.
Still, even though this man has been elected, even though he is a man of color,
there is underlying, there's still underlying racism here in the United States.
It's just, it's kind of, you know, under the radar,
but there are still things that happen here, and you know that it's because of racism.
You know, albeit, we always say, no, no, that's not, that's not going on in the United.
But there are still parts of the United States where it's loud, and it's boisterous, and it's ugly.
And then their parts, our places in the United States where it's just that, you know, that little underlying thing going.
Right. Well, and there's also idiots everywhere, but I'll tell you, Maggie,
you know, I've lived in many different countries, and I was just talking about this the other day with my wife,
that I have never witnessed so much racism as in the United Kingdom to be, to be really honest with you.
And it's, you know, and it here, it's like right now, the, you know, I don't know if you heard this,
that Prince William, he had some videotape when he was with his army buddies from two years ago,
and it got released to the papers, and in that tape, he says, oh, there's that packie guy over there.
Oh, that, that's my buddy, the rag head, you know, kind of the way the way we talk, right, you know, kind of the way buddies talk,
and it's not such a big deal, because everything within context can be racist or not.
But what's funny is all these politicians are on television saying, well, this is so wrong,
and it's right that he apologized, blah, blah, blah, and meanwhile, I'll say,
how the amount of times I've heard from an Englishman, you know, like just a guy driving a cab saying,
I guess what color they were, and like, I'm shocked, I'm like, what did you just say?
You just say someone's action based upon their color.
Well, it's true, and like, oh, man, you know, so just so you know, Maggie, we could be doing a lot worse,
the United States.
We know, but it's, it's, it's, and see, you were offended.
So imagine.
Yeah.
The person that, that that remark is being, of course, thrown at, of course.
It's like, oh, just stabbed you in heart.
Yeah.
And these are the kinds of things that we were hoping with change here in this country.
You know, little by little, the barriers are breaking down, but it's still there.
And see, this is the 20th century.
We're supposed to be enlightened.
We're supposed to be above and beyond all of this.
Did it, that you rhetoric.
But it's still, in some places, it's still there.
And then it's like, you talk, you still, if you talk to most people,
then the city, San Francisco, which is the most diverse city, I think, in this country,
other than New York.
And there are still people who are saying, oh, wow.
The black man, Juan, do you?
Yeah.
And I'm like, yeah, sure, dude.
I love a feisty black woman, Maggie.
You know that.
Yeah.
I'm proud of who I am.
Again, you know, it comes from a long history of players in my family.
People who were involved, my dad, my grandparents.
It was a group during an after World War I.
My both grandfathers fought in World War I and they were both seven years.
And when they came home from World War I, they decided that they had to form a group
and they were called the Beaconies.
You know, they were churchgoers.
That's right.
And they had to use this organization.
Fight off the racist, the racism in the South.
After they had fought in World War I.
But then you know, the story, World War I, World War II.
Disegregation in the Army, all kinds of stuff.
But you know, here we are.
We still have people, young men and women of color, who are fighting wars.
And that are, and when they come home, they are still being treated.
Like nonsense.
Yes, yes.
In fact, 25% of San Francisco's homeless are veterans, which is just disgusting.
Yes, they are.
Absolutely disgusting.
That hurts me to that hurts me to the core.
Every time I see one on the corner, you have to sign saying, I'm a be let.
Now I'm back.
I have to stop.
Take out my wallet and say, you know, this is what I have.
And you can have it because you made a great sacrifice for us.
Yeah.
Now I'm, I'm for, you know, my background, my family.
So yeah, I'm very much the same way.
Maggie, I just like to get into the inauguration because you are not only going to DC,
you're going to be front row and center.
How did you manage that?
How did that come about?
Well, what happened was my girlfriend, her name is Deborah McIntyre.
She belongs to, she's a constituent of Alameda County.
So her congressman, George Miller, put on a lottery.
So he, you know, 34 tickets into the ring.
He said, if you want to try for these inauguration tickets,
you'll have to go online, sign up, get out of Yada.
Okay, I think there was something like 2,000 people that went online
to sign up and try when these tickets, a lot of tickets.
So she said, you know what, Maggie, I'm just going to do it for the hell of it.
I said, okay, you know, you know, we're hurt.
And they called her a couple of weeks later and told her that she could
want two of the tickets.
So she called me and she said, you will not believe this just a woman.
I said, what's up?
She said, I want two lottery tickets.
And I said, oh my God, that you like.
She said, no, I'm not Maggie.
She said, we are in Washington DC.
I said, yes, we are.
So we have been planning ever since we tried to get really cheap airfares.
We couldn't do that.
We tried to get a whole scale.
We finally had to go through a broker to get a whole scale.
Oh wow.
Yeah, we would do it.
You know, I could have gotten you.
I could have gotten you.
I could have gotten you a really cheap ticket.
At least to the Hudson, maybe not to the airport.
But I could have gotten most of the way.
I would have had to pick the answer.
Well, Maggie, that couldn't have happened to a more deserving and nicer person.
Yeah.
And you know, we will, I'm coming out the end of the month.
And of course, undoubtedly, I'll have plenty to say about the policies of the president.
But a true American tradition, we support our president no matter who you voted for.
And we give him the benefit of the doubt.
And I am going to uphold that tradition.
But you know that I'm pretty skeptical that he is actually lying to you.
No, you're skeptical, but that's all right.
You're a good guy anyway.
But you don't think keep this in mind.
There are people, you know, there were people who were saying, yeah, no experience or experience.
I don't any American president in the history of this country had any experience when they went into the office.
And one of our greatest is that if we are, and I mean, even Lincoln did not have the experience that he needed.
As these two men, Abraham Lincoln and Franklin Delano wrote to those words, two of the greatest presidents that we've ever had in this country.
And we're going to add a rock Obama's name to that list because he's going to make a change here.
Because we all want that change.
And you have your country behind you saying, you know, rock, Obama.
We are with you 100% we know it's going to.
It's not going to be easy.
It's going to be a lot hard road to tell.
But we're going to be with you.
No matter what happens.
Well, Maggie, I'm right there with you.
And I, you know, well, I totally agree that if the country can all get together and say, hey, we're in it.
We want to do something good.
We want to make this this change happen.
You know, that type, the, the, the public is always much greater than any of the leaders out there or any force.
So that, that would be truly amazing.
But the, the also have to have the courage to stand up when, when was wrong is wrong.
So we'll see how that goes in the future.
But again, Maggie, I hope you have a great time.
Please take lots of pictures.
And don't worry.
I am going to, I am going to be the cleanest pictures.
You know, I'm going to be in everybody's face.
Well, and finally, what are you going to be wearing, Maggie? Come on.
What are you putting on?
Oh, I have, I have already packed six of the most fabulous ball gowns that I have.
I don't you have like some hot little little number.
You got something sexy.
I have some hot, I have some, I have some passion for the behind.
Okay, I can say, I have some here, but I've got some passion for them.
I have pulled out some vintage dresses that I haven't worn in years.
I'm fabulous ball gowns.
Cocktail dresses just, you know, my husband told me, do you know what?
He said, yes, she's going to be an inaugurationer.
You're just going to party though.
Yes, and yes, that would be the answer.
I don't know if I'm like that.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
Maggie, thank you so much for taking time. Have a great time.
I can understand this is just going to be so exhilarating.
And we'll talk to you.
I'll talk to you when I get out to San Francisco in a couple weeks.
Okay, and I'm hoping to just be able to stand after the stamina.
You know, that a personal no dose.
So I think I'm going to be able to hang.
I'm sure you'll have no problem whatsoever.
I've seen you hang with the best of them.
All right, man.
Yeah. Thanks a lot. Bye-bye now.
Bye-bye now.
Maggie Bishop, everybody, from Niveo.
And this is a little poll anchor to wrap it up.
Good thing I guess.
Because one could say, she's got the eye of the tire.
Rising up.
Back on the street.
Did but time took chances.
I went the distance now and back on my feet.
Just a man with the will to survive.
And many times, it happened too fast.
You changed your passion for the glory.
Don't lose your grip.
On dreams of the past, you got to fight.
To keep them alive.
Gifts the eye of a tiger.
Dream out of fight.
Rising up.
To challenge a rival.
The last notes of I ever stalked spring in the night.
Watching us all of the eye.
Of the title.
The eyes of my heart.
Place the face out in the night.
Hangin' tough, stayin' hungry.
sterically, on still we take him to the street.
We kill with the skill to survive.
Yes, this is the eye of the tiger.
The climate of white rising up to challenge a rival
And it's the last known survival stops in the night
Watching us all in the eye
The title
Rising up straight to the top, I got the guts, got the glory, I went to Disney's not gonna stop, just a man with a will to survive.
Hey guys, it's the eye of the tiger, it's the premon of fight, rising up to challenge a rival.
It's the last known survival, stopping prey in the night, watching us all in the eye.
And thanks to Maggie Bishop from the video for giving me her perspective on life and
I was beautiful, it was a beautiful story.
Of course, I could have shit all over her, but I'll do that at the end of the week.
At the end of the month, I go out and we'll go yell and scream to each other, which that one I also want to record.
And I know she'll do it too, but this is really what a great feeling she must have.
So I didn't want to harsh her mellow, I'm sure you understand.
And I'm sorry everybody on TalkShoot, there was absolutely no way I could figure out how to add that call into the TalkShoot
and a Skype puts it on a hold and all this crap going on.
So I have to work on that, I have to fix that.
I got some time coming up pretty soon, so I'll be able to.
All right, that's it for 817, the Fubar Friday edition ran a little bit longer than I expected to.
Our in 20 minutes.
For those of you who are in the United Kingdom, but look for demonstrations in your local time zone to stop this heinous war taking place in the Gaza strip.
Tomorrow at Trafalgar Square is where people will be meeting for the London protests and I'll definitely be a part of that with the kids.
And in closing besides the fact that you have to be very, very careful of your freedom while you still have it and use it wisely.
And I do want you to live your life with passion, but this new one I think is really summon it up for me.
Ask not what you can do for your country.
Ask what your government is doing to you.
Another fine, medial presentation.
Stick it in your ear.