Delta Sierra Charlie, 8-1-4.
$60 million worth of airplanes wrapped by aspirin.
The next generation brings you content in my ears.
We don't need no digging trees in.
I'd like to think I'm flying into the heat jar.
Fantastic.
Here's Adam Curry.
Hey, hello to my little friend.
I'm a carry. I'm editing source code.
You're such an inspiration from the weather.
I will never ever choose to be.
You're so mad.
They always remain a show.
You're how you say.
The cows abandon you.
I know you're the only one you're crazy.
I'm sorry.
I'm a human.
You're so mad.
We're just enc bamboo carries for you.
For you think we're going to run away.
You don't need no dig of your laughter.
I have a mind to ask you where I'm from.
I польз
I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again
I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again,
I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again, I'm going to do it again
You'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me
You'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it off me, you'll take it
course code episode 814 coming to you from the brand new curry terrace in southwest London
in the United Kingdom, which of course is the eastern part of Gitmo Nation, hey everybody,
how you doing first show coming from the, well second show really because no agenda started
off the new set up the new studio, which suck tremendous donkey balls, everything
got screwed up, so I had a really good long think about it and I rewired everything,
I was just actually looking at the chat on the phone bridge. Now if you don't know how to
call in, we have a special conference room where you can participate in the show later on,
you can find all the information at curry.com. There's a link on the right hand side at
curry.com, which says DSC live info, click on that, it'll tell you how to call it, to talk
show, which I do you need and what I was seeing in the chat is that people were saying
that they could hear my voice fine, but the minute the music kicked in, it sounded really
static. He not quite sure what's going on there. Well, I just have to have to mess around
with it. Actually, it was, you know, before I get to all that, let me tell you, it's been
a pretty, pretty crazy week. Hold on a second. Actually, a little bit over a week now.
Let's see, we had the best of the Charlie 2008 that was Ray, of course, put that together.
Actually, I got a voice comment about that. I'd like to play for you.
Amen. It's been a pretty one night or right now. It's about I am. But, you know, I'm
going to stick with the DSC. And, you know, they ran on the Charlie tribute and as a year,
awesome awesome stuff. They're ready. Very cool. One thing I have to say is, you got to
at least one more playing trip on the Charlie. Maybe more. I'd like more, but at least one more
this year, boss. I just, as I was awesome. A lot of great memories. Hey, you know, if you're
right, man, about the 2009's going to be a proven round. So, I can see how it goes, but until
then, give them more evidence. But hey, I'm open. Give me what you've got right here. Love
you get it. Hope you'll win. Yeah, man. And here's to 2009. Thanks.
Yo, it's going to be certainly a very interesting year. But let me go back to last year first,
just to collect my thoughts. So, we had that ray on the Charlie, the best of the source code
2008, which I loved listening to. I listened to it in two parts, partially, while packing up
the old studio at the old house. And, of course, unpacking in the new studio. The move,
I'd have to say, was we underestimated it severely. Now, this was not just a regular move.
It was a complete reboot of our lives. We like to do this from time to time. Last time was almost
five years ago. And that wasn't really a reboot because we dragged a whole bunch of stuff with
us, which you put into storage. I essentially was paying for a second house for our stuff, which
we never looked at. Never had no idea was in there. We went through all that clean that out. I mean,
we discarded so much stuff, particularly paperwork. So, I've got rid of all of that.
And then we moved, and you know, the stuff that was in the old house in the, in the manner,
we got rid of a lot of that as well. Literally gave it away. You can't even sell this stuff anymore.
No one wants furniture, even antiques. People just aren't interested. They're rather by a flat
pack from IKEA. That's the way to go. And so, what was it? The 29th, they packed everything up,
the 30th was the first shipment that went up to London from Gilford. And it kind of didn't
stop from there. It was literally nonstop. Now, this place is four stories. So, and we have the
top floor designated as, okay, that's where we're going to store all the stuff that once again,
we have no place to put. Or, you know, the Christmas tree ornaments, that kind of stuff. And my
boxes of wires, boy, I've discarded a lot of crap, and still have boxes of wires left over. And
power supplies and cables and ethernet and USB for how about instruction manuals. Anyway,
you have no idea how much crap you'd you wind up gathering and schlepping around with you.
So, that's kind of done with. Then, you know, I still had to do mevio today. I'd taken a couple
days off and I thought, ah, you know, I'll just take two days off, because that is actually quite a
bit of work of, of whittled it down to anywhere between three and five hours a day of work,
but getting faster. I learned an enormous amount. I've got a
a Mac xenon quad hoopla machine here now. And I couldn't figure out why it wasn't going very fast.
It's like, why is it? There's the rendering going so slowly. It turns out that I had thought I
dragged a, an as a folder full of assets over onto the over onto the new edit machine,
but it actually created an alias. So, the reason why it was taking so long to to do stuff and
render it because it was pulling this data from my laptop through the Wi-Fi hub. Yeah, no wonder it
was taken hours. Took a little while for me to figure that one out to find out exactly what was
wrong there. And then I got a, like, a little bit of the flu. And I once, I don't know, flu is really
the right word. It was definitely a stomach bug. Let's call it that. But just for a day,
had a little, had a significant fever, I'll say, for about 24 hours and kind of started to come
out of that funk yesterday. And today is a day where as far as I know, we have no meetings,
normally we have meetings scheduled around 5 o'clock, which is 9 a.m. San Francisco time. So,
perfect timing to roll out to a source code. And we got people on the phone brood. Let me just,
let me see. Who's this? Hello, Jamie. Hey, Jamie, how are you? I'm good. How are you? Excellent.
Now, I see that you're in the chat room there and you're kind of talking away with people.
You say it sounds fuzzy. slightly. And it was, um, during the song, it became almost complete
static where it was sort of coming in and out. And, but mostly all static. But once you started talking
and then when you played the audio comment, everything, you know, mostly sounds fine.
Is it loud enough? Maybe maybe I'm over modulating it or something. Is it, is it,
is the sound that's coming through the phone loud? Volume was fine for me. I actually turned the
volume down on my phone when you were playing the audio comment. Okay, so I'm going to turn all
that stuff down a little bit. Maybe that's what's going on there. It's, you know what? I installed
the new version of Skype and it has some kind of automatic gain control in there, which I can't
seem to find where to turn it off. So maybe that's it. Jamie, where are you calling from, actually?
I'm in Bergen County, New Jersey. Oh, near my old, uh, my old stomping grounds.
Yes, I live in East Rutherford. I work in Chicago. And have you been listening to the show for a while?
Two years? Hmm. I got to tell you, uh, you are, I believe the first woman to call in in,
ever since we, in fact, I don't know if I have any female listeners anymore. You may be yet, Jamie.
Oh, I'm listening.
Here's her out there. Anything in particular you want to talk about today, because I'm kind of going to
keep it a bit of an, uh, you know, open topic show since there's so much. I mean, I, I can't even start
to go back, uh, into last week, all the things that have happened, all the, all the news that
is taking place. Anything in particular caught your eye? Um, well, just from the world of, at large,
anything you want, Jamie? Well, actually, um, something happened today that I thought was spectacular.
Actually, it was last night, um, on Twitter, I follow at Armano, ARMA, ARMA, ARMA, N-O.
And he actually, he and his wife have taken in a family, it's a woman and her three children.
She left her husband, um, because it was an abusive situation. And he posted a PayPal link
and in less than 24 hours, it's up to almost $12,000, has been raised. And, um, and this is
decided to see how, you know, the power of this. And this is to get them back on their feet and
uh, get them going again. Right. They're trying to, you know, locate, um, an apartment for them, so they
can, you know, move into the wrong place. So I'm, I'm so touched by the whole thing. I was happy
to donate. And I think a lot of other people are as well. Excellent. Give me the, uh, the Twitter,
name again to follow. So if people can write that down, uh, it's Armano, ARMA, N-O, ARMA, N-O.
Armano at Twitter. So just go follow Armano and, um, and contribute, I say. That, that is, uh,
that is a pretty good gesture. We're going to be helping each other a lot more in the future.
That's for sure. All right, Jamie, you're going to hang out for a bit? Yeah, it's a for you. Excellent.
Thanks.
When they're tired, it goes, you know, it's got to be.
You're made and grown.
Yeah.
When you're back, I go. I fly down to my square floor. I want to strike all the big red
words. I'm a little black boy.
Don't you just want to be? Don't wear no shots in shoes.
With nothing good to believe, all the time you know.
I'm going to take it myself for whole. I'm going to lay down in it till I satisfying my show.
Oh, let the world pass by me.
No, I should push it full, shake it finally.
And if you don't come in, all's the ball, I say, no.
When back, I'll return to my square floor. I guess I'll take my hands.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, some kind of one of those musicians who were among them,
now it's having problems with safari and what I was thinking of doing is I have
two hit tests still left over from actually have the new years hit test and I have a new
one that young sent me I'm basically two behind and I was thinking if people could actually
hear it in the in on the conference bridge then it would be very cool to have everyone
participate and actually play along with the hit test and now of course I'm having troubles
even downloading it so let me see if that fixed the problem ah yes there we go
um let me see uh why don't I uh unmute everybody who's called in here for a second
hold on is that uh everybody okay so you're uh you're unmuted we have a Spudboy Michael
Dell and uh Jamie is probably still on yeah how about Spudboy and Michael Dell you're right
it's the question and I am the real Michael Dell that's not the answer to that
oh man you're you're calling on Skype I just I got to put you back on mute it's so horrible
by the way if you want to listen to the show you should you probably not the best
thing to listen to it um through the through the talk show system talk show system um that's
basically a Skype out that I'm doing into talk show so that's always going to sound pretty
crap um so it it's better to uh to listen to the stream if possible now this is going
to be interesting I'm actually I'm going to do this hit test those of you on the phone
and again everyone who uh everyone who's dialed in now is uh unmuted hold on a second
let's make sure I got everybody uh so if you know the answer uh give it a shot
point yeah yeah thank you so hit test number 153 and it's the new year's edition so here
we go with intro number one if anyone on the phone call know that no number two I'm too
for two on this one no I know this one what is it Jamie oh no no doesn't you got to say
it and number three oh I know this one that's uh you two New Year's Day that was
really forward the other ones uh and it's time for the answers and this is answer number one
may be it's much too early oh Mansabi on
I'll ask you just to see what are you doing in New Year.
New Year's Eve.
Tell me.
Oh, romantic.
What the hell was it, young?
You're doing New Year's Eve in the version by Gladys Knight and the Princess Answer number one.
Alright, then.
And this is Answer number two.
No more champagne and the morning seems so...
Oh, that's my wife.
Is that not?
Yes, that is.
Sounds like her.
Not my wife.
If we turn all the time.
Happy New Year, Eve!
Okay.
This is Answer number three.
One, this is You're too.
One is right on New Year's Eve.
We'll be with you back in the morning.
Oh, you're here, babe.
And some number three.
You two, New Year's Day.
And that concludes it.
It's number one, five, three.
Yeah.
So Adam?
How did you do this week?
Well, collectively, we all pretty much suck.
Yeah, I got New Year's Day.
And Jamie thought she knew number two when of course that was ever.
So better luck on the next one.
It is concludes.
The New Year's edition of the hit-est.
Like always, the answer's end, of course.
The iTunes links.
So you can buy the tracks featured on the hit-est online.
Or to be found at hit-est.mevio.com.
Adam, thanks for playing.
Thank you, young.
Everyone else.
Thank you for listening.
Next week, I hope to be back for not a hit-est.
So until then, have fun.
Take care.
Think with your hearts.
And happy New Year, everybody.
Bye-bye.
I was just looking through a couple of my notes while young was wrapping it up there.
And with all this stuff going on in Gaza right now, which man, it's unbelievable the way the mainstream coverage is being portrayed.
At least when I'm seeing here on the BBC and the United Kingdom, here's a couple things I've noticed.
And it leads into this article, which is from Middle East Online.
Of course, everything's sourced from the source code drop.au slash daily source code.
So first of all, what is interesting at least to note is that all the footage is primarily of horrific images.
And they always set it up by saying, some of our viewers may be disturbed by what you're about to see.
Now, God forbid we show a nipple, a breast, or a dick on television.
No, or people having sex, doing something good and fun and good for you.
No, no, no, no, of course not.
No, we'll just disclaim the murder and mayhem that's going on.
Absolutely horrific images that we're getting from from Gaza.
And then they'll cut back to the guy standing on the hill outside the perimeter and you see the Israeli tanks going in.
And from time to time, you'll see one of those bottle rockets that Hamas apparently is building themselves, shoot up.
But you never see any of the destruction of the Hamas rockets. I haven't seen it.
I'm sure it's there. And I know that three or four may be more civilians in Israel have been killed by these rockets.
But they never show it, which is just interesting to note, or they'll show like a hole in the ground.
And then you see this, I saw a rocket the other day literally, you could see the weld along the fins.
It was a completely home-built, but they're just not showing that, which is interesting to note.
They then always show the Israeli soldiers being buried.
You know, it's where they show the ceremony.
What you also don't see is the protests that are taking place.
There were 12,000 people the other day at the Israeli embassy here in London.
And they were getting pretty rough with the police.
And now the new thing, which is, I guess it's a worldwide meme, is the shoe throwing, which of course, already was an insult worldwide in Islamic culture.
But now it's being pretty much taken over by all these protesters.
And they're throwing their shoes at the Israeli embassy.
And you don't see any of that. You don't see, as I have not seen a single bit of footage.
I saw something online on a newspaper website. I mean, people are reporting on it, but the majority of these reports are exactly what I'm telling you is being shown.
You see huge destruction in Gaza.
And then this prompt is usually an interview with an Israeli official who says,
Well, we don't care. Look, if they want to sit in UN school buildings and use that as a shield, we don't care.
And I understand where everybody's coming from in this one, honestly.
But there's something very, very emissed with the information about it that we're getting.
It just, it doesn't add up.
And under all of the, you almost got to think, and this is of warning,
oh, man, do have a little warning. Maybe I should do a warning sound here. Maybe I should do this more often. Here we go.
Conspiracy alert, conspiracy alert, conspiracy alert.
Maybe this thing is being escalated at this very moment for specific reason of timing.
Now, we know that we're still a few weeks away from the inauguration of our new president Obama,
who I got to talk about that press conference he did yesterday.
If you haven't seen that, you should definitely check it out on the drop,
because there's some things that are kind of weird, even Patricia noticed some stuff.
But anyway, I just got to wonder that this is to distract attention perhaps away from something else,
or maybe, and again, it's just conspiracy thinking on my part.
Maybe just to show us that some people have had much worse. Maybe that's it.
But whatever it is, it's definitely a combination of the media,
selling us a particular angle, a particular story, making us feel a certain way,
and it is grabbing the majority of all of the headlines.
Now, here is the final thing I want to say that I find interesting in all of this,
where is Osama bin Laden? Where is Osama bin Laden?
I mean, with what he, of course, would consider to be atrocities,
anyone who loves life and human beings sees that this is atrocities on all sides of the conflict.
Why is he not out there screaming and yelling? Why is it the so-called al-Qaeda deputy
who has to come out and say, we're going to get you for this?
Where is Osama bin Laden? The only thing I can think is that he's probably dead.
We'll hit the phones in a second if you want to talk about this situation,
and guys, I'd love to hear your opinion. This is the source code, 814,
with some good advice from the chili peppers. Certainly in these days,
from this information, rules the airways.
Throw away your television, time to make this clean decision,
last awaits for its collision now.
It's a repeat of a story told.
It's a repeat and it's getting old.
It's a repeat with fatigue, just lay the plate for its contagious
for the plug and take the stages. Throw away your television now.
Throw away your television, take the loose off your ambition,
return, return, return, return, return.
It's a repeat and it's getting old.
Throw away your television, take the loose off your ambition,
return, return, return, return, return.
It's a repeat and it's getting old.
It's a repeat and it's a repeat and it's getting old.
it's a repeat hell yeah actually while that was playing I remember there was a fantastic
video on on drop dot IO slash daily source code and this isn't video yet who knows one day
I might put all that together as well but baby steps folks baby steps this is the title of it
a girl with balls blocks Israeli soldiers and even the audio is really compelling this is
which sounds like a western most like American young woman who was literally standing
opposite Israeli soldiers who are shooting at at children and she just stands there and well have
a listen for yourself that this is absolutely outrageous they're standing behind barbed wire
so by the way the reason why you're hearing a voice over and a foreign language is because
you won't see this stuff on television in in gitmonation all right so these kids are all standing
around and then these Israeli soldiers start shooting at them I don't know what they're shooting
probably the low velocity bullets or maybe rubber bullets it seems like they're making a lot of dust
but it doesn't matter
okay so now the kids are throwing stones from across the road
now they gotta get to this girl okay yeah it looks like they're rubber bullets still
I should have killed this up earlier now it's kind of confusing if you don't
let's get to that piece come on where is she here here it is this is amazing
all right she's walked right up to them right up to them she's standing in front of a
pointed rifle one polystyl engineer came back I could be don't you understand that
that what? If you're sorry back that was just a Whole bag
whole bag she serves Who hiding human use they're going to die
This is amazing.
She's standing right in front of them and they're trying to shoot these kids.
She's just standing there.
She's pointing his rifle right at her.
She's putting her hands up.
She stands there.
She's just standing there.
This is amazing.
And now the Israeli soldier is taking aim.
You got to take a look at that.
I don't know if that comes across at all on the stream.
Probably not.
But just outrageous.
And what courage?
So meanwhile our president elect says he's deeply concerned.
Deeply concerned about the loss of life.
Not quite the message of change I was looking to hear from my new president.
And we're hearing similar noises from our current president, which is just so completely disappointing.
Chris from Washington.
Yeah.
Hey Chris, how are you doing, man?
I see in the chat room.
You're talking away.
You've got an opinion here on what's going on in Gaza.
I do want to say, hey, I'm glad I could finally be awake on time.
Jesus is too early in the morning here.
Yeah.
On the other work.
No, I just think they were not seeing the whole truth as usual.
Because you see I'm seeing in their five miles away.
Just watching, you're not talking to people in Gaza.
They're not seeing if they're getting aid.
They're not seeing if they're getting food.
So you know, as usual, you're seeing what they, you know,
and what it's to see.
Absolutely.
And what everybody needs to do is go to alternative news sources.
And I, of course, would recommend drop.io slash daily source code.
Because, you know, when you see video like this, it's a embedded YouTube video.
I mean, it's, it's a lot easier to bring some things into context as to what's actually happening where
the mainstream press is not able to gain access to.
Oh, yeah.
If you're just a little driver or Twitter, you know, if you're going to get like the real news,
you're going to get people's home video accounts of the posting kind of letter.
Families know they're okay.
You know, so you're going to actually get some, some real on the ground step.
Exactly.
All right.
Chris and Washington stay on the line.
Woody 426 asked me if I know a British corporation named Wollsley.
What would that be about Woody 426?
Uh, don't settle county throughout Europe and America and county.
Oh, man.
You know, I, I, I wish I could hear you, but the Skype connection is just just degraded to poorly.
So, uh, type it into the chat and I'll see if, uh, see if I can answer it for you that way.
Here we go.
Comic strip.
It's time for New Year's Message from my very own CSB.
Hello.
Here is CSB, you correspondents.
So every six months, new EU country takes over EU presidency.
And in 2009, it will be Czech Republic in first half and then Abba.
I mean, it's with it.
Maybe laughs with it.
Okay.
Not many people know that many beers, including Budweiser and Pilsner, uh, originated in Czech Republic.
And generally, I had 100% agree with position of Czechs on everything.
So my message to EU is shut the dark up and listen to Czechs.
You know, I, I really wish I understood what he was talking about.
It was something about beer.
That's for sure.
So, um, this was kind of interesting.
A press conference called by the office of the president elect non-existent office.
Doesn't exist.
Made up.
But it's, uh, our future president Barack Obama sitting there with,
I recognize Roman Manuel who throughout the entire press conference is kind of like nodding
at people, uh, apparently in the audience and smiling and acknowledging whatever they're saying to them.
And some dude right next to him, uh, it's probably, uh, what's his name, Axel something.
He was just sitting there where the really unhappy frown the whole time doesn't say anything.
And then some woman who comes into the shot, whoever Barack says something,
she's like nodding or head almost like, yeah, he's, he's getting it right.
Just really crazy.
But, um, I showed this to Patricia and I said, you know, this, this is really, really funky.
Just look at this video.
And the first thing she said is, well, listen, listen to the audio for a second.
The first thing she said is, why am I hearing all of these old fashioned camera clicks?
These shutters going off the whole time.
Listen to it.
Yeah, this is, uh, the core of my economic team.
And actually, I'm just, I'm just noticing the video starts off with a shot of, uh,
let me say, let me just roll it back a little bit.
It starts off with a shot of how many I'm going to count them here.
Uh, three photographers.
And then it pans to the right.
And then there's an edit.
And then it's basically a new shot.
But the sound of the cameras, listen to this.
Yeah, this is, uh, the core of my economic team.
Uh, and the message is meeting.
And the sound of these cameras continues throughout the entire press conference.
It does not stop.
Just listen.
We are.
It almost sounds like someone's on a typewriter.
The economy is bad.
The situation is getting worse.
Now, you know, and, and here's why Patricia commented on it.
She said, it's funny.
There's someone looking, looking through a curtain in the background.
Uh, it's so amateurish.
Uh, it's so funny.
And he's saying nothing, by the way, excepting going to try and get the, uh,
the stimulus package through Congress before or the day after I'm president.
That's essentially the entire message.
But the cameras continue.
And on these cameras, electronic don't all, you know,
a press photographer certainly paparazzi.
Don't they all have silent cameras that just take the picture?
I mean, I can understand hearing a flash.
But I'm hearing, you know, seeing, you know, like reflex lens is here.
Uh, by partisan leadership group this afternoon.
And the, the most important message today is that the situation.
Listen to that.
We've got to act boldly.
And we've got to act swiftly.
We cannot delay.
Uh, I said it in my web address is.
Anyway, I, I actually, if I had time, I'd analyze all those clicks and see if it was some kind of a loop, which from time to time it does sound like.
It's weird, you know, it's weird that they had that, that edit in the video, the pan.
And I don't know why other than they just slap and shit together.
And trying to make it look like something actually, uh, official.
I don't know.
Have a look at that.
It's on the drop drop dot IO slash daily source code.
Oops.
Shipman, we already did that one.
This is the one I meant to hit.
Hold on a second.
Let me do this.
There we go.
You know what?
Instead of that, I got a better idea.
Since I screwed that up already.
I'm going to, uh, unmute everybody here.
Everybody is now alive.
If you want to say something, because once again, we're going to try another hit test hit number 154.
You got all the answer if you know it.
This is the hit test.
Hit it test.
YUMBOLESS!
So you don't want to hit this number 154.
And here we go.
We're in drone number one.
Uh, Diana Ross upside down.
Come on, people on the conference.
You guys can't hear that.
I mean, it's obvious.
Diana, we're all on.
Are we kidding?
Number two.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Pots, all young.
All young, uh, won't you come back, please?
Oh, no.
I think it's won't you come back.
All young.
And this is number three.
Oh, come on, you guys know that one, don't you?
We're the gana?
No, Madonna.
No way, it's the power station, some like at heart.
It's Madonna.
Oh, it's time for the answers.
All right, everybody's sing along now.
And this is answer number one.
I tell you, me and you.
I said stop to me.
Oh, sorry, misqueer.
Oh, they don't that I need.
Oh, sorry, down.
Boy, you turned me inside out.
And round around.
I'm sorry, down, you turn me.
You're fine, you're fine.
Oh, I'm instinctively.
Round and round, you turn me.
I say to be respectfully.
I'm sorry.
And you're number one, Diana Ross upside down.
And this is answer number two.
Three, two, three.
So there we go.
You said you'd be mine till the end of time.
Who don't wait in a longer?
Why don't you come back?
Please hurry.
Welcome back, can't stay.
Oh, good this time.
Did you come back here?
Stay, oh, good.
Answer number two, fall young, come back and stay.
And this is answer number three.
Can't believe who is tough for you guys, just easy.
I think we're gonna do the work.
We'll be the best.
Huh?
Some like it.
Answer number three.
The power station.
And that concludes hit us number 154.
So Adam, how did you do this week?
I did pretty well.
I did six out of six.
Folks on the call, socked.
I'll get better over time.
Maybe it was really hard to hear.
I don't know.
Appreciate it though.
Two and one day.
The answers to this and any other hits as well.
So the links to iTunes, you can buy the turks.
Featured on the hittest online.
To be founded hittest.mefio.com.
Thanks for playing Adam.
No, thank you young.
Everyone else.
Thanks for listening again.
Next week, I hope to be back for another hittest.
So until then, have fun.
Take care.
And remember, try to think with your hearts.
Bye-bye.
We back hittest.mefio.com.
In hope young.com.
JNPOLT.com.
My natural rescue bill fails in Congress yet again.
The value of your home could plummet.
Families looking for a new home will be unable to get alone.
It's going to be harder for you to get a mortgage for your home.
New car sales will come to a halt.
Or the loans you need to buy a car.
It would be more difficult for you to get the loans you need to buy a car.
Or send your children to car.
No longer be able to get loans for college.
My businesses would close their doors.
And they'd be unable to pay employees.
Thousands of businesses could call.
In millions of Americans could lose their jobs.
Millions of jobs could be lost.
We failed to act.
Ultimately, our country could experience a long and painful recession.
There you go.
That's the proof that they're all reading from the same script.
Many more examples like it because that's exactly how it works.
Lady Patricia started to catch on to some of this as well, which is kind of cool.
She's more often than not.
She's saying, hey, you know, there's something really weird going on there.
She's starting to figure out that maybe there is something behind this shadow, shadow
government that is controlling everyone like puppets on strings.
Really good article.
I'd like you to check out.
I will drop this into the show notes a daily source code.com across post that on curry.com.
Written by David Burn, of course, of the talking heads.
He wrote this on December 18th.
I'm not going to read the entire thing to you.
But it's kind of the topic we've been on today about the news and how mainstream news is reporting
certainly the events in Gaza and Israel in a certain way.
Good battery different.
It's certainly not the whole story.
It really does, it pisses me off that you're not seeing any footage of these protests and the shoe throwing.
What a great meme.
Wow, that's something I believe the whole world can get behind regardless of religion.
The message is very clear.
It's a great one.
And when you see Nike shoes and Adidas, you know, not sandals, but, you know, boots, you know,
get out there.
Throw you a monoloblanix.
So David Burn at the talking heads wrote this blog post on his,
David Burn dot com journal dot David Burn dot com.
No more news is the title of it.
And he basically goes, he starts right off with media ownership,
the tribune company owns the Chicago Tribune, the Baltimore Sun, Los Angeles Times,
Cubs, bunch of TV stations, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And he goes through exactly how mergers acquisitions work,
what happens.
He's own experiences when Warner Brothers was purchased by AOL.
What that means for, you know, when a, when a, certainly media companies go from being a,
a business running cash flow positive or profitable to huge expansion and debt and,
and what takes place.
And essentially that, you know, the mainstream news outlets just aren't,
they, they, it's no longer in their DNA to do investigative reporting.
It just is not read through it to get his take on it.
It was, yeah, I was pleasantly surprised by, by what he wrote.
And good to see some of the musicians from the old school getting back into the game.
Chrissy, kind of the pretenders, the pretenders have an album out and there's a new song
and a video to go along with it.
She's always been kind of a rebel.
And I'm getting, I'm getting permission to play the MP3 and they have some tickets.
Apparently the, the record company is really,
someone over at the record company loves the show.
And has said, look, we'll, we'll get your permission to play the song.
You can play the clip, whatever you want to do.
And they're going to get me some tickets to give away to, to the chuckleheads.
Hey, everybody, we're going to give away some tickets.
Ah!
Let's see.
I got one more savant who, uh, sent in a, a call.
Hey, yeah, Adam, it's a prolific program I hear from San Francisco.
First off, there, we, um, the CSB and I always respond to your DSC with an answer show.
Usually every weekend, most of the time, um, sometimes not because we do get lazy.
Um, about the Irish rejection, I used to live in Ireland.
Oh, I didn't know that.
British, but I do, I was, I was living in Ireland, like I said before.
Excellent. This, uh, all of a sudden, prolific programer has expanded as universe.
All right.
So lay in on me. This, of course, is about the Lisbon Treaty, uh, which I read through again.
Someone sent me a, or dropped, uh, a consolidated version.
I was looking through it again, laughing at all of the,
legalese and references and language that essentially sets them up for exactly what the plan was for this new economic world order as they're calling it.
Um, allowing this to take place.
And then, you know, in hindsight, you go back and now you see what's happened with the economy and the financial system in general.
And now you see this, this Lisbon Treaty makes so much sense.
And why it had to be done in October because they knew that it was going to come crashing down at the end of the year.
So they could take swift action. And now, of course, they're acting under what they call the Lisbon principles,
which is basically, as if the Lisbon Treaty have been ratified, but there's still two countries,
Czech Republic has not ratified it in Ireland, even, they have not ratified it.
They have declined it thrown it out by, uh, way of a referendum.
And, uh, that, of course, is not acceptable.
So the, uh, the true global elitist who owned the world will just force Ireland to have a second referendum.
Hell yeah, until the end of the third one until they get it.
Yes.
And it seems to me that the new church, the way they call it, by Mr. Brian Cowell, is not as convincing as Bertie.
I heard was, given that Cowell is not as popular as I heard.
And the economy there in Ireland is narrowing the toilets.
Yeah, they're going to, that's, that's what you're saying is now they're going to vote. Yes.
The point of Lisbon was the final nail in the coffin.
See, the, the boats in Ireland are not 100% for against referendum.
They're more like 55 or 50%.
It's like, that was a little bit more than that.
Okay. First of all, it was a high turnout, and it was more than 55%.
And the state, um, therefore any little, and by the way, 55% in the United States election,
it would be considered a landslide.
A little, a few votes can tip it with me or the other.
Anyway, happy Christmas, all the best.
And I look forward to you, plugging the D.S.E.D. bug at D.S.E.D. bug.mevio.com.
That's D.S.E.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D
D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D.D
It's fun to have some real-time feedback in the form of a chat room.
You can do that in the talk show, web page or client, however you want to do that.
It keeps me kind of awake and on my toes, and once I get my production schedule kind
of in check, I believe I can get back to a pretty much daily schedule.
Now it may only be 40 minutes, which I think many people might find desirable.
All we might go long or short, I don't know, but I'm slowly garnering control over
my schedule.
This week and actually it's when I make the big flip, I've got to produce a double time
so I can be one day ahead, currently I produce on the day of, and then I'll be much
more flexible, but still, it looks like I'm going to have to shoot for late in the afternoon
slash early evening, UK time in order to get as many people on the phone as possible,
to get enough interaction just to get the West Coast in.
It's really tough though, I think we're going to have to figure out maybe coffee break lunch
time with that work, which would pretty much be my exclusive UK folks, I don't know.
I don't know.
We'll figure it out.
Anyway, play one last time for you.
It's also came from the drop.
Unfortunately, no information in the comments.
It's titled The Future soon.
It's said I love you, signed an anonymous friend, turns out she's smarter than I thought
she was.
She knows I wrote it now, the whole class does too, and I am all alone during double
skate.
When she skits ball, it's in God and on, but I know that I'll forget the look of pity
in her face.
When I'm running in my soul, I don't want a platform in space, because God made a future
soon.
I won't always be in this place, but the things that make me weak and strange can't
end in a way.
It's going to be a future soon, never seen a quite so clear, when my heart is breaking
I can close my eyes, it's already here.
I'll probably be some kind of scientist, building inventions in my space, laughing space.
I'll end world hunger, I'll make dolphins speak.
Work through the daytime, spend my nights, and we can't perfecting my warrior, you know my
grace.
Newling them well as you got out of time, I'd love to my best to teach them about life
and what it's worth.
I just know that I can't keep them from destroying me, but we've got a future soon, I won't
always be in this way.
When the things that make me weak and strange can't end in a way.
It's going to be a future soon, never seen a quite so clear, when my heart is breaking
I can close my eyes, it's already here, I'll end world hunger, as I piece by piece,
it's the place by self, and the skill and circus will make me home, but I still feel so long
until Laura calls me home.
I'll see her standing by the moderate, she'll look the same except for Bionic Eye, she lost
the real ones in the robot world, I'll say I'm sorry, she'll say it's not your fault or
isn't she'll eye me suspiciously, we're in the world of the servers inside, she'll scream
and try to rock it, but there's no way she can't hide it, when crazy side of all
wants to make you his robot life, when it's going to be a future soon, I won't always be in this way.
When the things that make me weak and strange can't end in a way, it's going to be a future soon, never seen a
quite so clear, when my heart is breaking I can close my eyes, it's already here, now I'm kind of a happy song,
in a way, that wraps it up for daily source code episode 814 coming to you semi live from the
curry terrace in Southwest London, the eastern part of Gitmonation, I'll try and do it again with you tomorrow,
we'll figure out the time, subscribe to my Twitter, Adam Curry is my account and that way you
will be certainly notified in time when we're going to go live until then, thanks everybody,
on the call, thanks for hanging in there, actually I'm just on mute you guys for a second,
so Jamie and Woody 426, thanks for hanging in. No problem. Okay, and I'm sorry to hear about
I saw on the chat room there, Woody, you just got let go or made redundant as they say here in the UK.
Yeah, I was relieved, not about a server. Relieved from your services or released.
Yeah, I was a lot more concerned about that, so hopefully 2009 we'll get better for you. Jamie, thank
you and we'll talk to you guys very soon, enjoy your freedom while you still can and whatever you do,
live your life with passion. Another fine, beefy old presentation, stick it in your ear.