Delta Sherechari 230.
You're DJ.
I'm your DJ!
Your DJ has only just begun.
A $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking friends, you?
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I gotta tell you, just keep on getting fun,
or doing these shows.
It's a source code for Monday, everybody.
How are you? How are you? How are you?
And that would be Monday, August 29th.
We are awaiting the arrival of Katrina in New Orleans.
Southern states there, not much news as of right now.
It is 2 p.m. in the afternoon in the cottage.
That's where we're bringing you the show from today, once again.
It looks like plans have changed once again.
I'll be off to Nueva Yorker.
I think on the 5th of September for just a couple days,
then I'll come back.
Oh yeah, it gets even better.
And then I'll go off to New York Chicago Santa Fe.
Hey, it's gonna be a real busy month, the month of September.
Besides the fact that it's my 41st birthday on the 3rd.
I don't think you're supposed to celebrate the 41st.
Isn't that like a plastic plus,
birthday, 41, something like that?
Damn, I'm home.
I did a lot of production work over the weekend,
created the 5th of the supposedly 4 episodes
of the Spike Lee Inside Man podcast.
There was an awesome human human,
our shadowcaster went back on the set
by a special arrangement with Spike,
who just did not want to do only 4 episodes.
And we got some great stuff, some great,
a lot of safe footage,
but it is audio footage of actual shooting on the set.
And of course, Spike goes off again as usual.
So feel free to look out for that in your iTunes
if you're subscribed to the Inside Man podcast.
And I got a new production system,
which I'll talk about, using a new outliner.
And that means incredibly well organized today.
We're going to kick it off with a mashup.
It's from the Agro1 week over at mashuptown.com.
Agro1's got Michael Jackson and Janet Jackson under pressure.
We're going to kick it off with a mashuptown.
And we're going to kick it off with a mashuptown.
And we're going to跟 it off with a mashuptown.
Got it all.
And we're going to kick it off with a mashuptown.
And we're going to fight that.
We're going to kick it off with a mashuptown.
And we'll kick it off with some mashuptown.
mashups and purchasing tracks from that little bit later on the show.
Podsafe, the music on the way, of course, plenty of promos, and as I said, I've really got
my production set up all everything's together now and it really motivates me, I really feel
like doing, I want to do a show, I want to, yes that I had my the digital audio workstation,
I had, I was using it as a remote to control deck on the other Mac so I could actually
control the faders by using the faders on the, on the workstation.
That was cool, I mean, I've known it's been possible for a long, long time through MIDI,
it's basically you turn it into a MIDI controller, but it really, you know, it saved a lot of
time actually on setting volumes and stuff, but it was just fun, I've got the crapload set up on
the top shelf here, I've got it wired through the board so if anyone were to call on Skype,
I mean, literally now I can see my mail coming in, I've got my Skype set up, I even worked on some
of the samples, the on board samples that you can load into the workstation. Now of course the
stuff that I want to load in is more than the memory will allow, but it has a couple of
interesting little bits preloaded in there, you heard the one at the beginning of the show.
Okay, all right, maybe it wasn't all that spectacular.
Lots of stuff from the mail bag, as I've been scurrying between 98 and 100% on my
Gmail allocation, Jeff Garcide said he listened to the August 24th podcast and was wondering
I thought he would share his experiences about his British Airways flight from Moscow.
Now we've talked about this that Gate Gourmet has gone on strike and there was no food on the flight,
and there are no food on any flights on British Airways. I don't think that they've gotten
it back into full swing yet. As Jeff writes, while the plane was being refueled, I wonder what
it was refueling, it was refueling in Germany or somewhere. The stewards and stewarders had gone
out and purchased food for the passengers. Each passenger was then given to bag of food,
so as they boarded the ple-reboarded the plane, in the bag was an Apple banana,
canopy, sandwich, and a Mars bar. Personally, Jeff thought it was the best selection of food
you'd ever had on a flight anywhere. So much nice to be able to eat when he felt like it rather
than the slice of time that they have to put the food in front of him. Yeah, okay Jeff,
I have to agree with that. Patricia, by the way, is someone who always takes a couple sandwiches
where they're on any trip. Any flight, it doesn't matter what she's doing, she always takes
long a couple of sandwiches with cheese and just stuff that'll keep for a long while and I must say,
many of the time have we enjoyed that sitting in an airport terminal waiting for a flight.
Before I forget, I don't have a promo for it, but there is another digital
flotsam that's been released. PW Fenton, who of course produces the pod show on serious and
is quite a wheel within the pod show organization when it comes to pulling out the promos and the
pod cast and the pod safe music and the mashups. Definitely check out his new addition of digital
flotsam. It's a short one. It's like 17 or 18 minutes. It's, uh, what was I think it's titled,
growing up a geek in a society that worships jocks. Any nerd will completely love this episode
of digital flotsam. So make sure you check that out at digitalflotsam.org. Of course,
all the links to the show will be included in the show notes for today's podcast at dailysourceco.com
or www.curry.com and then do it in the new format because I'm now using my new favorite outline.
I've always been using frontier or radio user land and I'm the outlineer, which I think is a
Mac only product is really fantastic. It's has so many incredible options and you can output
your outline as dynamic HTML. So my thought is I'm going to get back into the hang of
releasing both the OPML for the show notes as well as inline show notes in outline or format with
nodes expanded and collapsed so you can immediately go to the stuff that you want and if, you know,
or the the top line stuff and if you need anything any additional info just expand the note. I think
I do that with an eye frame. I'm going to have to play around with that a little bit. But that is
all for later. First we have some promos. Welcome to 101 uses for baby wipes. Okay. It's a podcast
about parenting from a dad's point of view. I know that. With your host Dennis Gray. Thanks,
radio and answer Jeff. On the podcast we'll explore news and current events related to parenting
in the internet age. Oh yeah. Lighthearted topics for discussion, some fun guests,
little pod sake music stirred in. And of course a special segment each week featuring things to
do with all those baby wipes you bought at the big box megastore just before your kid finished by training.
To the dad, dad, dad, dad, dad, dad. My son, he's five. He runs the mixing board for me. So how can I
go wrong? I'm not going to join this red thing. Hope you'll subscribe and listen in as we follow
a reluctant father's journey through parenthood. You know I'm going to join that red thing.
You can find us on the web at one zero one uses for baby wipes.com. I know that. I know that.
I know that. Thanks for listening everybody. Oh, we're also on the pod safe music network.
Man, I tunes. Thanks, everybody.
Hi, Joe. Content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
Hi, this is MB, the host of Ferry Till Corner. Ferry Till Corner is a new podcast where we feature
classic modern and original fairy tales that are safe for the whole family. Here at Ferry Till Corner,
the only four letter F word you'll hear is frog. Hey baby. Sure, Ferry Till Corner has a
share of scary and maybe gruesome events, but it's all good. Only the bad people have bad
stuff happen to them. Things like having your eyes plucked out by pigeons or heels and toes cut off
by a knife. So join me in Ferry Till Corner. You can subscribe to the feed at feeds.feedburner.com
flash FTC. Oh, that didn't sound too good. I was messing around. Shit. I haven't seen this
happen a long time. It was messing around with the outliner. And then I pulled. Shit. I pulled the
mouth. Oh, there. Oh, I see what happened. Of course. What is that damn thing? All those widgets?
Man, I hate it when that pops up. Okay, let's see if we can get the, uh,
you know, maybe I just rolled that promo out again because that did kind of suck. Hold on.
Let me see. We'll do the the Ferry Till Corner podcast again if you don't mind.
Hi, this is MB, the host of Ferry Till Corner. Ferry Till Corner is a new podcast where we feature
classic modern and original fairy tales that are safe for the whole family. Here at Ferry Till Corner,
the only four letter F word you'll hear is frog.
Hey, baby. Sure, Ferry Till Corner has a share of scary and maybe gruesome events, but it's all good.
Only the bad people have bad stuff happen to them. Things like having your eyes plucked out by pigeons
or heels and toes cut off by a knife. So join me in Ferry Till Corner. You can subscribe to the feed
at feed.feedburner.com slash FTC or visit our website where you can download individual
episodes or subscribe to the feed. The website address is www.chesnutbay.com slash FTC. So join me and be
at Ferry Till Corner. Reminds me of the movie we saw last night. It was on the sky or on ITV.
It was you've got mail, Meg Ryan and Tom Hanks. Never seen it before and of course,
the minute you see the movie you know what's going to happen in the end and you still sit there
and watch like a more on. But it was kind of cute. Meg had the little bookstore around the corner
and it was basically a kid's bookstore. I remind of me of that promo. Back to the Gmail bag,
plenty of comments. This is really cool when you do something on a Friday and you wait over the weekend.
The comments just keep rolling in. So last week we talked about the accuracy of the GPS receiver
that I used for a couple of my flights and when the plane was basically stationary it was recording
it as if we were bugging on all over within a hundred yard radius of actually where the plane was
and I think it was a PW sent in that the US government purposely sends down some kind of
scrambling stuff with the signal. What apparently this is called Selective Availability Dithering.
And I got several emails. I just wanted to share a couple of with you. Here's one from
pilot Mike from the pilot cast. It says you should know that the Selective Availability Dithering
for the GPS signal has been gone since its removal was ordered by President Clinton in 2000.
It has not even been restored in wartime. It goes on to say it's a competing GPS system called
Gaida Leia. I think we've talked about that before, which is being set up by the European Union
specifically. So they have a system where well where the US doesn't have the awesome which.
And then there's another one. Another GPS system called WAS wide area augmentation system
and local WAS where ground-based GPS transmitters and repeaters are being installed to get the
kind of precision needed for precision approaches. A.O.P. that's the aircraft owner's pilot
association president Phil Boyer demonstrated using a new WAS approach at Frederick Maryland
compared it to ILS instrument landing system. You said it was amazing. Okay. So I actually
subscribe to the pilot cast. It's kind of cool. I've been subscribed to a number of aviation
podcasts and some of them just seem to seem to go away or are very very infrequent.
Typical lazy ass pilots, but I'd like the pilot cast. Greg Grusby says kind of the same thing
goes back to a 2000 and the removal of Selective Availability built into the GPS system. He says
by the way and we'll talk about this later. I have purchased original back catalog tracks after hearing
remixes and mashups on the daily source code. He says I'd rather buy my music on iTunes music store
than any playsells. Thank you very much Greg. And the final from Robert. Let me see if he says anything.
He said well he says I work with GPS on cell phones all day. I can tell you that your listener
that said commercial GPS is less accurate than military GPS due to induced errors is bullshit.
There we go. And basically the same thing. Selective Availability. So I guess that's called triangulation.
We got three people saying that it has not been turned back on. This is kind of interesting.
Military GPS is better because the GPS satellites actually transmit data on two frequencies. Only
one of which is available to commercial GPS receivers. Okay. That's new data. Military units
listen on both frequencies. The reason for this is that large source of errors caused by
ionospheric interferences in the atmosphere. I think I have that this morning. Just before I
didn't my daily download. And then I was at about smart bombs. Bombs are moving entities. The
last source of GPS errors called multi-path reflection with a GPS single bounces off of objects and
causes the receiver to see duplicates of the signal. Okay. So clearly it's listed a lot of
bits and bytes to be fixed out. But if you're wondering why smart bombs were that email is for you.
So also now I'm going back to posting the actual emails into the outline with all the links
and all of that integrity left in there. So hopefully you'd like the new format of the show notes.
Then I got an email from Wichita, a brother for you probably heard his five minutes with Wichita
podcast. If not, you've got to listen to it. He interviews the biggest stars in country and western
and bluegrass. And it's only five minutes. And if they say the secret word, then they get the
place them horrible trick on. And it looks like Wichita is reaching out a bit of his email. Why don't
we do this as a podcasting community, podcasts for hurricane victims? Let's all do two to three
minute podcasts that won't inspire people to give to the red cross or food banks or whatever
organization they choose to help these folks who are going to be without food, water, shelter, clothing,
medicine, and Lord knows what all else this thing could get ugly very quick. So if we want to
prepare, we'd be ready to do what we do best to help them. We've got a big infrastructure now
as Wichita with millions of listeners true. Let's put ourselves in our podcast to the side
for a minute and put links to these organizations, whichever ones you choose as the main focus
and links on our sites. Okay, so there's a whole instruction email that he sent and I totally agree.
So I shall do tofully put in some links because we will have victims of the hurricane,
not necessarily casualties per se, but just imagine, you know, I've heard reports where
people don't expect to go back to their homes for a month. It's hard to imagine what kind of
devastation could be heading for New Orleans and for Louisiana in general. So God speed to all
and please support your red cross and other organizations that will be on the scene.
A hoi Adam says Caroline, in the daily source code today, this is from last week, you mentioned
that you hadn't gotten any feedback from teenagers. Yeah, I mean, I was talking about how
what a common bond we have as parents in the podcast where I can, you hear my daughter come in
and hear something she says and people will immediately email and identify with the situation
of the scenario. So Caroline says, here you go, I'm about the same age as Christina,
2015 and a couple months, and speaking as a teenage girl and oldest child, I can tell you that
fathers are no picnic either. Your relationship with her actually reminds me a lot of mine with my
dad and although I love him dearling, he's a hassle. It's just job the knife in. My parents
haven't experienced a child grow up before and it seems to be harder for them to let go of me
than for me to renounce them. Oh, well, gee, I'm sorry, they're Caroline. I guess I didn't
find the manual either. Also worth mentioning, I think, is that in my case, much of the insulin
and rebellion is calculated. We teenagers are smarter than you think. After 15 years of living
under the rule of parents, I love this language. We have learned how to manipulate,
play Kate and annoy you in ways that I don't think you understand or maybe my parents are just
easy. Whatever the reason I think that us capable and intelligent teenage girls are vastly
underrated, I don't really know what Christina is like, but I would bet that she has things much more
under control than you believe. Thanks for your great podcasts. If not for your love of teenagers,
Caroline. Well, that's very nice, very appreciated that you responded. I totally believe that.
And Patricia and I were talking about it last night. You know, when I said, well, when you were 15,
what were you doing, what you into? And then she said, and I said, well, yeah, so why would that be
any different? I think the thing that's a little bothersome these days is what kids are into and
what's important to them. Now, of course, most of that has to do with commercialism and with
commercial television, I totally believe, but also I was looking through the Vogue today, the latest
edition of Vogue, which is it's thicker than a Bible. It is, of course, the fashion Bible,
but it's thicker than a Bible. And it's all advertisements, which is, and it's a, what a great
gig. I mean, what a fantastic publication. Basically, your advertisers pay for the content because
that's what it is. It is all advertisements with a few bits of editorial thrown in between and by the
way, who cares about the, they've been doing gadgets in the Vogue now as editorial or advertorial
and whatever you call it. So it's really about the, about the pictures and every single one of them
is all sexually oriented. Not one is different. It's all women laying down, you know, showing leg.
And it's all beautiful stuff. I totally love it, but, you know, when, when that is what the entire
fashion Bible consists of, you know, you got to start expecting kids to be influenced by it.
Turn on MTV. Please turn on MTV and watch it for an hour. And, you know, and people say,
oh, don't watch MTV in the more exciting music videos. They most certainly do. And they're at
very important hours. And go and watch what's going on. It's all about being in the club and being
successful and having the chicks and got, got your cars and got your crib and being back in the club
and it's all about the club and it's about the drinking in the club. And, you know, what do we expect?
Look at the example we're setting. I didn't have those types of examples. Of course, I wish
I had at the time, but, so we got to provide some balance. I think that's, that's the main thing.
And that's probably balance in viewing habits, which I think we can totally change. I think we can,
you know, I loved it when when I was a kid and they said, your brain's going to rot from television.
It's going to rot away. Don't sit too close. No more than an hour a day. Or your brain will rot away.
You know what? Let me put that in my show notes right now. Time once again to hold on.
The Zen TV experiment. If you don't believe me, that the television is bad for your health,
do the Zen TV experiment. I guarantee you you will not be disappointed. Probably about once a month
I pointed out, just read it, take a look at it. Maybe even if you do half of the Zen TV experiment
tonight while you're watching TV, I think you'll understand what's going on with your brain.
I'm Mini Paul and I produce a podcast about minis. Not the shiny new,
but very variety, but the old classic ones which have been around for 45 years. I talk about the
goings on with my own 1966 Morris Mini and all the mini related shows I tend up and down the
90 Kingdom. You can join me at www.miniPaul.co.uk.
Hi Adam, this is Al. And Kathy from www.WidVid12.com, the wedding videographer's podcast.
WidVidTalk has 30 shows uploaded with a half dozen more strapped to our belts. You mean recorded
and ready to upload? Yes, Kathy. You know Adam says with 16 million tons of airplane. Oh,
have a mind. Adam, we're fans of the Daily Source Code and we want to wish you a very happy birthday.
Yes Adam, happy birthday. Oh, thank you. Now that's the way to get your promo played,
dammit. And of course Saturday we had Christina's birthday. She turned 15 birthdays are a real
big deal in the Netherlands where people come up and congratulate every member of the family and
they'll say congratulations with your daughter's birthday or your niece's birthday, your granddaughter's
birthday and they always do big decorations and presents and everyone calls all day and people
come drop by and visit. Of course no one can drop by and visit that easily from from
back home, but there were plenty of phone calls and we all slept really late, which was nice.
And Christina had a girlfriend stay over and then she invited John out to dinner and she
wanted to have a posh dinner. So we went to cafe de barri and it was great. And they were all grown
up and stuff. Friends as Adam letting you know, I'm a Senseo Connoisseur as well.
Hold on, I need to have a little sip while we're talking about it.
From listening to your show, I discovered this product. I'll tell you this podcasting shit works.
And so last weekend, I took my cash down to a local department store and got one.
And here in Australia, the pods work out to about 33 cents each, so it's cheaper in the long run than
getting takeaway coffees from a cafe. The dark roast pack is quickly becoming my favorite.
It would be good to know what your roast is. What's your preference?
Also, if there is a Senseo or coffee podcast out there somewhere, you know, the agency for Senseo
did call us and I know that of course we responded. I haven't heard anything about it, but you know,
we should really put together a case study with the source code and with Senseo. And what that can
mean to a brand and what it can mean to sales, you know, I don't know what's going on with them.
I'll have to ask KJ, see what's going on. It would be cool. I mean, I've been doing it just for
the love of the product. And I make about, you know, like a hundred, 150 bucks a month on selling
Senseo's and people also click on the Amazon link on curry.com and buy other things through it.
And we'll be talking about affiliate programs and just a little bit on the source code,
because there's some exciting stuff to share regarding that.
Barstools, I've been, I've said that I needed a barstool after standing on my feet all day
on Friday Thursday and really noticing that that's not going to work.
So there's a couple of suggestions that came through, I'll post that in the email gray.
I'm actually sent me a link to the bombo barstool. I've received offers from people who sell
barstools and which, of course, I said, yeah, sure. Send me a barstool. I'll promote it on the show.
No problem whatsoever. And Brian, I'm going to say, Sherry or Shiree, Sherry, I think.
Mr. Curry says, that makes me feel so all.
Mr. Curry, love, Delta Sherry, Charlie, got turned on to iPod when stationed in Iraq,
just heard the August 16th show. I love this about podcasting. It's so,
me just says the delivery is a synchronous, so is the listening. And people catch up,
you know, they listen to old shows and sometimes like, wow, what's this person talking about?
It's something from a show from weeks ago or even months ago.
So this is, this is the August 16th show when I talked about Iraq and the war against Terry.
He says, you've used about the Iraqi people are right on target. I was stationed up a
grime after the scandal broke. Thank you. And most of the detainee prisoner population weren't
Iraqi. Mostly, they were Syrian. After all, how can a group of insurgents galvaned across the
country unfunded? The Iraqi people are so poor. They couldn't fund this type of terrorism. My
thought is that the Syrian government is afraid. They are thinking, first Iraq, then us.
Syrian culture is economically politically and religiously a mirror of that of Iraq.
Just my two cents. That's all. Love the daily source code. I remember you back from the
days when MTV actually played music videos. Well, they played them with different themes
then in the club and cars that bounce up and down. Although, I wouldn't mind having one of those
cars that bounces up and down. I think those are. Those are definitely kind of cool.
Yeah, so Syria, huh? Yeah, I would believe that without a doubt. I mean, I think it was it now
officially proven or not that the Syria was responsible for Pan M flight 103.
And, of course, that's going to be interesting because Tony Blair, we didn't
we see him just a few months back, make a nice to, um, good doffy. That's his name, right?
Or is that Libya? Fuck, man. Syria, Libya. Jesus. Okay. I think I have to go
polish up a little bit on my geography. The obtuse angle. Steve DuPont dot com.
Now, say, tone, minus Gary, do you see? It's cool. It's not what? Who is why?
Holy moly, that's pretty good. Uh, can you argue that the fact that the trees are made of dirt?
An air?
Is a lightning bolt air tight? In terms of just being a show.
Now that's funny. The obtuse angle. Steve DuPont dot com.
All right. Time for some pod save music now on the source code.
Some different that I picked up from the pod save music network. The bit of reggae.
There's a beast from the east. No one can tame him. There is a child running wild.
No one can name him. I remember what the club I said.
Yeah, yeah. Thank you for more days. You must be a topi.
Topi. Topi. Yeah. Don't know, not topi.
Shut your try. Plus all the wild. There's a flower, huh, she said the, huh.
Yes, that's the, huh. Yeah. Always the love.
Oh, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it's a love, it
takes my breath open um we're just keeping your wall
keeping the bond
then nothing, nothing will break my heart
I say it's the air
Cause I'm saying now I see what I'm telling you
Tell me
air
But don't matter what it's a scam
Look around chimes, she said love, yes there's love, well, always alone, always alone,
yeah, always love, always love, always, always, still remember what that could not forget.
Who makes my heart not to happen to yet?
I'll come up with you that's not my taste though.
Take my breath away just keep in your want.
Even you know, but I remember what they kind of must say.
Yeah, yeah.
Back in the morning, didn't you know, she would have told me, you know, don't tell me, she said tell me.
Yeah, we're gonna talk like you don't try, you know, you're the smile from love, she said love,
I guess there's love to be up all the way from all the way
Always, always, yeah I always love always love always
I love and love always love always love always love always love always love always love always love
All in Love
Scott Church and always love discovered on the Podsafe Music Network
Podsafe Music Network.com. The place where artists and podcasters come together
so you can get Podsafe Music you are allowed to play on your podcast and of
course point them back to the artist site and the circle and the loop is then
thereby closed. We're near in our 35 minute mark talking about biodiesel and now
with the price of oil, 70 bucks a barrel and we have established that this of course
is supply and demand and you know demand is just big and supply is just dwindling and
now the Gulf production is closed 650 million barrels a day that won't be
produced so we're getting a lot lower and dipping into the reserves and I've
heard a lot about biodiesel I've read a lot about it it apparently is more
expensive than regular diesel but you can basically grow your own fuel and wouldn't
work for a lot of farmers in the United States and then I get a couple of
couple of emails the first one from Jurgen Schlunt from Germany atom and you last
daily source code you mentioned to buy a diesel and use biodiesel don't do that
now he says it's cheaper than normal diesel I don't think so because you shouldn't do that
here's why biodiesel is a synthetic product made out of rapeseed and methanol okay
I thought you could just take a crap and it would basically make your car run
although the molecular structure is similar to diesel it may damage your engine
diesel fuel may out of oil has a lot of lubrication capabilities for the special injection
and pump parts of it oh okay so this is a good point actually you don't just want to buy
any old diesel and throw it in there that I know is is true
he even says Volkswagen does not approve their current diesels for biodiesel the old ones are
approved though so maybe just buy an old car it goes on and says there's huge German diesel
community on the internet with these topics I'll discuss very contrary but most of the young
most of the people agree to my opinion that is not worth saving 10 or 15 cents for a leader of biodiesel
I know it's to me it's not about the price I mean the price is expensive I mean I have the Audi A8
4.2 liter you have no idea Jesus Christ we went flying just the other day it was like 350 pounds
to fill up the plane I mean who am I to complain right but I do remember a very different time so
I'm not too worried about a little bit of extra money but if it's going to you know
in the long run if it's going to ensure us of a fuel option to keep cars and and there lots of
planes by the way with diesel engines and even helicopters these days and I'm all for it
and I'm seriously considering getting as something that will accept biodiesel I think it's a
it's a lot more friendly yeah we grow our own fuel and inclusive for S Pen I wonder if he's
related to or if he is Sean Branden's brother forget biodiesel check out bio heat for home heating
eliminating another avenue of fossil fuels and he put a couple of links in there to bossen.com so
you can find that in the show notes at the A's podcast and then finally buying from iTunes after
hearing a mashup or a hit test at least on the daily source code lots of email about that I was
overwhelmed just a quick step Paul Stringer says to random notorious purchased spurships literally
about 10 seconds after hearing the mashup mark cats I frequently purchase songs on iTunes after
having heard them on daily source code in the hit test great to hear that music in the memories
it rekindles congratulations Paul I'm a heart surgeon enrichment virginia I'm likely older than
your average listener if I can be a resistance from the standpoint of medical information
in your continued progress promoting podcast and peace field of contact me oh mark hey mark
let's do a podcast you know what let's do a heart podcast Patricia has has a bilateral artery
that is clogged and I'll ask her if she is any questions you bet you and you know we'd love to get
more medical professionals in the podcasting I mean there's such a wealth of information to be given
out and it could also be good for business I guess Antonio Rosario Adam thought you let you know
that after listening to the hit test on your latest podcast I too went to the iTunes music store
and bought earth wind and fires fantasy while I was there I picked up four more of their songs
that I was surprised they did not have my collection yet so hell yeah the hit test sells songs
see let's see do I have more I got I'd have so many um and my new system is working
Adam I've purchased four songs from iTunes after hearing them in mashups you're right it's a
great way to promote back catalog I hadn't thought about rock steady by Arita Franklin for years
her to snippet in a mashup went to iTunes downloaded it dragged my eye pod done and then there's a
little plug in there for the chub creek pod cast this is this is really phenomenal I mean if this is
just the the people that felt they should respond then the percentage of people actually buying
back catalog through iTunes after hearing a mashup or after hearing a hit test I think is fairly
sizable Kevin Crossman won't even further yet purchased to Rob Costlo tracks and Stevie Wonder
superstition after hearing booty booty what is booty station that was a mashup also downloaded
lots of mashups and pod safe tracks that you play you know the kind of stuff you can't purchase
even if you wanted to would happily happily happily purchase mashups if I could I think that
we've got something here I really do if these mashups are actually enticing people to buy the original
tracks that's fantastic unfortunately I'm in our Australia says Brett Rand don't have much option
for buying music online I think there's a couple but it's windows media player DRM stuff and we're
100% Mac house so that's a that's a barmer he says I'm looking for earth winded fire fantasy love that song
okay so he would do it if he could I didn't know that the I thought that iTunes music store was pretty good
in Australia apparently not and Frank Hurfs finally referring to hit test driving track sales
question yes I have bought a lot of music for my teams after listening to the daily source code
main reason that I did it after hit test and night years before simple I didn't know the
name of the band of the song young plays a lot of great songs from the 70s the time when I grew up
I've always liked this music but it's too young to keep in mind the artists when they were at the
crest of their fame 30 years later I hear these great songs again but today there's a big difference
you and young can tell everyone from whom the music is and and that's fantastic with this knowledge
iTunes helps me find what I'm looking for and usually it takes only a few minutes until the song is mine
and this is a big thing that we talk about it pod show it it appears that so many people are driving
pod casting and music sales with text you know where's all the music where are all the shows that
how women like the source code you know we've got to have many other shows of people driving
you to places and as you can tell it works the hit test sells back catalog
podcasting with battery I suppose you think you know when you use it yes I know what do you
test young bollet
hello young hey Adam I apologize for the background noise but that's because I'm on a train
from Rotterdam to Apple do I have the call and hit test number 52 with my notebook
on fast-blast in the train so hopefully everything goes well so here we go
this is intro number one
now the question is which version is it because it exists in 15 different versions but I'm pretty sure
that's Billie Ocean Caribbean Queen and this is number two
young first rea on the beach I mean that's a legendary tune and number three
I love them all I can't wait to hear the answers you're gonna be singing along
Steve Windwood higher love I think I got three out of three finally and times up it's time for
the answer okay and this is answer number one it's Billie Ocean from 84 this is Caribbean Queen
and number one Billie Ocean Caribbean Queen and this is number two
from 86 yeah it's Chris Rea this is on the beach
the screen is so long
this is around melody takes me back to the place
now under me
it's 420 s
So, not many people looking strange at the end of the day.
Answer number two, Chris Ria.
And this is answer number three.
Oh yeah. Also, something from 86.
It's Steve Windwoods. This is higher low.
We got a three young.
Answer number three, Steve Windwoods.
And high above.
Really great song to end up this. It has number 52.
Well, that's it.
I'm going to trim this file to get rid of the silence at the beginning and at the end.
And as soon as I can, I'll try to upload it to the server.
Well, it's always two addresses.
Hit us at gmail.com for feedback and young.lid.com.
J-A-N-P-L-E-T.com for information about the hit us and the hit us podcast.
Okay. Well, this is the first for me recording the hit us on a train.
Hopefully it's not fine.
And it's good enough to upload it to the server.
Okay. We'll see you next time for 53.
So until then, bye-bye.
All right. Young for that.
Selling back catalog faster than a speeding bagel.
With the hit test.
Thank you very much.
Y'all love that cast blaster on the train.
Work perfectly.
And Y'all has some great news.
You should check out his weblog at youngpolet.com.
He's got some great things going on.
He's starting up a radio school, a broadcasting and podcasting school
in the Netherlands under the auspices of Veronica Radio.
So that's very cool and very happy for him.
And part of that basically came through the podcast.
So you go, you've worked out.
And I think Y'all is going to be spawning a whole bunch of great new podcasts
from the Netherlands.
Very, very soon.
And for now, it's time for me to cut out of here.
What are we at?
46 minutes.
Bit long.
It's a daily source code for Monday, August 29, 2005.
And I plan on having a show every day this week
because production has lightened up a little bit
and everything's all kind of squared away.
So I can get into my email.
And of course, I got that new outlining system.
I'm so happy with it.
Totally enticing when it comes to setting up a show, putting it together.
So I'll be hopefully setting this up with an eye frame.
So you can easily access it in the show notes.
I have no idea how that's going to work out.
We'll find out.
And thank you very much for subscribing to the daily source code.
You can find the podcast feed at dailysourcecode.com.
Just search for Adam Curry or daily source code in iTunes.
That's probably one of the easiest ways to subscribe to podcasts
and to find them.
And of course, this is my weblog at www.curry.com
for comments and feedbacks and show notes.
Feedbacks.
Feedback of course.
Adam at Curry.com, please.
If you're going to send me all your feedback,
stick it up on a server somewhere
and just send me the link.
Alright, I appreciate that.
And if you've got a promo to submit, send it off to submit at podshow.com.
And I'll put it through the funnel.
We get into the podshow on serious.
We can get stuff into the pod finder on iTunes
and eventually find its way into the daily source code.
I'll talk to you, everybody.
Thank you very much for listening.
Stay subscribed.
Bye-bye.
One other podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.