Delta Sierra Charlie, 1 9 or 7.
On Show.com, makes no claims regarding the quality of its hot chillers or the sanity
of its producers.
Listen at your own risk.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
This is a remote broadcast of the source code.
I wanted to make a point, wanted to prove it to myself, but I could actually take my
entire kit out on the road, and be completely mobile, something that would take tens
of thousands of dollars to do if you're a professional broadcast or the professional setup.
I'm sitting in the downs with my crap list.
I mean literally, I am sitting here on the downs, I think I've explained that that's kind
of like a grassy meadows that go first, just hundreds of miles all the way from where
we live down to the shore, and I'm sitting in the middle of the menow talking into the on-board
microphone of my crap list, which actually sounds, I think, better than the headset microphone
that I normally use.
Of course, I'm missing a little bit of low end there, a little bit of resonance, but
I think it'd be kind of fun to check it out.
Today is June 21st, 2005.
Wait a minute, doesn't summer officially start today?
Is that the deal?
Some like that, at least.
The future comes home today, so that'll be nice looking forward to that.
Actually, I've loaded everything up for yesterday's source code.
I've loaded up a course on running this on task last year, the, just in the screen.
A task last year, data 15, which has all the tricky limit of stuff in there, so I really
don't have to do much more than just hit the, just hit the buttons at the right time to
fire off the sound sequences.
It's really quite enjoyable.
Okay, we're going to kick it off today with a mashup.
This is, let me see, Tagan, Sarah versus Milo, walking with a ghost in Paris.
I think Dylan Joyett.
Meanwhile, I'm going to have a sip of tea and roll one up.
I'm going to have a sip of tea and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up
up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one down and roll an up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one up and roll two up and roll one up and roll two up backwards one up and roll one up and roll two up and roll one up and roll one through two up one up, two up and roll one up and roll one up and roll another one up and roll one up and roll a regen up, one up and roll one up and roll one up you have a regen up, two up and roll one up, two up and roll one up and roll one up and roll one half and roll one up and roll one up you have a regen up and roll two up okay one up and roll one up and roll two up and roll one up and roll it one up a
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
first 2005 coming to you from the downs behind the cottage.
Let me just stand up for a second and give you a little... I'll turn around here and
I'll just do a 360 so you can hear the sounds from all over hold on.
I'm sure you can hear the birds. You can also probably hear the fan of the
craplet going nuts. So this is actually working out very well. I'm quite impressed
with at least we're not really the depth of the sound of this little hole that's in my
screen but the fact that the compressor limiter functions of cast blasts are really
pulling up the voice enough to make it work. As I said, I was planning on
doing this last night on the train. It was been a great weekend. Patricia was
off to visit her family. So Christina and I were home alone and I had lots and
lots of podgeo business, lots of interesting people we've been talking to, lots
of great stuff coming up very soon. And then last night I went to London,
a guy named Rom Shuri Rom who's definitely Silicon Valley insider was in London
for Wimbledon which of course is kicked off. And so I had dinner with him and we
chat it a bit. He was one of the... I think it's one of the initial investors in
Google. Very interesting guy. And so we had a nice chat and I was planning on
doing the source code on the train ride home and I got the... the 10... what is it?
The 1030 train? No, yeah 1030 train which got me into Gilford at 1103 but it
was actually was quite packed and of course I felt a little bit to self-conscious to
be sitting on the train talking into my laptop and loud tones. So I think maybe
I should not do that. But I had everything loaded up anyway and oh man we've had
such a heat wave here. It's so incredibly warm, 91, 92 degrees which is
beautiful of course although none of the English infrastructure or the British
infrastructure is set up for this type of weather so there's no air conditioning.
The studio, the daily source code studio is freaking hot my friends. It's not
all good at CC would say. It's you know I've got fans and everything go on and
it's just not helping so particularly with some of the equipment that's in there.
I've got three or four machines, three or four computers running and well
talk about the tube amp, the preamp that I use which has tubes in it which
actually generate heat. That's part of what they do. So it's just almost
unbearable. So I figured I'd just sit out here on the downs and use the
crap foot for the source code. Let me see what I'm going to talk about. Oh
whimbleed it. So whimbleed in. The television over here is doing some pretty
amazing shit. The BBC has 52 cameras and you know a multitude of microphones
and angles and when you switch on and we have sky digital which is basically it's
a satellite service so you get your 999 channels of which 300 a
porn starting at 700. But when you tune into BBC 1 you can press the red button
and then you can actually select which court you want to watch which is
fascinating stuff. It really works too. You know there's a little delay and when
it first loads up all the different screen shots. So you have an overview screen.
You can look at all the court simultaneously and you can switch between them.
It's really it's you know they're really doing some progressive stuff here.
It's it's pretty interesting. Oh boy there's so much to talk about. Oh wait a
minute. Got something very important here. Hold on. See I don't really have a
stand. I'm trying to I'm trying to use my knees to pop up. Can you can just hear
how cheap this tablet is. Hey there pure plastic everybody. This is something
that I should have talked about last week but it unfortunately was still on the
pile and I picked it up yesterday. Congratulations to the Wesowitz family.
Rick Wesowitz we've talked about him before on on the source code. He it does the
ICM raw podcast as well as all the technology and engineering. I believe for
WGBH's morning stories because there's a new addition to the family. Matthew
James Wesowitz was born on the 15th of June. 24 p.m. seven pounds three ounces.
20 and a half inches. Deliberat via cesarean section. Mom is fair.
Data's tired. Matthew is just fine. Thought you'd want to know. It says Rick.
Well congratulations Rick. To you your wife and your family couldn't be happier.
That's awesome news dude. Hoops. That's awesome news dude. Here comes.
Hi Adam. This is Karina. Oh my god. I'm speaking to the pot father and so nervous.
Okay, please add them. Listen to the following announcement. It's important. Very
important. Hi Adam. This is Thomas. You know the man with a Pope voice from Germany.
Today I would like to announce sushi radio.com. What's that?
It will blow the top 10 of podcasting away. But in a good way.
Podcasts we call them sushi makers all over the world are sending us their sushi's.
This is Delphine for sushi radio. This is bicycle mark with you live from Amsterdam
from the hourd kite mark. This is for sushi radio. One is Lloyd Davis and I
log in podcast from Perfect Path.head of UK. I'm based in London in the UK.
I'm doing this short podcast point for sushi radio.com today.
So little time. So many podcasts. Head over to sushi radio.com and find delicious
tidbits for your ears and your listening pleasure. Go sushi radio.com.
People can send us sushi's about topics they are passionate about. So listen to sushi radio
to get a sound collage of our world. Do you like this Adam? Okay the guys from sushi radio told me
I should ask you for a sushi. Maybe some sound seeing in gulfod. Maybe something special
from Dutch history. Whatever you want. They are just two rules. Not more than 10 minutes.
And at the beginning please say this is Adam Perry for sushi radio. Just send it to
sushi radiomail at gmail.com. Hope you are joining us at sushi radio. Bye bye.
Okay sushi radio. I'm a little conflicted about that. I don't know about calling podcasts.
Especially because I had sushi last night at a wonderful restaurant Zuma. It's the name of it.
And some nice tempura. I could go on about that. Was it on Friday? I think we talked about
why is it that whenever someone calls you in the middle of the night and they wake you up
and they say did I wake you? The first thing that usually comes out of your mouth is no not at all when
it's a total fucking blatant lie. Wilson Alfonso sent me some little emails. When someone calls
and asks me the question, my favorite answer is no no I just welcome up to answer the phone.
That makes sense. Okay let me say I got a whole bunch of printed out emails here.
And then I wanted to take care of let me say no. Here's something we got to talk about.
The Apple iTunes 4.9 launch which of course includes podcasting. That's going to be soon.
I don't have an exact date yet but I would say within the next two weeks probably. Maybe even less than that.
And one of the parts of this innovation really in podcasting is this giant leap forward that we're
about to make. As I think it's 38 million desktop have iTunes and they will all be prompted to
upgrade to receive the podcast functionality. I think that's really exciting. Is that Apple is going to
release a name space. They're extending RSS with a name space which will allow for certain tags,
certain synopsisies to be entered. Stuff the will of course completely work with with iTunes.
And they're doing it in a valid way as far as I can tell by creating a name space. Now there's
a pod name space. So you'll see tag showing up in these feeds as pod colon and then whatever the
tag happens to be. So there's one if you do not want to be included in the iTunes music store.
So that's an opt out feature in that case which in my mind means that everyone's going to be in and
we have been working very closely on helping Apple get all of our directory information.
They are going to reorganize it but of course that's how an open directory works. Still no
word on if they're going to open up an open mail back end to their directory but I am pushing
for because that would of course be the right thing to do to feed that back into the community.
So that's one. There'll also be an explicit tag and a couple others that works specifically
within with an iTunes. So as soon as I have information away you could find the name space
document of course I will put it on query.com and I'm sure Apple will be announcing that as well.
So be on the lookout. Adam I'm doing it and I'm about and we've got a new podcast more hip and
hip-ing we promise no granola no patchouli no the earth is doomed and we're not going to have sex.
What what no no what other we're all about living happy.
You want to be good to your favorite planet but I'm a part of our human.
Your father said that she's made a forget it caught in you used to know why but now you forgot
and you traded your suburb and for a hybrid car you're more hip than hip you know who you are.
Oh man we make it so easy. How about us two chicks can do it anybody can. We want to make a
field guilty you probably already have somebody in your life that does that for you. So check us out
more hip than hippie you can subscribe or find out more information by visiting www.morehip than hippie.com.
Thanks Adam. Sure girls you sure you don't want to have sex with each other on the podcast please
please kind of hung up please. Okay guess not oh you know what couple drawbacks here now that I'm laying
in the meadows of the downs one it's getting hot and the time right now is 1053 AM and it's really
heating up so I'm starting to perspire another drawback is and of course this is a drawback with
all laptops and computer screens very hard to see the screen with the wind maybe if I turn around
well I could face directly into the sun but then it's getting even hotter. Oh boy but the proof
is in the pudding we can actually do remote broadcast this way and it's all in there it's fucking great
I love it so we are in the final throws of getting ready for the public beta release of cast
blaster beta number 15 I think we'll do a beta number 16 which has a few more tweaks and
improvements that cast blaster mic was working on so far though I'm just totally delighted with the
results and so that will be a version that you will be able to download there will be an extended trial
period for you to try it out and and actually I believe if we think it's good enough we're going to
sell this version which will be a completely independent and you'll be able to use it with you know
basically any any way you want to to create your RSS feeds and any way you want to put your podcast
of course the version after that we'll have all of that built in automatically. She sent me
touching me I'm taking that feels good. She's the middle. We're driving from Florida home. She has her hand
down your pants I guess yes. Do you like trying to talk to the family because that'd be hot.
You know her hand but I don't want to stop I can't hold it back and then finally I'm
being in her hand. Do you remember like times were like close to getting caught but not like they
caught me off card like some of these coming down the steps and great that I'm not a little boy
18 and some cultures consider that being a man and I mean I'm in big going on finishing the race.
I'm like let's see if I will do it all and then you got to talk to me but only one hand is free.
Hi could you hear me a towel or not my towel I guess a shirt because I'm normal just hand it to me.
I didn't know the etiquette. So I say thank you could I rub your arm while you're doing it. I like that human
touch. I think the circle. You know I hadn't heard Keith in the girl yet I'd heard a lot about him
and after I heard this promo I immediately subscribed to the show very good I like it a lot
excellent excellent podcast. I'm not going to say something that just slipped my mind. Shoot I don't know
let me read another piece of mail here. This is from Keith Moreno. He says it's been a locker on the
daily source code for about six months. I've been using podcasts from my online tech classes and
started my own that I'm rolling out very soon. I'm trying to figure out the best format right now.
Podcasts and education provides another way to connect with your students. My students love him. Keith
says the last quarter the number one comment I got was how they enjoyed listening to my podcast. I've
now included them in a class. I just developed as a weekly commentary on the topics on a discussion.
I never see my students face to face so this provides a way for them to feel a part of the learning
community. This is great and I'm hopeful that well even with stuff like cast blastering and we
can make it easier for education to jump on this. This is just who man the possibilities are so
freaking endless when it comes to this stuff I'm excited about it. Oh I know what I was going to say
Michael Butler, the Rock and Roll Geek Show, Rock and Roll Geek.com. Now you know that Steve
leads from a serious satellite and I have been working on hooking him up with an interview with Joan
Jet which Joan is doing nothing absolutely nothing won't speak to anybody at the time being.
So we kept pushing and Michael kept pushing and well so we got Joan's manager for an interview
which was supposed to be like a 10 minute deal and is this Kenny Laguna who at one point actually
was my manager in the MTV days and Kenny is Kenny and his lovely wife, Merrill, there are
trip man they've been managing Joan for since I don't know 1979 or 1980 and the interview was absolutely
fantastic. Talking about the old days of rock and roll Kenny also played in Tommy James and the
Sean Dells you remember Moni Moni was a big hit before Billy Idol, read it of course.
He talks about the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and how it's kind of rigged. That's typical Kenny
you will enjoy that it's the most recent episode of the Rock and Roll Geek Show. It's a three
parter so make sure you catch it. Potset music now it's a speak of clay and she said on your
daily source code for Tuesday June 21st 2005.
It's a lot to go fast. I don't care as long as I have it here that's enough nothing more than
what she said.
All the time, I ask you to see a dead city
The sun, the night is gone, take a bus, I don't care which one is out of here
That's enough, nothing more would you know, that's it
She said, she said, we love you forever
All the time, all the time, all the time
All the time, all the time
She said, feed of clay on your daily source code
They're also podcasting as a band
Pretty well established actually, feed of clay is
And of course I'll put a link to their podcast
Inside in the show notes for today's daily source code
Something else really cool going on, Spike Lee is working on a new movie
Which will star big names this time, Denzel Washington and Jodie Foster
And he's doing pre-production in New York as we speak
And it looks like we're going to be making a podcast out of that
So look forward to that, and of course I'll be back tomorrow on your daily source code
So I hope the sound of the microphone didn't put you off too much
Again, I'm just talking to a pinhole in the lid of my computer
So it's pretty amazing what it's going on here
Everything you heard on today's podcast will be available with links in the show notes
A daily source code dot com
And a daily source code dot com is where you can also find the feed for this podcast
You can find the archives of older shows and of course the
The most recent show
Feedback more than welcome Adam and Curry dot com
And on a second one, you can see three or four times
I'm just looking at my numbers here to see which button they push the fire off
Comments welcome at www. Curry dot com
And oh yeah, of course all the submissions
Because we want to get your mashups and pod save music
And of course your podcast for the series show
So here's what you do if you want something played on the pod show on serious satellite radio
You got a promo or if you want to put your podcast in
Send it off to submit at podshow.com
For pod save tune, of course podsafe at podshow.com
And for mashups and men, they're really
Really really happening now
The mashups are cranking out all over the place
Mashup and podshow.com
We did a lot of years from the online show
And it was just nice
And I have some kind of warning message
What do I have to do?
Oh, I got a call somebody. Oh, perfect timing
Besides that, I'm sweating like a pig
So, time for me to go my friends
Thank you very much for subscribing
I'll be back tomorrow with the hump day edition of the daily source code
Bye bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear