Delta Sierra Charly 206 Bravo.
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It's the daily source code for July 11, 2005.
And this is Delta Sierra Charly 206 Bravo because I already recorded the show once.
And upon my usual check, turns out that I have a tech open, another audio editing program.
It was just too much for the MP3 code for an audio hijack pro.
Which means essentially it was skipping on what it was writing off to this.
And I think it had, you know, if there was one or two skips in it would be okay.
And I just got the casual email.
I was skipping every 20 or 30 seconds.
Really sucks. So now I got to keep my eye on it.
Because it does report if it's skipped.
I just didn't see it that time. Oh well.
It goes along with the other technical glitches of the morning. My cell phone has been blacklisted.
Which is always fun because you then get to talk to the virgin team.
A virgin mobile, oh yeah.
Thanks for holding on. One more moment.
We'll be connecting you to a member of our team shortly.
Well, shit. Anyway, when I find it, speak to my team member Garth. He was quite helpful.
And he found out that my phone had been blacklisted.
Which means it's been electronically denied receiving or making calls.
This is usually something that's invoked when your cell phone is lost or stolen.
In this case, it was probably hijacked because, according to Garth, there are many third parties who will take money from you to then put someone's phone on the blacklist.
The blacklist being a central database that all the telcos use.
So you can imagine there's lots of room for error there.
And if someone has your phone number, they can just, I guess, get it on that blacklist for a minor fee somewhere.
I'll put a link to more information about blacklisting in the show notes for today's podcast as usual.
Got some podcasts, music tunes on the way.
We have a backtrack podcast.
It's always fun, lieu of a hit test.
And a couple other things.
And of course this show is intended for material audiences only.
Is the mash up that Agro 1 made spending one of these nights with Kelly.
Wasn't long till we called you mine.
Yeah, yeah.
Since you've been wrong.
And now you'd ever hear me say,
I just have to make some new feel for you.
That's all you'd ever hear of me say.
But since you've been gone.
I can't breathe all the birds flying.
It's so good to know you, yeah.
Thanks to you, I can't.
What I want.
Since you've been gone.
How can I put it?
You put me on.
I even fell for the stupid love song.
Yeah, yeah.
Since you've been gone.
How can I never hear you say?
I just want to be with you.
You've never felt that way.
But since you've been gone.
I can't breathe all the birds flying.
It's so good to know you, yeah.
Thanks to you, now again.
I can't get what I want.
Since you've been gone.
How can I never hear you say?
I just have to make some new feel for you.
You've never felt that way.
But since you've been gone.
Since you've been gone.
I can't breathe all the birds flying.
It's so good to know you, yeah.
You've never felt that way.
But since you've been gone.
I can't breathe all the birds flying.
It's so good to know you, yeah.
You've never felt that way.
But since you've been gone.
Since you've been gone.
How can I never hear you say?
I just have to know you, yeah.
Since you've been gone.
Why don't you get whatever you want?
Okay it's official. Kelly Clarkson is now a member of the Eagles. God damn that was good. Patricia
was just in. She walked in and I cranked up the volume on the speakers for and she was like
my God. You don't even know where Don Henley starts and Kelly Clarkson ends is really fantastic.
Art dub, adub from mashuptown.com sent me that one brought to you by Agro. Of course the
Eagles and Kelly Clarkson mixed together in a mashup. What you hear in the background is the
cooling unit Patricia purchased for me. It's been it's been well we've had a great weekend.
Certainly something that everyone here could use in light of the London bombings.
Good weather always lifts your spirits a little bit and it's still amazing to me how incredibly
resilient the right word everyone's using the word vigilance but that's for moving forward but
the Londoners have just been you know so fuck you we're getting on with our lives you're not going
to bring us down about all this. One of my mom's friends Brenda New York she actually said wow and
she's been around long enough to know that the attitude is exactly the same that the Londoners
had during the Blitz Creek when the Germans were bombing London in the 40s only the cultural
makeup of London has changed significantly in the past 60 years 65 years 65 years yeah so
it kind of makes you wonder is it maybe something in the water you know so anyway so speaking of
water this thing that's in the background Patricia opted when when I was in the States for two weeks
so it was just a long time to be away from home we had a heat wave here and of course
near with the equipment in my studio slash bedroom slash office things really heat up here with
the sun shining directly on it so she's getting me shades those have been ordered and this
cooling unit unit isn't an air conditioner it's like a what is it a con a con there it goes nicely
with my senseo machine this con ver does it's and you pour water into it and the water circulates
in front of the fan and it gives you more cool air than you normally would with just a fan that's kind
of blowing the hot circulating the hotter around so it works I like it and and it's good for the
energy bill as well and let's see probably my shoulders still messed up we've deducted what or deduced
what what this is you know I'll tell you that story in a second because we got some other stuff
I got to get to this is Daniel from the My Life Bites podcast and you're listening to Adam Curry
on the daily source code hot Joe content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother
now this can only happen to a guy like me and only happen with a die like this
so may I say to each of you most gratefully and she shows each one of you a fist
this is my kind of dog match-wise Dean is my kind of dog match-wise Dean is
my kind of yeasty snatch you can't match her podcast and each time I think match-wise Dean is
making me think match-wise Dean is one die that reputantly constant life she's my kind of die
man how cool is that? hello my name is Simon and I'm a friend I heard this bit I did perform
that song you just heard I'm sorry I've just got this obsession with match-wise Dean
but I'd like to assure you that you weren't here anything like that on the slam idle podcast
which is the the podcast that I do that's a podcast that has features poetry performances
from all around the world in order for my obviously so but you definitely weren't here anything
like that crap sorry bye. I hadn't heard that but that came through openpodcast.org
and I was just thinking oh ma'am so jealous I wish I had people making up songs about my
podcast that's awesome it's from match-wise Dean yeastradio.com of course okay I was going to
talk about shoulder briefly because I have to go to the actually it was an email about this let me
see if I had this email here it is. Adam love this revolution do you have a t-shirt of the daily
source code would love to get one if you do no I don't we've talked about it and we might
do t-shirts if I had a fricking logo well I have I had to actually do have a logo so yeah
maybe we'll do t-shirts um I'm a physical therapist writes um David Brown and I do that in Jacksonville
Florida my patients are now requesting that I play the daily source code during my morning and afternoon
torture session so I listen to the Delta Sierra Charlie sometimes twice a day who knows maybe I'll
start my own podcast titled daily screams from the torture room yeah that's hot okay so that's how
I was going to talk about that was the bridge I was going to build to my my own physical therapy
which starts today at 530 at least I'm going to go over there and get myself checked out here's
what happened um we figured it out when I was flying in Portland we were doing like five days
four hours a day so it's a lot of intense flying and if you can experience pilot you know not a
low time fix we can pilot like myself then um you're a lot less tense obviously in the cockpit
now you use most of the work is done with your left arm most of the physical work that's we you know
even though it has two handles to it the the yoke or the steering wheelies you might call it you
usually um operate that with your left hand the right hand is always on the throttle or on the
controls or on the navigation there's a lot of instruments there the right hand utilizes or on the
left hand left hand knee of your passenger you know any of that stuff that pilots might have to use it
right arm for so um now the way you reduce the load on the yoke is with this you probably
see this if you ever seen a cockpit a big black wheel with little nubs on it so that's the trim
and with that you can basically do anything you know the you reduce the stick load that's the
foreign and back motion on the yoke uh and experience pilots of course that they're very commonly
kind of with the with the yoke between the thumb and the forefinger and everything's done with the
with the trim and of course I was much more tense and uh exerting sometimes even exerting
physical force without even have to because the plane was perfectly trimmed anyway and so that
probably you know I don't do anything with my left hand you know except pull back on the yoke once
no so the the next morning after I got my license I flew to Portland from Portland to Miami
and there was a stop over in Houston and I fell asleep I think on the first leg um with my head
on my my my palm of my hand bent backwards up on the rest and I remember on the arm rest I
remember waking up and going oh my arm is numb and so the result of all that is uh on my shoulder
blade or near my shoulder blades either tendon or muscle or god knows what it is I don't know if
it's inflamed or if it's been twisted but it you know it's basically um I think pinching nerves down
my left arm sometimes I feel tingling in my index finger and stuff so it sucks and at five
thirty today I will finally be looked at and see we can fix this I sure hope so maybe just bring along
some delta share a charlie huh right now though it's time to switch over to our man on the scene
he's following the hurricane in Florida it's Chris Perillo from Vancouver I'm watching TV now I'm
safe for the television I'm watching the coverage happened right now on CNN it seems to be on
channel let me verify this yes channel thirty three I'm close to the screen I can't tell exactly
what's happening there seems to be a lot of water on the screen not my television screen as I'm
sitting in a hotel room in Vancouver British Columbia which is far enough away from the storm
that we should be safe completely safe that I know of have seen no signs blowing around downtown
Vancouver right now uh Ponzi is in the bathroom she's in the bathroom clipping her fingernails
right now that I know all the fingernails are going directly into the trash can I've asked her to
be caught again I'm not sure she's wearing her cupcake shirt right now with her sweater hanging
over her shoulders I repeat her sweater is over her shoulders I'm close to the television screen
getting a little closer and this is very very dangerous especially for your eyeballs you've got to be
careful that your eyeballs don't touch the screen because your eyes will be damaged with flying
plastic might fly through the screen down from Florida I can see that the headline currently reads
Dennis makes landfall between Pensacola Beach and it looks like the very beach I'm not exactly
sure if that's the pronunciation maybe I can get a confirmation from the studio right now it's 425
Pacific time I'm sorry no I repeat it's actually 125 Pacific time this is in the afternoon hours
on Sunday afternoon I'm watching the crawl as it goes by there are horrible horrible things happening
signs flying all over the place Anderson Cooper's in directly in the line of this hurricane
putting his life in danger to let us know that signs are flying around they're standing in front of
the hotel and about to toss it back to dirty Sanchez in just a few minutes we don't know there
seems to be a lot of green now flying over the state of Florida a little bit of blue according to
the graphic is on the screen and then yellow right in the middle red yellow purple and if you're
in the pants of the red yellow and purple if you see this in the sky please hunker down take cover
you have to watch out for what's going to happen right now there's cat three we don't know
if they're going to be upgrading to cat six which of course is fully capable of gigabit ethernet
will keep reports you know streaming to you as soon as we find out again like this is a category three
at this point cat three with winds of 120 miles power you have to be careful slow down your
streams hunker down and I gotta go I gotta go you know I don't want to make light of the
situation in Florida but Chris Brillows point is so well made with this man where do they get these
everybody wants to be a fricking hero standing out in the in the street in the wind it's like god
ah they make it so incredibly hype you see how easy it is to do and see how you get drawn in I mean
it was long enough right it was like a two and a half minute bit there but it really drew you
when it's like oh my god what's going on purple stuff is floating over Florida hunker down for the green
stuff that's on your screen oh man hey I've been kind of collecting all of the comments and emails
and man I got a lot about iTunes and the seems we have three major areas that need to be worked on
and I know that the folks that I pulled listen to this podcast as well so I'm gonna see if I can
sum them up this is nothing that they probably don't know already but maybe there's some solutions
we can come up with because the amount of listeners that iTunes is driving is phenomenal unfortunately
we're reinventing a little bit of the wheel here and there which I think can be circumvented quite
easily and I know the community would be happy to jump in and help we just want to get it right
and we want to get working because we've kind of been through all of this once before you know certainly
in the past year or we've been kind of yeah figuring out how a directory should work figuring out
how a pod catcher an iPod or an aggregator should work and you know the the secret about
big companies is they usually have very small development teams and you know that doesn't mean
the teams any better or worse than a big one but you know there's only so much you can focus on
and there's a lot of work that goes into this stuff so the first thing is submitting your feed
to Apple so this can take up to three days now from what I understand because they're basically
creating a internal feed that works with the iTunes music store so this is a complicated one I
guess what's happening is they have to go out and scan all of these feeds you know hopefully
once an hour but it could be once every four hours it could be a pretty big process to do that
and to see if it's anything new and then translate that into their internal format now what happens
on the internet is shit breaks and you just don't get to certain feeds or maybe the time
out is a little bit too tight and it moves on and it comes back on the next scan to look at that
feed which means something you've updated could easily take four hours or longer before it's
taken care of and I'm sure there's all kinds of dead feed trackers in there and stuff so
you could get lost in the shuffle so that's kind of yeah I mean that's just something that
that has to be worked on you know I'm not sure there's there's an easy fix for that that's just
the nature of distributed computing then there is the issue of people not being able to be added
to the directory another thing that can take you know that can really take a couple days
mainly because it's a human process and that's something we learned with iPodr.org is it's
much easier to maintain a directory when you have people maintaining their own individual categories
and subcategories and are only responsible for that piece you know that really works well
and you know particularly for categorization and I think the way iTunes displays the results of
a search should could be different so instead of you know if I search for a daily source code
it'll pop up three times because it's listed under technology it's listed under audio blogs
which is actually the way it's listed an iPodr.org as well only perhaps you just bring up one icon
one subscribe link and and then say also listed in these categories and you could then you know
zap over those categories here's the here's the problem that's really hiding under the covers though
and this is something we do have with the distributed directory is when people add a feed
into the directory know their responsible for and let's say the feed updates and someone else adds
that to a different spot on the directory you now have two different addresses for the directory
maybe that's something that we could automate I guess let me just write that one down that's
something we could work on but that's so that's clearly going to be an issue with all directories
just maintaining you know or defeating link rot but that's kind of the problem we have with
the web anyway so I've got to figure that out there's also people not getting listed because they
don't have the appropriate explicit tag in their extensions to their RSS feed that's a mouthful
but I think everyone's working really hard now providing iTunes compatible feeds is funny
I think I mentioned it on the previous source code I said oh yeah you can you can just go over
podcast alley if you're in the directory there you have an iTunes feed and I couldn't find it but I
know I know it works so it's there somewhere and although we don't control any of the things I
don't control any of the things that Apple is doing but I have offered you know some of our services
to you know take the load off we already have some of the infrastructure we can you know we have
some of the distributed stuff that could make the directory a lot better but I do understand you know
this is something Apple is publishing and if you don't have the explicit tag in there or if they
missed it somehow you know they're not going to add you and then you you know look how many people
can be working on the directory to Apple you know it's only so many resources you can
put it on something like this so that's why I like the distributed model much better maybe there's
a way that you know we can just say well maybe podcast alley is a good solution for that
although we have to make some changes there as well I'm just ideating here for a second because
you don't want to be locked in anywhere so I think the solution there as you'd have to be able to
to register a domain name that would point to your iTunes feed something like that so you can
easily take it away with you if you wanted to okay I'll talk to Chris we'll make it so we'll try at least
this is your daily source code I'm Adam Curry I'll try to do this every single weekday
doesn't always work out that way but when we do well as always the unexpected you can experience
the following promo for the story of you daily is not appropriate for listeners under 18 or
those who are easily offended is not kidding hey this is your chance to turn it off or load some
Mario speedwagon or eating per cat in your player so I'm doing it right if you're three seconds
it's very an ensu horrible things are going to be coming out of your iPod so true or media player
one two three we warned you I haven't him hence him from distorted you daily if you haven't
been listening to the podcast here's which you missed this week I'll take your survey I'll
take it and I'll cram it up your ass like a puffy vagina either just honoring their history it's
like colonial Williamsburg except with more pussy Latin men gang banging you in the back alley
of a tall bell the detective went on to say that the man's wife was all like yeah give it to me
oh right there oh beautiful good self described pervert time high as a kite you know this can't
and well that woman's pussy is too puffy the idea that she was going to puke shit and piss
since a feeling of total freedom through her she opened her mouth wide and led along disgusting
string of dribble go down her chin and a sick and helpless kind of fashion how dare you
I have offended an outrage granny's got a bloody pussy she was talking about giving yourself an
enema and a bath tub puking and pissing all while all I'm finger blasting herself and you think
that's hot puffy and she got all like angry I mean she's like well you don't you don't want to
help your community and I said no I hate my community so sorry to burst your penis bubble there
I'm probably going to die as the thing she felt the brown water turned into violent
squirting diarrhea before subsiding to occasional spasms in her hole
hardship glad you listen to this bromo puffy pussy's an exploding diarrhea that's that
started new difference it's 10 minutes of your life you'll never get back come for the news of the
weird stay for the audio pornography what it's the distorted view show most of our
high spots were coming to us now by TV series central but not this one series 148 Adam Curry's
hot show experience the unexpected tell the world tell this to everybody forever they are
through the central 148 I'm a little confused about all this anime fire about drug laws
and holy walls and people freaking out over what they want to freak about
oh so tired there's nothing on my radio some little girl who laughs and swing me
low she tried to say how she wants to dance for me I sometimes wonder what they gave to be there
the trouble people you came from know I won't be where you're being
I don't forget about all the people you'll have been to your head
did I never fall did this is election come on anything at all did video I'll mix
my tricks it caught up in a bag of tricks and that's what we want to hear
hope we won't find our next year
set it by their religion they at all
trouble people you came from know I won't be where you're being
I don't forget about all the people you'll have been to your head
I'll just take the heat for you