The Daily Source Code Thursday, January 20, 2005.
Yes, Mr. Corey. Yes, this is ten from Starbucks on the manager here, sir. And I'm calling
to apologize, this is somewhat embarrassing. So the actions of one of our former, and I do
emphasize former assistant managers. Apparently, this person who I will remain
nameless had a mate at BT. And the two of them conspired to interfere with your efforts
to get broadband at your home. So according to my notes here, they were misguided to say
the least in their efforts to prolong the exposure our store was getting on your show.
I'm not quite sure what that means, but that's what it says here. In any case, I do
apologize and I'd love to offer you three Starbucks for the next year, but this is England
and I'm afraid the best I can do is offer you my sincere apologies. So I hope you all
accept them. And now I'm afraid I've got to get on the phone with BT because apparently
there's several homes on your street that are now receiving broadband who never ordered
them. So have a good day, sir, and cheers.
I'm proud of you casting with Adam Curry.
Hey everybody, it's the source code for Thursday. Thursday, January 20, 2005, coming to you
from the Ocaro hotel. In Amsterdam, boy, this is maybe a little bit funky. So we're in
the Laughalier microphone, so I cut down on the baggage rate on the plane.
It's been a weird day. It's really got some interesting news on telephone calls today.
I've kind of been enjoying this room that I scored completely through the weblog.
Watch some of the inauguration, like I could watch anything else on television.
And yeah, just chilled out a little bit. Got a little re-energized.
Okay, so I actually didn't start to record. I did a little bit of... I tried to do some
sound seeing recording this morning, but it just didn't work out. It was a real hassle
because I think at first I thought, it's actually really easy to put the receiver,
while it's receiver in my bag along with the I River recording everything.
But then I thought, really, when it comes to the sound seeing stuff, I want to be able to hear exactly
what it is that you're going to hear, because it's totally different that you're ears
here without listening, listening all the way through the recording device.
So yeah, and that would mean that I'd have to have all this stuff with me and have to take
it off going through security, and I just decided to ask for it. I don't know how to do that.
But maybe another time, another flight. It was another un-eventful, easy jet experience.
Although there's always that, I don't know where it is. Maybe the, well, you know,
actually they're just a very well-run airline, I guess. And at the very last minute,
I was thinking like, wow, it's 10 o'clock, 10, 10, 10, 10, 10, 15.
Maybe they should change the, you know, weight for gate announcement to either delayed
or to give us the gate. And then all of a sudden, it just, you know, does pop up,
and then it's real efficient, boom, you're on board.
Loved it again, completely. And, you know, that whole thing, you know, you throw out
your own trash and they come through the aisles with the trash bags.
And, you know, so even with your fellow passengers, like, hey, can I borrow your newspaper,
a guy next to me said, yeah, sure, go ahead. You know, here's the pieces that I've already read.
And then he said, yeah, the, some candy, whatever, you know, can I offer you some?
It looks like you're kind of like, you're all buddies, you know, on easy jet.
Totally digging that. So, what's it? Well, of course, I have a lot of stuff written
down and stuff in, in my outline for show notes that we can do today.
I want to say a little bit about this, about this hotel room.
First of all, what happened is, I posted on my weblog as I've been doing recently,
you know, who knows a decent hotel room in X, X being the place
that I'm going to travel that has good Wi-Fi.
And so far, the web is always steered me in the right direction, both for the room
and for the connectivity. And through this blog post, the PR manager for the
Akura Hotel in Amsterdam, which is, it's beautiful hotel. I mean, I've been here many times.
There were actually, I don't think I've actually, oh, yeah, no, Patricia and I actually stayed here
when we had our first night together. Oh, yeah, that's right, baby.
And so they rebuilt a number of floors and the 22nd floors, the first one that's done.
These are junior sweets. And no one has ever slept in them before.
In fact, there's no one else on the entire floor, which is kind of creepy at the same time.
But they really did this right. I mean, so I got an incredible deal on this.
I'm not, not free, but I got a great deal.
This is exactly the kind of room you want if you're away from home.
And you need your kind of like your office space, you need to really comfortable bed, you want to be.
And this is, it's also a guy room, you know, it's got this wood paneling.
It's totally, that's actually, that's something I just noticed.
This is a very much a guy interior, not a chick room at all.
But they got the nice, the tulips, very nice touch there.
And it's very cute. But you know, then they've got the massive plasma screen flat screen, which, you know, I have a flat screen company.
But I'm definitely not a 16 by 9 guy, which, you know, is the extended stretched out screen.
Because many of the broadcasts that I watch are 4 by 3, which is the regular television screen size.
And then these plasma screens, they stretch it out.
And I don't like it. I don't like seeing down. I want to see what people really look like. It's weird to look at that.
So then if you switch it to 4 by 3, then of course you have these black banners on the side either side of the screen.
So anyway, I'm not going to mess with the settings. It's fine.
And there's also, I thought it was an LCD, but it is a little mini plasma that's in the bathroom as well. It's cool.
And the service is great. And I'm able to crack a window open. It's really windy. It's been very windy in Europe.
It's been windy in the back in the UK, which I was telling me today.
I got a great view of the entire city. That's really nice. It was foggier earlier on.
So this is, yes, this is like the ultimate dorm room. You know, it couldn't be any better.
So I'm totally enjoying that.
How to meeting up with the bunker today with Crystal my PA assistant, well she's one of PA.
She really does a lot of crap.
Take care of a lot of shit.
And see, well, there's a phone call that I got, which I want to talk about later on.
First, let's just give you a little quick little sound seeing two or of the room.
Because I hold on.
There we go.
So I'm going to go with the window here for a second.
If you can hear the wind holling.
It's quite a down a little bit.
So this is the bed.
And walking past the desk into the hallway.
This is the entrance hallway.
Now I'm walking into the bathroom.
And you can hear the little flat.
It was a matchline, Philips, matchline, flat TV.
It's a, I don't know if I made it.
There's LCD.
It's definitely not plastic.
Or it is plastic.
Yeah, there's LCD.
Cute though.
I have snook her all.
Yeah, it's really nice.
It might actually take a bath.
Now what they also did very well in this room is, the plasma is, and it's a very,
it is a guy room.
It was totally business room.
So the first channel when you boot up the plasma screen is an info channel for the hotel.
The next channel is CNN.
Smart.
That's what everyone wants right when you walk in.
Next one is CNBC.
The Sally Crochet City Group CFO.
She's kind of cute.
Maria Bartaromo.
Have you ever seen her?
On CNBC.
She's cute.
Hmm.
Talk numbers to me, baby.
But now she looks all like flat and pudgy.
Because of the plasma.
Hmm, okay.
So the next one is Sky News.
Then it's the hell this is.
This is BBC.
They probably got a lot of English people staying here.
It makes sense.
They're at right.
So here's BBC 2.
Okay.
Then BBC World.
Now of course the BBC has their 16 by nine shit all straightened out.
So the screen immediately went to the right proportion.
That's a big problem with this stuff.
These guys saving money.
Most of the commercial stations don't do it just because it's expensive to install that shit.
You know, the encoders or whatever the hell it is.
Okay.
So now this is where they fucked up.
So I got like four empty channels.
Then we hit the local commercial RTL RTL 5,
SPS6, our old station.
Here's Jamie Oliver's that's RTL or net 5.
Then we go to German.
The German net works.
This is Spanish.
TV is Spanish.
Oh, then of course we have an Asian channel.
I don't know.
It's got like 15 different subtitles.
Okay.
TV 5.
That's French.
Right.
We know Italian.
Discovery channel.
We're like no audio.
Then we got audio.
Okay.
Lane.
Then we have, what's this?
Okay.
Some kind of info channel.
Then we have MTV.
Not playing music videos, of course.
The music factory.
Then there's the Snooker game, Euro Sport.
Then there's Bloomberg.
Bloomberg's kind of cool.
It's kind of like a weblog with a video blog in it.
Oops.
Just lost our host.
I was like, Bloomberg TV is kind of interesting to watch.
Maybe a movie channel.
What is this?
Oh, porn.
Yep.
Yeah, baby.
Oh, cool.
Okay.
I'm not going to tell you what I'm seeing.
Do you have your own little fantasy there?
This is a good sound seeing experience.
Alright. Let's see if there's more.
Oh, there's another one.
Oh, hold on.
You got to get some better sound here.
Yeah.
It's cool. I don't have to pay for it.
See, these guys are smart.
Just give that shit away exactly.
There's more channels.
Alright.
This is the boring part of the porn movie.
Now it looks like that was it for porn.
What?
Back to porn?
Okay.
We'll back up.
Let's back up to the first one.
No.
I want to go back.
How'd that cost you?
Okay.
Alright, that's enough of that.
You've had just about enough.
Okay.
Right.
Good.
Well, I've wasted about 14 minutes of your time so far.
Let's have someone else help us out with some
stuff.
Let me see.
What was this?
Oh, I think.
Yeah.
If this is what I think it is, then.
Yep.
The security is planned for the balls in the parade.
Characters will be positioned by presidential motorcade when George Bush is
sworn in for his second tour.
That is told just like the first says Michael Moore.
Brad and Jen may not divorce.
Just have a trial separation.
Brad still wears his wedding ring.
That could be another care of the invocation.
Unless Brad did have an affair with Angelina.
That would remove the but they were so in love with Tina.
A 67 year old woman had a baby.
The oldest mother in his story.
She took fertility pills for nine years.
They be she lied about her age of his own.
Lazy 63.
The inauguration will go ahead to spline plan protests against the Warren Iraq and the cost
of wanting and dining Bush's guests.
Not one damn dime will be spend on January 20th.
A professor's money.
There knows maybe money.
But they won't buy cleanest.
Whether the weather is cold or sunny.
Stay tuned for late breaking.
That's the tap dancing.
Yeah, baby.
Love to hear that.
The tap dancing podcast news.
I'm sure there's going to be a new one after the inauguration today.
So I'll try to get that on tomorrow's daily source code.
Or you can pick it up on open podcast.
It doesn't ever come through with ID three tags identified.
So you're going to like catch it and search through all that stuff.
Let me see.
It's like late for me here.
It's 9.38 p.m.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's UK time.
So here it's 10.38.
And I'm just kind of tired.
You know, I had room service.
It's kind of weird.
It's hotel rooms.
I'm not a big hotel room fan.
So it is nice.
You know, I had this hotel room.
Because I'll trick it out.
But in essence, it's like,
I like having people around.
And there's no one here.
And I had a lonely dinner all by myself.
I had a steak sandwich.
Let me just remove the porn for a moment.
That's a little bit distracting.
Just a little bit.
So I don't know how much of the following story I've ever told.
But I'm not going to go into it too in depth.
A number of years ago,
I had a partner.
His name,
a Simon Cavendish.
Or so we thought his name was.
And I'd known him for a number of years.
And he had made some money.
And with an ISP that he sold.
And, you know, I'd made some money with my company.
And I sold.
And, you know, we'd always wanted to work together.
And so we created a number of companies,
including an aviation company.
And, you know, we had a lot of interest.
Writing on, you know, some trust.
And all of a sudden one day he freaked out.
And it was like, you know, I don't have any money anymore.
Okay.
So he's broke.
That's one thing to deal with.
But my name isn't Simon.
It's, you know, it was irrelevant.
I've been wanted by the Scotland yard.
He was a British guy.
You know, I've done jail time for Grand Theft Auto.
And manufacturing MDMA in a whole country graph.
And he sent this email to everybody.
You know, all employees, bankers, financial contacts,
the aviation industry.
So that pretty much destroyed a lot of shit.
And I'm still dealing with a lot of throwback from that.
And so, of course, we were in all kinds of legal hassle.
It was all bullshit.
I mean, he was, it was bullshit.
But anyway, took out a call today.
He died.
Motherfucker died.
In Cambodia, where he was hiding,
like God dammit, you motherfucker.
You couldn't even, you know, can't finish anything,
including this, you know.
So it was funny because I got the call and I was like, you know,
I've gotten the someone died call before,
but I didn't have any kind of shock reaction with this.
I was just like, fucker.
So, and of course, then I felt a little different later on.
You know, you go, it's weird.
It's just weird.
That's something you don't expect.
And the weird thing is, he has a claim against me,
which continues because he sold that claim to some fucking lawyer.
He's a weird ass country man.
So the dead guy is still suing me,
and though he has no leg to stand on literally.
Some other guy should, should the, should they win a suit?
Which won't happen.
Would actually get the dead guy's money.
Is that a fucked up world?
Anyway, I've written that off, fuck it.
So tomorrow I'm going to go up to Grandmaster View.
That'll be good.
Hang out with some of the guys.
You know, hard-working.
That's a tough business.
This flat screen business is telling you.
Got this fucking podcast.
Just telling you that, whether they're no good.
And let's see.
Let's play another promo here.
This is one of my favorite podcasts.
I really like this one a lot.
So everybody else.
This is Richard Smith from yesterday at Radio Ball.
And we have moved to our brand new web address on the internet.
You can reach us at www.rjs.com.
That's www.rjs.com.
Tune in for some great old-time radio.
Gotta tell you, I've really gotten my,
now that the broadband is back and cranked.
I've been able to listen to so much more.
I feel so good.
And of course, I'm glad that this hotel has excellent
connectivity as well.
Just so much to listen to and there's so much coming
through on audio.weblogs.com.
And even email goes so much faster,
although I'm still kind of swamp with that shit.
Oh, man.
I finally caught up on Madge Weinstein podcast.
Oh, man. I love it so much.
When it's Madge Weinstein and it's not scripted,
you know, this guy is great.
What was that?
Someone in the hallway?
I'm going to try and call Madge Slash Richard
around midnight Amsterdam time.
I think, yeah, right.
That's the only time that we can really connect.
So, because I've just been, I've been dying.
Some of this stuff.
I mean, the quote over the week definitely was
Madge Weinstein saying,
Gentlody and some crowning.
That was just too much.
Again, I'm kind of sick.
And I've been totally digging using these,
or playing the podcast on my eye river,
which is getting tremendous mileage to one double-a battery.
Storage is sufficient.
In fact, I kind of because I've set it up so that
it can't go over like a gigabyte,
which is exactly what I have,
and it works perfectly.
It really does.
And I've been talking about the eye river.
I've got an email from Michael Ellsdiffer,
who says that there's the rock-box,
rock-box project,
which is at rock-box.org,
ROCKBOCK.org.
Of course, find this in the production show notes
for today's podcast.
And they are actually doing some interesting stuff,
hacking the firmware.
I think what I've seen is that essentially,
they've created an open-source version of firmware
that will let you play back and record.
It's fucked up.
We'll have to recreate the wheel here,
because the playback and record that I river already
does is great.
Just like to have a couple of different functions,
and have a few other things hacked in there.
And I'm seeing more and more people
figuring out how to do bookmarking,
and then Doug K is put up some script that I've heard about,
which seems complicated for me to put anywhere
as a PHP script or whatever.
But you can actually point to a piece of an MP3 file.
I haven't tried it out, but apparently it works.
And the eye river also,
if you turn it off or it goes off or powers down,
it power back up,
it remembers the spot that you were at,
and it stays right there,
which I'm sure has something to do with it being flash-based,
instead of a hard disk.
And if you notice at the beginning of the show,
and now everyone's kind of doing this new show tags.
This was something that I don't know who started this.
It was when the Apple shuffle came out,
which of course has no screen,
you don't know which podcasts you're listening to.
So if you have more than one daily source code on your iPod shuffle,
then you can't always tell from how it starts off,
which show it is.
So I'm doing these show tags.
I'm hearing Don and Drew do them.
And Don and Drew, if you haven't heard their episode
where they received a shuffle from one of their listeners,
they got a great audience.
So you got great fucking listeners sent,
sent them straight from the Apple store,
an iPod shuffle,
and they reviewed it.
And these were the first people that I've heard
talk about who actually used it and played with it,
and turned it around,
and Don tried to threaten to turn it into a barret
for a hair.
But it sounds like a pretty decent machine actually.
And that is, I think, the verdict that Don and Drew gave
on the iPod shuffle is it's okay.
It's a good little box for the money.
And it also remembers where you left off
in a podcast.
That was definitely something that was worth mentioning.
So that's a coffee,
which is cold by now,
but I need to get something running through my veins.
Because, of course, you know,
the minute I hit Amsterdam,
taxi Eric who picking up he always has,
has something to smoke ready to go.
So if I don't have meetings,
which I suppose I have a meeting,
but I got canceled,
and then so I just went to do all the admin stuff
with Crystal,
and then came over to the hotel on the afternoon.
So, yeah, I've baked it up a bit.
That's Amsterdam for you.
From Amsterdam, let's go over to London.
Email from Chris,
as he just started listening to the Daily Source Coden
as iPod,
bloody fantastic and weirdly addictive.
Yeah, you'll get over it.
Anyway, it seems that other people send you funny stuff
for the show you may have heard this already.
So, Bennett, if not, Bennett,
throw it toss it in the bin.
If not, if not enjoy,
not sure who did it.
It made sense to me,
but if you ever use the tubes,
I'm sure you have, it's bloody hilarious.
This is about the tube,
is the subway in London.
It's titled London Underground,
and it's from Adaption.
Some people might like to get a train to work,
or drive in,
and have been over a mug.
Some guys like to travel in my bus,
but I can't be bothered with a phone.
But the bus today,
I gotta take my bike,
because once again,
the tubes aren't strike.
The greedy bus,
it's one extra pay.
The sitting on their asshole day.
Even though they're in 30k,
so I'm standing here in the pouring rain.
Where the fuck's my fucking train?
London Underground.
They're all lazy,
fucking useless,
come to London Underground.
They're all greedy,
can't so want to shoot them all with a rifle.
Oh, by the way, this is not safe for work.
London Underground.
They're all lazy,
fucking useless,
come to London Underground.
They're all greedy,
can't so want to shoot them all with a rifle.
London Underground.
The flaws are sticky,
and the seats are damp.
Every platform has a fucking tramp,
but the divers get the day off,
when,
where we'll wait for,
working in London Underground.
While we're awake,
London Underground.
Take your voice to cut
and shove it up your asshole.
Oh man.
London Underground.
What was that?
That was really good.
I quite like that.
Adaption.
Thank you very much for sending that in.
And please, if you've got
tunes, podsafe music,
audio comments,
let me know in the comments.
I'm going to show you
some of the things I've got to do
in London Underground.
I've got some,
now I'm getting some cool ead Gmail
addresses that I'm going to be able to use
pretty soon.
I'm working on the sound seeing stuff.
I haven't quite figured out how I want to do
or how we can work,
you know, work this together,
or maybe just become a human aggregator
and just provide an RSS feed of,
you know, cool sound seeing podcas.
Because I've received so many,
you know,
I do want there to be a place
where you can find it.
So maybe we make that a separate feed.
In fact,
that's exactly what I'm going to do.
Maybe I'll even do that tonight.
So,
okay,
we'll definitely just write that down.
Hold on.
If I don't write it down,
RSS feed or
sound seeing.
And I'm not going to do a website.
I'm just going to do an RSS feed.
Right.
And the notes for it will be in the description field.
Make it just real, real simple for everybody.
If you're new to the daily source code,
and by the way,
you know,
I've gotten into the habit now
if someone said me email
that I were a corresponding about the show
and you know,
whereas in
back in the day,
when I was doing radio,
you'd say,
hey,
what do you keep listening?
Well, you'll think,
hey,
now I'm like,
stay subscribed,
really?
Because that's really what it is.
Keep in people subscribe.
Interesting word,
by the way,
subscriber.
Subscribers are a big measure
of a lot of internet companies.
Yahoo is measured by subscribers.
And subscribers don't,
hotmail subscribers,
you know,
MSN,
messenger,
God.
You know,
it's interesting,
is that messenger,
I think everyone has a messenger account,
everyone I know,
and it's like,
it must still be the
raining,
instant message client.
I even have,
you know,
someone wants to,
I don't use it,
but if someone wants to,
I can certainly fire it up.
And it does keep all of your contacts
in its accounts.
So whenever you,
I've seen people log back in
after two years,
and all of a sudden,
they've been re-acquainted with all
their old buddies from work,
whenever they last used that MSN accounts,
they've been really interesting,
pretty damn interesting stuff.
But,
so those of you who have just joined
the source code of start listening,
or maybe you started podcasting,
one thing we talk about here,
a lot on the show is,
is Cowbell.
Morning, Adam.
This is Tunnel 2,
from the LSN podcast,
over at,
blog,
hashtag,
smartman.
And,
well,
I'm not going to talk about that,
now,
basically,
what I'm going to,
So,
is this Stigginson,
yes,
the Bruce Dickinson,
is a TV show,
an L4 Discovery channel,
its called Flying Heavy Metal,
its on a Wednesday,
is Wednesdays and it's Wednesday.
So it's on on Wednesday,
9 o'clock from 9 o'clock from 9 o'clock,
about topic of planes,
jet engines,
and the like,
today,
you start at the 707,
or
kind of remember the first thing is,
But that is totally cool.
Bruce Dickinson of Iron Maiden is doing a show about planes and jet engines and cool
shit like that.
So, I'm going to see if I can record that.
I guess this is from the UK, I mean, okay, so who is Bruce Dickinson of Bruce Dickinson
of course is from the Skit from Saturday Night Live with Will Ferrell and Christopher
Walken, which is the Skit by itself is great in the videos floating out there, I think
of linked to it before on the source code.
But what I love even more is the original More Cowbell, don't fear the reaper, the
Coventry mix and it was recent to me, I've had it before because that was the first time
I was introduced to the whole Cowbell concept, Chris Copeland sent it to me and I just got
to play it for you right now because even if you've heard it a thousand times, you just
can't get enough of fucking Cowbell.
Don't fear the reaper, take one, roll, run, one, two, three, four.
You sure that was sounding okay?
I've been honest!
Fellars, sounding great..
I could use the little more calmer, I could use the little more calmer, I got to have
more calmer, I got to have more calmer, I could use the little more calmer, we're going
to want that calmer, I got to have more calmer, I got to use the little more calmer,
I got to have more calmer, I got to have more calmer, I got to have more calmer,
I got to have more calmer, I got to have more calmer, I got to have more calmer, I got to have
more calmer, I got to have more calmer, I got to have more calmer, I got to have a
The last time I checked, we don't have a whole lot of songs to teach you the Caldas.
I guess I have more Caldas.
Yes, what?
I got a fever.
And the only person who's more Caldas.
Oh, man.
That is just so legendary.
I love it so much.
Excellent.
Great to hear that again.
I am just totally wiped out.
I've got to tell you.
I'm really, really tired.
I'm just going to turn the big fat ass plasma towards the bed.
Hop in.
I'm going to cruise through the channels a little bit.
Get some sleep.
I'm big picked up tomorrow at 11.
And I don't know.
Everything that kind of messed up on my first appointment got canceled today.
And then the weather has been so shitty that even though it would be nice to do a
sound seeing tour of parts of Amsterdam, even in bad weather, the wind is just too strong.
Even the wind screen I have on this lovely or mic would just wouldn't cut it.
I know it wouldn't work.
So we'll see how it is tomorrow.
Maybe we can do something because we're getting towards the weekend.
And we're going to kind of slow the mood down just a little bit.
But wait first, let's do some of this.
This is always fun to be a trivia before we close out the show.
Hello everyone and welcome to mostly trivial.
I'm your host Brian Pippa.
Today's category is one hit wonders.
In 1982, what band had a number one hit with the song, Come On Ileens?
For bonus points, here's a question only the band members, Dick Clark and Adam Curry will know.
What number one song did come on Ileens knock off the top spot?
Okay, Dexie's midnight runners.
Come on Ileens.
I guess I'm stuck.
I'm no Dick Clark.
The answer is Dexie's midnight runners.
Ileens was a girl that songwriter and band member Kevin Rollen grew up with.
I just loved that song.
I mean, come on, let's be honest.
First of all, remember the video for that and they were wearing like these,
they were these whacked out guys from down under who actually, I think they look kind of,
they had a good vibe going on, but the thing that was weird was the, you know,
Mr. Greengene's suspender pants, you know, the overalls.
That sucked.
That looked stupid and lame.
I hated that.
And the whole thing about that song was it was like, come on Ileens, right?
You're like, you know, come on, come on.
Everyone knows it.
That's why that song became a hit to start off with.
It got the attention because it had that hook in it, you know, it's like everyone
to come on Ileens.
We're all singing it, you know, come on Ileens.
And we're laughing and we're smiling.
Our parents are going, oh, the kids have a nice little song with the
Congolung to their relationship became romantic when the pair was 13.
The band.
Ooh.
I'm boy.
This name was inspired by the infediment drug Dexie drink.
Okay, that I did not know.
You said, you got me on that.
Now, about who who was bumped off the top spot.
Who did that?
What was the question?
Who were they bumped off?
And the song knocked off the number one spot.
The song knocked off the number one spot.
Gosh.
Here the wind.
Yeah, now's really picking up.
All right, I give up.
Michael Jackson.
Oh, Billy Jean.
Yeah, of course.
You should ask him any more.
Can you found it songfacts.com?
To suggest a trivia question, leave me feedback.
Comments.
Questions?
Is it mostly trivial.com?
Thanks for listening.
So before I leave you for today and we're almost at the perfect weight.
Almost 40 minutes.
I've been privy to a couple of screenshots of the new iPod or lemon version.
And here there's also a new iPod or X version coming out.
I haven't seen anything from that yet.
But stuff's looking really good.
And there's some great features.
And I can't wait to try them out.
In fact, I'm also buying a Windows machine for a number of...
I don't know if I told you about this.
But one is to get the Skype phone for Patricia.
And also, I want to try out some of these Windows iPodters because, you know, shoot.
And I'm still in the minority here.
And I'm really not seeing a lot of progress.
And a lot of the stuff that we need to make podcasting really fucking simple.
You know, we've seen some interesting tools.
I haven't had an update on Maccast Live.
I really like that.
And I really want to try that out.
But, you know, go to have a Windows machine.
And I guess I got to figure out.net.
I guess I just kind of installed that like Java or whatever.
So that should be too hard.
But I'm definitely going to get a Windows machine.
Because I feel like I'm not totally living in the world where a lot of people are.
And we still got to figure out, you know, how to make it easier to just create a podcast.
Including your podcast feed and everything just kind of work.
So I've been thinking about that.
So I'm thinking about you, y'all.
You know, that's just the love I'm saying.
I'm excited.
I'm so excited.
So I'm so excited.
Oh, yeah.
For the Thursday, January 20th, and it was a fun hangin' out with you for a couple of minutes here tonight.
Okay, hope you had a good time.
Tomorrow, I'll figure something fun to do.
We'll come up with some shit that we get into.
Right now, I just got to go to bed at this time.
Actually, I'm gonna see if I can get an earlier flight back to our night.
Maybe I'll figure out a way to record that.
They will put the microphone through the X-ray machine for our time.
And once I'm through that, then I pretty much can just go on the plane with a transmitter, right?
I know it doesn't interfere with any of the antibiotics because we've tried that in all kinds of airplanes.
I guess.
Alright, feedback was np3 feedback at gmail.com.
And out of the Prairie.com, I just want to send out an email.
And of course, the weblog is www.prairie.com.
I'll see you tomorrow for the thank god it's Friday edition of the Daily Source Go.
Bye-bye.