Transmidders, we don't need no stinkin' transmitters.
Oh god, we're casting with Adam Curry.
Hey, finally, a source code.
It still exists.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
Coming to you from Curry Cottage.
Yeah, I got lots to talk about because we are still not connected.
But we don't need no stinkin' transmitters.
We got the podcast.
That's right.
Your source code for Thursday, January 13th, 2000.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Whoah, boy.
My goodness.
That's all you.
It's been quite a few days.
Last time we spoke was Monday, which was was it.
That was the temp.
That was the last podcast from South Beach in Florida.
Since then, I have been, well, pretty much in transit.
My back just aches from sitting on airplanes, sitting in cars,
and doing anything with actually exercise.
And of course, it's a throwback to the motorcycle accident.
And you've got to exercise that shit.
You know what I'm saying?
No matter what, 40 minutes for you on the source code.
Let me see, what is it?
I'm trying to think what's best to start off with.
Well, maybe I just tell you a little bit about the trip
where I've been, why I've not actually been able to record a source code.
I got to tell you that I actually did have a chance doing that yesterday.
And the car as I post on curie dot com with taxi Eric,
as I was going from Amsterdam to Antwerp to close on the sale of the castle.
But I was just so tired.
I've been sleeping.
I'm like a super model now.
You know, not eating.
Sleeping everywhere I can.
Every limo.
Well, shoot.
I forgot.
I don't have any limo.
That's overrated.
Okay.
So left Monday after winging by the apple store to pick up an ice skin for Christina's iPod Mini,
because apparently they're all sold out here in the area.
And I didn't know there was an apple store in the area in the Gilbert area.
And then went off to the to the airport.
Of course, my flight was delayed.
But what was cool is that I guess that's this is probably the perfect time.
Maybe here's the secret to British airways.
If you want to get an upgrade.
First of all, you've got to travel at the right time of year, which around Christmas
time with a winter time to Miami is clearly a very desirable time to fly.
The tickets.
I got the world traveler, which is like economy, but economy plus so that if you want to, you can
change your ticket.
Which I thought might, you know, could actually be one of the possibilities being in
South Beach and the meetings we were having.
There was a possibility maybe we'd go up to New York or maybe I'd go directly back
to Antwerp, which of course didn't work out that way.
I had to go a day later, which screwed it up.
So anyway, what you want to do is you want to have that world traveler so that you are
the first in line before the real economy tickets.
If there's an upgrade possibility.
And combined with the fact that it's in the winter time and everyone wants to fly
to Miami or it's flying back or it's traveling to and from Miami.
They're overselling the economy seats.
So if you were calling on the way over, I got upgraded to first class on the way back.
I got upgraded to business class or club as they call it on British Air.
And that means that you do get a sleeper seat, which is not quite this.
It used to be different.
I remember the first class sleeper seats and you get like a little mattress.
They put down for you and they put sheets in and they folded back and you get
little pajamas.
This is when they had, I don't know if you care about this shit.
But it was interesting.
They had a for a while.
This great offer.
You could fly with the Concord from London to New York and return first class on the sleeper
seat on the 747, which is the overnight flight.
For a total of, I think, if I was, this was back in the, so this was 90.
Most of this was 90.
No, this was 2000.
Maybe.
Well, before they took the Concord out, maybe it was a little bit before that.
But it was no more than like, I think it was $4,000.
And of course, this is pretty all the new pricing and all these wonderful airport taxes.
Please don't, don't think it's a fucking tax from the government.
Okay.
It's just a way of airlines sucking more money out of you and pretending it's something
due to the government by calling it a tax, which it's not.
It's just landing fees and more costs that they're writing off as a tax.
That's what they're telling you.
Oh, yeah, sure.
They have to pay the airport of fee.
I mean, that's always been that way.
You always have to pay the airport of fee per passenger or per weight of the plane.
If I land with a rinketing plane, I also have to pay a fee.
But now they're basically just passing it onto you and calling it a tax.
Anyway, so don't get me started again on that.
But the, so it's not comparable to what it used to be.
But still, it was nice to lay down almost completely vertical.
And I almost fit entirely between the footrest and the headrest.
So it was better than nothing.
But arrive needless to say a little bit, you know, broken.
I am 517 after all.
And there was no lovely little, what do you call it?
Mattress to lay on.
And of course, you know, it's an overnight flight.
This is the jet lag flight, right?
So I got home and there's all kinds of crap going on with the, with the closing of the house,
which was the next day and Antwerp and there was like a taxation issue.
I mean, you don't want to come home after that flight and have to talk taxation issues.
And then of course, as it sold, then Christina's horse princess or pony actually,
it has to be brought over.
So that's this Friday.
And so just all kinds of things to coordinate.
My god.
What horrible things to have to coordinate.
I'm not really complaining.
I'm just letting me in my life.
Okay.
And then the next day, I was up early to go to Antwerp.
And the only choices I had were drive two hours almost to London City,
which has a direct flight on the VLM Airlines to Antwerp.
Or go to Gatwick.
Actually, yeah, go to Gatwick.
And then I had taxi Eric drive me down, which is probably about an hour and 15 minutes.
And of course, an hour and 15 minutes back.
And I was able to see a couple other people on the way, such as my friend's purple rain in Brida.
Remember I've spoken about them, my Moroccan friend.
And I wanted to talk a little bit about actually about easy jet.
But first, oh yes.
Of course, we've got some cadence for you.
And I apologize in advance.
I have not been very good with my show notes.
I had kept this one because I knew that I wanted to play it.
But not quite sure where I got it from.
It's called testicular fortitude.
Enjoy.
45 minutes or 45 seconds of cadence.
Just good enough.
Well, I support out.
The testicular fortitude and other cadence on the daily source code, apologies.
I just don't know where it came from.
And of course, the title of that reminds me of the my pods forecast, which I played a couple of.
Well, maybe a week and a half ago.
It's the podcaster that does stock picks and most recently lottery numbers.
By consulting his testicles.
Shoot man.
I got to find that.
It's coming through on openpodcast.org.
But I think if you go to my podsforcast.com.
And actually, what's most amazing is the math that he uses behind coming up with the yes,
no path to finding out the path to choosing numbers.
Please listen to that.
It will be well worth the time.
So about easy jet.
I never actually flown on easy jet.
And this is a very short hop to go from London to Amsterdam.
It's about, I can totally guess you really know flying no more than maybe 35, 40 minutes.
Of course, the, let's just say in our altogether, depending.
And that's really from takeoff to landing.
And it just depends on, you know, road and weather conditions, obviously.
And I'd been on British Airways.
And I'd done KLM, of course.
And as I was reserving this trip.
And I was doing that in South Beach.
I was looking at the ticket prices.
And, you know, of course, what happens is when you do a round trip.
You book on January 12th to go to Amsterdam and return January 12th.
So all of a sudden, for some reason, I guess you're positioned as a business customer.
And your, your coach fair ticket.
Your coach ticket fair is like 300 pounds.
You know, that's close to 500 dollars.
Like, I don't fucking think so.
So then, of course, I tried to beat the system by booking one way.
Or booking January 12th is going over.
And some ridiculous date, like February 20th coming back.
And I saw the, of course, the trip over was all of a sudden, only 40 pounds.
And then I, of course, tried to do the reverse.
And, well, they do kind of catch on that.
You know, where I then booked a trip back from the 12th.
Or from the 12th to London and a return trip.
And a much later date, but they, they kind of catch on that.
But it doesn't really work.
So I said, screw it.
You know, and I, and I checked a couple other airlines.
What is it to be in my British Midland?
And they were.
So that was still 180 pounds.
So 250 dollars.
And I just, this became a sport.
You know, it actually has become a sport.
Because I really don't give a shit.
You know, if I'm flying in the toilet, or if I'm actually flying the plane,
which I couldn't with this, these particular models.
But, you know, I just want to do it efficiently and effectively.
And, and the game is to do it cheaply.
So I looked up easy jet, which had never really flown.
And they have a flight from Gatway to Amsterdam.
And the total price round trip with the times that I was going.
So I'd left around 11 of an even in the end.
Whoops.
Did we hear that?
That was kind of funky.
Thank God for digital recording.
So left around 11 a.m. on Tuesday.
Was it Tuesday?
Wednesday?
Sorry.
I'm so confused.
Left little 11 a.m.
And returned on the quarter of ten or five to ten p.m.
same day.
And so the total was about 80 pounds, which I thought was really good.
And so I went to the airport.
You know, all you do is just show up with your printout.
You don't even have to do that.
You can just say your name, show your ID.
And you don't even have a confirmation number.
Or you do, but you don't need it.
Give it a boarding pass.
And it's just, it's a really nice experience.
All the way from, you know, going to the lounge.
And everyone's the same, right?
There's no, no one gets preference over anything.
There is a number on your ticket, which is a labeled like,
you know, one to, well, depending on the size of the plane.
Maybe a hundred, let's just say.
So you can say, you know, people with the numbers one to 50,
you know, could you please start boarding now and about two minutes later.
It's just crowd control, basically, to get you to line up nicely.
But there's really no checking.
You know, they don't have to go through any real computer systems,
looking at spots where you're sitting, because there's no reserved seating.
Everything is all the same.
And when you get on the plane, a couple of things I noticed right off the bat,
because the whole intent of this service is to be like a bus.
And it is just like a bus.
There's three rows on the right hand side, three rows on the left hand side.
It's a very broad plane.
And it actually, well, go figure, it is the Airbus 319.
That's the model that we flew.
It's really comfortable to walk in.
You don't have to crouch or anything.
Certainly for tall people like myself.
There's plenty of storage space.
There's just no, no frills, no thrills, right?
It's just seats, right in left, three, three, everything's three.
There's no two seaters, no one.
There's no single, actually, the exit row.
I take that back.
The exit row does have a little bit more space,
but you can't move your chair back.
So you want to avoid the exit rows.
But for some reason, because you know that you're guaranteed absolutely no service,
because that's the deal, right?
You get no service.
There's just, you know, we're going to help you on.
We're going to keep you safe.
And the girls are great.
The cabin crew, I only had stewardesses or flight attendants,
female, both going and coming.
I don't know if they have a male flight attendants.
I'm sure they must.
Totally nice.
Because all they have to do is basically keep you safe.
So they're smiling and they help you sit down.
They just have to make sure you get your seat belt buckled.
And otherwise, there's nothing.
Of course, when you're in the air, then they say,
hey, would you like to purchase a drink?
So they don't come through the aisle.
They just say, look, if you want some of the drink,
or something to eat, just turn on your overhead light.
And then also in the old jump in actions,
there's maybe five flight attendants.
And they just run back and forth real quick,
get you whatever you want.
And they give you a chance you pay to pay for it.
So I think I bought a tea and a big cheese and tomato.
You say tomato, I said tomato.
I said tomato now.
A tomato sandwich was like four pounds,
50 altogether.
I guess cheaper than if it's actually built into the price of the ticket,
clearly.
And then when that's all over,
when they've delivered everyone,
whatever they purchase,
then it's very simple for them, right?
They don't have to really prepare anything.
Then they come by with a big trash bag,
and everyone just chips in and throws your shit into the trash bag.
They've also passed out the company magazine,
which they come back and collect.
So that's where a lot of the savings come in.
You know, it's not like you.
You don't, I think I guess you could take the magazine with you if you wanted,
but basically the operation just really smart, really tight.
And there's something about knowing that you're not going to get any service,
and knowing that the flight attendants don't have to provide any service,
which just makes it great.
You know, it's like it's, you know,
I'm not expecting anything,
if I get a smile, I'm already happy,
and let's be honest.
You don't get them any fucking smiles from first-class flight attendants.
You know, I'm liking it.
Those Steve Ross, what is it,
set the guys name?
George, Jorge, George, Steve Ross.
Shit, I should look his name up.
Ah, of course I can't get on the internet right now.
Yeah, let's talk about that for a second.
So anyway, easy jet, fantastic.
I don't know what it would be like to travel more than two and a half hours,
if it was really packed, but I, I'm going to tell you,
I'm going to do that, I'm going to, this is a great formula.
And it has a lot to do with the way the plane is configured as well.
It's not just the cheap tickets.
Oh, and by the way, their tax is interesting.
You'd think that if it really was a tax,
all tax would be the same.
No, you can fly the same distance,
this from London to Amsterdam with the KLM.
Their tax is 44 pounds.
Easy jet's tax is only 10 pounds.
You know why?
Because it's horseshit.
It's not a real tax.
Okay?
It's a fucking rip off.
Just say, you know, we're charging you for our overhead.
Okay.
I tried to stop by a wing commander Williams place on the,
on the trip back from Antwerp.
I really wanted to drop by, but everything took so long.
And you know, house closing sometimes can just be a,
yeah, it's not a pain in the asses.
Of course I'm happy, but just, you know,
read through everything and there's questions and answers.
So I didn't get to see him, but he said, Adam,
you better get your ass over here for a couple of days.
Gonna teach you how to fly.
Get you going because, you know, this commercial flying is just not,
not for boys like you.
You're right.
I need to push metal the metal pull back on that stick.
Put on the autopilot and pour my own cup of tea.
And I'm sure we'll have some podcasts about that in the future.
So let's talk about bandwidth.
So of course I came home.
I told you that, well, I showed you the emails.
I put them on the weblog.
Yes, the bandwidth was going to be here.
Plugged in the router or router, as we say.
And got the whamlight flashing and flashing and flashing.
So I'm gonna cut straight to the chase.
I've had two days of straight calling around with easy net
with British telecom.
Everyone has a different story, but the, you know,
everything, the job is completed, but yet it's not working.
The measurements are wrong.
We don't understand.
So I finally found this guy Lee at easy net.
Then he had a different number.
He had an O2O number, which is different from the O845 numbers
I've been dialing.
And Lee definitely has a shit together.
So I say, Lee, you're my man.
And about 30 minutes after speaking to Lee,
British telecom shows up at the door.
This is good news, I think, because here comes the cavalry.
They're in.
They're gonna fix it all.
They're gonna figure me out.
Shoot, hold on.
I have something to, need to share with you right after I talk about this.
Okay, here we go.
So these guys, and it's, they're nice guys.
John and, um, who was his apprentice.
He's got an apprentice.
And I can tell he's an apprentice, right?
He's a young kid.
And he's got a, like, his, his British telecom jacket.
It's like crackling fresh.
I was bustin' on him because he, you know, he could, he said.
I said, what's going on?
Because John was on the phone and talking to people,
I don't know.
I'm really new.
So yes, your jacket gave it away, my friend.
So I actually took pictures of this.
You're not gonna believe it.
So we follow the line.
In my office here, there's the jack.
It's got the jack reference number and it's all set, right?
We follow the line to where it goes out the house.
And down the side of the house.
And into the junction box and the side of the house.
And there you see.
Yes, I had to take a picture of it.
It'll be on the, the web log.
There you see the wires just sticking out of the junction box.
Connect it to nothing.
And if you go down to the corner to the curb, actually,
and you look at the, the BT box at the corner,
of course, they opened it up for me.
I guess what?
They were like a pair of wires sitting there,
just ready to be connected to the ones in my house.
Which apparently, according to all the paperwork was done,
but obviously wasn't completed.
So that does kind of explain why no one could get the fucking measurement right.
And it just went from, from bad to worse, from worse to horrible,
from, so then it's like, well, we can't open up a new order
unless, I don't even want to get into it.
This fucking crap.
So anyway, so I called Lee back, he's working on it.
And what has to happen is literally some other guy has to get the order to come out here
with 40 feet of fucking wire and connected from the curb up to the house.
And I have half a mind to go get some goddamn wire myself
and solder that fucker up tonight.
But I'm going to give him a second to tell me when they,
and it's convenient for them to come and actually do this for me.
So until then, it's me and Starbucks or me and the neighbors.
And I just, you know, now I really should go figure out which neighbors
providing this Wi-Fi to me because I've been fetching off it for so long
and I have to continue doing it.
I just hope that I wouldn't have to deal with it.
Anyway, one thing I wanted to say that when I do that get disconnected
and I'm going to say Monday, well, I'm a business customer now, right?
I'm not just some asshole residential smuck.
Now I'm a business customer.
I get, I get escalated.
God, this pisses me off.
I was going to say, so anyways, I get escalated and maybe Monday, maybe Monday.
All right.
Adam Elman sent me an email.
Adam, hi, hopefully by the time you read this,
you'll have your net up and running.
I thought that this song for my band's recent album
will help you celebrate broadband at home again.
Adam says, I once had SPC accidentally disconnect my DSL line.
Took six weeks for him to turn it back on, almost went insane.
So I know where you're coming from.
Okay, the band, sinister dexter.
And of course, put a link up to their site.
They're also on garageband.com as slash syntax.
Song has a creative comments license.
So completely pod safe music.
You'll like the title, dig the tune.
This is called broadband connection.
I was just a hot beer.
I'm gonna get funky.
You better shout it out.
I'll get into your room now here.
Can you feel it to your heart's size?
Yes, can you hear our hand of your insights?
Can you feel how it is to feel it though?
If you read right around your head down to what your toes closed up,
I hope the heart that doesn't dribble drops a groove.
Did you expect a powerful gun to make a fire and move into it?
Good luck with this sound.
Let their rhythm roll and make a run back and action to your soul.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, hey, ah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
One, two, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four, three, four
Yeah, broadband connection to your soul brought to you by Senator Dexter from the city, Dexterity,
check them out on garageband.com, of course, in the podcast show notes is where you can find links to them.
Being in South Beach for over a week, I didn't, as I think we discussed, I didn't really see any,
any, I didn't watch any television, I just like the last day I watched by an hour of TV,
was actually blown away by the speed of the hypnotization process. Within seconds, I was like,
I'm hypnotized, I'm like, I am slave to the machine, but, you know, with everything going on
with the tsunami, with the state of the entire fucking world, and what's this with the,
don't we have, we're blasting into some kind of comment, we've got, what is it,
to such a Bruce Willis type name, deep, deep mission, or deep blaster, or mission critical,
something, we're trying to shoot a rocket into this meteorite to see what happens, basically,
is what I understood, but just mesmerizing stuff. But the big news that I miss, and it really is
big news, everyone was talking about this, is the Brad Pitt Jennifer Aniston split, and I,
first of all, I got to tell you, I was shocked, I really was. I liked them, you know, there's such a,
such a beautiful couple together, and it was so perfect, because you know, the Brad really needs some,
he's, he needs a mom out of take care of, I mean, you know, the Jennifer's, you know,
she's a strong woman, and she takes no shit, and she's going to take care of him, and, you know,
you just see the way they interacted, I thought that this was a real, this could really last,
I thought that this would really work, and that if anyone could make him, especially then, you know,
the, although I think Brad can probably, Brad Pitt has more sex appeal than Jennifer Aniston,
clearly, it's amazing when you, I mean, his world is just filled with people throwing themselves
at him, female and male for that matter, and, you know, they're both famous, it just, it works,
it's so perfect, and you could, I thought really the way they, they communicated together,
the way they acted when they were, you know, or at least what you could see on television,
and news, I don't know, either of them personally, and just the way they talk about each other,
I thought that was for real, and maybe it is for real, maybe they just can't live together,
but to, what happens is immediately the spin goes down, you know, it's like, well, it's, of course,
it's because of Angelina Jolie, because Brad did a movie with her, and she's known to, you know,
sleep with her co-stars, and, well, I don't know if that's true, right? I'm just telling you what I'm
reading, and the papers here, and with more follow-up on this, on the breakup, and what I saw on TV
in the States, and having been the subject of stories like that, although, I guess it was only
really in the beginning when Patricia and I, we've been married for 17 years, we've been together
for almost 19 now. So, no reason for this, for this shit, to not work anymore. And let's
broadband, doesn't get fucking fixed, because I'll just go fucking insane, and she'll have to
divorce me, it'll all be the fault of British telecom. So anyway, so that's the story, right,
is that Angelina Jolie, she seduced Brad, and Jennifer would have none of that, and, and of course,
then this, and it's something really hurtful that is out there now, is that Brad wants kids,
Jennifer doesn't, because she still wants to move her career forward, doesn't want to enter
career, I guess having kids meet ending her career, in this, in the context of what I'm reading, right?
She wants to do some serious acting, doesn't want to end on the, I'm the Dits from Friends
vibe, which I can totally understand, and I'm not quite sure how old she is, I think she's in
her early 30s, so I think she has a little bit of time, if she, if she's so prefers before having to,
you know, kind of catch up with a biological clock, that's pretty hurtful shit, you know,
when people say that, it's just, even if it's true, it's hurtful for it being discussed,
and of course, the reason, you know, that everything all went downhill, as they were in the
Caribbean, you know, having a reconciliation weekend, don't know if it's true, and Brad had
tickets to the Super Bowl, and so he went left to go back to the Super Bowl, and then he came back,
and then they split up, and whatever, so there's really no revelant, relative, oh, man,
wait, let me get the latency off, no relevance, between my life and theirs, except for one thing,
because I said to Patricia, I said, you know, so wait a minute, so you're going to tell me that
because he, let's just say he slept with Angelina Jolie, right? So they're on the set of the
movie, you know, it's, you're working hard, you're in close proximity, I have no idea what the
movie is, but maybe there's a love scene, there's, I mean, come on, it's a beautiful, beautiful guy,
beautiful girl, there can be some attraction there, and so let's say that they did have a hot
wicked affair, you know, said, so that's, is that really the reason why Jennifer is, is
divorcing him, or that they're getting divorced, and Patricia said, yeah, I think that she's
really, she's a tough cookie, she's taken no shit, you know, and with her, you, you do that
and you're out, and then so then she took a beat and she says, besides, you know that, you know,
if you called me, I'd say go for it, I was like, hold on, can I get that in writing, just in case
I meet Ms. Jolie somewhere? Oh, anyway, what are we at now? We're at 29 minutes, okay,
still got some stuff to talk about, and I'm really trying to pair down a lot of the
elements in the show, and actually, this is going to be a good reset moment for me, and I
hopefully erasing for all of you, I'm getting lots of email actually from people saying, oh,
you know, even though it sucks that we haven't had a source code in three days, it's really cool
that we can actually sync up and catch up on previous episodes. So that's good, so maybe I should do
that once a month, you know, drop a couple of days and see if everyone can kind of sync up.
There are of course some comments that came in. Yeah, let's do a, I had something else lined up.
I'm going to do a comment, audio comment first, and I'll get back to some other stuff that's
been floating around the, the, the, the, the, the blogger sphere and podosh sphere. Greetings and
salutations to you, Prince of Podu. Okay, this starts off great. Isn't that wonderful? This is
Jennifer, the girl on tech. I host the girl on tech podcast at girl on tech.plogspot.com,
and let me get the old Boeing out of the way here, a Boeing moment for you. I enjoy the show tremendously
especially the, uh, I heard that I got some email from, uh, from a couple of people that
Letterman had Boeing now in the top 10 of, uh, of ways to make the news cooler, I think it was,
and maybe it was CBS news, uh, Dan Rathers show, um, and number five was, uh, ad comedic
volume, after every item. The, you know, the Boeing's are getting out there. Now it's mainstream,
you know, Letterman's picked it up. So I guess, well, that's the quote with something else.
A recent show you did the, uh, walking through a South Beach and beautiful Miami.
The sound seeing too. And just keep doing what you're doing out and you're doing a fantastic job.
Okay, Jen. Hey, just talking about Jen. It's my own Jennifer.
Um, quick question for you. Um, as I've mentioned on my blog, I am doing a lecture
at the 2005 Indiana Computer Educators Conference.
Uh, is that hot when we're in talk like that? Hold on, let's just be the real one.
Uh, keep keep me out, baby.
At the 2005 Indiana Computer Educators Conference, excellent teacher. Uh, January 26th through the 29th
and uh, at the Indiana Convention Center in Indianaapolis. My goodness, teacher. Okay, great.
And I'm doing a lecture entitled Classroom MTV using classroom MTV. Wow.
I don't know if the words classroom and MTV can actually be fit into the, into the same
setting using digital media to enhance standards and learning. And all the participants of this lecture
actually going to receive a CD with a software and manuals and how to use that I'm putting together.
And one of the areas that I'm definitely going to cover is blogging, RSS and podcast course.
Um, in the CD, I'm actually including some sample podcast one from James Basour.
I've actually gotten an okay from Jay Rosen to include his academia lecture from blogger
com 3 and I was wanting to ask if you would allow me to include your podcasting lecture
from blogger com 3 as well in the little sample CD. I'd really appreciate it. That's basically
all I've got on my mind. So again, keep up the great work Adam and uh, here's another
boring for you baby. Oh, you have baby. Thank you. Um, that's actually, I guess there's a question
for, for Dave Winner. I'm not sure. Um, I would presume. It sounds actually like the CD
you're making would be a fantastic resource. Uh, so maybe that would be something to think about
if we can get all of that stuff on, uh, on a, on a, on a, on a site somewhere. I mean, that would be
great. Patricia just walking while that clip was playing. You still there, huh?
Come here. You can't do that. Dude, come here.
So Patricia's standing out. And you know, this is why this is why we have studio doors right
that have a big red on air light and has soundproofing. So you can't have like people
standing outside and listening. So she heard the whole Angelina Jolie bit did I lie? Did I lie? Did I
lie? I heard did I lie? Did you say that or not? I said that. Yeah, exactly. And but I'm sure
of myself. I've got great lips too. Oh, boy. Thank you. Okay. I love you very much. I love you, too, baby.
It's okay. But you know, if, if you want to have sex with Angelina Jolie, it's okay, too.
Could you just take a, like video? All right. Okay. She's into it. She, uh, to totally
into it. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Let's call her. Yeah. All right. Cool. Okay. Let's talk something
completely nerdy. Going from the sexual to the nerdy. And he hurts felt. I don't actually
know, I didn't know too much about him, been reading up on him. He's not, not an original founder
of Apple, but he did come in pretty early on the Macintosh. And he's, uh, I think he's coming out
with a book, but he was interviewed recently at, uh, was it seen it or by seen it? And I don't think
he quite understands podcasting. I'm just going to read this bit to you because it was in a written
interview. He says, I'm down on podcasts. I think it's ridiculous. Suddenly it's taking the
information and making it completely inaccessible. You can't read it and besides a podcast is
nothing. It's streaming MP3s. That's good. But no one can take credit for inventing a new term
because streaming MP3s is simple and has been around for a while. Doing it through RSS enclosures
is basically bad to automatically download big files before hearing them. The whole thing about
audio is that it has, that it has to be small, uh, since it's a weird sentence. I'm going to read
it exactly the way it's written. The whole thing about audio is that it has small enough bandwidth
that you can stream. Okay. You just can't stream from an iPod because it doesn't have a network
connection yet. I'm excited about getting an iPod with 802-11 so I can stream to my airport
express without carrying my Macaron. This is, this is so typical. This is exactly the problem.
I presume that Andy Hertzfeld is, is an engineer. He's thinking exactly, he's, he's completely
missing the point and this is probably why Apple hasn't picked up on podcasting because they're
thinking exactly this way precisely the, they're thinking from Apple out to the rest of the world
they're not seeing what's happening. And, you know, to to misunderstand the idea of downloading things
before you've heard them to have, you know, a high-quality experience. I mean, yeah, Andy, sure,
if we all have fucking fiber up our ass wirelessly attached, yeah, okay, I can probably get there,
you know, but it's, anyway, so the entire text is going to be in the production show notes
and it's very discouraging. Of course, it also, you know, this plays completely into, you know,
a lot of the things we were talking in South Beach about and this is where all the opportunity is,
so great, you know, I'm just blown away and you know, these guys aren't dumb, they're just not seeing
it, just not seeing it, not, not living in my world, that's for sure, okay. Wow, yeah, pretty interesting
and how about that, you know, let's, while we're on Apple for a second, let me, what time do I have?
God damn, I'm not going to be able to, well, I could just hurry up through a couple of things here.
So the new Apple products, I think the, the mini is very intriguing, I might actually just buy one,
just to hook it up and see how it works and, I don't know, interesting, very interesting,
there's a little computer like that, although, you know, okay, you're getting laptop,
territory, it's interesting, but the, the iPod shuffle, what? This is like, like, makes no sense at all,
and I, you know, I love stuff that Apple makes, I really do, I mean, clearly, you know that,
but what is up, you know, this shuffle thing and, no, makes no sense to me, and for that kind of money,
I'd get an I river and, and a pair of white, you know what they, do they actually just sell
white headsets, you know, there's a market for you, all you got to do is just sell the white
headphones with a white wire, that's it, that is a million dollar business right there, I'm sure
someone's already doing it, but you've got to totally, you'll go out, market it so that you can
walk around with a piece of shit, MP3 player and iPod, whatever, you know, iPod equivalent,
as long as you have the white headphones, then, you know, you're cool, you're going to be with it,
and maybe, you know, I don't know, but this thing, for the money, it just made no sense to me,
absolutely not, okay, well, I guess, let me see, I had a good joke in there, but I don't feel
like doing a joke today, I'll keep that for tomorrow, okay, although let me just put that down to the
bottom of the outline, yep, still working with my opml show notes, okay, I'm going to play this one
little bit from the podcast brothers, that's a podcast, I listen to regularly, they do crack me up,
and these guys, not quite sure who they are, what they're about, I think they're organizing a podcast
conference pretty soon or maybe a trade show, so I'll have to listen up and check them out and
listen to, you know, what's going on? Of course, I have to go to Starbucks now to download the podcast,
so I may drop behind a pick and how long it takes BT to connect that 40 foot piece of wire.
You can check them out yourself at podcastbrothers.com. Of course, all the podcasts are listed in the
iPod.org directory, that's a great resource, so we can go basically search in the directory
by category, and if you want to hear the list, 100 podcasts, it's audio.weblogs.com, so here's this
clip that was actually released as a clip, I think on the opempodcast.org by the brothers themselves.
Instead, listening to that day's podcast, we noticed that Adam was talking about his hair, so
we didn't get a mashup of his podcast, we hope he likes it.
My hair cut. Personal grooming, my hair, the total package, you know, my eyes, why am I doing
this? She did my hair. I love it when Patricia does my hair. It just looks so good. Could you please
do my hair? So wash it, cut it up a little bit, just perfectly, just the way I love it. And now I
got to be real careful with it. I just did your hair, so it's not to mess up the hair, so the hair
will be beautiful. So Adam, we're just Adam, you're hair, man. Yeah, yeah, you must use a lot of
hair products. Actually, I don't use a lot of hair products, actually. I don't know. I just
like it really dirty, kind of like a rostophari. You know, so you can mold it and shape it and
bend it anyway you want. Some sure. Yeah, hey, you know what? He would be a good, good commercial
now for geeks for a hair product. Well, he should eat. Hey, geeks, you too, could look like me and
get hot chicks who will have sex with you and Angelina, Jolie. Should get somebody should sponsor him.
So hair product. They should. And Adam, who does his rose-coded glasses, but those are cool.
They're also real. They're actually prescription. Minus 2, minus 2.75. And did you see the shirt?
They've won or posted some pictures with them. That's not totally fair.
Oh, my, I mean, South Beach, sorry. South Beach. And these boys are listening to the show.
Adam, very sharp dresser. Really? I haven't seen a picture of Adam Curry.
What? I haven't seen Adam Curry since. Oh, yeah, you got to go check it out.
Yeah. You're like, I don't know. I'll tell you. I'll email those colored glasses on.
You're going to see those colored glasses. And they shirt. Adam, I don't know if
you have his shirt. He does. He actually called yesterday just for that reason.
It's your daily source code. Oh, man. How cool is that? The syvee is biddies everybody.
Great. Give it up for him. Fantastic. And I have it on very good authority that we could be seeing a
bitty cast before too long. That's it for today's podcast.
Come Thursday. And of course, tomorrow we'll be back with the thank god's Friday
edition of the daily source code. All right. That's it. Oh, by the way,
could someone please send me a Gmail invite so I can open up a Gmail account for audio comments?
This is, you know, it's not a control on the Mac account. I only have like 200 megs left over
whatever. So, send me an invite so I can open up something at gmail.com.
Okay, that's it. I'm going to rush off to Starbucks to shoot this up to the server and
be home just in time for some South Beach phone calls. Hey, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
I have more about what's going on. Maybe a British telecom update. Thanks for checking out
take care. See you tomorrow.