Daily Source Code for May 26, 2005, episode number 185.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's the Daily Source Code coming you from LA.
That's right, Los Angeles.
How you doing?
It is, well I'm just, just my volume here.
It is relatively late, 130 as AM been here since around 8 o'clock and got some stuff to talk about.
So I figured trying to blow out a full source code.
I'm still trying to get my levels all set here, hold on a second bear with me while I just set this like that.
Oops.
I'm, uh, there we go, that's better.
I'm on the, uh, under G4 Powerboard.
My, uh, my tablet is with Brian, who stayed in San Francisco.
Brian is also, uh, he does operations for Pod Show.
He's, uh, got some work out there and doing some meetings.
So I don't have cast plaster in my disposal.
Um, but I do have some cool stuff to play for, and some stories to share.
So first of all, I got to let you know that, um, after, you know, the week that we had in San Francisco,
Apollo Alto, um, in the Bay Area essentially, uh, staying in, uh, you know, kind of, more, uh,
mid to low scale hotels.
We splurge and where the Beverly Hills hotel and lovely Beverly Hills, I've never actually, uh,
stayed here ever, ever been here myself.
I don't know if Ron has or not, but, you know, we're treating ourselves, but we think we've deserved it.
We've worked hard.
So it's, uh, so it's really nice.
Had some room service stayed in, um, oh, man.
I've, I've got to do my laundry.
Um, so I have to send stuff to be pressed and some stuff has to be, uh, has to be clean,
because of course I really only packed enough stuff until Wednesday night.
But Patricia even said to me, she said, um, you know, I should probably pack more,
because I know I have a feeling you're going to be staying longer.
You watch, you'll be staying longer.
And, uh, she was right.
Of course, because the wife is always right.
We've discussed that before, haven't we?
We've established that.
Um, anyway, they're doing fine.
I miss them terribly, both Patricia and Christina.
And, uh, yeah, man, we've, uh, I should tell you this, uh,
it's such a long story.
It's so late, but reminding to tell you about a Christina getting hit at school,
uh, on the nose, actually, well, it's such a great story.
Anyway, the Patricia wound up, uh, you know, basically kick in some ass at the school,
and she's, she's like, uh, reminds me of that, uh, of the movie,
of course, of the real-life story of, uh, was it, uh, Joe Brown,
the principal who had the bullhorn and, uh, and the baseball bat, you know,
it's like Patricia all of a sudden did that to the, to the school,
and have fun on the right over now, and she's really, I don't know.
It's just, uh, something beautiful happened there.
And I'm, I'm really, I'm pissed off.
I wasn't there, man, because, you know, together,
we're really good at stuff when we're, we're, we're,
it should happen. So, anyway, parenting stuff will, uh,
uh, Patricia and I should probably do a podcast pretty soon.
We can catch up, uh, and while we're catching up,
which is kind of stuff that, I think is nice and works well.
So, anyway, um, staying out here,
going to stay for a couple of days longer,
through the Memorial Day weekend,
and then going to do one more meeting on Tuesday,
and then I'm going to go fly back, because then it will be,
uh, shoot almost, uh,
or is it 10 days or something like that?
So it's pretty long, but it has been so worth it,
so much cool stuff has happened yet again today.
Um, and we're going to talk about some of that.
Uh, I'm going to try and keep it within, you know,
30, 40 minutes, but I also wanted to play some excellent music.
I saw that, um, I've been following the Michael Jackson trial now.
There's, uh, it just looks like, um,
he was completely being railroaded, and as I predicted,
and I don't think it'll be convicted of anything.
I think that, you know, this is very clear what's going on.
I'm telling you, I have some experience in this.
This should happen,
and spiraled out of control in his case.
It really did.
And the media mainstream media has, you know,
basically even when you say, you know,
wacko jacko, you're editorializing a report,
you know, your news, right?
And it's, uh, we know that's happening,
but that stuff is fucked up, you know,
his name is Michael Jackson.
Anyway, um, so a mashup came across my desk.
P. Doug, PW Fenton has been, uh,
producing the pod show over serious,
and he's just been lining up some fucking awesome shows.
Uh, really, really good stuff.
We've got some great submissions.
Uh, let me just, uh, I have his show notes,
which, of course, show up as my show notes.
And then I pretend like I did all that laborious work on them.
Uh, this is, uh, home on a second.
Uh, you're gonna love this.
That's something, uh, it's a little different.
I'm not in my, my normal studio now, of course,
and I don't have my mixer and my external processing,
and, and I've kind of forgotten how to do it,
but it does, it does still work pretty well.
Um, this is, uh, sent in by DJ May Lune.
I think it is.
It's Eminem versus Michael Jackson,
versus Justin, and it's extremely timely.
It's timely for, uh, what's been going on.
Listen to it.
No.
This is my best.
It's so beautiful tonight.
Your eyes are so lovely.
You're not this sweet.
Never thought I would end up this way.
A lot of people misunderstand me,
but it's because they don't know me at all.
I just want to touch you.
No.
I don't know you.
I think everybody's all gelatin-ship,
because I'm like the lead singer of the band.
And I think everybody's got a fucking problem.
Me, did.
And they need to take it up with me after the show.
Go to the free.
Just you, you're free.
Now I'm here, then be, now.
Or I'll be, now.
Go to get your mind.
Don't you like that.
Use your own.
Do that, Do that.
Going to fight.
I'm giving you.
Only now free.
I just wanna swear.
You're my, now I'm giving you.
You're the watch, you're my old man.
I'm who you can keep.
What is your about?
I'm a friend, you have seen nothing, there's a way to bite it, do a big fun, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better,
I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, it's better, I'm better, I'm more, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm first, Ior, I'm more, I'm better, I'm younger, I'm more, I'm better, I'm older, I'm a better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, I'm better, myself,
I think everybody's all yellowish and shit
Because I'm like the lead singer of the band
And I think everybody's got a fucking problem with me
And they need to take it up with me after the show
And I think everybody's got a fucking problem with me after the show
And I think everybody's got a fucking problems with me after the show
Yeah.
I don't know. It sounds a bit of the first time
Oh no
No, no, but it's a timely mashup, you know, so that's kind of cool.
Daily source code, you know, at the Beverly Hills Hotel, this is a really famous place.
This is where a lot of leading ladies have been discovered.
There's all kinds of Hollywood history that comes from this place.
They've got the bungalows here and yeah, all that Hollywood magic.
All right here.
They actually make a custom hot dog.
16 dollar hot dog.
Okay.
So I had reconnected recently with a good friend Julia Goldberg, who used to run all technology for us at
Think New Ideas, like 600 people in the company.
It was a lot of laptops of crap and if you think, you know, if you think XP is difficult now, you know, think back, you know, like
7, 8, 9, 10 years.
You know, that was sucked, man.
It was Windows.
It was at Windows 98.
Yeah.
Windows 98, I guess.
And T, maybe 3.5 or something like that.
And so she lives in Los Angeles.
And, you know, we had reconnected recently through Steve Leads once again, kind of.
But that's a whole nother story.
And so I said, now I might be coming to LA, so she lives nearby turns out.
So she came over.
And of course, Julia understands me.
She's, you know, we've worked together for a long time.
Exactly.
Julia knows what the hard work and boy needs.
So she's a buddy.
She came over and we just caught up, man, we talked for a long time, actually.
And I had the custom made hot dog and the shrimp cocktail.
And she had tuna salad sandwich.
And it was actually, it was really good.
And then all of a sudden, she kind of comes clean.
And she says, you know, she's been listening to the daily source code for eight months.
And she, I mean, but like every single day, every single day.
She knew every single episode.
And man, she's had a lot of time to think about this stuff.
And she had some really good ideas.
And of course, I immediately told her she had to start a podcast.
So I'm sure she will.
And I'm really looking forward to that.
But it was, it was great to see her.
And even cooler that she brought along nice little gifts for your podcaster here.
And the Beverly Hills hotel feeling so lonely.
By the way, I haven't checked yet.
But I bet you they have porn here.
Hold on a second.
Where's the shoot?
I got it.
And this is old school, man.
Did this use the plug?
Oops.
I hope.
Yeah, there we go.
When I was in the castle.
Okay.
I have a love mic on.
Obviously, let's see.
Many accessing interactive services.
Large net movies.
Select one for movies.
Still in theaters.
Hollywood hits.
Yeah.
Adult desires.
Okay.
Adult's only.
Not for minors who are offended by sexually explicit content.
Extra large.
Cool.
Hmm.
Okay.
Anyway.
I have some other exciting stuff to talk about.
So we can.
Shit.
Sorry.
Okay.
Apple today.
Yeah.
Went to Cupertino.
Oops.
Sorry.
I'm over modulating a little bit.
Went to Cupertino.
And met with the team that, well, I guess actually this is the iTunes team.
And iTunes music store team.
And there was an one developer there.
All really nice people.
And I think Amazon's actually done all of the podcasting coding.
And it was amazing.
Now obviously we made an agreement that I just wouldn't talk about, you know, what's in there.
I certainly could tell you about how the meeting went.
But.
And we're working.
Apple is not a company as you know that releases information early.
And they didn't make me sign anything.
No NDA.
You know, it's just a gentleman's agreement.
And I'm honoring that.
But we are talking about, you know, when we can release this news.
And they're admitting this is new for them.
You know, they never release it.
You know, any kind of news before the big unveiling of the product.
But this, this.
Um, community is new to them.
This, this type of content is new to them.
And they really want to step in in the right way.
And they really want to help.
But I know it sounds unbelievable, right?
But, um, not all big companies, you know, do things for the reasons you think they do them.
Um, and I can certainly tell you why Apple is so incredibly interested in podcasts.
And that's because, well, for one, they sell iPods.
And that's great.
And so they want to facilitate that and do that as an open, as open fashion as possible.
So, um, and we really had no agenda for this meeting.
But at least we didn't agree on one.
Just, hey, let's continue our conversation.
So we went back and we sat down with this, you know, like five people.
And, um, it turns out that they, uh, wanted to show me all the features, all the functionality.
Uh, all the ideas, you know, what, what's going to happen where, what you're going to see.
And if, uh, if I agreed with what they were doing, if, uh, if they thought if I thought it was a good idea,
what was there anything missing, um, uh, I think was unbelievable.
It was, this was, uh, it's going to sound crazy.
But this was users and developers partying together.
And I realized that this meeting, that that doesn't just mean that it has to be, you know,
independent users, uh, with independent developers independent of the platform vendor, I guess.
So we're trying to say that, uh, a good platform vendor, of course, will party with their users.
And here it was, it was actually happening, um, with this whole iPodter, I,
iPodter started out of frustration that this wasn't possible with iTunes.
And it was basically a way to make iTunes perform an action, which carried through to the iPod.
And of course, that branched out with, with, you know, with incredible work from so many cool developers, um,
which kind of developed version one.
And, um, what, what Apple has been doing has been, they've been listening, they've been watching,
they've been observing, they've been paying close attention.
Um, this, of course, they've been doing, I guess, relatively silently.
I had no one to say, hey, I'm, I'm from Apple, and I'm doing this.
Well, actually, that's not true.
The dot Mac people have certainly, um, you know, been working with us and working through their own issues,
uh, and, and helping out, you know, they've been providing bandwidth and not shutting people off who've had high flow,
and they've been doing that purposely, um, because they just wanted it to, to go, you know,
of course, we're going to have to all figure some stuff out.
And, uh, you know, there's lots of, lots of stuff to be looked at, but as it comes to, um,
iTunes as a, uh, a pod catcher, an iPodter?
Yeah, they got it fucking right, totally.
Um, and then doing some, some other stuff that, um, it's just going to be great.
So, uh, it was fantastic, you know, to have this thought and, and there it was,
a company and actually listened and created it and, and just done just an amazing job.
And I know it's, this, of course, sounds like I've been either hypnotized or, uh,
assimilated by the board, but, uh, what if it actually was true?
What if it really is all the things that we've been talking about?
Um, and, but, but still in the, um, you know, as open as we, as all of our tools are,
what if it was really true?
Um, I can't, you know, and I'm, I'm always looking for the bullshit.
The bullshit detectors on, on high alert, um, I can't see it.
So anyway, um, I've, as you know, I've requested, you know,
when I'd like to start talking about this, um, and I think that's a good thing.
And, uh, wouldn't it be interesting if, uh, if Apple, you know,
let us open up that dialogue and started, uh, getting some word out.
So anyway, so that was just fantastic.
It just blew my mind.
It really blew my mind, uh, to be there.
Very interesting people, um, and I see nothing but benefit all around totally.
Uh, okay, uh, but we'll, uh, back to some tunes.
What are we at now?
18 minutes. Oh, cool. That's not it. That's not that bad.
I thought it was going to take longer to get through all that.
Um, what should I do? I've got, oh, um, Mad Weinstein was, uh,
was going to Manhattan this week.
And, uh, she'd emailed me about that and I said, well, would you like to go and
check out the serious satellite radio studios where podshow, uh,
broadcasts on and go see for yourself.
This is amazing. What's going on over there.
And, and there are actually some people who are doing some really creative stuff.
And, you know, yeah, their infrastructure is different, uh, way different from ours.
Uh, but, uh, you know, people who are doing, uh, exciting new stuff and people
who are doing more traditional stuff. You know, it's all there.
Uh, and there's some really wacked out people. That's interesting.
Um, and what's cool is Steve Leads, who has been on this show, uh,
and been mentioned on this show, uh, he, uh, he does a lot of stuff over there at, uh,
it's serious satellite. Um, and he kind of did a sound seeing
tour together with Madge. And I just want to give you, I mean,
it's what it's like 35 minutes. This is part one.
And it's, it's interesting to listen to, but there's also some, you know,
some typical Madge bands. And here's a Madge is being introduced to someone.
And she's going from studio to studio meeting of these different people
making different shows in different formats and different ways of, of creating them.
Um, and here's an example of what that sounded like.
I think it'll come in here for a few hours and then that's it.
I mean, I imagine they can't spend a whole day like that.
So, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If you had to four hour shift and theory, you should be able to do it in about 45 minutes.
Nice. This is Rich and that's Jose.
This is, this is Madge.
Alright, one's team. Madge is going to have fun.
Oh, cool.
We're on the, hey, Jose program is the hard rock style.
To represent Madge and rock and the, I'm going to set out which is sort of a college piece.
Okay.
Yeah, welcome.
Thank you.
But you play on your, what are you going to be for?
Well, I mostly, um, I do, uh, talk and we do a left wing sort of, um, I call,
people like, uh, amculture accounts.
Oh, they're nice.
I say really nasty sounds about assholes.
Yeah, I'm with, um, Adam Curry's channel.
I love to be helping him out.
Excellent.
Programming that.
So it's a podcast.
We're on a podcast.
Oh, right on.
Yeah.
Right down.
So we're going to take you to the recording right now.
Yeah.
It's like done the radio for the first time.
So I'm on the radio.
I'm on the podcast.
But your name.
No, that's great.
No, man.
Who?
She's.
She's got this tool, her son.
Oh.
Did it be cut in by her?
Yeah, this is a great story.
You got to listen to this guy.
You get the music.
Like this is a neat invest of.
Like a satinist.
Ah, uh, wow.
It was pretty fucked up.
What is cool.
Yeah, I don't know if this is to do it with your students.
And then you've confirmed the program.
I kind of knew Satan would be so high in the sky like this.
But I try to keep it even now.
I mean, it's true.
But we've got it.
It's Satan.
I try to keep it.
If that player sits down and he's back,
I got to take her shit back.
Right next to her.
No kidding.
So it's like a meal.
It's pretty cool.
That way I keep balance.
And the guy laid his things.
That's interesting.
But you get the devil's promises.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
But I definitely appreciate what he's got.
So you've done a lot of drugs.
Yeah, too.
I don't know.
Oh, man.
That kind of works as serious.
He should be working with us.
He should be doing a podcast.
That's very interesting.
Okay.
Podsafe Music.
This one is a good friend of PW Fenton.
Oh, fuck.
Excuse me.
I'm uploading some tracks to his server.
And it's like crapping out.
I hate that.
Hold on.
Shoot.
Oh, man.
See, it's great.
You can do everything from the road.
But the internet connection.
Sometimes are just not really that good.
Okay.
Fenton PWbs.
This is the New York Blues Queen.
This is Podsafe Music from Roxie Perry.
It's from a new CD.
Back in Losville.
And of course, I'll put links to Roxie Perry and the show notes on today's source code.
I've been down this road.
Many times in the past.
This time the trip is going by so fast.
Every stop, light, every street.
It's pouring me one way.
And the lead is in me.
Yeah, the lead is in me.
Right back to shoot.
My back in blue is there.
And she'll love Paul's heart.
When you have a hug behind me.
Love for me is due from the start.
I fall so fast.
I'm the fat of you.
That it all goes down.
And that pretty suit.
On back in blue is there.
Back in blue is there.
You know the hotel there.
Just keeps my room on home.
And in the register book.
You know they're all my lemon gold.
They'll have blessings.
I told you that.
You got more values this time.
Then I'll feel it all my red.
All the best.
All the back to blue is there.
Yeah.
Roxie Perry.
Back in blue is there.
There was actually this song that motivated me to do a source code at this kind of day.
Did I just say night of day?
That was stupid.
Time of day.
Oh man, that sounds great.
And hopefully we'll speak again on Friday.
We don't have a great Memorial Day weekend.
Somewhere I'll put something out there.
So good things happen in my friends.
Really positive.
Like it.
And we flew first class in American Airlines.
Just a spite America rest.
You're not everybody take care.
To twor all the door in hot hours.
Thank you for watching.