Daily source code for Monday, April 25th, 2005.
You're DJ!
I you don't!
Your DJ has only just begun.
60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped in my ass.
Do you need me?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Everybody welcome to your daily source code to start of a new week at the 25th of April.
And we are in the big lady green thing at the cottage.
Welcome to your daily source code.
When I try and highlight everything that's going on about podcasting, play some promos,
bringing the latest pod save music, got some mashups, not one but two today.
And our pod save tune is something special.
It's a horrible day outside, at least it's gray.
And I guess this is the typical British weather you would imagine if you think of what Britain is like.
And of course the reputation that it has.
It's not like that every single day, but today definitely right on par.
I'm all alone in the cottage because what Christine has at school took her off for early this morning.
And Patricia is off to London with her sister Ivonne.
And Ivonne's daughter, Roxy, who is 22, I think.
So despite the rain, the girls are going to make the best of it.
It's not our honor, it's not our honor, it's our honor, it's our honor.
Plenty of talk about today.
The cast blaster beta has been put out there.
Although if you've submitted, it'll take at least a week and a half before you actually receive the cast blaster.
If you're chosen, I know it sounds all political and shit, but it really isn't.
Well, let me put this way, I've learned a tremendous amount about windows.
It was about time for me to join the other 95% of the world and see what's going on.
And men, you guys are so damn critical.
At least in the audio department, it really has really not that fun the way this stuff works.
Everything works different.
Every hardware manufacturer, every sound card has a different way of explaining what their mixer looks like.
And to get it all to work in the cast blaster is reasonably challenging.
So if you haven't seen the posting on www.curry.com, here's the deal.
You download this little program called CBMT, which stands for cast blaster mixer test.
This only works on Windows XP, by the way.
So I'm sorry, people running Windows 2000 or Macintosh's.
This beta is not going to be for you.
You download it, you run it. It basically does a scan of your mixer.
It tells us what your mixer is doing, what it calls certain things.
Because that apparently is not standard across all Windows machines and sound cards.
If you're looking for a, for instance, the stereo mix portion of a mixer in a sound card.
Some may call it the stereo mixer.
Some may call it the red fader.
So basically we have to build up a database of all different types of sound cards.
It's just fucking horrendous. It makes absolutely no sense.
I did it that way.
But here we are. And that's what we have to deal with.
So to answer the questions right off the bat,
there probably won't be a version for Windows 2000.
And they're, I can almost positively say they will not be a version for the Macintosh.
And by the way, believe me, I'm totally bummed out because I am a Mac guy.
I'm just for obvious business reasons.
Mainly because most of the world is on Windows.
We're creating this as a Windows application.
But there is some solace in all of this.
After the first round of testing,
they will open up to a public, public beta.
What is going to happen essentially with the cast blaster?
After we get through the first phase, which will include being able to record an MP3 file
and save that on your desktop,
the next round will be tied into the podshow.com service.
So that when it'll save the file to your desktop,
but it'll also upload it, create your RSS feed.
You know, all the stuff that everyone is doing.
This is not our number, the number one part of our mission.
In fact, I'd say it's,
well, it's high on the list.
Again, we want it to make easy for people to listen to podcast.
And one way of doing that is getting lots of people to podcast
who have a couple of listeners.
And then that culture and that community starts to breed upon itself
and people help each other out.
But we still have to make it a hell of a lot easier.
Personally, this is the type of interface that I've always wanted
to use for podcasting straight from the computer,
which is kind of, you know,
our new version of the radio studio, right?
But it has to be simple because otherwise,
you can just get so bogged down in features and options.
And I just want something that just works.
So people can play a couple of promos or jingles or music
or whatever it is.
Have some auto leveling in there,
which the cast blaster does have.
So we can start to protect people's ear drums
from blowing them out by playing really loud audio clips.
What we're planning on doing though,
and I think this is the exciting part,
is once we've got the cast blaster up and running and working,
we're going to open up the API to the podshow.com system,
which means that any developer can basically create an application
that will work with podshow.com.
Which I think is extremely exciting,
if I look at the universe out there,
of applications for all platforms,
for windows, for Mac, for Linux, mobile devices.
There are so many programs,
and many of you are using them like audacity,
or maybe you're using sound recorder or something like that.
So essentially, all that will happen,
and I'm trivializing the all that will happen,
is that developers will just add a little gateway to our API,
and they'll be able to add a podcast button to any software
that already exists.
So I think this is really exciting,
because we'll see a whole,
hopefully we'll foster a whole development community of recording devices,
basically, because once you have the podcast and taken care of,
all you have to do literally is just, you know,
drop in that functionality, connect up,
and then provide a way for your users to log in,
so it's just a username and a password,
and you're off to the races.
So if you don't like the interface,
for instance, that the cast blaster provides,
if you think it should work a different way,
if we're just going to work better for you,
and believe me, there is no right and wrong when it comes to this stuff.
I mean, having been around radio studios for years,
and having built several,
it's, you know, it's an art.
It's not, well, it's science as well,
but it's just, you know, whatever you find easy.
In fact, many broadcast studios today,
come highly configurable, so that the, you know,
the station engineer, presumably,
in dialogue with the people who are going to use the system,
and the setup can actually, you know, customize it.
So I like to have my microphone over here,
and I like to have my, my music controls here,
and, you know, maybe I want one on the right,
and you know, whatever it is,
you'll be able to set all of that up.
So that's coming with the cast blaster in data now, officially,
and we're choosing people based upon their sound cards right now.
Don't feel bad if we haven't gotten to you.
It shouldn't be more than three weeks
until we get to the public beta, maybe four.
Of course, the part of the development team
has to go on vacation, too, right?
He can hit you with a mashup.
This is, is when I found on,
through ipodder.org.
This is from the hitmaker,
who does a podcast of all his mashups.
A brand new way to listen to 70s rock and roll.
He was like the first time versus foreigner
on your daily source code.
This is from the hitmaker.
this is from the hitmaker.
The hitmaker.
This is from the hitmaker.
We're going to do a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
but of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of
I have waited a lifetime, spend my time so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I
I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full and I'm so full
We're going to do a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little
little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little little bit of a little bit of that little bit of a little bit of an opportunity to do a little bit more of a little bit drill out the dough to make it more easy.
You know what, guys?
Ohh, guys so heavy
Are you still hungry or something like that, SlBoy?
Sorry to hear you fighting!
Great
You know what I'm trying to do, man
Open up the door
Woo, stick it in your ear, man, blue-bram, thick-jones,
probably tripping out of there here in this one.
The hit maker feels like the first time versus foreigner,
fantastic mashup to get the wheat cranked.
Of course, I loaded this into one of the jingle cartridges,
so I don't know exactly when it's gonna end, right?
Don't have a progress bar on that one.
Too much stuff to play.
Yo, oh, man.
A little music heavy on today's show,
but that's okay.
As I said, I have another mashup coming,
and let's see, a piece I wanted to play
from the vinyl podcast, and of course,
got a couple of promos for you.
Yeah, I know, I'm a word nerd.
Hey, you might be one, too.
Are you curious about words and language?
Then check out the word nerds.
Go to the word nerds.org.
Go ahead, be a nerd.
Be proud of it.
Right on.
We love the nerds.
Hey, I got new glasses, everybody.
I'm gonna be a nerd.
We were in town on Saturday,
and basically I used to wear contact lens.
I think I've told you this before.
I used to wear contact lenses all the time.
The disposable type, which you could basically keep in your eyes,
I don't know.
It says a day, but I think I usually kept them a week,
and I had the week lenses that I kept in for a month.
And it wasn't until I've also mentioned this until I started doing
some night flying, when I put my glasses on,
and was able to do an AB comparison.
I was like, whoa, I'm missing a hell of a lot,
by looking at the world through contact lenses.
And so it was, was this about a year ago,
I did a promotional spot when I was still doing the radio gig
in the Netherlands for a big chain of eyewear stores.
And I guess something was fucked up in the sales department.
They didn't really have any budget left or whatever.
I said, you know, fuck, I just give me a year supply of contacts,
and give me, you know, give me a pair of glasses.
And that's when I got the rose colored glasses,
which I've received plenty of comments about.
Although I really enjoy looking through the world,
looking at the world through rose colored glasses.
It is true, it does just make you kind of happy.
And they also gave me a pair of great prescriptions,
sung glasses, which I used for all my flying,
because they're intended for driving,
so you can see the more clarity in colors,
more hue, or more whatever the hell it is.
But they're great, because you can really see definition
between clouds and other aircraft.
So I like them a lot.
But it was definitely time for something new,
not only because, well, you know,
you just want to like, got to change your glasses, right?
So I got, and we were actually looking at some,
what my daughter, Christina, was calling emo glasses.
So that would be like the black horn rim glasses,
and you put a band A to the middle, almost bought a pair.
Instead, I got this wonderful pair of,
what are these?
Oh, they are brand, actually.
They weren't that expensive.
They're Bugari.
And this time I went for a very light blue tint.
It's just something about the tint that just makes it all work.
And so they're very comfortable,
and they work extremely well.
And I'm going back today after I do the podcast.
Right now it's noon, it's three minutes past 12
in the afternoon, UK time, local time.
I'm going back to have an eye test done,
because I am going to go back and get some more contacts,
because there are just certain times when contacts
or are convenient, I guess.
And as I was thinking about all this,
I saw a new podcast come through an iPod.
Or by the way, I apologize for the big porn picture
that was on the homepage the other day.
In the way it works is,
there's a whole bunch of scripts and little programs
that run to parse through this entire directory,
a whole lot of stuff that come from basically anywhere,
anywhere within the directory of a new podcast is listed.
It's supposed to bring that to the top.
And then it automatically posts those on the homepage,
and then I usually do a scan to see if there's no spam in there.
Believe me, there's plenty of people spamming that all the time.
And I think this was the porn cast,
which I got nothing against the porn cast.
I know who's doing this is Ed,
who created the porn cast in Holland.
But I guess it was a JavaScript or something
if you didn't actually, until you actually clicked on something on the page,
this image wouldn't appear, so I didn't catch it.
And of course, I was asleep while in the States,
everyone was freaking out about this picture on the homepage.
So I just removed the picture.
I'm not going to remove the listing for the porn cast,
of course, because that's up to you if you want to subscribe or listen to that.
But that was going a bit far, I think.
Anyway, my point is, I came across a great podcast
that I just wanted to share a couple of bits with you.
I downloaded the whole thing.
Let's just listen to this for a second.
Hi, I'm Marlene and I live in Seattle.
And I have only just recently discovered
the phenomenon of podcasting and being someone who loves audio
and has played with audio for all of my life.
I immediately wanted to jump into it and give it a shot.
So I've been playing with it my whole adult life too, Marlene.
A shot.
So I've started a podcast called Marlene by ear.
And it's my blog is going to be called the blind spot blog.
And the website is www.blindcast.com.
You're starting to catch on, right?
And in case you hadn't figured out, I happened to be blind.
So Marlene does a podcast.
And with her husband, who is, she calls him the board guy.
They also do a radio show, I think, in Seattle.
But when she's doing the podcast, her husband is called the I guy.
But he has his own disability, he's in a wheelchair.
So this is a wonderful pair.
But it's great.
They went to the Museum of Flight in Seattle,
which by the way is where the Hercules is based,
known to some incorrectly as the Spruce Goose,
that's how it hues enormous wooden aircraft.
If you've seen the movie The Aviator, then you know what I'm talking about.
So they go to the Museum.
They do some flying in the simulator.
They hook up with seeing eye dogs as puppies,
who are going to be trained to be seeing eye dogs.
But really, it just hit me.
It's like, wow, you know, where is the entire community
to do podcasts for blind people?
It must be out there.
You know, can't we, and believe me, if someone will help me produce,
I'd be happy to do it.
You know, we should have readings of newspapers.
We should have readings of magazines of, you know,
all kinds of stuff.
There are lots of people out there who really
would like to do something with podcasts.
But maybe, you know, maybe you're just not,
you don't know what to say.
Maybe you have no content.
Hey, there's plenty to be done for the blind community.
And the community is obviously huge.
And what an opportunity.
What an opportunity to do some great, great stuff
for an entire segment of the population
that has really been crippled by today's media.
Yes, sure.
We've got close captions on television and, you know,
we have radio, but, you know, to really be able to expand
into any, any area that currently is not sufficiently served
by, by the media by, I hate saying,
well, I guess I can say traditional media or mainstream media,
you know, radio and television and newspapers,
all in print as well.
It's just a great opportunity.
So think about that.
And of course, you should check out,
Marlene, by ear, her podcast,
which you can find in today's show notes
for the daily source code at dailysourcecode.com.
Hey, Adam.
It's Chris from the Technoblog.com audio feed.
Just sending the promo over.
So you know who we are and what we do.
What do we talk about on the Technoblog.com audio feed?
Well, we talk about video games.
It's their main topic because it's a huge industry
and you gotta know what you're doing.
You know, so you don't buy some grabs.
So we're going to make sure that you know what you're buying
and know you'll enjoy it.
What else do we talk about?
We talk about the new systems that aren't even out yet.
We got the new Xbox.
Everyone's coming out with these new systems.
And you can't know whether it's worth buying or not.
And we're going to tell you.
We're going to talk about the new as it comes out.
So that you can be an informed buyer when those come out on the shelf.
So what are you waiting for?
Go to Technoblog.com right now.
And sign up for the Technoblog audio feed.
Just throw it in your RSS reader and you're set to go.
Because the Technoblog.com we take live.
One CPU cycle at a time.
Now back to you Adam and the daily source code.
See, it always happens just when I'm recording the show.
I start to get phone calls.
So that was Crystal the PA from Holland.
So I'll have to call her back in a second.
She just have to wait.
I'm so sorry.
Doing the podcast.
I was listening to Morning Coffee Notes.
That's Dave Winner's podcast.
And he was in Seattle.
And he was there with.
Oh, man, I should really open up my browser.
My browser should not.
I was either with Mr. Terone from the formerly of the Engadget podcast.
And he was there with one other person who I think was from Microsoft.
Oh, that's my.
My voice mail telling me that Crystal is left a message.
Hold on a second.
I've opened up Firefox here.
Let me just see here to Starbucks.
Yeah, coffee notes podcast.
Filterone who is left.
Engadget.
And is the Engadget podcast now gone?
Is that now a gaping hole in the podcast industry that needs to be filled?
It might be.
He's now at Make Mag.
And oh, Beth goes a Microsoft.
So they were in Kirkland Washington.
I guess that's near Seattle.
And the audio wasn't too great.
So I'm not going to play any of that.
But what was really interesting was the thought that came up.
I think it was Beth who mentioned it.
That wouldn't be awesome.
If, you know, now we have these satellite companies.
These satellite radio companies.
Examine serious.
If there could be a channel, which we could flow podcasts through.
You know, and she called it kind of like a community.
Was it like a community access channel.
Which sounded a lot like what openpodcast.org is doing.
Which I love.
I'm a subscriber.
That's one of the feeds that I listened to all the time.
I've been a pro.
Most of the time.
Sometimes they actually communicate through openpodcast.org.
And, you know, one person will say something to the person will come back.
And you can access it through different ways.
You can dial in with a phone number.
They've got and just leave a voice mail.
And I get sent out of this podcast.
Or I think you can email a URL where your MP3 file can be found.
I don't know if you can actually mail an MP3 file itself.
Of course, you'd have to have some kind of.
It's going to sound like gatekeeper controls.
But I guess that's kind of what it is because, you know,
I see with iPod.org, as I mentioned earlier,
people will just spam the shit out of anything that's wide open.
So you have to have some kind of controls on it to.
You determine what goes through.
Based upon not necessarily content, but probably length.
You know, imagine someone tying up the community access channel for.
For hours.
So you have to put some kind of time limit on it.
But I thought that's a great idea.
And I thought that's something I've got to talk about.
Talk to some people about.
I really, really like that idea.
And I was on my way to the US.
I think the last trip.
And by the way, I may be leaving Wednesday again for a quick.
Lightning tour of San Francisco and New York.
That's not entirely set in stone, but it looks like that's going to happen.
So I might leave Wednesday and come back during the weekend.
Oh, yeah, it's busy.
And I'm a big fan of the vinyl podcast.
And the vinyl, but Cody does the vinyl podcast.
What does he call it to fair use of music that's out of print.
He plays vinyl records from his own collection.
And he played a song which we've all heard a million times.
I guarantee you've heard this.
If you've been listening to music since the 80s.
The early 80s, even hip hop, you have heard pieces of this song.
Predominantly the sample of the drum bongo beat.
That is featured predominantly throughout the track.
And there's really this whole break at a certain point.
And you'll just say, oh, man, I've heard this in so many hip hop records.
One of the most sampled songs.
The incredible bongo band.
I'm not going to play the whole wind up because Cody does a whole intro to every single time he plays
a tune about the background of the song and the singers and etc.
And some of the history.
So I'm going to skip that.
You can find them at vinylpodcast.org.
And of course, it'll be listed in the show notes.
But check out a little bit of his intro and then groove along to the incredible bongo band.
Welcome to the vinylpodcast.
Fair use of forgotten music.
It was supposed to, it wasn't supposed to rewind.
It was supposed to start when I cut it up.
Hold on.
And it's worse.
The group sounds like a cross between a marching band and a cheesy big band.
But at its best, the percussion breaks a rock solid and funky.
My general feeling is that Apache, the incredible bongo band's cover of the shadow's song,
often veers toward the cheesy.
But I long ago cease to be a reliable critic of this song.
It all sounds good to me because I know what's coming a little more than two minutes into the song.
One of the funkiest and most iconic drum breaks I've ever heard.
These drums were a staple of early hip hop played in the parks by Africa Bandbada,
covered by sugar hill gang and sampled over and over again.
I just love them.
So do me a favor.
Bear with this track for a couple of minutes or if it's just too much to bear, fast forward a little.
Here's a passive struck by the incredible bongo band on the vinyl podcast.
Now crank this shit up.
Recognize it.
Oh yeah, baby.
Oh yeah.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Yes.
Oh whoa.
Oh.
So you can just imagine me sitting in the airplane, I got up, had this song on the headphones.
You need to go for a bathroom break and then all of a sudden the Vongo break came and it just tripped me out.
I was freaking in the aisles.
Why it almost made me want to rap?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, one, two, three.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, my name is Matterbox.
Catch with large army.
The fuck's your ladies and I'm my best part.
I'm going down in history.
As the widest part has never built.
So I'm feeling the highs.
And you're feeling the lows.
And the beat starts to happen.
Two, two, two, three.
I've got a degree in rap.
I've got a PhD in rap.
I'm cannon here on the source probe.
Baby, think I too much time.
Check it out now.
Okay.
So, you get the picture, right?
Incredible, Bongo Band.
If you want to hear the whole vinyl podcast all the information and the link to the show of course can be found in the show
notes for today's daily source code.
So, this is just another, you know, perfect example of how
We can work to adjust the music industry to give us this stuff.
You know?
Like, man, this is like so incredibly valuable,
So incredibly valuable and look at all the hits that were based upon this and you know, if you
Taking to account where people are doing with mashups, there's so much stuff that can be done
It's to me. It's extremely exciting
say
Have you ever gotten the feeling that you want to listen to a kid rebel about random stuff? Sure
Have you
Ever wanted to
Know the opinions of the younger generation. Yeah the source code mini ever have that fetish
to
Listen in on a kid's mind
Definitely well guess what now you can and
You could check
Oops, I don't know what happened there. Why did that that wasn't supposed to happen? Let's try that again
See we can get that
promo roll it well
Shoot so for some reason it unloaded. Okay. It's the source code mini
13-year-old podcaster and yes, indeed
I am subscribed I definitely want to live inside the head of a 13-year-old because well, I've got a 14-year-old here and you know
I got to pay attention to what's going on basically
This is one that I caught from the dawn and do show. They played this and
Found a link to the song in their show notes so I'll reciprocate and put this one into my show notes for today
You got to love the song about podcasting. This is podcast star on the daily source code
Just have to be a big man. I'll bet it's too well
She wants fame and I just want her back
It's up a microphone recorded some thoughts what I was alone
Looking for love. I found what I could be
With the knowledge
I just want to be a podcast star
I just want to be a podcast
Good with my friend, Pat, we cut a little weekly podcast called this, and that.
Until if you joke, then spill our bones of you.
Once you will.
Stop it, I really suck.
Now it's fun to watch as I know, but it's grown.
Tell all your friends who you listen to.
I want to be as popular as doing it true.
Don't let true, don't let true.
I just want to be a protestist.
I want to be a protestist.
I want a young time, I can't until I drop
Follow the history, look at me, at me, at me, at me, at me, at me
Take good home, America, is a roof for us in this hysteria
Someone famous, one release, I want to be a star, can I have it please?
I just want to be a fighter star, I just want to be a fighter star
Man, how much does that rock?
I just want to pay a podcast star on your daily store's code.
Hi there, Adam.
My name is Annie Rubens, and today I want to tell you something about an endangered species.
The species is almost extinct, and as far as I know, there's only two of them left,
two of those little funny creatures.
And well, the species is German female podcasters, and the only thing you can do to help
us not get extinct is listen to our shows, and mine can be found, it's a three minute
daily podcast show, and it can be found at www.annigroobens.de, and it is called Schlaflos
in Mnchen, which means sleepless in Munich, okay?
I hope you tune into that.
Thank you, bye-bye.
All right, thank you very much.
One more problem to go, then I got a mashup before I got to get out of here, sis.
Hello?
Oh, unable to play.
The hell was that?
Ooh, I got a cast blaster error, this is cool, oh by the way, I have upgraded to beta version
10, so you need to provide some feedback on that one, all right, let me play the last mashup
then, which you'll be able to find in the show notes for today.
The four tops and weird al-yangritch, ebay, and me and your love.
You better crank this one up, stick it in your ear.
Be back for a run, me and snow have loathe us, Murphy, TV-travel, I bought on eBay, my house, is filled
with this crack, shows up in bubble wrap, most every day, where I bought on eBay,
tell me why, baby I need your love.
Tell me why you got the phone on your love, baby I need your love.
Tell me why you got the phone on your love.
Oh, I got a phone on your love, you need me, just like my feedback, it plus plus.
They all say, they love me on eBay, go to buy, baby I need your love, baby, I need your love.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Yer watch please, I'm buying...
Where is being there?
Baby I need your love
Who is inside to have all your joy shown?
We're now in the four tops Ebay, I need your love and at the end of the daily source code for Monday, April 25th, 2005.
And I got a lot to do today as I said.
We actually have some financial stuff to take care of, which means paying the bills.
And that's why crystal is calling.
I also got to get those contact lenses.
And oh yeah, remember, I got to talk to Chris from Podcast Alan.
It seems he's found out a sure fireproof way to stop all the voting scams and the cheating that's going
on.
He's really figured it out this time, which I'm excited about.
Do you want the ratings to be as honest as possible obviously?
I think I'm going to get him on.
Maybe I'll have him on the show for tomorrow.
We'll talk about what he's doing because the results may change significantly.
And some of the folks are in the top.
And no longer be in the top five or ten.
So we'll see if we can get him on the Skype tomorrow for the main review of what's going on over at Podcast Alan.
Alright, that's it for today's show.
Comments, Adam at Curried.com or leave it on the weblog www.curried.com.
You can find the podcast feed and the latest show.
And some of the archives at www.damicorsco.com.
And if you'd like to send a promo send it to Adam at Curried.com.
And the subject would DSE space promo.
And the name of your show.
And I'm linked to the MP3, but I can play.
And hopefully the cast blast will take care of all the rats.
Alright everybody, I'll check you tomorrow. Bye. Bye.