Delta Sierra Charly 217.
Your DJ.
Are you doing that?
Your DJ has only just begun.
It's Adam Curry.
You are a bitch.
Oh yeah.
I apologize.
I'm a dick.
So dick some respect.
Wacky stuff.
Oh yeah.
Ditto yeah.
You know I'm an idiot.
I'm an idiot.
Don't get so much fat.
Ditto yeah.
Wacky stuff.
By the way, you're hearing that wild cherry sign.
I was like, what's that 1970s?
It's a 78.
Something like that.
Really think I give a shit.
Ditto yeah.
Wacky stuff.
Touch anything sniffed off.
Ditto yeah.
Touch anything and touch anything.
I'm an idiot.
Watch it tots you touch it tots.
Touch it tots you touch it tots.
You're a bad man and you made me cry.
I hate you.
You're, you know, I'm an idiot.
Ditto moaf few
What you just said is one of the most insanely idiotic things I have ever heard.
At no point will you even close to anything that could be considered a rational thought.
Everyone in this room is now dumber for having left into it.
Oh boy.
It's the end of the week almost the end of the month that your source code for the 29th of July.
In the entire week doing their source code every single day, truly the daily source code.
Languette is doing a funky.
It's Friday.
The weather is nice here in the UK and we're going to be a little heavy on the pod save.
I hope you don't mind.
It's a little funky day.
My mom is in the hospital.
She just had just actually got a phone call that she finished her operation.
It's just finished.
This was a...
Some kind of...
Well, when I quite sure what it was yet.
Some kind of abscess.
Some kind of tumor thing in her hip.
It's been a bit of a bummer a year for mom.
But everything went well and I'll be able to talk to her in about an hour.
So I figured I'd send out some good positive vibes and play some cool rock music for her as well.
So we're ramping up.
We're getting ready for our vacation.
We'll show all of you an exactly one week from now.
Oh, it reminds me.
I've got a books and flights.
Take a look at that.
As I said, weather is really nice.
Kind of like high 70s, but not too much sun.
I do have the Converre wearing away in the background.
You'll hear that and we'll get rid of some of the music.
And let me see.
Got a couple of things we want to talk about.
The feedback has been enormous on three topics in particular from the past couple of days.
So we'll be looking at some email as well.
But to kick it off, I figured we'd play something that I pulled off of the pod safe music
network.
These guys were on the warp tour.
I only know about the warp tour because my dear daughter Christina has been wanting to check out
the warp tour, one of these summers.
Listen to the pod safe music network and music.photshow.com.
I think you'll dig in.
This is Dila Vega.
Let burn on the source cup.
I'm trying to see if I can tell they need school mode.
Why you ain't trying to get away.
We don't have our new nation.
It's about to turn to respect for your reasons.
Don't worry me, my cousin.
That's how this is on the warp tour.
These summer war is mine.
The war is dead.
No, they summer war is mine.
It's about to turn to respect for your reasons.
Don't worry me, my cousin.
That's how this is on the warp tour.
Listen to the pod safe music network and music.
Listen to the pod safe music.
Listen to the for the pod there.
took some time to actually explain the difference between the high quality guaranteed delivery,
you can stream it and listen to it in real time versus the subscription ban with lots
of suggestions, a lot of marketing-based suggestions, releasing stuff at different times.
Now actually there's a couple of pieces of feedback I'm going to play today about that.
But I have a question for you because I feel that we don't have time on our side in this
particular issue because podcasting is growing.
There's relatively a few people that actually still know what podcasting is about,
just because iTunes came out, doesn't mean the whole world understands it yet.
In fact, there's a whole new slew, this whole wave of press is coming back and I really get the
feeling that there's going to be another round of articles, maybe focus a little bit more on
the business aspects of podcasting, maybe hopefully more focus on the music aspects because
we're doing it. We are completely creating our own music industry only now is only for the
sales to start kicking in, which is happening slowly but surely. And I'm very, very excited about that.
But when it comes to the bandwidth, we've got a lot of mainstream media out there wanting to
podcast now and actually they are podcasting. And as I said earlier, the problem is the bandwidth
is not free. It may seem that way and maybe you think you have an account that offers unlimited
bandwidth but that's changing very, very rapidly. And as we've gone through this before, there's
kind of a slash dot effect certainly from the daily source code. If I mentioned someone,
lots of times they run out of bandwidth, they go down and it sucks. So we have to come up with
some fixes very, very soon. So here's a question for you. This is what I'd like some feedback on because
while we're figuring this out, while we're figuring out different ways of delivery, should we
be releasing stuff in the middle of the night, incentivizing people to subscribe, which by the way,
I think we should do anyway because subscribing to podcasts, it really is, it's magic,
you know. And when there's a new show which is shows up, you know, there's not going to be that much
benefit. I'm not even drinking a sense out when I'm actually, I put water in my coffee cup,
maybe that's it. Maybe just the the faint aroma of the sense here does it. By the way, I got
a call from the agency that represents sense here. Let's see if something comes out of that, huh?
Um, so, you know, there's a whole bunch of things that we need to work on, but I don't want to be too
late, you know, because as podcasting starts to grow, the small, you know, the small indie podcaster
is going to run into more and more trouble and just cost money, you know, ranging from anywhere
from, and I've really, and I've talked to a lot of people about this, and a lot of content
delivery networks, and a lot of bandwidth providers. And it's still, you know, if you're looking at
your per gigabyte transfer charge, it's anywhere from 10 cents to, you know, anywhere up to 3035
cents per listener. And, you know, again, this is what killed the streaming business. It is,
uh, besides the fact that you had to listen to that app, your computer, which wasn't all that
fantastic because we're to listen to the radio in your car, which is what the iPod gave us. Um, but
the, you know, it's not a very good model when every person you add to your listener-based
costume more money, unless you can offset that with revenue. So here's a question, and I want
you to really think about it. Let's say, um, okay, just for argument, say, I footage the bill.
And I provided free bandwidth hosting for anybody who want any indie podcaster that is,
who wants to do a podcast, whether you have 10 listeners, and I think every podcaster has at least 10
listeners, if you count yourself, your friends, and your family, which is great, you know,
but even that is still, each podcast is going to cost you, you know, three bucks. Now,
you can put that yourself, but if you start to grow and gain traction, and I guess ultimately,
it's cool if more people are listening to what you have to say, if you got it all for free,
would you be willing to take a obligatory advertising? So, if the offset of that cost was,
that you had an ad at the beginning or the end of your podcast that was inserted automatically,
would you be interested? Now, I'm sure there's a lot of people who would not be interested,
and that's okay. I don't want any geod shit about advertising or not. And, you know,
and I'm not talking about your typical radio spots, 20 seconds in your face bullshit, but yeah,
or, you know, there are many different ways, and I hope that we can change the face of advertising,
the way we're changing the face of music, but would you be willing to offset that? Because that's
a deal, I'd be more than willing to make, because I think that we could do that. And by the way,
not just an offset, but if it really started to take off, then, of course, you'd get a cut of that advertising.
That's what I'd like you to think about over the weekend. Don't email me immediately for two reasons.
When I want you to think about it, and two, my Gmail accounts pretty full. Hello?
Hello? You were supposed to start there on cue. Oh, man. Now, what the frick is going on here?
I've got the spinning beach ball of death. Oh, how do I hate that? Okay, so while that thing is spinning around,
like a jackass, let's go to some email then, shall we? U.S. Highways. A lot of feedback on the U.S.
Highways thread that we've been talking about. It actually looks like my computer is locking up here.
This is not a good sign. Now, I can't get to my Gmail, or as that totally hosed out as well. Hold on, let me see what's
my connection is still good. God, I wasn't such a such a vibe there.
Okay, still have the beach ball. Hold on a second. Let me try this. Hold on.
Okay, I know what the problem is. Actually, pause that for a second. It's the same frickin problem we've
had before. If you have a mounted, draw actually had my eye disc mounted. And when you want to play a song,
for some reason, Megaseg, you know, well, no, not for some reason. It tries to talk to your file system.
The file system is busy trying to get the shit rolling. So, I've just disconnected my eye disc.
Now, let's try it and see if it works now. My name is Kevin. And I am his youthful ward, Doug,
and you're listening to the strange brood.
We have a podcast where two guys come as you with a whole lot of funny from the Chicago suburbs.
Each week, we'll give you a several segments that you can count on to put a smile on your face,
including Dr. Phil's asschapers. And this really does.
We show my hand into this, you know, wet sticky goo and water began to just dump about us.
I walked around a few steps and obviously, you know, something was sticking in my foot.
Politics. Well, and you did work for the Howard Dean campaign. I did do a fairly
substantial amount of work for the Harry, Harry. Yeah, Harry, Harry, Harry, Harry, Harry.
We do man on the street interviews, including this gem from the game lesbian Pride parade.
Subscribe to me once on top of your car here. Well, it's it's a rooster, but it's the
Chinese new year, year of the cock. And we are the only podcast with the weekly Ilitavaya's
Trombone Dwayne. Like this one.
So check us out at www.TheStrangeBroodBROD.com. TheStrangeBrood be ready to expect the unexpected.
Unless you expect funny, because you'll get a crap load of that.
Hot Joe, content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
Welcome to the first UK Direct reel, podcast for Scoons. Our aim is simple.
The search the internet and present the best quality podcast we've been find to support
teaching and learning. Explore with us the educational potential of podcasting.
Selected podcasts can be viewed at our website www.ipodcast.org.uk.
If you have a podcast suitable for children and young people, please let us know. Contact us
via our website www.ipodcast.org.
Alrighty, the UK podcasters doing fine. Grons steadily as we speak. It's about three
20 in the afternoon on Friday here at Curry Cottage in the UK, Patricia just came in.
And so what were you? What were you cursing about? So I've disconnected the IDisc and now it should
be. That little blip you heard in that previous promo was me disconnecting the IDisc. I guess that's
a problem, you know. And some things going something peculiar is happening here. It seems that
I've got this really expensive bandwidth provider that provides me with a huge mega pipe to the
house, but sometimes it's actually just say the service level is not up to par. That's easy
net. We've talked about that before. So I'll have to delve into that. I'll do that next week. I'm
just not feeling up to it right now. For app as long as I've got some bandwidth somewhere. So anyway,
we talked about the server bandwidth. That was in the previous bit. Now Willy Wonka, my goodness.
I got a lot of response about saying that I'd heard the review on cinecast and that,
therefore, was not going to go see it. But I, oh man, I think that was a mistake. Let me just read a
couple of emails here. The most exciting one was from Dawn, Micelli from the Dawn and Drew
shows says boyfriend. I'd love to once he starts off like that boyfriend. We went to go see it and we
fucking loved it and I'm hardcore about the original. The DVD of the original is so interesting as they
interviewed the kids who have all grown up into freak accountants. Oh, can we please hire one of
them for the pod show? Yeah, of course. Go find them, girl. But then again, Johnny Depp makes
me tingling my swimsuit place. But then again, so the Gene Wilder, even with this terrible hair.
So I got a, just a crap load of, of comments on Willy Wonka and Christina actually
matches well. Madge Weinstein also said, you know, go see it. You're going to like it. So,
we're going to do that. Christina and I are going to go Sunday. We're going to go see it and I will
provide my unobjective review. Objective review. Objective review, obviously. So,
yeah, maybe it is something I want to see. I've just been such a die,
die hard fan about, you know, about about the original. And, you know, I told you I could watch it
anytime and still love it. So, I'm going to go. I hope I don't get disappointed. But from what I'm
reading, the feedback has been really astronomical from a lot of other people whose opinions I also
respect. So, let's see. Oh, I want to talk about the blue angel again, the NBA 3 that I have.
I'm really loving this box. I don't know, it has this voice dialing. So, first of all, what it does
is when a call comes in, it'll announce the number with a voice and I have the English voice
loaded, which is kind of sweet. But you can also just say, you know, call someone, call them on their
mobile or at home or whatever, and it'll dial it for you. And I'll ask you verify if that's the
number you want to call. So, you don't mess that up. And so, I love that because I have it
clipped to my belt now and it's a pain in the ass to have to go look and see, you know, who's calling.
So, you don't have to do that. That's a very cool feature. And additionally, this transcriber,
where you can write on the screen and then it recognizes your handwriting, it actually works.
So, I'm kind of for going using the keyboard, which is a nice feature that you slide it up
and there's a built-in keyboard. I rarely ever use the pen for tapping it on the software keyboard
that's built into the interface, but now this transcriber thing, I'm all over it. I'm totally, totally
loving it. Here's a song that's not listed on the pod save music network yet, but it could be soon.
It's her and get away, country rock on the daily source code.
Time for a break from this downtown real regrets when I leave.
It's my way to be free. I need a gateway far away, a place where I can't stay. I can't wait,
and I won't delay, so I can't stand on the night with you.
I'm traveling alone, finally on my own. Done with the past, if I'm too low,
I won't be certain to you. Don't know if I'll make your edges wait as soon.
No regrets when I leave. It's my way to be free.
I've done enough, way in the end.
I won't stay. With no fear, one was foggy then, it's crystal clear. There's no free in my own company.
It's my way to be free. I need a gateway far away, a place where I can't stay. I can't wait,
and I won't delay, so I can't stand on the night with you.
I'm traveling alone, finally on my own. Done with the past, if I'm too low,
I can't stand on the night with you.
Yeah, I could be listed on the podcast music network. I meant it should be listed on the
podcast music network her, get away sent to me by just a little singer of the band herself.
Like that, very much. You know what it is? This is almost seems like a new music
Tuesday on a Friday, right? I've been in the middle of the hits for most of my adult life. I was on
big time radio and television since I was 19, and I really lived in the middle of this big
compressed top 40 sound, and I had forgotten how to listen to music, how to appreciate music,
how to, it's hard to explain. It's just like I had a complete overdose of the hits, and it was
very, very hard for me to, it's taken me actually years to get kind of back into living,
able to listen to music, and with this podsafe music, it's happening. I'm loving it. There's just
so much good stuff out there. It's funny I was talking to Don Katz, the CEO of Audible. We've
talked about him before on the source code, and we're talking about podsafe music, and he said,
so what kind of stuff is it? Is it any good? What's the quality of it? I said,
first of all, the recording quality is no different from somebody who's been releasing
records through a record company for years, because we've got the same tools, the exact same
tools that the so-called pros use is what the podsafeers are using. So then it comes out on a song,
writing a musician'ship, and talent, and artistry, and you know what, there is a cool, there's a
lot of it out there. Hey Adam, it's Chris for the financial aid podcast at www.financialaidpodcast.com,
with some audio feedback on interstate highways, two curiosities. In the United States with three
digit interstate city, indicates it's a spur loop. It's something that goes around the city,
so for example, if you're driving I-95, there's I-495, which goes around the city of Boston,
so you don't have to go through it. When you're driving out towards Worcester, I-90 goes through
Worcester, I-290 goes around it. The second thing is, when you look at the exit signs,
if the exit sign says exit 20 or exit 22, the little thing at the top of the sign, if it's on the
right side of the sign, it's a right hand exit, it's on the left hand side of the sign,
so left hand exit, if it's in the middle, then it's anybody's guess. Love your show, hope you
have, I have in a great time, back in England, hope to see you back in the state soon. Take care,
have a great vacation. Thank you very much, Chris, for so I tried to get to my Gmail earlier,
I think I can get to it now, because I had a couple more interesting tidbits that people sent in.
Uh, I don't know, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, that's from Kevin, hold on, I want to get to the,
get to the right one, hold on a second, because it was really interesting.
Where is it? Okay, Brian Matthews is one of several people who sent this into me that Eisenhower
also required the one out of every six miles of interstate be straight, so in times of war,
they could be used as impromptu runways for aircraft, I find that fascinating. In fact,
I'd like to try that one time, I'm flying in this state. Also, a lot of information about the
TSA locks, I've got some links that I'll share with you on, um, in the show notes for today's
source code, there are indeed two officially sanctioned locks. One as we discussed is travel
century, um, but essentially if by mistake, the TSA cuts a lock, oh, that's Skype. Go away,
go away, go away, I'm busy. It's amazing, you know, you can't, there's no way to keep Skype on,
but the shut it up, you can be invisible, but people can still call you. Hold on a second,
let me give it to this. No, no, oh, it's cast blaster Mike, I'll get to you in a second, Mike,
we're gonna call it, uh, oh, we're gonna call, we're gonna call. Now, we're gonna call it a
fokk hola. Oh, uh, oh, uh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Sorry for that small interruption, um, but apparently, if you, um, if it has been cut off,
the, um, the lock that is you can get a replacement, so I'm gonna, uh, next time is Sanfurt
I'm just going to go back to the Tummy store and see if I can get a new lock and ask
them exactly if they know what happened.
So stay tuned for more on that and highways and other extremely interesting stuff that
makes you feel good but doesn't make you richer.
Hey Adam, this is Jeff from podcastshuffle.com, great show, love the source code.
Just an idea for you and your bandwidth was, why don't you delay posting the MP3 file on
the website and encourage more people to subscribe.
If you're posting the MP3 up on, you know, curried.com, the same time that it ends up
in the RSS feed, you're really encouraging people to continue their existing actions.
Now I know you've mentioned the past like 60, 70% of your downloads are from the website
so you have to be careful not to upset anybody but, you know, if you really want to encourage
people to subscribe, that would be one of my suggestions is, you know, give this subscribers
a benefit and you know, encourage the web browsers, web browser users, you know, to subscribe
in order to get that benefit.
You know, it's happened in other medias like magazines.
I know as a subscribers at Business Week magazine, I get it before it shows up on the
newsstand.
I've had a couple of video games, mags, where, you know, since I subscribe to their magazine,
I got a, you know, like a free demo CD and if I didn't subscribe to it, like if I picked
it up at the newsstand, I would have to pay extra for that.
So just a thought, maybe it would work for you, talk to you later.
All right, thank you very much.
So we were talking about that earlier and again, I want to see if what we talked about
and again, this is something I want to think about over the weekend, don't send me email
immediately, but think about if you got everything for free in perpetuity, but it would
be offset by advertising and above a certain level, you would actually start to make
some money on that, would you be interested?
Do I hear my phone about it to ring?
You know, I've got to just shut off all communications when I'm doing the show is too much
incoming.
All right, let's wind up the week with our anthem.
I just can't get enough of it.
I have this on my earphones all the time, singing along like a hurt cat.
Cruise Box FCC, dig in.
We back last summer, when mainstream radio was such a fucking bummer, no ending music, nothing
to funny.
Clear channel motherfuckers, edit for the murder.
It's a lie, I heard it fall.
Now you can't have it all.
I heard it on a podcast, rockin' fucking radio, you wanted it, you got it.
Just downloaded a part it on a podcast, no one's gonna stop you telling KFC seats, pick it, pick it,
the revs, shows off.
Do you remember your first computer, that place that shit was like a freakin' roater,
now we go by by downloading files fast, this meant to everyone who's ever done a podcast.
It's his duty, now you're seeing each and every nation.
Real is got to do its own multiplication.
Me, that song, sing along, mash it up from the tip.
Real fucking loads of out-of-gurn things in somebody heard the call.
Now you can have it all.
Everybody have made it.
Everybody has made it all.
People who are in theuktion of T Sound.
All with no evidence to make it clear before the end of a podcast is broken-
Rockin' fuckin' radio, goin'
Rockin' just downloadin'
Rockin' on a podcast
You know what's gonna stop it,
Belly, air, C, C,
Stickin' giggin'
Don't ban the blue shoes on my podcast
Rockin' fuckin' radio,
Wantin' giggin'
Rockin' just downloadin'
Rockin' on a podcast
You know what's gonna stop you,
Tellin' C, C, C,
Stickin' giggin'
The rummaging of all
Still sorta like this
Sorry had to sing along, couldn't help it
You know what's so great about this song, you'll never hear it on mainstream radio, because it's got all those bad, bad words in
Here's box, tell the FCC to stay in our world
Alright, that's it for the source code for today, why not up the week
Hope you enjoyed it
If you're interested in any of the songs that you heard just head on over to
DailySourceCode.com or www.curry.com
And as you can find links to everything we talked about, and of course all the pod save music
Alright, so I'm going to go talk to Casplaster Mike, we had a call scheduled for six minutes ago
And after that we call him my mom, apparently everything's fine, so just see if I can give her some more positive vibes
And I appreciate you tuning in, if you want to send me feedback out of Maccurry.com
Please don't attach files, at least not through the weekend, because I'm still trying to get the ratio of usage of my Gmail to the ever growing
This space of my Gmail in the correct ratio
You can always just point to a file somewhere at number five
You want to send in promos, you could use a couple more
It's submit at podshow.com
Pod save music is pod save, podshow.com don't forget to check out the pod save music network
And of course, mashups, mashup or podshow.com
Have yourself great weekend
I'm just going to chill out do a little bit of flying tomorrow
As I said, the in laws are going to be picked up and I can do an hour
So near the cottage just to get some stick time
Thank you very much for subscribing
Take care of yourself, have a great weekend, bye bye y'all
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear