Welcome to Better Bad News, and in the news today, Adam Curry did not take credit for someone
else's work today.
He is, however, rewriting world history and you will be surprised that the things Adam
Curry has done.
Adam Curry has never gotten the credit he deserves for inventing flannel socks, really simple
flannel socks.
If you know about something else that Adam Curry has not received enough credit for, please
feed it to BetterBadNews.com, and somebody here will correct the record.
Adam Curry wrote large sections of Leviticus, but nobody can translate it for instance,
what does this mean?
Be not unclean in fields during the time of month reserved for unsubstantiated rumors regarding
the new attitude at Google.
If you know about something else that Adam Curry has not received enough credit for, please
feed it to BetterBad News.
So, we bring good podcasts to life.
Listen to the world with all the remains, and they will see you again.
They will be dead in price, just bear with you the night, take care, and we will see you
again.
Can you know, this time is no way out, take care, no one else will be your man,
take care, no one else will be your man, take care, no one else will be your man,
take care, no one else will be your man, take care, no one else will be your man, take care
and we will see you again, take care, no one else will be your man, take care, no one else will be your
man, your man, take care, no one else will be your man, take care
Sometimes my life is not a way
Who heard so sweet I can't lie
No one can't deny
So let him come in no
Nobody knows, nobody knows
I'll be on my mind for a day
Because I can't lie anyway
Take it out
I don't want to see you lie here
This guy is no way
I'll take it out
No one else can't deny
What a fuck you
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Take it out
I'll walk you in my hand
This guy is no way
I'll take it out
No one else can't deny
So let him come in no one else can't deny
The perfect way to kick off your Thursday
Nice and dreary here outside the cottage
Everybody, how you doing?
Welcome to the Daily Source code
It isn't either Thursday
And today we're going to talk about
a lot of music industry stuff
industry stuff we got yeah actually just a lot of music industry stuff it seems
that a lot of stuff has been popping up we talked about some of that yesterday bad
news here I don't don't don't you know don't worry too much but the bad news is
our community mac in the office the one the old G four power no the was that
titanium the titanium power book that man I've had that one for four years I
think the screened crapped out I've had that connected to a cinema display the
old model for years I think yeah maybe even maybe even two years and this
morning this is what Patricia uses to get her email and you know it's been
meticulously set up the setup I have but of course I don't have a backup of the
most recent information which would include some of her emails although she
seems to clean out her email box pretty regularly yeah the drive crash and no
warning this time it just went and then couldn't get it to reboot put in the OSX
pardon emwa the OS 10 startup CD no drive recognized for fact so what and it's
not it's not that I wasn't expecting this to happen sooner or later or that we
had to replace the mac is just now I don't really have time before I leave for
San Francisco to to get a new mac and at the same time to install it so that
it works for Patricia because she does have a certain configuration to use to
so big time bummer yes and he asked you about the rules of Canada
France and about the commercial radio and Germany now comic strip blogger
our buddy on the comments at curie dot com posted a pretty interesting piece
about German commercial radio seems that they have very weak signals and it
really isn't much of an industry but I got an interesting email from Jason
Bryant about Canadian music radio laws and he knows what he's talking
about he says well I actually agreed the first paragraph here on data source
got to 92 you mentioned Canada's rules regarding Canadian content as a
tenure veteran of broadcasting I am all too familiar with Canadian content or
Kant Kant as it's referred to Kant Kant a Canada radio stations must play
a minimum of 35% Canadian content Monday to Fridays between 6 a.m. and 6 p.m.
okay I thought it was much higher stations must also play 35% Kant Kant between
6 a.m. and 12 midnight Monday to Sunday
uh wait a minute that doesn't make a lot of sense well they break down the
time slots like this so stay show okay they break down the time slots like
the so stations have to play 35% during peak times and not just load up the
evening show with Kant Kant okay I got you so 35% is not that bad actually
I think I you know probably a lot of this is a commercial radio in Canada
that's the other question I had um he uh he goes on to say a couple of very
interesting things but in short he says protectionism protectionism protectionism
and over regulation do not work I can only hope our government continues to
move in the direction of free speech and choice as for me I no longer work full-time
in radio I do voiceovers I'm an actor I recently worked on the movie just
friends with Ryan Reynolds which was released by Newcaste in the last month and
I also started a podcast new human podcast with Jason Ryan okay Jason thank you
very much I hope you post this on your uh on your web blog or talk about on your
podcast because I think it'll be good to know a little bit more about that and I came
across actually I'm subscribed to on the record this is from ipressroom.com this is
the show that I played you a snippet from when Ron was interviewed he has a
special episode out and this this thing is fantastic you've got to listen to this
if you want you want to hear a history of podcasting listen how the
California copyright commission discusses this with a panel of experts so the
California copyright commission podcasting panel in this podcast features
Anthony Bruno of billboard magazine Bob left sets of the left sets letter and
attorney Kevin Cole-off and attorney John Ajash Waddles and they go on the record
online on how the recording industry is dealing with the challenges post a
podcast by podcasters to the traditional business of music licensing and you
have got to listen to this first of all there's at one point there's someone
is explaining podcasting and says well Adam Curry you got fired from MTV like whoa
that's new sorry I think I left my own record I don't think I got fired but
you should listen to how they would to first of all to what their
understanding is of the concept of podcasting I heard one quote in there saying well
I don't really think there's anyone listening oh man oh that really blew me away
but most of these guys hadn't heard of podcasting until just very recently it seemed
like the audience was switched on and I don't know if was someone on the panel because
it's very hard to hear it's recorded with an omnidirectional mic just kind of like
sticking up in the air someone actually either on the panel in the audience was very
switched on it was you know was talking about different business models and but
essentially why this is working on what mainstream media has done to drive particularly
radio has done to drive people to podcasting so it's just fascinating to listen to
please listen to the legal conversation about copyrighted music and you can almost
feel where they're coming from no you can feel it they all they in fact they say
where they're coming from and I really encourage you to listen to this
if you're interested in pod safe music or licenses that will come and they are coming
this memory talked about the association of independent music which is musicindy.com
I gave out the wrong website address the other day musicindy.com so that's a UK
organization they have I believe 300 independent record labels and they are coming out with
licenses they've announced it first they told the BBC was coming out then they announced it
which have done now they still haven't published the licenses apparently you have to call them up
and then they'll do deal with you based on an individual you know on an individual basis but
now they don't say outright that everyone has to pay money so if you have a I think if you have
a podcast that you're not making any money from that they may give you a license or a very
normal fee but they're definitely out to get some money from podcasting and they will have
time limitations so details are still not available which is unfortunate you know I yeah
I'd like to know more about it but I think they should be announcing and we shouldn't have to go
requesting that seems a little backwards to me at least that's my personal feeling about that first song
guitar shop asshole I heard that where did I hear that song topless girl is the name of the song
I heard it on extra backshaw big mic played it and it's rough it's it's hard it's it's punk
but it really took me back 20 years in time like yeah I remember I used to be able to pogo for more
than three seconds before falling down and the controversy the controversy continues surrounding
the podcast hijacking it seems to be the most discussed topic on the podcasters email list
at Yahoo I really really do not like in fact I've probably propelled this myself a little bit
but I really don't like the whole concept of the word hijacking when it comes to this story because it
seems like there's just a small lack of understanding between two parties I'm not even sure if
they're now if it's all worked out or if they're friends yet but to call it hijacking you know
that's really what gets you know and I don't think this has been a main a big mainstream press
article just yet but keep calling it hijacking and it will be you know that's the whole idea
hijacking podcasts it's two really sexy words that you just put next to each other and I think we
want to stay away from doing that and hopefully it'll work itself out in the course of the next
next couple of days now it may not be your cup of tea but I encourage you to listen to this song
the shapes
hey who are you guys how'd you get in here
stepping away from the microphone at those guns you're going to fall now go and go pig
time up please don't hurt me a fragile we are the podcast liberation front we have taken
Adam Kree hostage and if I jacked the daily source code be my la revolution be my la revolution be my la revolution
dude you're not even shooting your gun man you're just going pup pup pup pup you and pointing
your fingers in the air well really side man I don't I don't want to shoot nobody I got two strikes
already man and I don't want to punch on in the car then go get it man okay but I need some
quarters for the meter dude you're a real shitty revolutionary if you aren't married to my sister
I never would have left you in the podcast liberation front anyway thought we were the podcast liberation
army man I couldn't get the domain name why always the army why can't we be the podcast
liberation navy because we don't have any boats dumbass my isn't dumb you're as just dumb
dude quit fighting don't you understand we have Mr. Adam Kree we can have whatever we want
he's right let's not fight man all the madness is we have Mr. Adam Kree right Mr. Adam Kree
video Mr. Adam Kree what should we do with him I need time to think dude really commercial or
something I don't know how to work this thing man don't you get a button man
what's the matter Karen I have a terrible sore throat do you have any throat lasenges well
I have my balls my balls what's that it's a throat lasnshape like a lollipop nothing will
sue the or throat faster than my balls wow they sound great do they last a long time absolutely
in fact you can leave my balls in your mouth for hours at a time and that smooth soothing
feeling never goes away wow I can't wait to try them here you go now tell me don't my balls
feel great on the back of your throat mm mm my balls throat lasenges the next time you're
throat hurts lick or suck on my balls now a new limiting bag flavor we are the podcast these
stars we have hijacked a daily source code
yeah free-day whiter man free-day podcast 7 who are they man I don't know man I think one of them
is that Mad wine Steve that chick is one cadente dude you know magic is dude he's better
I'm not knowing hey we still haven't figured out what to do with the out of curry I say we
pass them around dude you're gay you're gay no you're gay no you're gay dude dude look over there
a packo he's got Mr. out of curry oh my boy no really boy oh the packo's gay man he's gay you
do go around the cottage and see if you can find and create stash of leprechaun gold a capitalist
pot father peed what's in the closet here man oh Mr. Adam Curry doesn't seem to want us to
look in there open it up man holy shit in hot damn those video tapes man what's on them
it says here uh introducing every rolls has its torn by poison me 1989 next one says introducing
girl you know it's true by nearly vanilla June 1989 I think these are all of Mr. Adam
Curry's MTV shows all of them see there must be 10,000 tapes in here he's not healthy to
upset about your past Mr. Adam Curry maybe we should put on some MTV for Mr. Adam Curry to watch
I think he likes MTV there you go Mr. Adam Curry hey who the hell is that it looks like
the creep keeper it says it's current loader my way I heard he was dead he is dead man he died in 1997
and he spiced girls press junk in that's a dedicated corpse and amied with wires and shit that's creepy
man look you can see the strings if you look close enough shhh turn that off I think someone's here
he near podcast promo that'll bore them away hey Adam and all the daily source code listeners
this here is random acclaim from North Platinum Brasske inviting everyone to come check out my show
the Nebraska Duce cast the only podcast that's all about Duce in in Nebraska every week
we'll tell you where you can find the best Duce's who's got the best prices and we'll have a
world famous side by side Duce off where we'll pick the week's best Duce's against each other and see
which ones the best we'll tell you which Duce's have the best bouquet which ones are the most
vinegary and which ones are just two-game water in a drink hmm now that's just some fine
taste and Duce right there boy which one you'll just have to listen to the show to find out
so come on by the Nebraska Duce cast and Nebraska Duce cast dot com
Duce cast dude what kind of people listen to this daily cold sore
a daily source code man I don't know man but I'm starting to think they don't get out of the
house too much it was Paco man I think he's still with Adam Curry Paco you okay in there man
boy boy hey wait this gives me an idea I think I know how we can make a lot of money man
Pacific Co's tell way presents a special offer for men women and lovers across the world
if you're looking to spice up your love life look no further than me Adam Curry sex toy
it's not some cheap piece of latex it's not some battery operated plastic gadget no
the Adam Curry sex toy is in fact Adam Curry the Adam Curry sex toy will service your
every need and enhance your love life like nothing ever has with over 35 points of flexible
articulation the Adam Curry sex toy comes ready to perform whether you're a woman a man
a married couple a gay man a gay married couple a group of gay men ready for a party or just looking
for that special something to add to the atmosphere at your bathhouse the Adam Curry sex toy is just
what you've been looking for but never dared to dream possible the Adam Curry sex toy comes
prepared to perform or receive a wide variety of love-making activities including missionaries
doggy style reverse cowgirl don't keep punch fish eye hot lodge and the filthy sand jazz and thanks
to the miracle of podcasting the Adam Curry sex toy now comes with hot vibrating lip-flabbing action
warning hotly-flaping action cannot be turned off so if you're looking to bring your
love life to the next level try out Pacific Coastelways Adam Curry sex toy available
exclusively at Pacific Coastelways.com it puts the ass and podcast and this hijack is going nowhere
hey any of you ever done this before see I was involved in a failed assassination attempt on
Kennedy with the Cuban back in the 60s no dude with Martha Quinn in 1992 she wanted that
ugly for a gay Kennedy on MTV wrote down man don't turn off your phone man we're in the middle of
a high jacket sorry sorry hello mama I can't talk right now okay mama I gotta go I gotta go mama
oh sorry what did you do man I'm not over this statue here man what is that a really Martin figurine
I don't know it it's just a bunch of hair man I think it's him Mr Adam Curry has a
hairy little statue of himself I think it was an award or something man look there's an inscription
to our favorite big hair flag love Pacific Coastelways oh that's really sweet man those guys are the
best oh yeah I hear they give a lot of money to the poor and stuff and they support social causes
and they all have really big penises man dude how would you know that Pacific Coastelways.com
and they got pictures and everything okay first of all that's not even true second why would you look
if it was true I can be curious man the cops we gotta get out of here
buckle you gotta get off Mr Adam Curry man we gotta run I'm stuck I'm stuck I need you to help me
we're doing what do you mean man he got so mad I'm sorry Mr Curry this is gonna hurt you more
than it hurts me oh just put some ice on a mat it will be back
okay I gotta ask Mark and John what a hot lunch is oh man
all right that was definitely interesting thank you very much that that was how long we
take to put that together three days four days there you go once again I've invented something for
the first time the first real official podcast hijack thank you very much to the Pacific Coast
help players Pacific Coast Hel way dot com as we can hear that podcast so continue to talk about
that was that was you know that was that was that was that was a long way to go to for a promo
is what that was more feedback about the music industry please this isn't I even though
we're having some fun here today this is a pretty important show there's some important stuff
that's that's happening I believe that the RIA affiliate members are starting to wake up and figure
out what podcasting is and I don't care what you play just make sure you have permission to play it
make sure you've got both bases covered people ask me this all the time you have to have
permission from the owner of the master so say do you own the masters yes okay could you please say
you was owner of the master's give me permission and you have to have a waiver on the ask cap
be in my broadcast rights so that's also it can just be an email I think is probably sufficient
these days but you have to have permission and you know in hindsight man it was good that
the bronze musician and I'm a broadcast or slash podcaster because we it's almost like we
first saw this coming you know that's what the pod save music network is about is that you have an
automatic license just by signing up as a podcaster or as an artist and if you have any troubles
figuring it out email either Michael Butler or a CC chap and probably if you're a podcaster
a CC can help you and and if you're an artist and you're interested Michael Butler can help you
and feel free to CC me so I can add some signal to noise ratio in there hello Adam my name is Omar
and I live in Fort Lauderdale, Florida and I wanted to let you know about something that really
ticked me off and has a lot to do with licensing and the music industry and all that but I don't know
if you've heard about this particular twist on it I like a lot of people use the widgets feature of OS 10
on my Mac and I really like using this one which it called Paralyrics and it's written by a guy
at the pairworks.com it's a great little widget and like so many others that have been around
when you play your music and iTunes it automatically goes online and displays the lyrics to a song
essentially it's really just a fancy web browser because it's getting what's already on the internet
on those lyrics website. Well I wanted to go and get a more current version because I had a
dot four beta version of it and I go to his website and come to find out he got a cease and the
cis letter apparently a widget that goes out and gets lyrics is now illegal and the studios don't
like it so I looked around and found out that almost all the lyrics if not all of the lyrics
reading widgets on Apple's website which list all the dashboard widgets available are gone.
So now apparently the music industry is going after applications that simply go to the web
and get lyrics are already posted on websites and I don't know if they're going after websites
that post lyrics now but it seems that it's getting a little out of control when you can't even
read the lyrics to a song that that you may or may not own and it just really bugged me and I thought
I'd like you know that this is going on that even lyrics are being wiped off of the internet.
So you and the folks at Pawt Show keep up to good work and the revolution goes on.
Yeah, Vivalada overly was gone!
Yeah indeed that's kind of interesting that that would happen now Omar.
There was a time on the internet when there was a huge issue before the RIA I think was really
organized well enough to do what they're doing now which is combating and protecting their
copyrights. There was an issue over not just lyrics but also guitar, a tablature.
So printouts of what the chords are that are used and that's a publishing right.
You know if you write something, if you find something in a book,
unless it's under fair use you cannot just publish that legally because there's copyright on it and
fair use is a really fuzzy thing. Although it's very clearly defined still I find it a bit fuzzy but
regardless. So now I think that the the music publishers are seeing that this probably not much
you can do about it and I think that was it probably still is quite a significant revenue stream.
lyrics song books teach yourself how to play something with lyrics. You know that's when when
you print up a book like that there's royalties to be paid to the owners of the copyrights of the
words and of the music of the actual score. The notes that are used. It's a very complicated
stuff. I'm you know we all know I'm not a lawyer but I think that what the I don't you didn't
mention who these seasons assist letter came from but probably from the RIA or affiliated company
or a publisher's organization. I don't think they probably realized by now there's no stopping it
you know you can probably shut down some big sites. I don't know if there's been any news about that
recently. I always seem to be able to find something through Google if I'm looking for lyrics.
But I guess what they're trying to do is go to the next level which is stop the application that is
closest to you that deals with this infringement. Now personally I think it's I agree with you.
I think it's stupid you know I think that there's still a very valid market for publishing lyrics
and and score a music in paper written form. I think that lots of people will continue to buy that
but I can see all kinds of reasons why you would not want to restrict access to that information
online. So just be prepared for it because that's they're going to crack down on everything and this
is what happens. You know the radio industry was already on its last legs which arguably could have
gone on forever had you know had podcasting not arrived had satellite radio not come into threaten
the scene. iPods in general just people listening to music their way being control of their own
programming but they were consolidated and that's usually the last gas of any industry is consolidation
and so it's not really true there's only a couple of players. There are many players still certainly
on a global aspect but in the United States there are a couple of players who own a shitload of
frequencies same thing with the music business they've been they're consolidating they're now
really three big labels who work on on the traditional models and who make up the RIA and that's EMI
Sony and Warner Warner Brothers time Warner and and so now they're you know they're just going
after everything they can. There's no more creativity left in that industry. I've been to Warner
I've been to Sony not the EMI but I've been to two of the top three and the carpets of
frying you know it's all you see is suits and lawyers there's no music blasting through the hallways
a very different scene than say only 10 years ago so I think someone's run a little bit of
stray of the airport so that's really who's running the show over there and that's about it just
be very very careful what you're doing because as we grow as we as you know every listener we take
away from mainstream media that's a loss for them and that's the way they see it and they're going to
come after anything they can the same way they did with filed and continue to do with file sharing.
Hey Adam this is Robert Cole the internal candidate a long time listener to the daily source code
and soon to be co-host of the think big for 13 minutes podcast but that's not what this message is about
you often tell your listeners to send you a link to a audio file you want audio feedback you just
say put the file up somewhere on a server somewhere but most people don't have a server somewhere so
the thing that I try to use for you and we'll see if it makes it on to the air the daily source code
is you send it.com you send it.com is up you can transfer up to a gigabyte file we're trying this
with the way file for you to get this message and if it worked you'll get it on the daily source code
or you'll tell people about it if it didn't work well I'll never hear about it but again if you send
it.com it's a server you can just put large files up to a gigabyte there and daily source code
people that don't have a server to put a file up to now can do it anyway from Toronto Canada where
I'm freezing in the cold I'll see you on the flip side now everybody thank you well I really only
played this to let you know that it did make it through here's the reason why I asked people
to make MP3s and put them on servers I don't want to make it too easy certainly you can use
voicemail and I know you can use services like what do I have a J2 number that you can call
up and leave a voicemail it's sent to me as an audio file not an MP3 but at least something that
I can open and convert if I want to I can play easily it's at a.au or probably one of those mobile
formats that it leaves that you get now but you know if I make it that easy then I'm going to spend
a lot of time listening to you know a lot of comments that may be very very long and when someone
has to go through the trouble of creating the MP3 file putting it up on the server doing the
ID3 tags not only does it make my life easier I think it really does filter out the quality of
the feedback you know if you really want to say something here's what you're going to have to do
and otherwise just no way if me to get through all this crap it's unbelievable how much I'm getting
and let me just give you a current Gmail quota I can't remember exactly when they upgraded me to
four gigs which was of course extremely cool let's see it can only have been maybe a month
two months maybe at most I think let me just log into the Gmail right now and see what see what the
current quota is. Man it takes sometimes it really takes a long time here we go.
92 percent three seven five five three thousand seven hundred fifty five megabytes of your
four thousand ninety six megabytes so I'm already 92 percent it's going to it's I wonder since
they put me on some kind of manual manual sizing if it'll grow as I start to approach the
99 to 100 percent or if I'll have to start begging me I really love it though and I gladly pay for
just tell me how much you want me to pay for the storage people tell me all the time they send me emails
about these thirty gigabyte some email services the one hundred gigabyte email services that's
not what it's about what it's about for me is the email program itself the way it works is fantastic
the whole idea of not throwing anything out but really using the power of Google search to find
messages very quickly I have yet to see a service that does that well the short cut cut the key
key short cut commands it's just it's a fantastic service I really really love it so that's
why I just want to stay with it and if I can buy my gigs for storage please I'd be happy to and
I know I think that lots of other people would be happy to it's a great service not paid for this
endorsement by the way yeah and this is Charlie Thompson in Austin Texas it was great to hear
country western tune even though I'm a rock and roll or we live out here with our three
Arabian horses and well you know country music goes along with that anyway my comment to you is
don't you think the ANR guys at the big record companies are digging through the pod safe music
network looking for potential stars I mean talk about a cheap ANR budget now they don't have to travel
from club to club to hear unsigned acts all they have to do is browse the PSM I'd love to hear
your comments on this Adam thanks cheers yeah well good bye cheers back at your buddy
Arabian horses nice well first of all I don't think any of them are doing that yet they will of course
they will and by the way I don't think you'll ever see an artist sign purely based upon
one song or a couple of songs record companies traditionally have a process although it's fuzzy and
can vary from executive to executive but there usually is a showcase involved because they want
to know what the band can do how they look how they perform you know are they right for MTV
all that stuff so yeah but you know what fantastic we want everyone to to discover new music I don't
care if if record company guys do what I think from the the pod safe artists I've spoken to many
of them have done the math and have figured out it just doesn't make any sense why would you want
a mainstream record deal you know a big co record deal why would you want that you will probably
sell more records if you are fortunate enough to be one of the small percentage that does actually
become successful through the through the the music business through the system but based upon
you know selling it directly to the listener with help of all you know your own marketing places
like my space but certainly with podcasts you may sell less records what you'll probably make
more money at the end of the day won't have to sue anyone over it won't be tied to the man
and you own your shit you own your own shit you don't need it I know plenty of pods here the
love spirals they've sold 50,000 records you know Angie B who sent me as wonderful wonderful
throaty feedback comments 50,000 records you know this stuff really does work I just don't think
that you need to resort to the mainstream record companies now there is something that's called the
distribution deal I think there's something very different with this distribution deal is I think
very exciting and that's if someone offers you a distribution deal you definitely should talk to them
because that means they can get your CD into stores this is what a lot of the smaller urban hip hop
R&B labels have with major companies and you know look at them you think those guys got some
bling whilst because they're doing it right because they got the money and they of course they also
take a whole bunch of risk associated with it because you know if you want to if you want to
get your record played then you will have you will be responsible for paying money to stations and by the
way it's exactly how it happens it goes through independent promotions companies but you know you'll
have to pay so only just settle the $10 million lawsuit in New York that spits her brought against them
they paid 10 million bucks because that that's how it happens there is absolute payola you know you'll
have to go and suck some you know what over at the BET and MTV and VH1 and any other music
channel video channel you have to make your own video you'll have to pay for it I think it's freaking
worth it by the way I really am waiting for the first video blogger is that my phone going off
on a second let me just check shoot it was wrong I'll get back to later I think that there will be a
collaboration very soon between a one or more pod save music artist and video bloggers who will you
start to work with the art and the skills that they're honing right now and create fantastic music
videos that will be able to enjoy online there's plenty of communities that trade music videos watch them
I'm really expecting some some big things from it tomorrow got a pack get ready to go it's
going to be a fun weekend San Francisco we have our company Christmas party the first one and it's
going to be in the new office is like could not be more excited I don't have a lot of hair I just
like what for my course and let you know that I think you're great as I know that a lot of heat
for the same things that is on truth it's the shame because I think everyone makes mistakes on
the internet I do mostly things I think everyone's changed a bit about some of the websites I go
so let's look on the right side this is not facing a firing squad of Vietnam this Christmas
anyway here I want to talk about anything then just remember I only let 42 and half minutes
walk from your house and that you are welcome to the home but nice to now Roger do you hear what he said
let me just make sure I heard that correctly did he say he only lives 42 minutes from my house
this is starting to get frightening I'll have a second let me listen to that I can
I don't have any Roger here I'm just a bit about some of the websites I go to but look on the
right side this is not facing a firing squad of Vietnam this Christmas is that a Gary glitter reference
what the hell is that you're not facing a firing squad in Vietnam this Christmas
anyway here I want to talk about anything then just remember I only let 42 and half minutes walk
from your house and that you are welcome to the home but nice to now Roger
okay Roger just to make it very clear please do not come over okay do not come near the cottage
all right thank you very much very nice very kind feedback and I appreciate you know your your
thoughts okay everything happening here once but no Roger that's okay Roger apparently is a
podcaster who lives in in Guilford as well I must be closer in the city than then where we are
okay let's roll out another one from the pod safe music network the you may have noticed
that some of the categories have dropped out we fixed that thanks for the feedback everybody so
you could now search on holiday and this one just mind pop up Joe Copish I'm your snowman baby
I'm your snowman baby you're cold as I so with a 15 don't fall for a flake the frost is a
morning I ride a slew just like as I'm morning I'm your snowman baby you want to taste
of this ice cream I'm your snowman baby get yourself a freaky frozen thrill
I'm your snowman baby let's take your tampongin down the hill
I'll see you in the forecast it's perfect if it inches overnight if you catch my drift
I'll just know man baby the hotter it blows the lower the winch you
I'll just know man baby the roads are slippery so the go where there's so
I'm your snowman baby I get deeper when the temperature is over I'm out in the cold
I have the snow falls the perfect time to play with my snowballs I'm your snowman baby
then you can be my snow blow up
hey baby yeah you want to get your drive with loud
oh yeah I can solve it too baby oh yeah clean your side walk all the way to your
man go
I'm your snowman baby you got me working on a sweat
I'm your snowman baby and when I'm out I'm down I get wet
I'm your snowman baby I'm your snowman baby and now you know that you
miss out but I got you baby don't I'm your snowman baby right on plenty of holiday music at the
pot safe music network and of course I continue to update the xmus.podshow.com podcast
to Christmas songs back to back with holiday greetings from podcasters and podsafe
music artists alike playboys coming out with something called the podcast which will be
basically a video podcast targeted specifically at video iPods and Sony PSP PSP's
with pictures and videos of negative women you can just wait for the parent groups to get
up in arms over that the perfect it's the gift that keeps on giving the perfect Christmas gift
that's going to be interesting thanks for all the tattoo ideas they keep to they keep
streaming in and it's starting to look better and better and wouldn't it be weird if I
actually wound up getting a tattoo that someone I don't even know other than a listener through
the internet and maybe some email conversation that drew that that would be pretty interesting
send more Dr. John says my specific suggestion is to record yourself saying something like
freedom free media or even sent sale then take a screenshot of it take it to your tattoo
artists and hit it that way you could make it something really personal to yourself what is
talking about here oh man he's got a really complicated idea about the audacity icon
oh we think maybe should use a waveform I get it oh okay that's pretty interesting so I could
have wings and then in the middle would be would be a waveform of something that it wouldn't
that be funny then everyone could look at my arms start comparing to find out what what the waveform
actually represents if you took a picture of it maybe you could recreate it that's an interesting
idea Dr. John I like that okay that's cool waveform I think I think we'll go on here I think
there's something happen waveform in the middle and then nice pilot's wings on the outside that's cool
one more brief item about soundvertising Jim said we've come full circle dude belching makes us
think of senseo seeing senseo adds makes us think of the daily source code seeing the senseo
itself makes me belch will drinking senseo make us listen to the daily source code well yeah that's
of course part of the evil plan Jim and I encourage anyone to soundvertise with their audience
based upon a popular television commercial or a product that is unique okay Adam at
curry dot com daily source code dot com if you're listening to us on a serious star's 103
we have Pacific Coast Hellway coming up next followed by magic wine steen and don't introduce show
we keep on going up until 10 o'clock this evening I'll be back tomorrow with the thank god
it's Friday I'm almost ready to travel addition of the daily source code just before I head off
for the weekend to San Francisco and then of course the next show you here will be coming from the new
hq thanks everybody
pod show the best podcast a man can get