Daily source code, Friday April 8th, 2005.
You're DJ!
Are you done?
That's right!
Your DJ has own pages.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
There's been the next generation radio content in my ears.
You don't need us.
It can kill me.
I like to think I'm sighing into this jerk.
Fantastic kiss.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
This is the Daily source code for Friday.
Oh yeah.
Okay, this is a test of the cast blaster.
We're up to date at number four right now.
And a little bit late to unrecording the podcast today.
I've been working with the developers on getting all this stuff working and rocking.
So yeah, I'm still, I figured out how to do the auto function.
Oh, it's kind of interesting.
Which means it's taking care of all the levels for me.
And it's actually sounding pretty good.
Let me just lower the mic a little bit there.
So we have a better mix.
Let me see.
Is this what we want?
Okay.
Oh, Matt.
This is making my life a lot easier.
So it's April 8th, I thought, I hope I said 2005.
I don't know.
Let me just demonstrate my jingles here.
Hold on.
We should do it like this.
There we go.
So I pressed the talk button right now.
Wow, it actually works.
The software is actually taking care of the mixing for me.
What I've done is I have hooked up my regular microphone.
And I believe it's the sound is pretty much where it should be right now.
I've got a great story to tell about this.
So you know, I have the tablet, which I'm recording this on.
It's the only PC I actually own and control.
The only other PC in the house is, well, not own, but controlled by Christina.
You know, you know how that goes, right?
She basically doesn't want me messing around with her shit.
So on the laptop.
Oh, my second one here.
There we go.
On the laptop.
There is only a microphone in.
And yesterday a lot of people commented on the sound on the quality of the sound.
And I said, well, you know, the software doesn't sound too good because your microphone
sounds are muffled.
Again, I wasn't using my regular setup.
What I was using yesterday was an altec lancing, which I don't really think they're known
for, like, banging all of some quality.
It's just one of those, like, you know, kind of like an airplane or helicopter pilot head
sets.
We got the headphones on and there's a little mic that sits in front of your mouth.
Now, that, of course, is the entire reason why it didn't sound as good.
Although I have to say, even for that microphone, it didn't sound too bad at all.
But I really do like the processing of my own mic.
Actually, I want to hang up there with me one second.
I just, what I'd like to do is put on different set of headphones.
I've got the ear buds in here and it sounds like one of them is malfunctioning.
Hold on.
I mean, just walk over to the other side of the studio.
Okay.
So, here's the altec lancing.
Hold on.
I'm just going to plug this in as a headset and see if that sounds any better for me.
Hope we don't get any feedback.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, this sounds much better.
Oh, nice.
Okay.
So, you can hear that now, my echo chamber is working.
I've got the compression on the microphone.
I'm not wearing my glasses right now, so it's kind of hard to see.
If it's, is that working?
One, two, one, two.
Yeah.
Sounds pretty good.
Okay.
So, on the laptop, you only have a microphone.
And on the laptop, you only have a microphone in.
And I tried just putting my, the output of my mixer, which has all the processing of my microphone.
Just so I could use my current microphone.
And of course, these types of mics, the sure SMSM7 that I'm using,
doesn't have a, you know, won't output a signal that you can put into a, into a mic per say.
It's all kind of mismatch between
the prosumer gear that is windows and the professional stuff that, that is my, that is my studio here.
So, I needed to come up with a way to weaken the signal coming out of the mixer to put it into,
what's it, what we call a line output.
Oh, excuse me, I just ate dinner.
Sound like mad.
I'm bloated.
A way to weaken that signal, so it wouldn't overdrive the mic input,
because basically a mic input is a very sensitive, you know,
a very sensitive input to take any kind of microphone and just amplify that.
So you can use it, which, of course, works great with the LTCH Lansing.
But when you, when you put a line signal into the mic jack, it completely overmodulates it.
And then you can, you can, you can turn down the recording to almost like just a,
it's open just a hair.
So it doesn't overmodulate, but then because you kind of like trying to squeeze all this sound,
the input into this, into something it doesn't, you know,
it's the wrong stick in the wrong hole, basically, folks.
I needed to weaken that.
Now, we went on vacation.
And while we were on vacation, my in-laws came to stay.
I think I mentioned that.
They stayed here to take care of the animals, take care of the house.
And you got to know my father-in-law.
First of all, one of the most talented people I know, hands down,
not just as a musician, he can write entire scores for, you know,
24 piece orchestra, just in his head.
And he writes that down by hand.
I mean, that's an amazing talent.
I mean, that's, you know, that's virtuos, essentially.
He plays keyboard, saxophone, violin.
He has a perfect pitch.
It's just an amazing musician.
But he can also, and Patricia has a lot of this talent.
He can make anything with his hands.
If he can think of it, he can see it, he can do it with his hands.
And this is just, it's, it's an amazing talent.
And I, I joke about it all the time.
You give him some, like, gaffer tape and some toothpicks and he'll build you a house.
And so he's talking about this.
He said, you know, John, do you have any idea how I could fix this?
He said, well, yeah, just have to build a little thing with some resistors.
And this and that and I, I don't have no fucking resistors.
Resistance, we don't need no stankin' resistors.
That's old school technology.
And he went into the garage, and I was up here,
basically on Skype all day talking to Ron, talking to people,
doing my thing.
And he came back upstairs.
And he first brought me the prototype.
And I've taken pictures of every single step of the way.
And I've included links to this on, on the show notes for today.
And he built this box, which, well, so he's, this is the great thing.
I didn't have resistors.
And you know, I said, so it comes back from the garage.
He says, hey, I found, like, a two broken dimmers, light switch dimmers,
and found some other gear, and I pulled that out.
And so essentially, he made this little box,
and one side, a little mini jack.
I plug in my, my, the output from the mixer,
and then a jack on the other side.
And that goes into the mic in of my laptop.
And there's two, uh, saw it off,
shaving down, um, um,
um, potential meters.
So basically the knob that you used to dim the lighting.
And you can completely, um, regulate the output from the mixer
down to an acceptable signal from the microphone.
And it's a beautiful little metal box.
And these two, um, two things,
they can actually, I'll twist one of them here for you.
Let me see, because it's stereo.
That's why he built one.
So I'm turning down the one,
and I can turn it up a little bit.
And so you can't, yeah, well, that's, that's 20.
There you go.
It's probably why that dimmer was in the garage.
It's broken.
Uh, so it works.
It works.
Well, can you perfectly?
I couldn't be happier.
Whenever I turn up my, uh, my microphone gain,
all the lights in, uh, in Gilford, uh, dim.
So let me give you a quick walk through, um,
uh, of a couple of, uh, a couple of features here.
Uh, by the way, I saw some, some comments.
Could I put up that screen shot?
I'll just like basically did the,
I love that cool little sniping tool.
You can use on, um, on the Windows tablet.
And I saw comments somewhere.
It was on podcast.com, which is, you know,
Dave Winner's new place where he's tracking all the technology,
uh, all the podcasting tools and services,
which is actually a pretty good resource.
Good comparison chart there.
And I do agree with a lot of what Dave is saying is that,
you know, you don't really need to go reinvent the wheel
and a lot of this stuff.
Um, and it's actually not that hard to come up with,
you know, things that'll work.
I think it's all about interfaces.
You know, that's, to record a signal and play it back
and create an MP3 file and do the right compression.
I'm not going to trivialize it, but it can be done.
You know, there's, there's enough knowledge out there
that you could put that together.
But then you really create the interface that works for a podcast.
So that's what I think is, is going to be important.
So I took a little bit of my radio background
and injected that into, uh, into the development group.
Um, and it came out with some, some really, uh,
yeah, it was something really cool.
So actually, me, uh, so if I right click on one of my, uh,
where my cartridge, uh, buttons here, uh, wait a minute, he had,
ah, there were all these great sound effects that,
that is now come with a program that, of course,
I've immediately lost.
Let me see. Oh, now I have to go do the windows trip,
ladies and gentlemen, hold on.
So I have to go to, what is it?
I guess I go to my computer, right?
My computer shared documents.
Is that where I find it?
No, not shared documents, hold on.
Local disk. Okay, uh, program files.
Yeah, there we go.
Now we have to find, was it cast blaster?
Ah, okay. There we go. Oh, here they are.
Here's the, here's the stuff.
Yeah.
So you can load up these files.
And of course, I still have the, yep, got that.
Well, that's lined up for, uh, for easy, I'll get real tight
or that pretty soon.
And, um, I don't have any songs, uh,
well, I guess I could load up a song for you.
Let's, uh, I got some promos that I wanted to run by.
And this is going to be another reasonably short show.
Um, just because I didn't have, uh, I'll be honest with you.
I really haven't had enough time to, to do all the prep today
that I normally would.
But I definitely wanted to get, uh, a different sounding version
out of, uh, of the cast blaster.
So I'm just going to play a couple of these promos.
Okay, now this promo has to be great because we're going to
sit it out to Adam Curry.
Who's Adam Curry?
Adam Curry.
Do you know who Adam Curry is?
Oh, that's right. That's the guy that does love line, right?
That's Adam Corolla.
Adam Curry from MTV's, like the God of podcasting.
Okay, I haven't heard of him.
Okay, whatever. Look, just let me lead the promo.
You, you just kind of play along, all right?
Sounds good.
Okay, by the way, I can now stop anything that's playing.
And when I started again, it starts in exactly the same spot,
something that we changed from the functionality from yesterday.
I don't know if it just heard a drop out on that.
I don't know if that's the file or if that's, uh,
the playback or what it is, but we'll continue with the promo.
Okay, here we go.
And we're rolling.
Hey, Adam, this is Don.
And this is Jared Ardman.
And it's a major honor to have our promo be played on your podcast.
Uh, yeah, hey, we wanted you and your listeners to know about our new podcast.
It's called DVD Weekly.
And each week my brother Jared and I are going to cover the newest DVD releases
as well as recently released title.
And we do it all in our special kind of way.
And, you know, we're not going to be as good as Adam was on MTV.
But we think you'll still get a kick out of what we do.
That's right.
So join us on DVD Weekly today.
You can find the link on the directory at digitalpodcast.com.
Just look under movies and entertainment.
Dude, what the hell was that?
All of a sudden you're like all up into Adam Curry.
You didn't even know he was a couple seconds ago.
Are you kidding, man?
It's Adam Curry.
MTV.
Come on, man.
The god of podcast.
I just told you that a couple of, uh, good Lord.
Wait, wait, wait guys.
Okay.
So there's another promo that came in that goes along perfectly with that one.
How to pimp your show.
Step one massage the egos of fellow podcasters.
Before the daily source code.
I was a complete wreck though.
The daily source code brought happiness and joy back to my life.
I listen to the daily source code every day.
Step two.
Pimp your own pod show by praising their show.
I tried to model my show.
W.
I'm a great penguin.
That com.
After the daily source code.
Without the daily source code.
My show.
W. W.
That.
I'm a great penguin.
That com.
Would not even exist.
The show.
W. W.
That. I'm a great penguin.
That com.
Oh, is it all to you?
The daily source code.
That is how to pimp your own pod show.
W. W. That.
I'm a great penguin.
That com.
I think we've actually played a promo for them before.
I've talked about them.
So again, I'm not sure if the dropouts are coming from the playback or if they're coming
from the cast blaster itself.
That's something I've got to look into.
I don't think anything changed on that.
So it's a little difficult to tell.
Okay.
Notice something here.
And this is, I guess, another beta cast of the cast blaster software.
And we're going to get some betas out to people pretty soon.
Trust me on that.
I have four slots for playing.
For playing audio files.
That include.
It includes a track bar.
So the jingles are just a single button.
That's the blank thing.
Or the.
This is.
This is really fun to do this with the pen.
You know, it's it's a very interactive way of doing it.
So I don't have enough to.
I guess I would need a way to add more more tunes to it.
Because if you have a relatively long podcast and you have a lot of stuff, then four is not going to cut it.
So let me.
You know what I'm going to do?
Let's do something really tricky.
I'm going to open and load up a new file.
But what I'm going to do is I'm going to.
Draw it from or this is going to be fun folks.
Let me go.
I'm going to try and get something off of my.
Macintosh.
So wait to hear that.
That's the.
That's my wonderful little box.
Okay.
So I have it loaded as a network.
Place.
I think.
Let me see open.
There we go.
Works.
Yes.
Beautiful.
Now I'm in my.
Now I'm on my Macintosh.
And.
Oh, here's something we can do.
Oh, the lot of found this.
This is.
Oh.
Man.
This is great.
I'm.
I don't think I can play the whole thing.
When we're in Miami.
Did you hear that?
Let me just adjust this.
This is.
Okay.
We need to fix that.
That one little different.
We got to fix the light dimmer for the audio.
One of Matthew Bischoff's buddies.
Now, of course, some bogey on what his name was.
The hell was his name?
Hold on.
Let me see if I can.
Let me.
All right.
And now we're going to do something cool.
Check this out.
Me a fire up Skype for a second here.
Okay.
Skype is firing up.
If Christina's online downstairs, and I'll just call her and ask her what his name is,
because I've completely forgotten.
Let me see.
Wait.
Don't tell me she's not online.
Skype always takes a couple of seconds to find everybody.
There we go.
That's much better.
There she is.
Okay.
Oops.
There we go.
Let's call her.
Okay.
Check that out.
It works.
Okay.
Of course Patricia's going to answer now.
Watch.
That'll be funny.
Hello.
Shvarky.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm recording my show.
Okay.
Hey, let me ask you a question.
What was the name of the guy who did that interview with you?
The podcast?
Robby.
What's his last name?
Trinchiny.
Okay.
Is okay if I play a part on the daily source code?
Sure.
Go for it.
Okay.
Hold on a second.
Actually.
If I play this, maybe you can hear it.
Hold on.
Listen.
Giving you an interview.
The first time ever.
Hey, everybody.
The strawberry jersey.
What?
He took a lot.
Can you hear that Christina?
Yeah.
Okay.
So you want to set it up.
You want to tell me what happened.
What happened to Miami?
How did it come about that he did this interview with you?
He kept Skype me the whole time.
I was on the internet and it kept really annoying me because I had so in your laptop.
And over time I heard, wouldn't it?
He was totally out of control on the Skype.
And he was annoying Ron as well apparently.
Yeah.
So I decided to give him a piece of my mind and tell him to just fuck off.
Oh, no.
Mind your language, dear.
I'm sorry.
He's annoying.
And then all of a sudden I felt bad for him.
And I said, well, if you leave everyone alone, I'll give you an interview.
And he said, oh, okay.
And he didn't really keep his word.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let's play another piece of this for a second.
Clive.
Giving you an interview.
The first time ever interview.
Christina Curry.
Yes.
That's right.
Adam Curry's daughter.
Welcome to the show.
Hi.
Oh, man. The sound quality sucks.
It's because Mom was like vacuuming in the background.
I hate it when she does that.
Yeah.
And I said, mom, and she's like, oh, it doesn't matter.
You can't hear it.
And we obviously can.
Of course, the way around that is maybe you or I could have done some of the vacuuming.
Okay.
Let's listen to a little more.
Hold on.
So um, Christina will jump right into it.
Um, what do you think about your dad and podcasting?
I mean, does it judge the effect you or are you just okay with it?
Or do you not like it?
I love it.
I love how my dad's just like created this thing out of nothing.
And everyone's going for it.
I love the idea.
And hopefully I'm going to start podcast one day when I have something to say.
And I was born.
And it's really clear.
What the hell was that?
That would be you calling me.
Oh.
Okay.
For you.
We should play the part when I told him to not get his panties in a gun.
Do you know where it is?
Was it the beginning?
It's like in the middle.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me drag this over in the middle.
I'll play it.
I think that it should be something that we should watch.
And if needed, we could always go in and bash people's hands.
Is it before after that?
This is it.
Yeah.
Okay.
I think you shouldn't get your panties in a bunch of better.
I mean, people were always because of me saying,
Oh, but you're so scared.
I said, don't get your panties in a bunch of pieces.
Oh, okay.
Just show, you know, podcasting.
Oh, that's so funny.
That's great.
Okay.
All right.
So, did he put that interview up anywhere?
Is it an official podcast somewhere?
No.
But I did get an email from one of his little geek friends saying,
how funny it was.
Yeah.
Well, how did he hear it then?
So, it has he posted it?
Is there a URL?
We can point because it's like 30 minutes or something, right?
Yeah.
I don't know where it is.
Did you check his website?
No.
Why don't you check it for me?
And then when I post the show, I'll put it in the show notes.
Okay.
Hey, this worked.
You can hear it.
Yeah.
You can hear everything.
That's great.
I mean, I'm recording.
It works.
I'm so happy.
That's what I'm doing up here all day, dear.
Wait.
I'm on his website.
Hold on.
Let's see if he posted it.
No, he didn't.
Okay.
Well, you know what?
Send him an email and ask him if I can put it up on my server.
And I'll put a link to it.
Okay.
All right.
Which, of course, means he'll start emailing you a thousand times, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
All right, baby.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Bye.
Love you.
All right.
There you have it.
The first test with Skype.
And you'll notice that not only were you able to hear her as I recorded Christina,
but she was also able to hear what I was sending back to her.
That is cool.
What's happening at Adam and the Daily Source Code listeners.
This is Todd Collins from the podcast.
What's really going on?
Yes.
I am a Daily Source Code listener and a Mac user.
But I've got a unique show for you right now.
It's from Beatmar recordings.
Beatmar recordings is a small indie urban label.
And it's a show about behind the scenes and a look at what goes on in the world of recording,
recording business as well as the tech side of the productions.
So come join us.
We'll talk about sports, snicker culture, upcoming artists and releases.
But most of all, content from you.
We're going to take questions, comments, feedback, all of that in email form, or in MP3 form.
To www.rgeopodcast at gmail.com.
You can also visit the what's really going on podcast at www.lipsen.com.
That's www.libs-y-n.com.
Or you can subscribe to the RSS feed at www.lipsen.com slash RSS.
Hope to hear from you soon.
And that's what's really going on.
Now back to you Adam Curry and the Daily Source Code.
All right.
So I am now convinced that it's something with the program that is tripping over on that.
I don't know why it's doing that.
Probably what I should have done this being Windows.
I probably should have rebooted before recording anything.
I don't think anything changed with the playback.
I wasn't seeing that behavior yesterday.
So that's something we'll have to work on.
So you don't have to email me that there were stuff dropping out because clearly I figured that went out.
Cool.
Let's see.
Twenty-two minutes.
You know, I've been upstairs almost all day.
It's 9.15.
So I am going to cut it reasonably short.
Last night the in-laws are here.
And particularly since John was so incredibly nice to make this sound dimmer for me.
Which I think we should put into production.
This is actually I told him what I wanted next.
It's a little box that you remember.
I tried to combine my microphone with the iPod and have that record onto the iRiverb.
And I got the huge impedance differences.
And then whenever the iPod would shut off and all of a sudden everyone's ears would blow out.
So he's got an idea for a little box to fix that as well.
So look out.
We may put some of that stuff into production in one of these days.
Hey, Adam, of course you heard of the sound of the day.
Well, I'm here to bring you the smell of the day.
Just the latest installment of worldwide web zaniness and here you go coming right up.
The smell of the day.
And then we get all that with the smell of the day brought to you by the daily dribble at www.dali dribble.net.
Okay, so cut out a couple times there as well.
Okay, now let's try something because I did ask something to be changed in the players.
Essentially, before if you wanted to stop something, you know, to comment on it, it would rewind all the way.
We've now made it so that a right mouse click or on the pen, which means holding down a little button and tapping.
You can rewind it manually.
Maybe that's something to do with the way the playback was changed.
So bear with me as we beta test this.
So I'm going to load the exact same promo.
Hold on, I'll load that into one of the jingle cartridges.
That's the, that's the ones that you really aren't supposed to be able to rewind.
Although I just found out you can.
Let me see if it has the same cutouts there.
Hold on, which one was it?
Smell of the day.
Okay, so we heard smell of the day cut out.
Let's play it again and see if it doesn't cut out.
Cut out when it's in a different player.
Hey, Adam, of course you heard of the sound of the day.
Well, I'm here to bring you the smell of the day.
Just the latest installment of worldwide web zaniness, and here you go, come and write up the smell of the day.
Oh, there you go.
That was the smell of the day brought to you by the daily dribble at www.dali dribble.net.
Okay.
That settles it.
We figured it out.
This is what beta testing is all about folks.
We figured out that something on the players, the ones that have the status bar,
is making the audio drop out and skip intermittently.
Okay.
Wow.
Okay, I think I've had enough beta testing for one day if you don't mind.
And it's time for me to go have some coffee with the in-laws.
So, special thanks to the development team of cast blaster.
Really enjoying the work.
We're going to try and fix some of the little buggies and gotchas there.
So, maybe I'll even do something over the weekend.
Now that Skype is working so great, I can finally record perfectly with Kenster J for MTV Chronicles.
Just gotta make the player stuff.
Gotta fix that.
I'm sure that I've already got a buddy there in Holland going.
Damn, I know exactly what's wrong.
I'm probably fixing it already.
All right.
Feedback.
Adamacore.com.
You can leave a comment on the weblog at www.curry.com.
And of course, there's daily source code.com where you can find the new source code,
this program, where you can subscribe to the podcast feed and find the archives.
Hope you have yourselves a great Friday.
Take care everybody.
I'll catch you over the weekend. Bye-bye.