this is the daily source code episode 184 it is well let's see 1239 that's
past midnight it is the 25th of May 2005 coming to you from Palo Alto
California from the lovely creekside in which is actually a pretty a pretty
dynamite little hotel oh boy let me tell you I'm sorry I'm already blowing
into the microphone it's been another extremely long day and I apologize that
I'm not able to bring you a source code with you know the promos that I
that I love to bring you and the pod safe music and the mashups and all
the fun stuff but the the hotel that we're in and by the way most hotels are
pretty full here in Palo Alto before we stayed in San Francisco of course there's
a lot more capacity there for for people staying overnight or a couple of
nights Palo Alto just seems to be pretty much booked up and this hotel has a
free internet which is great unfortunately you get what you pay for I'm not
quite sure what's going on but it seems like the connectivity drops out you
know every five minutes or so it'll drop out for a couple of seconds which is
just enough to mess up any Skype call you happen to be making requiring a
readile team mobile by the way which is what I have here in the states for my
cell phone is almost non-existent in this area so I guess we're roaming on what is
it singular cellular and the whole on second this is Paris Hilton's new
commercial home just check I love Paris Hilton I got to tell you she's
she's smart she's really smart now okay so what's the controversy guys she's
washing her Bentley
okay whatever so because of that it's very difficult to download stuff and because
we're pretty much on the road all day there's just no other opportunity and we
just got back from dinner about about forty five minutes ago I didn't
was Steve Gilmore who was in the neighborhood so whatever one San Francisco
Steve seems to be in the neighborhood by the way oh and before I forget to
night so that's Wednesday night at seven o'clock there's a San Francisco podcast
there's meetup hosted by Michael Butler rock and roll geek I I really would
like to go but I think that Ron and I are gonna have to hop a flight for Los
Angeles Wednesday night so that's obviously I'm recording this Tuesday night
but officially Wednesday morning so we're gonna try but because of all the
mess up in with the America West in Phoenix and and we just had to shuffle a
whole bunch of stuff around so I just I figured update you know this is
sometimes I'd like to post stuff on the blog just in in text and I just
have no energy for it so I'm actually lying in bed watching TV or another
drawback of this hotel no porn channels that's a wait a minute what's this
button ACH what's that just gives you the previous channel no porn
channels not that I'd watch that or anything like that I noticed that what is this
new program on television I did may not be new CJ I know what stands for
it's kind of like an entertainment tonight and now they've got where they
got this Phil Spectre trial you don't hear a lot about Michael Jackson these
days except from the CJ show I see like a daily update of Michael Jackson
trial and now that he seems to have a have an upper hand and that well his
team is really attacking his accuser particularly the mother and it's not
looking too good for her man and you know what right Lisa I told you I've been
supporting Michael Jackson on this all the way and in a sitting till proven
guilty right so this morning started off very early we had breakfast with someone
who I've known for let's see 12 years but a never met and person so when
who was pivotal in my mind pivotal in in early internet days and created created
some stuff that has really you know been a big benefit to people all over the
world I'll tell you a little before I tell you who it is the story is in 1993 I
had registered MTV dot com by the way that was with total approval and knowledge
of MTV and I was running something called a go-for server this is before the
worldwide web and a go-for server it was basically a text based linking
system with menu so you'd have a menu of you could basically determine how
how many different options there were on each menu on a screen so you know
numbered one through whatever and if you either hit a number key or if you used
your cursor keys you could navigate to a link essentially that could take you
to another go-for server or to a or to a page of information or picture and it
was it was pretty much a hyper linking system and I remember getting an email
which of course at the time was something pretty new as well if you ever listened
to the MTV Chronicles cast that can Clark and I have done we've done three now
we're still another one by the way she's like a fourth wrap up on that
I was going to say
shoot oh anyway so I had my adamant mtv dot com at the time I received an
email and said hey Adam really love what you're doing with the go-for stuff
you know you should check this out because this will add pictures and and
some layout capabilities for your screen and included with it was
I think it was and maybe even an attachment at the time you you encoded if
you remember those days some of you might of something called HTTPD I think
it was version one dot three and that email was from Mark and Riesen and he
many of you remember started at the University of Champagne or Bona and Illinois
with the first browser which was Mosaic and later of course he went on to
create Netscape and I remember that that day when I was like you know and I
actually installed it myself my own server was a headless sun three and there was
this mosaic software and you had you know a couple of sites you could go to
it also could do go-for links by the way and FTP links it could
understood that as well and I remember like you know looking at this page and
saw all these boxes with blue outlines and all of a sudden pictures started to
appear and it was just a such an eye opener and and of course Mark thought that
you know I would be into this because MTV was a highly visual medium and we're
moving from text into pictures and it was funny because at breakfast this
morning we were talking about that and he said man you know back in those days
I had had like a big target on my forehead and people were so angry because
they said pictures gonna ruin the web and you're you're ruining our our
medium and get out of here and stop this and you're bad and you're evil and I
don't think anyone can say that that pictures turned out to be evil on the
unit well some pictures arguably but so it was good kind of reminiscing and
I never met him and we met at a place in downtown Palo Alto is it downtown I
guess yeah called the most at the creamery and this guy's tall he's tall
than I am like man you're a big he's like well I didn't know you were this
tall either but he's these bigger than I am that was pretty interesting and
that was funny you know and he's a big satellite radio fan he has he has
serious as well as XM I believe and you know we're talking about music and
he's got a new company which I think is actually located above the
creamery and he promised me that when he's ready to talk about it he'll come
on the source code and he'll do it in person or we'll do it through Skype and
he'll let us know what he's up to and what's going on so it was really fun
that was just the kind of a feel good meeting you know we're in town and
and able to hook up and it was cool it was cool meeting him and let me see
oh man what this is so much to talk about throughout the day by the way I had an
opportunity to listen to KU radio which is the AM station here in the Bay Area that
is broadcasting podcast it's interesting I don't think they're actually doing
podcast 100% of the time it's well there's a lot of imaging and and sound
stuff that you know kind of positions it has open source radio there's a lot of
that a lot of music notice that and it sounded like that there still had some
some kind of other stuff in between in fact was very hard for us to I didn't
know the frequency off hand was searching around trying to find it and must have
skipped over to couple times either because they were in commercials or there
was it sounded like a very typical you know dial-in talk show or something that
was going on so that was a little bit confusing and most of the podcast and of
course in lots of podcasts we we mentioned dates you know it's like 15th of
March 20th of March and I guess that's the process of basically the submission
process that they have to deal with is you know they have to listen to everything
or approve and screen everything before it goes out because of the the
the obviously the decency or indecency laws but it was pretty cool it was
interesting to listen to that and not not much different from pod show and
serious except that's more current and we have you know the concept of
promos which is something I don't hear a lot of on KU radio but it was very
interesting to listen to it then we met with oh this is interesting a couple of
was it last week what's it last week as before I left actually I heard on
morning coffee notes the day wine or does he was talking about a gentleman named
Randy commissar who is with a venture capital firm
kind of Perkins here in San Francisco in the Valley and
what Dave was saying I'm paraphrasing of course is that a company like a
cleaner person should sponsor some of the legacy of Silicon Valley and a good
place to do that would be on the Gilmore gang and so when I met Randy and he
said you know I spoke to Dave and we talked for a while about podcasting and I
said yeah I know he said oh really yeah because Dave podcast he hadn't heard
Dave's podcast so I also know that he suggested you know you sponsor the Gilmore
gang and he said yeah yeah that'd be great as well I'll be submitting a proposal
for you tomorrow so that actually might pan out and and if it does I'll make sure
that the Dave gets a commission on it that was it was it was it was a great loop
closing there was a lot of fun let me see what did I write down here oh meanwhile
in New York Madge Weinstein was visiting New York you probably saw that Madge
did an interview with the famous famous drag queen bunny and I just saw
that that was up and posted excuse me but I'd also hooked Madge up with the
tour of the serious satellite radio studio facilities and spoke to her as she was
on her way back to Chicago and she said oh I'll add him so wonderful I met all
these old guys these radio stars and celebrities and she'd basically did a
sound seeing tour and hopefully that'll be up in the in the next day or so I
cannot wait to hear how that one over just haven't Madge walking through the
serious satellite radio studios I must have been pretty interesting let's see I
just going through a couple of things I wrote down just because I wanted to
update you on everything that's happening tomorrow see tomorrow we have a follow-up
meeting at Apple and Cooper T no never been to Apple which is interesting because
I've you know I always say that I'm a beta tester for Apple products ever since
the Mac Plus essentially and I've always paid for the privilege to be
into beta test all the Apple products so it's going to be great to kind of
get a little bit of the vibe of the company and of course this is a meeting
about you know what's coming in iTunes what I'm going to ask them is since there's
so much noise about this and and so much talk going on and I can see that
there's a lot of confusion in some cases and some things are just you know
it's just not a love information out there but I think there's enough that I
I'd like to ask them if I can talk a little bit more about what they're going
to be doing and if I look at my calendar I say and this Steve Jobs is pretty
good for if he says 60 days when something's going to be released you can
pretty much bet it's going to be 60 days so let's say that's T minus 57 and
counting so looking forward to being able to talk a little bit more about
that just to I think the community deserves the podcast and community deserves
note what's going on because it's going to affect us all in very very positive
ways so that's tomorrow then we're going to hop on a plane and go to Los Angeles
a couple a couple meetings there some some entertainment people that we've
been wanting to talk to who are interested in course and and what we're doing
I don't know that you know there's a lot that we can do with with with Hollywood
in particular but yeah this well besides the fact that it's close and it's just
a plane ride away there's lots of people that I know in Los Angeles who I
really I want to hook up with and haven't been to LA in a really long time so
looking forward to that and then we have another kind of important meeting
happening on Tuesday so I talked to Patricia what we're trying to figure out now is
you know it's I've been away now since I left on Saturday I'd really like
to go home and just spend the weekend with with my girls with Patricia
Christina and then I would just come on out I fly out again Monday for for Tuesday
meeting and Patricia's always saying and you're not stay out there but I
don't know I gotta figure that what we're gonna do and back at the ranch
exciting things happening at podcast alley I'd see Chris McIntyre is working
on I'll tell you what the name is and you'll understand exactly what what's
going on he's working on something called my alley I love the name I just love
the whole branding and the whole concept of podcast alley it's if you ever heard
John Jet had an album out once called up up my alley up your alley just the
word alley is is a great word you only have alleys in the east coast that's
new this is a real New York east coast thing is an alley and that's some really
cool stuff that he's that he's working on and I find myself using podcast
alley more and more these days to find things he's got some you know the the
metadata is really starting to come together in the forums man that's where if
you want to know what's going on and what's what's happening in podcast and
what's popular podcast alley is definitely the place to check it out and I've
never asked anyone to vote for me on on podcast alley but I can see how if you
have a podcast and and there's many different ways you can get people to to vote
for your podcasts it you know if they like it obviously it is a great place to
get to get to get exposure for for your podcast and I think that I've got just
the bombs I get through everything I want to talk about yeah so 17 almost 18
minutes and it is almost one o'clock so I'm gonna shut down for now I'm gonna
be waking up in the typical six hour night that's what it seems to be when we're
on the road and then from alley I hope to have some better connectivity and
more opportunity to bring you a full blown source code because there's so
many cool things being sent in for the pod show and serious which is now
it's almost become my new show prep PW Fenton is doing a great job at you know
basically scheduling everything making sure that everything gets on to the
the pod show and that's really where I'm getting all these cool promos from
and the and the pod save music if you've got something you want to send in
for the source code or for the pod show on a serious satellite send it to
submit at podshow.com if you got to pod save music it's pod save at podshow.com
and of course mashups send it off to mashup at podshow.com well that's it
I'm gonna turn off the light and a sleep and tomorrow sometime we'll be talking
to each other so take care and wherever you are talk to you soon right here on
the source code bye