It's time we've got to get that band with us.
Oh, you saw it.
The laser began as you reach Web Channel.
There were times this hit shut out of your text.
This is Ranger's final score last night at 9.
Really?
First on 635, I'll be joined.
It's Adam Curry.
Adam Curry.
Coming to you from Miami, Florida.
Hey everybody, good morning.
It is Tuesday.
It's January 4th, 2004.
Coming to you from my hotel bin.
That's right.
I feel like John Lennon is just for a minute.
Hey, it's the source code.
It's your daily source code.
We're partying together once again for this lovely Tuesday.
Okay, so I got a cop to it.
Actually, I tried to record this show last night.
I got about 20 minutes into it.
You might have heard me explain it in the past.
I have these meters that I hook up to make sure that I'm, you know,
that not only my voice, but also the sound clips that I'm playing
are be recorded.
It's about after 20, 23 minutes.
You know, I'm laying on the bed.
It's about midnight because Dave Ron and I had,
of course, dinner, dinner, drinks, you know, coffee, etc.
I also didn't notice that the meters are crispy.
Which is probably all for the better because, you know,
if you take the delay, the jet lag, the delay on the headphones,
of course, this is the latency that we've been talking about
and learning about.
By the way, I had a dream about that last night,
how I can solve this.
I need an extra wire.
I think I need to make a radio check run today.
We'll figure that out in a meantime.
I'm not too sad about yesterday's or last night's show
not completely working out because
I fucked up.
And as I said, it wasn't sounding good.
With the delay, with the jet lag.
And then, of course, well, you know,
you know, I snuck some weed into the country, right?
You know, I did that.
So if you slept weird on the wrong side of the clock
and you had a nice dinner and a nice chat
and you're laying down on your bed.
Hold on a second, what's that?
Oh, that's the alarm clock.
Hold on.
Okay.
There.
Everybody.
What a one point.
Listen to that.
Wait.
I can name your return to the century fire.
Yeah, for money, they have to retrieve the century fire engine.
That's radio today, folks.
All of this.
I'm gonna be turned this fucker off.
Okay.
Say to 8 a.m.
A rising shine.
The show should be up more or less by,
I'd say about by 9.30 a.m. Eastern time,
which is kind of, well, right on par, right?
So anyway, so I've got everything set up on the bed,
because in the hotel here, there's no Wi-Fi.
Of course, Dave has a linksis with him,
and Ron has a linksis.
I don't have one, but we'll be hooking all that up today.
So I've got the hard wired option,
but it is screamingly fast here at the hotel,
the Incernet.
Of course, you know, where I'm coming from,
anything can be screamingly fast.
I got lots to talk about.
I want to talk about a new podcast that I've,
well, actually, not a new podcast,
but a podcast I talked about recently,
but that I really had a chance to a scour on,
on the plane.
So that's coming up.
And I'm happy to report that it was not a fluke.
It was not a one-off.
We actually do have it every single day.
Ron, Ron, it is of the day.
Today is Cadence is from the Purdue University Drumline.
Yeah, can't give everybody a good morning.
You're daily cadence on the source code.
If you get the blood pumping y'all.
Yeah.
That was a role that made in so good day.
Okay, we got to work on the sweepers.
We got to get the sweepers in the,
and the, and the jingles worked on,
but lovely great cadence today.
And of course, we hope to provide you
with a new cadence tomorrow.
So we had,
uh, excellent start.
I'd have to say of,
uh, of our week here in,
in Miami, which I'm actually Ron's wife, Marta,
and I've known Ron Bloom for 10 years.
I've known Dave a little bit less than that,
probably about eight years.
Ron's wife, Marta, known for a couple years,
as well, six years, six years, I guess.
So Ron and Marta live here with his son, Augie,
in Miami.
And Marta was listening to a previous source code
and said, tell Adam, tell Adam not to say,
Miami, it's South Beach.
So I'm all for South Beach,
because that is where we are at.
And that's where you're gonna hear the podcast
coming from in the next few days.
It's also where the blog post will be coming from
and it's where we're just trying to figure out life.
Three guys, all middle-aged, trying to figure out
what we can do and how can we can have the most fun
and involve as many friends and family
and fun people as we can to really do something
interesting.
And so it's kind of cool,
because I know these two guys both very well
consider both of them, my friends.
And it's fun to watch them, seek each other out.
And in a way, it's kind of like dogs,
sniffing each other's butt.
Actually, I think of the butt sniffing phase as way gone.
But it's just learning each other's philosophy in life.
And from there, I think we'll have a pretty good
solid foundation to figure out what if anything we can do.
And it's just fun, it's kind of like,
it's a bit like Oceans 11.
Only since Oceans 12 has already been taped
and flopped, I guess, would be Oceans 13.
Where the old gangs get together,
you know, I started in a ran a company with Ron
and that was a very successful for the company.
It's investors.
I'd say most of the employees,
at a certain point after we were out,
I think everything that had a dot com next to it,
kind of had to cut and fold and do stuff.
But we sure had a damn good time.
And a lot of people had a good time with us.
And I'm happy to report that a lot of people we work with,
we still talk to, I dig that.
Anyway, for today's show, what I have lined up
is a couple of things that I was listening to on the plane.
And by the way, I want to thank British Airways
for taking such great care of me.
I had booked a coach class ticket
or what they call world traveler class.
Which is actually quite nice on British Airways.
British Airways is great airline.
Not the cheapest airline I have to say,
but you do get the service when you pay for it.
So if you're in the back of the bus,
you're still getting very nice service, very friendly service.
And actually the stewardesses are prettier in the back.
I have to say, so are the stewardes, by the way.
And I think that, well, first of all,
it's a very busy time to come to Miami.
It's very expensive.
I think my ticket was 2,000 bucks as it is just for coach.
Of course, I took a full fair coach,
because I did want some flexibility
if I wanted to change my return ticket, et cetera.
And I actually thought on Friday or Saturday, oh, man.
It's going to be like nine hours in this plane.
And I haven't slept too well.
I'm back hurting already.
Maybe I should just upgrade to business class,
which is what do they call it?
It's a club class.
And then I said, you can go online and you can say,
it would upgrade me one class of service.
And it was like 1,800 pounds.
It was like more than $3,000 just for one way upgrade.
So thank you.
I'll take the new G5, you know,
they'll just tell that the new power book, fuck that.
And good karma, you know,
because when I got to the airport,
I was nice and early and I checked it.
And the young lady at the check-in,
you're so nice and you said, oh, you know what?
Would you like, see, you have a window seat.
And like, man, could you try and get me an aisle
because I really, you know, especially in the back
or thinking, shit, I don't want people climbing over me.
I want to be able to get out.
I don't need to see out the window, you know,
I'm a pilot.
It's not unless I'm looking out the front window.
Thank you very much.
She said, well, I'm sorry.
I don't have a window.
An aisle seat available in club.
So she upgraded me right there.
And that was really nice.
And I said, thank you, yeah.
Of course, they write on your ticket, no lounge access
because you didn't really pay for it.
And then, as I was boarding the plane,
and these are, you know, these are big mother planes.
I think it was an airbus.
And already in the club class, I'm pretty sure,
a way as you get a sleeper seat, you know.
It's like, it's a, it's a great deal.
This, that's what I flew on when I went to San Francisco,
I flew club.
And you can completely recline.
And I'm six-four, and I can lay down entirely,
stretched out on these sleeper seats.
And as I walked in, they upgraded me yet again
to first class, because I guess they had to show
more people in the back or whatever it was oversold,
busy time, as I said.
And so imagine, you know, if club or business class is so nice
and I've flown first class plenty of times,
and I've paid for it plenty of times on British Airways,
but it's nice to get it for free.
And you get them, the Mahagatee sleeper seat, you know,
and the free magazine, and you get your personal video.
So you besides the 18 channels of the video
on the TV screen, you can also order a video tape
and plot that into your arm rest player.
So that was just fantastic.
And I slept, and I slept, and I was just great,
and the food was wonderful.
Although I'm pretty sure that the flight attendants,
that they know everyone who's been upgraded
and has been kind of bumped up to the first class cabin.
And I feel that somehow I got a little less service
than when I paid for it.
You know what I mean?
It wasn't discurdious or anything,
but they weren't like all over my ass,
asking me if I wanted this, if I wanted that,
I woke up about an hour before landing.
Normally, they'll offer you breakfast, you know,
so I had to kind of ask for it, but okay, it's all right.
It was a good deal, very, very happy.
And of course, then I still had to wait like 45 minutes
for my bag, you know, which is not bad,
but I've had it happen more than on one occasion
when you pay for first class,
and you're still waiting 45 minutes for your bag.
And that just pisses you off.
So anyway, started on a great note,
and I hadn't told Dave when I was arriving.
He knew I was arriving on Monday,
I just said I'll see you on Monday,
and he was coming in from St. Augustine,
we fucking believe it,
Ron picked me up at the airport.
And so, you know, take the 45 minutes into account,
and all the stuff that we never coordinated,
or it certainly wouldn't have worked
if we did coordinated,
and Dave was driving down from St. Augustine 350 miles.
I was coming in from London.
We arrived at, I mean, literally,
we were in the parking lot of the hotel
at the same time, love that.
Just means that we're in St.
You know, it feels good, feels good.
So anyway, moving along for today.
All right, so I was listening to a whole bunch of podcasts.
On my I River, by the way,
even though I loaded up the iPod with some audio books,
I basically drag my entire iPod or download folder
right onto my I River,
and I'm really liking this I River.
First of all, on one double A battery,
you get 40 hours of player time,
40, 40 hours of playing time.
I didn't even lose one little LAD on the readout
from my battery status during the trip,
and I had it, I literally was playing podcast
throughout the entire trip.
It's nice and small, you can set it
so that it loops through A folder,
you know, or you only place that folder.
You're basically looking at your file directory
when you're looking at,
when you're using the interface on the I River.
It's not bad, it really isn't.
I got to say I'm quite amazed.
And I heard a great, a great rock and roll geek show.
Of course, American Heartbreak is as we speak
on tour in Europe, unfortunately,
I'm missing the shows in Germany and the Netherlands,
but might be able to pick up a show
when I get back, so I've got to figure out exactly
where they're gonna be.
I'm on the guest list, you know, for every single,
American Heartbreak show during their European tour.
Just like hell, it was everybody.
But Michael Butler, in case you hadn't heard on just
the recent Rock and Roll Geek show,
hosted a concert in his backyard
for 50,000 of his closest personal friends.
It was kind of like a Barbara Streisand thing,
you know, except it was a rock concert.
He had a guy cheap trick there.
He had the nudge there, of course,
all his podcasts and buddies.
And at a certain point, Michael Butler comes up on stage
and I'll play this bit for you.
I did a fly by in the helicopter.
You got to hear the show, you got to hear it.
So here's Michael Butler, right?
He's on stage.
I got a question for everybody here.
Everybody here, like to drink alcohol.
Let's hear it.
Now I got a question here.
Anybody here, like to drink beer.
Let's hear it.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
We like beer.
Oh, yeah.
I'll like it too.
Now, what kind of beer do you like to drink?
Did anybody out there like to drink?
Lionakin.
What's the likes to drink, Lionakin?
Now you're listening to the guy who lives on Heineken, right?
So Heineken, I know you're listening.
I know someone who's listening to this podcast.
I told you, I called up Heineken.
I said, you guys, give him a case
of Heineken a month.
He is the biggest supporter of your brand.
What happens?
They come out with some like house techno music show
as a podcast and say, oh, we're podcasting.
You fucked up in this community Heineken.
You really did.
And listen to it.
This is what's happening.
Of course, Michael is such a nice guy that, you know,
he's a nice guy.
He's really is.
And so he's like, yeah, there you go.
He couldn't leave it at that, right?
Come on.
Let's hear it from us.
Yeah, come on.
We love the taste.
That's more alive.
But they got to get their ass out.
They're heads out of their ass.
That's more alive.
That's more like it.
Now, anybody out there like to smoke the weed.
Yeah.
There you are.
Okay.
It's a great show, by the way, because he has all these great
life performances by, as I said, Chief Trick, Ted Nujinta,
all his, all his buddy, all the rock and roll geek fans
stop by.
And it's a great show to listen to.
It's rock and roll geek.com.
And of course, you can always find everything I'm talking about
on this show in the production show notes at
curry.com or daily source code.com.
And as well, of course, all podcasts,
so they sit in the ipodder.org directory.
Welcome to the vinyl podcast.
My name is Cody, and on each show,
I play you a song from my collection of LPs, 45s,
seven inches, 10 inches, and 12 inches.
I got my 12 inch ready here myself, actually.
I'm focusing on music that's currently out of print.
You can find the show on the web at vinylpodcast.com.
And you can reach me with comments at Cody
at vinylpodcast.com.
Well, I suppose it's an inevitable point
that each podcast or reach is sooner or later.
Now's my turn.
This is the first official Adam Curry suck up a vinyl podcast.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Boy, oh, everyone has to go through it, right?
It's like initiation.
You have to do a suck up.
Ha ha.
It works.
On a show the other day, Adam played a live version
of Hang On Slupe, performed by Rick Deringer,
and it reminded me of this version of the same song
that I had in my collection.
So today I'm going to play Hang On Slupe
as recorded by David Porter.
It was on his album into a real thing, released in 1972,
I believe, on Enterprise Records.
But the version I have is actually on a 45.
The flip side of which is I'm afraid the masquerade
is over off of his victim of the joke LP.
David Porter is most well known as a songwriter.
He and Isaac Hayes of Shaft and Chef fame wrote a great deal
of hits for the stacks label in the 60s and into the 70s
and for the Enterprise subsidiary that this
and much of Isaac Hayes' work were released on.
This is a pretty odd version of the song.
It's nothing like the Rick Deringer version.
There's lots of strings and backing vocals
and it's a pretty elaborate early 70s soul production.
So here is Hang On Slupe, recorded by David Porter
on the vinyl podcast.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ah, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh,ooh, ooh, ooh. ooh, ooh give and do, ooh, so
Hanging up, you got your hands on me, then baby, hang on, hold me.
I believe I want to tell you, why they call my baby a snoop bag.
I remember one night, we decided to go out with some friends.
And we went to this big dance, you know, and we were trying hard to really enjoy ourselves.
And all of our friends were looking at us and snooping out, didn't care, we didn't think
about it.
But you know what happened, don't go and look, you know what happened.
The pain that was holding snoop is dress broke.
People were looking at snooping, they were looking at all of snooping itself.
And snooping turned to me and said, they did, they're laughing at us, I said yes darling, I know.
I hope it had nurtured too bad, and she said to me, no, David, it had nurtured me.
Because they came really, see, you see, they're looking at the outside of me.
But David, you see the inside, you can see within, because you know what's really there,
darling, you play it there, and I just wanted to do some strange right there, but I didn't.
And I just want to ask the world, have you ever seen a herd of a girl?
Like my swoeping.
Hey oooh snoobechube Ella!
Snooping, you got it ya!
Yeah, the time you know, the snoopy lets your head out
And it down on me, yeah
Baby, oh, snoopy, hey, no
It's got dark
Hey, oh, don't lose your hope
Oh, this loo we got
Let him talk to him
That was hang on snoopy by David Porter on the vinyl podcast
Adam, if you're listening, hope you enjoyed that
Dude, I rocked out to it, totally loved it
You can find the vinyl podcast on the web at vinylpodcast.com
Where you can listen to or download past shows
You can also subscribe to the RSS 2.0 feed
And have future shows delivered directly to your MP3 player
Excellent, so that's the vinyl podcast
I must say nice to hear
You know, a needle crackling on the vinyl
Then that sounds nice
I think it really, yeah, it makes it, it really does
I've subscribed now to the vinyl podcast
I think this actually did this come through
Openpodcast.org, I can't remember how
Now it might have actually
Anyway, vinyl podcast
And you could check out all the podcasts in the iPod.org directory
Let's see a couple updates
The morning at 830 British telecom was supposed to be at the cottage
To install the lines so that easy net
Can give my mega honk and pipe
Hook me up and connect me for my four megabit connection
Patricia Christina, we're already, you know, 830
The BT, they sent the confirmation will be between 830am and 1230pm
Of course, it 805am is when the guy is knocking on the door
And Patricia was like not totally ready
So she ran down probably
The guy must have gotten a shock
I don't know what she was wearing, but it probably wasn't much
And so hooked it all up
Install the line did all the stuff necessary
It said, oh yeah, but you know, you need another phone line
Huh?
Yeah
Well, you need another phone line
But it's no problem because we'll run one right up to the house
Which was the whole point of the exercise
So that's probably going to happen later this week
And the minute they do that
And basically they just have to dig a hole on the street
And run it up to the front door
They don't have to come in
Then they connect it and it should all work
I'm hoping, folks, I'm hoping
Patricia totally buttered the guy up, right?
Adam, you know, fed him tea and crumpets and whatever
And while he was installing all the wiring inside
So hopefully it will actually happen
I got the easy net guys on the case
Hopefully by the time I get back there
We'll actually be a router sitting there right next to my desk
With a big honk and four megabit incoming line
Oh god, please let it be true, let it be true
See what else was going to talk about today
Okay
A new podcast that I've become totally hooked on
I mean absolutely totally hooked on is yeast radio
I know I've played a bit of this before
Mads Weinstein is the host of yeast radio
And I don't know what Mads looks like
But just from the way she talks
And what she's saying and political statements
And a complete liberal
To me it feels like the young to Rush Limbaugh's young
If you will, you know, very outspoken
Doesn't hold back and by the way
You can do all this on the podcast
You can totally be yourself
Which is so wonderful about this medium
That we're building together about this
This public spectrum, you know, these airwaves that are ours
That, well, I guess in a way they are kind of airwaves
You know, you're receiving them through Wi-Fi
Receiving them in so different ways
And Mads is
I don't know just something about what she says
And the way she says it, you know, I was laughing out loud
On the plane when I was listening
I had three podcasts, I had listened to all of them
And I'm going to play you a couple of bits
Because it'll give you a real good idea
Of what yeast radio is about
And also it's all the bits where I mentioned
Of course, right?
Boeing moments, that's what we call them, Boeing moments
Shut up so I can start
Oh god, damn it
Shut up
I'm recording you asshole
Hello everybody
Shut up
This is Mads Weinstein with another on location
Issue of yeast radio
I'm at the home of Fausto Fernos
Who has a very important announcement to make
Before we get going on our conversation
Hi
Oh, Mads, it was so nice listening to Adam Curry
Talking about your podcast
It's like I haven't been listening to Adam Curry's podcast of his own
But when I first heard his voice, it took me about 10 years
Back to when I was a teenager
And I would spend hours watching him on MTV
Or was that the H1?
Oh, you be such
Oh man, there's a cup, you know, I don't care what you say
But the thing that always really hurts is when people say
Wasn't he on VH1?
Seven and a half years at MTV
Now, at the time when I was on MTV
There were people VJs on VH1
Most notably Tim Bird
And Tim Bird was a radio geek
And he had the whole radio geek thing going
He also had kind of like shoulder length hair
I was like, hey everybody, welcome to VH1
Video hits one, it's Tim Bird the Birdman
But here's some glorious stuff on
And then of course there was
The launching of a career on VH1
And I feel partly responsible for that
Because when she did her audition for VH1
She basically interviewed me and took the piss out of me
On camera, which was a great
Rosie O'Donnell
She started on VH1
And it was very funny
And I used to go watch her comedy clubs in New Jersey
And she crack on my hair and shit
And about the big MTV logo
I've got stamped on my butt
You know, so
Please, that's the only thing that gets my goat
It's when people say we're gonna be in VH1
But anyway, I guess I missed a show
Because, well listen what happens next
That was MTV
Now what else did you want to say?
I'm sorry for calling you a husband
Because now you reinvented yourself
Okay, so
Let me go get my dress
My internet guru
Yes
I guess I missed something
There was something something must have happened
And I didn't quite hear it
I must have been called
It has been
So I've been talking about
I don't think only it was one or two times
I talked about use radio
But so I was on the plane
Got the I River on
And I'm dozing off in the sleep right now
So I hear my name
And they're like
What?
And I just wake up
Oh my god
And well, here's the art of what I live with
I share it on the internet
The internet
And I've got a fabulous show
Lined up for you
Well, to be honest, I haven't got anything
Why?
Because I fucking work all day
You think I have nothing better to do
Than to write up
Of some god damn
OPML
So if you have something to listen to
And play
Mad, I love you
Now this is what I'm talking about
Clearly a very serious podcast
You know, into writing up show notes
Into OPML
And then just
Bitching at everyone about it
I love them
And bitch about
Complain about
No
I got a job
I got a day job
God damn
I think Mad actually manages a
Girl band
Mad
Send me an MP3
I want to hear what
You have what their stuff is like
You know, let's let's get some
Some pod save tunes going here on the show
And it's not fucking easy
Then I got to deal with gusty all day too
I got to support this woman
She works at the path mark
Okay, so then so you got a little bit
Of background on
I'm Mad's life here
Now here's the part where Mad started talking about me
And I have a song to play for Mad
After this so I'll come in
And I'll break into this bit
Once or twice
It's about two minutes
I think you'll enjoy it
Oh, by the way
Not totally safe for work
This used radio stuff, okay?
Anyway, I think I'm done talking about that now
I'm so pleased
Because Adam Curry keeps promoting me
This is the second time he's talked about my show
And I'm so touched
And I must say I'm also touched
That his mother is cancer free
I think that's so phenomenal
You know, it's wonderful
When you can have so many people praying
And hoping for your health of a loved one
You know, it helps
And I'm not a spiritual person in the conservative sense
But I do have my own sort of personal spirituality
Most let's be in the stew
You know, sure I have a few crystals
And I like to go to short mountain
And hold hands with some female to male
Trends gendered with their breasts locked off
You know, that's part of life
Part of life is hanging out
With your fellow sisters and brothers
Who've had gender parts removed
Or gender parts added
And yeah
I don't know, I have different fantasies
Man and I'm sorry
I'm a different kind of lesbian
In order to feel more whole
Which there's a little bit of irony
That's somewhere I can't figure it out
Oh Christ
Let's see
Oh do I have to sink my goddamn iPod
Did I not do my show preparation for this crap
Oh let's see
Okay, I'm gonna sink the iPod
So I need to belive
And by the way, that was something wonderful
Matt just said there about my mom
Thank you very much for that
And I totally agree it is wonderful
When you get that vibe
And I think everyone who has been
Thinking about my mom and praying for
She's home now
She was home before the new years
And literally the doctor said, Mrs. Clark
Because that's her maiden name
She no longer goes by curry
Mrs. Clark, you are healed
We're very happy
There's nothing more we need to do for you
You don't need any radiation or chemo
Go home, have a great life
We'll see you in a month for a check-up
That's the power
That was fucking beautiful
Okay, back to Madge
About five more seconds
While I'm trying to get this old wrapped up
Before the goddamn pizza alarm comes on
Because if you hear the pizza alarm
You're gonna hear Madge go scram
And this microphone's gonna fall on its ass
Well, microphones don't hear bass
But I show his help too
I got a big fat one
I got a big fat ass
And a hot cond
And ain't nobody gonna take it away
Hey, baby
I got so much to do
I was sick from work today
And I got to edit some more stuff
The image is totally into this editing
Doing opimil show notes
I mean this is a serious podcast
In saying films
You should check out my video site
In saying films.com
When you can watch me cook
I make my special being dish called les beans
I also make licorice
You get memorandum. I can get to this store
In my high-rise building
Before one hour from now
I want to play that nice little promotion
That I'm curry made for me
You know, if I were ever
To sit on a man's face
I think it would have to be out
I'm curry's face
I think I got to do a little boring here
Because I appreciate the thought
I'm sorry, but it would
You know, because he is
Well, I don't want him to blush
Maybe he'll stop listening to me
Oh, never, I'm committed
He's got the kind of face that a lesbian
Could really sit on
And it's all I'm gonna say
Studies, study, that's the point
That is a bit of each video
Mads Weinstein, this one's for you darling
It's going to be here
Hello, I'm 160
It's going to be anywhere
Ah
It's good to see a few old wins that I wake at 9
Yeah
When I'm sitting on your face
Nothing ever can we place the way
That I feel about you
I can almost see your eyes
There between my trembling thighs
But my tips seem to walk off the view
Ah
Some say that our love is immortal
But I think it's charming, yeah
You can't make babies with a tongue
So tell me
Ah
Who's humming
When you're talking to my friend
There is so much I can learn from us
With cunning linguists like you
I don't mind your more than us
When it's more the wind on the south
To the country I call my way away
Ah, I've got you white
Where you want me
In my favorite place
So I'm sitting here my dear
Looking in my two way mirror
Watching me sitting on your face
Hello, Airway
How is it big boy?
I remember you, I got wench mouth
When you're in the twenches
Hello hands
Still nine inches
A while
I've got you white
Where you want me
In my favorite place
In our own ex-weighted show
Me above and you be well
Diving me crazy
On your face
Girl would do shit
Your face all mine
Are we friends?
A big band of blues
Mary Lou
I'm going out to Madge Weinstein my new girlfriend
Sorry, Don
I got to tell you, Madge got to go and on
Check out East Radio, y'all
Besides the obvious sexual content
It's also just fucking cool
There's some really good statements about
Well, it's very liberal
It's very liberal
And please I invite all you red status
Please come on and listen
Join the Madge Weinstein East Radio party
Everybody in the kitchen
I'm taking a bath
Good night
Everybody
Take care
That's right
I'm going to end it here
Perfect timing just about 40 minutes for today's source code
Oops
Oh, that really sucked
It wasn't so professional
Let's try that again
And yeah, that's it for the show for today
Everybody for January 4, 2005
Okay
I'm going to go get some breakfast after a quick compression
I uploaded the show
And then
Yeah, it's the first full day of our week here in Miami
I'm sorry
It's south of each
Okay
Oh, bass is covered
Sure, respond
It's Adam and Curry dot com
And it's still going to quite figure out what's wrong with my email
I am able to get email and download stuff
Through the web naced version of my email server
But for some reason
I don't know, I just can't get it with my email
I'll leave don't worry
You can always leave a comment
It's at www.curry.com
And tomorrow there will be certainly another source code
Probably a trade secret sometime this week
And don't forget to check out scripting.com for morning coffee notes
I'll check it tomorrow everybody have a great day
Bye bye
I'll be back