Delta Sierra Charley 203
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
Then the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
Hey everybody, it is the Daily Source Code for July 6, 2005
The power of the Lord and the Lord
We are back home, back at the cottage
And it feels good
Or CC would say, it's all good home fries
It's Wednesday, and I said six of July, it is a quarter to seven in the evening
And it's time for a good old fashioned source code
You know what, it was great seeing my girls again, of course
And I've been away for like two weeks and a day
Or something like that, some unbelievable amount of time
Which is pretty much the max, any of us has ever been away
So I miss both my girls and then there's like a gap of nothing
I'm pretty big gap actually
But then falling up in like a close second is my mixer set up
It's like, oh, it's my microphone, it's my sound, it's my stereo limiter, it's my process
It's cool
It really does feel good, you know, just have everything
Or my office has been cleaned up, it's nice and tidy
So I had a pretty interesting trip back, we'll talk about that a couple of minutes
Actually, I took some notes and even though I'm a bit jet lag and I did fried
We got some interesting stuff to talk about
That welcomed me a couple of new podcasts and the pod show family
I got a pod safe tune, a really good one for a day like today in the UK
It's one of those dreary days
It's unbelievable, it's your got me all kinds of stuff for the heat
As we had a heat wave, and she got me a cooling unit
And she got me shades, so that the studio slash bedroom 2 would be nice and cool for me
And now it's like raining in 70 degrees
Anyway, I dipped into the mashup bin that PW always maintains
And found a couple of cool ones for it
This one I like the most, it's good for day like today
Beatles versus the four tops, this one's produced by Voice Dude
Now it's a quarter to three, what you want to talk about
When it's still evening, when it's still evening
When I was 64, sure the pod running, sure the pod running
So we didn't let you ask the tune, ask the tune
You need all that tune
And if you say the word
Like you say the word
Like you
Like you and we met different views
When your lights have gone
You can get to sweater by the fire side
Someday morning's gone from a crime
Knowing the dark, digging the breeze
I don't go as before
When it's still evening, when it's still evening
When I'm 64, sure the pod running, sure the pod running
So we didn't let you ask the tune
You need all that tune
And if you say the word
Like you and we met different views
When your lights have gone from a crime
Knowing the dark, digging the breeze
I don't go as before
So we didn't let you ask the tune
Girl, let's toss the flame, burn it in my home
Turn it all up on, no matter how I try
My love, I can't help, I can't help
Tell me your postcard, drop me a line
Stay tuned to point to point to point to point
In the kitchen, I say what you mean, you say
You're sick to see me, you're wasting a fire
And if you're outside, we'll never fall
I'm forever home, too
I'm willing to still meet me, willing to still meet me
When I'm the sixth year old
I'm sure the power, whatever
I'm sure the power, everything that I've spent to
I'm willing to still meet me, you're wasting a fire
And if you're outside, we'll never fall
But I'm sure the power, whatever
Hey, voice dude, I'm liking this
The title of this mashup, I can't help
I'm 64, the Beatles versus the four tops on the daily source code
Diggin' that, pretty cool
Okay, so episode 203
I hope I said 203 at the beginning of the show
Anyway, it was pretty funny, yes
So actually we spent fourth of July in Miami
I flew down from or flew across from Portland
After the whole fixed-wing license thing
Hey, yeah, I made another run
And so I had a, was it flew in on Saturday night
So Sunday, Ron, I had a chance to do some whiteboard stuff
Which isn't whiteboard, but we like a flip over chart
And we stick it up all over his house
Which was kind of fun
And it was still hanging there when I left
The fourth
I was invited to come along with them
To some friends of theirs
Who live in coral gables and they live on the golf course
You walk across that to the built more hotel
And it was a very much a traditional American fourth of July
Fireworks display, everyone kind of hanging out laying on the grass
And the music was turned up and
Not really synchronized with the fireworks display they had
But when you hear Ray Charles singing America the beautiful
And fireworks are going off
It's one of those real American moments
And you think back to, oh man remember Christina's first fireworks display
I remember, it's always the same
It's just kind of getting really dark and it's your laying out on the grass
And the fireworks start
When I was 12 and you know there was always that girl
I thought was really cute and you'd run around
Hide behind trees and stuff
It really worked for me
But then the next day was the fifth
And I was scheduled to leave it on a 630 flight
Virgin Atlantic which is my new airline of choice
If it all possible
And if I can take them
And since my travel had gotten all kind of messed up
There was no of the choice left then to fly
Well they call it upper deck
Which is kind of in between business class and first class
But you've got a sleeper sleeper seat
And it's whatever
Yeah, it's just what Virgin has is there
The top class but man
The amenities you get with that is it's astounding
I'm really digging it you get free limo service to the airport
And from the airport
Well free of course is baking to the price
You get something really cool
Which is in the UK
It's this concept of fast track
And fast track if you
That works if you have a certain
Gold card, mileage cards
Or if you fly first class with British Airways and Virgin
And probably one or two others
I don't know if it works on like American Airlines
Or other US carriers or foreign carriers
But you get a pink card
And then there's a separate line when you go through customs
And well really there's no line
Which is the great thing about it
And it's just astounding
It's like hey if you pay more then you get to bypass everybody
And the British Air they're not ashamed to have that
It's really quite interesting
I liked it
But anyway so Ron and I were actually on the phone
With the Chris McIntyre and his lovely wife
Ain't the other of me but she sounds great
They live in Nashville which is really sweet voice
And we were having a phone conversation
And I'm like Ron you know I got to go now
And so it was a 515
We walked out of his apartment
We said to get the car and drive to the airport
I don't know we were going fast
And I rushed into the airport
And they say Mr. Curry
I said yeah
Oh we closed the flight five minutes ago
But we said we wait for you know
I see if you showed up so I was like whoa
And then I got expedited
This is really cool
Expedited through the security check
Which kind of makes up for all the times
I've had everything but a cavity search
From TSA
And Pascal took me to the gate
And it was great
And you know hopped on
And it was nice
It was actually able to sleep
But it ever since the flight from Portland to Miami
Where I fell asleep on the plane
My head kind of on my hand or something
Oh man my whole shoulder and arm hurts
And my neck hurts
Anyway
That's enough complain
But version Atlantic
Very cool
Dougard
Was anything else though
I wanted to say about the flight
It was
Yeah it was just a
Stoundingly good service
I liked it really did
Okay
Plenty of promo stuff to talk about
What are we at now
We're at only ten minutes into it
Okay, let me hit you with a couple of promos
And we back will talk some more about some
Kuran stuff
Where in the definition of podcasts
Does it say that podcasts on the speech insistent
It doesn't
And that is why there is digital
In the fear of stuff or digital
In the fear of the stranger
Just like self and all radio
In the fear of it
In another way to gather
Just like this podcast
So light and up
Put some story in your life
Subscribe to the digital
In the fear and spot us
And teach you pride
You always have surprises on your birthday
Did you?
Go ahead
Change your life
Hot Joe
Content that will make you walk the dog
And kiss your mother
Cheat in the girl
You cannot hate me
After you start working there
Because my people will run you down
And then like two weeks later
I'm like, I fucking hate these people
And then like, should you stop
I'm like, I'm still gonna hate
I'm like, I'm still gonna hate him
I was like, he's working like
Oh, God, he's gonna taste
There's a lot of parts
And if you start a lesson
Somebody who's Jewish
I can put you on the phone
You know, I think they would understand my situation
A little better being that it is a bomb
It's a bomb
That's totally understandable
Thank you
Thank you Maria
And good luck to you
I know you believe in hell
Okay
I'm stupid
And if you're a vegan right now
You're banned from the show
That's stupid
No, I'm serious
Because we make this with butter
I'm upset
And I'm something
And I must have thought
It really doesn't make much sense
I got no
Stay manning
I think they realized
There's really no point
And I'm fired
Oh
You got fired for being pretty
I don't like to look at it that way
Yeah, right on
You know, I've been talking so much about the bandwidth
And she's me
And
Oh my goodness
Excuse me
You know what happened there, right?
I wasn't a sensational thing
Actually
I've been looking at all kinds of numbers
You know, that outside of bandwidth
We've just gotten so so many listeners
And subscribers to our shows
It's unreal what's been going on
Since the launch of iTunes
And I also looked at my Amazon
Associate stats
You know, I've had this
And say a machine on the
On the show notes for a while on the
Create.com homepage
And while I do get some unbelievable
Percentage like seven
And a half percent commission on
Every sense say I sell for some reason
I guess I've sold enough of them
I actually make more money
When I put an I river
I have p799 up
So I'm going to put that one back up
Because it's like three times as much
As much revenue coming
And it's unbelievable
It works
You can really sell
Gadgets and stuff
Through your podcast
This is what's astounding
This is not huge numbers of money
But, you know, we're talking
There was like a couple hundred bucks a month
You know, anywhere from three to six hundred dollars a month
That's not too shabby
And, you know, just from
People showing up and
We're talking about the I river
And we're talking about senseo
It works
Something to consider y'all
Hey, one of welcome
The mommy casters
Mommycast.com to the podgeo family
They
Well, I've played excerpts of
Mommycast
And they had explosive growth
Numbers in subscriptions
I feature them on the pod finder pod
Cast in Apple iTunes
And people are really digging
It turns out that a lot of guys actually listen
Which I guess
I think when I think about it
Doesn't really surprise me too much
Because I love listening to it
It's something I've really a side of parenthood
That you rarely get to hear as a guy
Also, the bitties with a bitty cast
They've been on the road
I think they're just about whining up their ten day tour
And they've been doing great podcast
From the road with live performances
Which I love, I love listening to the bitties live
And the quality of the recordings
I've really just gotten extremely good
So I guess that they're all wide up for it
So bitty cast also
Now a part of the podgeo family
And it's
Just go to bitties forever.com
It's also bittycast.com
But I'd like you to see bitties forever
And that's numeral for
Because they can really see what they're all about
And listen to some of the music
Which is also actually available in the iTunes music store
I went in there and I purchased
They're two albums because I had different versions
Of their stuff on MP3
But I really wanted all in one concise go
And you know, it was like 19 bucks or something
Which, by the way, I'm sure get most of
I should ask them about that
I think they get a really good deal on iTunes
All right, your daily source code
What else do I want to talk about
This
Well, yeah, of course, London
Everyone's freaking out here
Because it was announced that London will be the host city for the 2012 Olympics
And actually got excited
I listened to it live
I was around 12, 45 p.m. here
And a lot of people thought it might have been Paris
And it could have been Paris
I thought it wasn't New York in the running at one point
I don't know if they were in the final five or not
But London is just, you know, everyone in the UK is freaking out
They're loving it
Which, yeah, that's really good
Although, you know, when I think about it
It's like
2012 is like seven years away
How excited can I get?
I mean, look what happened with podcasting
In less than a year
Who knows what could it be happened in by 2012
I don't you just do it
Do it that's what I say
I feel it
You've been teasing me since I was school
You've been I am meaningful years
Come on baby, it's cool
Just do it
Oh baby, just do
No more flirting, cross the table
No more hints to say
And then
Better capture the moment
Come on change my mind again
You don't have to make a movement
Come on baby, just do it
Just do it
If you really don't want this baby
What are you?
What should show up now?
Oh
I was just going home
My baby
Just put me down
And I don't want to spend the night
Come on baby
Just do it
Such
To make your dreams come true
I ain't that lucky for you
Just do it
Come on baby, just do it
For a minute there, I thought it was like
It was a little sound like Johnny Guitar wants you
It's Roxie Perry from our back in Bluesville CD
which was made this year
Do it, it's a Podsake music on the daily source code
If you're just tuning into Podcast and don't know what Podsake music is all about
It's our router around the music industry
And it's really working
These are artists who are using the same tools as the signed artists
Or what would you call them the pros
You could call them that if you want to
Because they get paid for it, but supposedly that is by record companies
And so they're using the same tool
So, you know, great input, great output
And there's distribution all over the internet
You can buy songs, like the biddies through iTunes
Or CD Baby or soon through our Podsake music network
And what we've been missing is just the power of radio promotion
And now we've got artists allowing podcasters to play their tunes on the shows
Which is just phenomenal, it's working
So people are catching on, Rob Costlow's doing great
He's been checking in, he has all of his stuff coming out on a record label
Pretty soon, I think it's a small record label
So it's good to see all that pullin' together
It's exciting stuff, it really is
As you can tell from how excited I sound
I was going to say, oh yeah, I was going to say about iTunes
If you got a promo
Or if you've been thinking about putting a promo together
Now is a great time because
Every week, I think we're going to kick it off in a week and a half
But in iTunes now there's the pod finder podcast
Which is kind of a weekly overview of new podcast
And what's going on and what people are talking about
And whatever's happening in podcast
And if you got promo send them on over
I just send it all to submit at podshow.com
That's also where you can send stuff for the serious podshow
And for the daily source code as well
So it's just one place, send it all there
So far, I think we've been pretty good to get everything on the air
So send it off
As I said production cranking up weekly, pretty soon on that
So that's really pretty cool
In iTunes, I found something amazing
And leave it to Madge Weinstein, my girlfriend
Yes, don't get all pissed off
Madge is my girlfriend sometimes too
Somehow she got a video to come through on the podcast
Portion of iTunes and there she was making yogurt
So subscribe to EastRadio.com
I guess you can search for it in the podcast
Portion of iTunes
And you can also there are other ways to receive podcast
And they're different we call podcatchers or iPodders
That have different features that may be very useful
Like iPod or Lemon
I can find that at iPod.sourceforge.net
And I'll make sure there's a link to it
iPodrex.com for macOSX and there's
Oh man, in the directory, that's what I'll point to
And in the iPod.org directory
There's a listing of a whole bunch of different iPodders
And you can also search for it on Google
Different functionality
But I'm digging the iTunes stuff right now
It is working pretty well for me
Although there are still some quirks that I guess we'll have to get around
And for some reason my iPod didn't update properly
That's the weirdest thing
So I'm going to keep seeing these pictures on apple.com
We're supposed to have now music, library, library,
Purchase music, party mix, whatever
And then it's just a podcast and that top level
But I have podcast for some reason
As a playlist in my regular playlist overview
So I don't know what happened
I tried to reinstall the iPod update or something
And it did install and said it was installed
It was up to date current version 2.3 of something
But it doesn't look like the picture
It was basically
Okay
I told Patricia she could come on up
She should drop by
People keep asking about her
She had that
She's doing something downstairs
I hope she'll come up
Let me see, I've gone over that
We've got a couple more things to talk about
That's a really interesting stuff on the way
Including
Well you'll hear all about it
Stay tuned
Here we go
Come on in
Hello there
Skeptocality.com
Prezense Real Skeptical Thinkers
Seals
Skeptical Thinkers
Today we salute you
Mr. Internet Politics Debater
When everyone else is doing their job
Volunteering at the homeless shelter
Kissing a girl
Having a life
You are fighting with strangers
Over matters that you have absolutely no control over
For a slight people die
No matter if you are a Republican
Democrat
Libertarian or wishy-washy-pensitter
You make sure that your opponent looks like a
Fascist KKK Nazi hate-monger
Or a bleeding heart
Don't smoke a hippy socialist to your buddies
Come by our my law
Without you
We might actually have cut off our butts
And attended a protest rally or a political convention
To hear outrageous conspiratorial opinions
Or even heaven forbid
Read the politics section of a newspaper
Turned on AM radio or listen to Bill O'Reilly
No spins on my ass
So thank you Mr. Internet Politics Debater
Without you
Jay Rath
Skeptical Society
Skeptical friends network
And all other skeptic forums on the Internet
Would just be
Well skepticism
And for that
Many of us actually go on with our lives
And know that you are out there
Typing away
For the rest of us
Mr. Jay Rath
Politics Debater
A message from Skepticality
Visit us at www. Skepticality.com
True
In podcasting
Podcasting
It's a matter of courage
Backtrack's podcast
So you think you know your hits backwards and forwards
Yeah right
You're listening to the Backtrack's podcast
Exclusively on the daily source code with that
I'm correct
Check this out
All right Adam
Here's how it works
We bring three hits back from yesterday
And the form of a backwards sample
Then you have three seconds to name each song
Sounds like a familiar format
And you can give yourself a pat on the back
Because you're special
Okay Adam
Are you ready?
Yeah I'll try
Well let's make the first Backtrack's podcast easy for you
Okay
Here we go
Number one
Oh man
This is very hot
Uh
Time's up
Number two
I know what this one is
This is a tainted love by softself
That one I could hear
Time's up
Number three
Sounds like a rosanna
This is a very interesting variant on the hit test by the way
And here's number one
One last time
Oh
Jay Giles band free spray
Yeah
That's right
It's free spray
You're correct
And here's number two
Yeah I got this one right
I'm pretty sure
That's right
It's tainted love
And here's number three
One last time
I thought it was rosanna
Maybe not
Oh
You built this city
Grace slick Mickey Thomas
Starship
Okay
I don't know if I like this guy
But this is a podcast
You can subscribe to links to it on the show notes of course
All right, how did you do Adam?
I sucked
Well not well
Well you enjoyed the first Backtrack's podcast
You can reach us by email at
Backtracks at gmail.com
B-A-C-K-D-R-A-Z-K-S
And gmail.com
Special thanks to crack
And this week's hits
Catch you next time
Backtrack's podcast
Spin it back
You know what you get when you backtrack a country song?
Yeah you get you to dog back
You get your wife back
You get your house back
Backtrack
Delta
Ficture
Let's go
Rumio Delta
Rumio
One second
When I had just started with mtv.com
When it was all sanctioned by mtv
Of course at the time
There was a parody site called mtv
mptyv.com
And you know kind of like the the the the webmaster there
As I was for mtv.com was a madam furry
And this was a big hit back in the day
I'm talking 1993
I think
In 1993 94 was on a go for server
I think is what it still was back then
I've looked at the internet archive
I've not been able to find that
But with some guy from
It was from university
I was Caltech I want to say I can't quite remember
But it was hilarious
And so this came in this was made in the Netherlands
I'll just play a little bit of it because it's actually a whole podcast
It's called your daily portfolio
And it's a parody of the daily source code
Of course that's where all the airplanes
Hello
Hey baby
I was just about to play you have to hear this
You know it's about to play a parody of that's Patricia
My wife for those of you new to the source code
See it's my wife she's she's growling
Oh that's my dog I'm sorry
I'm bringing it's dog not me
Let me see if I can
I'll turn the speakers on
Okay
This is a parody
If come
It comes from Holland of course
It's funny though
Papa Oscar Delta Victor
Ego Romeo Delta Oscar Romeo
In the echo zero one
Something remarkable is happening here
Radio is springing free at the regulated gatekeepers who've managed
What you can hear since radio is invented
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass
Than the next generation radio content in my ears
Let's know what you said
I like to think I'm flying into the future
You're DJ
Hello everybody this is Adam Catcher again talking to your life
From my hotel room in Urgadgu
And for those who don't know where we're going
Who are going to do who I could do with the capital of F***ing Boocky Dupfoso
Oh boy
Yeah I know this is typical Dutch Yogas
What a great week
I choose at just released
And I choose is now fully supporting podcasting
Oh my goodness
And I talk to you right for my crepet
And of course I will be using the cost blaster
It's a good thing you might wondering why I sound like shit, you know how it comes.
It just comes from Karl's Blossom and Karl's Blossomike has just done a tremendous job.
You released the best version of Fully Public and that's, you know who it is?
No, I have no idea.
Is it not that, what's that?
The journalist from the internet.
Oh, Nikol Dijk's one?
No, no, I don't think so.
You want to do the hit test with me, baby?
First of all, I'm sorry for the echo, but you don't have headphones.
Could you shake your Stevens a little bit?
Shake and Stevens?
The echo?
Yeah.
What was one of his songs?
What was one of his hits?
Behind the green door.
On the green door?
Okay, why don't you play hit test?
Do you want to do the test?
You know that you hit test, right?
Okay.
Okay, you listen on the speakers.
Oops, did it work?
Could they fuck it up?
Here comes.
One girl in casting with Adam Curry.
Thank you.
One.
It's time for the hit test with Yon Poles.
Hey, Adam, this is hit test number 47.
And if you're ready, we're going to start right away.
This is intro number one.
You know that one?
I know where this is.
No, that's right now.
Each time.
Yeah, it's Madonna's protege.
What's his name?
Nick Cayman.
Yeah.
From the...
Ah.
I know that one.
Yeah.
I see Yon trying to trip me.
I'm glad you're here.
And there's always the final one.
This number three.
I don't know what that is.
Okay, time's up.
Okay, number one.
Yeah, I've got another one.
And this is answer number one.
It's Nick Cayman.
Was not the guy who was in the commercial.
It was with his jeans, yeah.
What?
No.
I was listening to Yon.
It's Nick Cayman.
Was not the guy who was in the commercial.
It was with his jeans, yeah.
What?
You didn't hear me.
No, I was listening to Yon.
What?
I wouldn't care.
Okay, you're next.
That was the robin-evil song, right?
Danger number one.
Nick Cayman.
And this is number two.
It's a song by the stars, shishishish.
And it's called.
So this is sung by your wife.
Yeah.
Your sister-in-law and a third singer.
I hope you're not into much danger right now.
The third singer.
And this is your wife again.
This is Patricia.
Oh.
How does a good song?
Yeah.
That was good, didn't you?
You should do something with that.
We should do something with that.
What?
That was just about it.
Yeah.
I don't know.
And it still feels like the first time.
It doesn't appear.
Or two.
And two.
And now back for sure.
And this is the third and final answer.
The second single.
It's been in a box.
Oh, this is the box.
No.
Oh.
I don't think we were there when this was a hit.
This one.
I don't remember this.
I know.
They've been in a box.
Sorry.
It was in Condon.
Not with this song.
No.
No way.
I like it though.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
I'm trying to hit this number 47.
Living in a box.
This is blow the house down.
Well, it's great song to end up this hit test.
I hope you enjoyed this one.
And you got three out of three.
But I have to wait until you play in the baby short coat.
So I am wondering how it's going to go.
Okay.
As usual, the feedback address is hit test at gmail.com.
And you can find all information about this hit test.
And also the separate hit test podcast on yompolit.com.
This J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T.com.
Well, thank you for listening.
See you next time for number 48.
Until then.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much, Sean.
That was good.
Yeah.
She'll show us over on where the thing is here.
It was good for me, baby.
Hey, uh, uh, shows over.
Will you sit in my face now?
I'm not sure.
Yeah, sure.
I'll be right there.
It's good to be back home.
All right, that's the source code for today.
You can find the podcast feed at dailysourceco.com.
Well, you might have found that in iTunes right now.
It's our source code.com.
Also for the show notes.
Also check out www.curry.com.
New servers on the way.
Marcus is installing stuff as we speak.
So that was kind of like the last bit.
Also for iPod.org.
We're trying to stay for X all that stuff.
It's just amazing how the 100 million listeners marches.
The siege deponus.
So welcome if you're new to what we're doing.
You can enjoy it.
You might even be a part of it.
Just start a podcast.
It's fun, you know.
All right.
So if you want to send me some audio feedback more than welcome at
Amacurry.com and submit your project.
Music to potsafe at podshow.com.
Your mashups to mashup at podshow.com.
And anything else promos podcast for the series show or any
for the pod find your send up to submit and podshow.com.
I will be back tomorrow.
I'll be a little more awake.
Trying to stay up until it's a normal bedtime.
And we'll do it all over.
With new stuff to get about.
New podsafe music and a new mashup.
See you tomorrow. Bye.
Music.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.