Welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Something different today.
New format.
Yo, there's a word again.
Works in software.
Works in all kinds of ware.
Works in program ware.
Podcast ware.
And in this case.
We're going to do something different today on the Daily Source Code.
And the number of reasons for that.
I'm going to talk about that.
What I want to do is take a walk with y'all.
It's just to go out for a walk.
What I've done here is, let me tell you a little bit about the setup.
I have taken my eye river.
I've set it to, I don't know what I set it to.
I set it to something.
At any rate, I set it to a reasonably high record rate.
I've plugged in my wireless lovelier microphone with the transmitter in my back pocket.
The receiver in the front pocket.
I don't really have a straight in microphone.
And what's great about this.
I just figured out.
And I'll tell you about that in a second.
Is that I can plug in my headphones.
And I can hear that it's recording.
So I can hear the throughput.
I can hear that the microphone's working.
I put my sunglasses on over my regular glasses.
You're not a good idea.
And one additional feature is that whoops.
Because I have headphones on now.
It kind of looks like I'm on a cell phone.
So people don't think I'm a total fricking idiot walking around.
Yappin in the space.
And of course, here comes the big story.
I already did a walk.
I actually did record some stuff.
However, it didn't work.
Which bites.
What happened is, even though I plugged everything in,
it was still recording on the internal microphone.
And my test when I was just testing it here in the room.
And I had it all hooked up.
It sounded great.
But of course, it was basically receiving me through the mic
and this device in my hand.
And then I put it into my pocket.
When I went to my walk,
it was basically when he stopped being able to hear anything.
So what I did get on my walk is a nice fresh coconut.
Which the guy who sold it to me on the street just chopped the hole
and it stuck a straw in it for two bucks.
Bingo.
I got some fresh coconut juice.
Let's make sure we're safe here on the recording.
That's always my fear is that I'll be walking around.
Well, basically what happened is that you come back
and you haven't recorded anything.
I was half expecting it.
So I was already kind of not too worried if
if it wouldn't record.
I knew that it would be a good exercise for the stuff I wanted to say
and it would be able to go back and do it again
and maybe a little more concise.
Mmm.
God, that's good.
That coconut milk.
It's heavy though.
It's not exactly the easiest container.
I'll talk a little bit about sound today.
And the reason for that is, well, first of all, as I said,
we need to do something new.
I need to do something new with a daily source code.
I could not create another show for you coming to you
from the confines of my hotel room, from my bed.
I couldn't go through the whole format again.
I just wanted to do something completely different.
And actually, if you're a broadcaster and I'm, you know,
we know the broadcasting podcast thing.
It's two sides of the same coin.
It's just what distribution mechanism we're using.
And of course, what confines do you get when you're broadcasting?
Hold on a second.
Just want to hear this.
So this is the hotel, but my hotel room.
And I've got to blow my nose, but I walk into the bathroom
and I have to turn on the light.
Now listen.
That's the most irritating fan.
Shoot me.
Most irritating fan I've ever heard.
Can't even keep it on.
You can't do anything.
You can't even be on the phone when you're in the bathroom.
It makes such a racket.
So we're going to be talking about sound today.
Ladies and gentlemen, about sound.
But first, some of the background to the change for today's format.
I've just said broadcasters.
I'm walking out my door now.
And I'm going to turn the corner on the ground floor.
So I'm walking right past the front desk.
And on my way outside.
There we go.
As a broadcaster, whenever you get responses,
basically what I learned in radio and television.
If the day after you did a program and that airs,
and people are still talking about your program,
then you've been successful.
Whether it was positive or negative.
More likely than not, it's probably negative because people say,
oh, I can't believe you said this.
But the fact is, and this is something that was pointed out to me,
it breakfast this morning.
If art, or the definition of art,
is basically that it elicits a response.
So I guess my creative gene feels really,
or gets pleasureed when someone or many people respond
to something that I've done.
In the case of yesterday's podcast with Madge Weinstein,
there was quite a lot of response.
Some very hostile, some negative comments.
A lot of stuff that I'm kind of used to,
caught me a little bit off guard because I got attacked
for some things that I thought are a little unfair.
If Madge Weinstein makes a joke about cancer,
and maybe it wasn't a joke,
and it was that to determine.
That's a nice one.
A powerful shit.
It's a liberator in Yankee, baseball team,
custom tank job.
Anyway, so if I then don't respond to that,
or just keep the conversation going,
I should be ridiculed, you know?
Don't tell me how I should respond to that,
and don't tell me how bad this illness is with that illness.
There's a lot of illnesses.
I don't know.
That was a little disappointing the way I got attacked for that.
I didn't think that was very fair.
Maybe people didn't listen very well to the conversation.
Quite honestly, Madge and I also didn't completely connect.
I didn't sound very much like Adam,
maybe as you used to on the source code,
and maybe Madge didn't sound like Madge.
But it was also, it was phone call.
It was the first time we spoke.
We didn't have any setup or preamble or pre-interview.
And that's why it was flawed,
which is also probably the beauty of a lot of these things,
which is maybe like,
got such an incredible response.
If we had already set up,
if we had talked up front and said,
okay, here's what I'm gonna ask you,
you're just gonna talk about,
and of course there would have been genius,
would have been brilliant,
but it would maybe not would have been real.
So, maybe that's where we got the response.
It was real.
Maybe it was real art,
and people liked it for that reason.
But back to the listening part.
Because I also believe a lot of people who responded,
may not have actually listened to a Madge Weinstein
used radio podcast.
So then you're not gonna get it.
You don't have enough data to pass judgment
or make a judgment or make a decision
and whether you like it or not
or whatever your feelings are.
And,
there's another piece to this is that,
this is something I've been learning from Dave,
a lot of the time we're spending here together
is learning,
well, I'm learning a tremendous amount.
I mean, I didn't go to college.
Yeah, I went to college,
like a semester,
really only because they'd let
freshman on the college radio station,
Salem College, Salem West Virginia,
every moment.
And after I was like running the station
after a couple months,
there was nothing left for me to do.
I didn't like it.
I was also far away from home.
I think I got home sick,
didn't dig it.
It wasn't for me.
College was not for me.
Not college life, certainly.
Last thing I needed to come in from Amsterdam
was to drink a lot,
smoke a lot of dope and drive,
you know,
didn't have done that.
That one was 15,
and then we get it over with real quick.
It's no big deal.
And then that alone.
So anyway, the aggression.
So what I've learned is that
if you have a feature that's in a product,
you can't take the feature out ever,
because people will go nuts on your ass and they'll complain.
So I've kind of slipped into a broadcast
rut almost.
I feel on the daily source code,
where I've created this format,
and of course it feeds upon itself
because I've got so many wonderful
comments and creative audio bits and pieces
that you get used to it, you know?
And so now it's gotten to the point where
if I don't play the drum cadence of the day,
people start to freak out.
Of course, on the other hand,
there's that.
There's so many...
damn, this isn't alarm.
Let's just see what this is.
I can't really locate the sound.
Oh, gone, okay.
So on the other hand,
there are people who say,
I'm not going to listen to this source code,
if you keep playing that cadence shit,
which of course is beyond me,
because isn't the entire point of this
or one of the major benefits
that you can skip past it?
Yeah, so I think that's probably an idle threat.
And I know, by the way,
that consistency is what it's all about.
If I have an off day, if I have an off week,
if I have an off month,
as long as I'm there consistently,
every single day, every single week day,
usually you'll come back.
Listeners will come back,
because they hope it'll be better tomorrow,
and it's not always, you know,
it's the things that's great,
the other person they think sucks.
So that's why you need consistency.
That's my motto.
It doesn't have to be every day,
but if you say it's every Friday,
it's got to be every Friday.
So it's every day,
it's got to be every day.
And then if you slip out once,
you know, of course,
your listeners will let you slide.
So yesterday was obviously a break in format,
because I basically played a song.
I did play a little bit of cadence,
couldn't help it.
I love them.
And then I went into the Madge Weinstein interview.
So it was a big departure,
but although it really wasn't,
because that's what we used to do in the beginning of the daily source code.
We're doing our kinds of stuff,
and I, you know,
I guess when I get accused,
and I don't take it as an accusation,
because I know how this works,
but when someone says,
oh, you know,
you only get on the source code,
if you mention Adam in your own podcast,
and like,
all right, fuck you.
That's the first of all,
it's not true.
You know,
second of all,
time for me to change
and morph a little bit.
So I want to talk about sound.
All the people that we're here with in South Beach,
all have something to do with sound
in one way or another in a professional manner.
Dave used to mix rock bands.
He did some radio as well.
So he knows what,
what can be done with sound.
I'm from radio.
Ron is a musician,
and he's done so much sound.
By the way,
I met the corner of fifth and columns,
if you know where that is.
So I'm going to hang right.
I'm going to go up to ocean,
and we'll walk on the ocean together.
And here there's a little bit of wind today.
It's not too bad.
I'd guess about 15 knots,
which is not too bad.
It's a very beautiful flying weather.
We want wind by the way when we're flying.
Construction site here.
So you can tell them about to walk past.
So,
I think we've forgotten about sound
and podcasting is bringing a lot of it back.
It is for me,
and that's why I want to take you on this walk
because although I may be on your walk,
often,
and we're not really walking together.
When people walk together,
they talk,
and there's all kinds of sounds,
and you have to stop for a second,
because there's too much construction noise,
or whatever it is, right?
But also,
well,
I know that we barely listen to each other anyway,
and when it comes to just humans interacting,
it becomes such poor listeners.
Let me see if I can cross over here.
Well,
some major wind coming through.
Hope I can,
there you go.
But if you listen to radio,
same thing.
We no longer have,
and we're not really making sound.
We're just pumping bits out.
You know,
we're pumping songs out.
And in the radio business,
there's this concept of dead air.
You don't want to ever have dead air.
Dead air means,
essentially,
that there was nothing playing.
Of course,
dead air is not really dead air.
If you've ever heard a station that had no signal,
you're going to hear all kinds of stuff.
You'll hear crackling of your radio,
because it's not always a clean reception.
Rarely is actually.
You just don't hear it when there's something playing.
You may even hear a slight tone.
I think it's 19 kilohertz.
That's a,
we call that a pilot tone.
Some people can hear it very well.
Sometimes it's misconfigured.
You can hear it good.
But if the station is on,
and it has no signal,
you can often hear very faint high pitch tone.
At the pilot tone,
essentially tells you a radio,
that this is a stereo signal,
it needs to split it up.
So there's no such thing as real dead air.
But of course,
what they're referring to,
you can hear I'm walking towards the beach now.
I'm going to shield the blanket a little bit.
What they're referring to,
of course,
is,
we're not making any money on that airtime.
Because, you know,
we have to feed in four commercial breaks in each hour,
and which is also the whole reason.
Or a big part of the reason
for the continuation of the fake voices
that we've discussed so many times.
Number one.
Because they've got to compress.
They've got to get the information out and short burst,
because time is money.
Every single second on the radio is money.
So the more you're yapping about,
your personal shit,
the less time there is to make money essentially.
So we forget,
we don't have time to listen.
One thing I learned from Scott Shannon,
who was brilliant.
Morning.
This jockey in the 80s.
I was fortunate to work with him
when, you know,
before essentially his format became old and tired.
And he didn't really grow and morph.
Nor should he have to.
He would say,
hey, let the room breathe.
And that was a big part of the success.
You know, you don't always have to jump
on top of the joke with another joke.
And, you know,
it doesn't all have to be gafog or funny.
First of all, it's not funny.
Don't laugh.
And don't pile jump.
And let the room breathe.
You know, sometimes just let the room breathe.
And the silence will actually
can be the punchline,
or it can be a total thing of beauty.
I never really forgot that.
Of course, I am related him totally.
In the 80s, in my radio ventures.
Certainly in the Netherlands.
And there's so much.
If you ever have a chance to listen to some BBC stuff,
they still do radio dramas, documentaries,
where you do hear sound.
I love it when people,
I love listening to journalism,
where people go out.
And not just get soundbites,
but, you know, actually walk with people.
And, you know, of course,
there's always editing involved.
I'm looking at a huge swing,
but walking right in front of me.
Let me just tell you where I am.
If you've ever seen South Beach Miami.
You know, the place where everyone's
rollerblading.
That's where I'm walking right now.
There's some beautiful people here.
And the weather is phenomenal.
It's about 75,
maybe 80 degrees.
And I'm dressed poorly for this.
I have my Gucci loafers on.
I'm such a honky from Europe.
I'm such a white boy.
I did, however, put on a sleeveless t-shirt,
which, of course, shows off my incredible physique.
Let's listen to what's happening here.
It's just a bunch of people sitting around.
This is my man.
He's got his headphones on.
He's talking to...
He's talking to everyone who walks by.
I know what, I know what.
I know what.
How are you doing, buddy?
And he's got his buddies. He's a happy man.
So, part of what I think I was missing
on the source code or in my own creative process is sound.
I haven't been able to do enough with sound.
And basically, I've now fallen into this spot on the source code
where people actually send me inflammatory emails
if they send me an audio comment and I don't play it.
Or I don't respond.
And that's unfortunate, but that's...
I basically have created all these features that people are getting used to.
So, I might as well break the pattern now
so that we can remain flexible because I don't want this to be set in stone.
How we do this.
There's so much more to explore.
And for me, actually, so much more to rediscover.
Because I used to be a much better listener
when I wasn't programmed to just listen to the hits.
And boy, was I ever programmed to listen to the hits,
even worse than that.
I was only programmed to listen to the intro and the outro of the hits
because when the hits were playing, I was doing something else
like prepping the next commercial break.
So, let me have grown up in the 80s with 80s music,
but I don't think I got to enjoy it as much as...
Well, that's why I'm so happy to enjoy it again, I guess.
That's the revival of the 80s exactly what I was looking for.
But sound, you know, when Dave's doing his morning coffee notes in this car
and he says, hold on a second, I've got to pass this guy
and then he whoops it up as he's accelerating from 70 to 85 miles an hour
and you can hear the engine kick in.
That's exciting stuff.
It really is.
I love listening to that.
It's something about it that...
You just don't hear it anymore, that maybe that's it
and it's real life and you know it's real life,
you know it's something going on there.
Or these guys with guns.
Why do people around here with guns in Miami?
I've seen marshals, I've seen coast guard,
and it...
well, people with guns.
Tell you what, where am I now?
I'm at Ocean and I can't quite see what the cross street is
and they see a little bit further up and probably around 10th.
What we'll do is we'll walk up a little further.
And then we're going to do some sound seeing together.
Which essentially is already started.
We're already doing a bit of the sound seeing
by walking up the beach side,
but now we're going to turn back and we're going to walk down
the cruising side of Ocean Drive, South Beach, Florida,
which is where all the beautiful people are.
Let me try and explain if you've never seen this.
It is so on the opposite side of the street,
so not on the ocean side of the opposite side.
It's basically all these deco art deco buildings
and their restaurants and clubs and cafes.
And you walk on the sidewalk,
and you can eat on the inside or you can eat on the sidewalk side.
Oh man, there's the cutting down.
There.
What?
Well, I'm on a sec.
I couldn't hear you. What's that?
I'm already talking about South Beach.
And you can also get ripped off by Israeli scumbags.
Oh, really? Did you get ripped off by Israeli scumbags?
What happened?
Well, he told me he was Israeli,
then he told me he's really Iraqi because he looked very similar.
Yeah.
And then it doesn't really mean to me.
What do you do?
His cousin was killed by an American Iraq.
And why did he say that?
To listen to response?
Let's fucked up.
Isn't it?
He said, you know what?
He's really going to rock.
He looked very similar.
Well, this is the same desert.
Yeah.
You okay, don't you?
No, he really scared me.
And then he said, why don't you go?
I'm linking road.
Yeah.
And opened up under the bushes,
which fills the crowd of about a year old already.
Yeah.
And take some of that stuff off before someone puts a bomb under the bed.
Well, how do you feel it?
Well, how do you feel about what's happening over there?
I don't give a shit.
I don't live there anymore.
Here, I still worry about my condominium.
Mm-hmm.
And my business.
What kind of business do you have?
catering.
Okay.
But do you pay taxes then, right?
What?
You know where some of those taxes are going?
I don't give a shit.
I live here.
I take care of my business.
Okay.
I still wait for a swimming pool to come here with tax money.
Like to have a new jury.
And New Jersey doesn't have swimming pools from tax money?
Wow.
I live, I didn't live in the wild.
I didn't see it.
Okay.
What are you doing here, Florida?
It's not like you're giving it to me.
I am.
I'm doing some sound seeing.
Okay.
I'm taking my friends on a sound seeing tour of a bush.
Drive.
Have you tried Lincoln Road yet?
No.
What's on Lincoln?
I think something.
I know a lot of people like to watch CNN.
Mm-hmm.
To the news.
Yeah.
I'll tell you what to hear.
I'm a friendly location to people already.
He did it.
She did it.
Corporate office was because everywhere.
Corporate office used everywhere where he did it.
She did it.
At the cross state line from California to Florida.
And then no one does their job.
There's garbage.
Under.
The bushes.
The garbage.
Inside the planners.
So what you're saying is it's all the hidden from sight.
It's being hidden.
And they're so upset already.
Who's going to clean it?
That's all I can put a bomb and do it.
And the reason why I say that somebody is really.
Are you from the West Bank in JavaScript?
Are you Israeli?
I'm American.
Are you Jewish?
No.
I converted to Rome with the file for it.
I used to be Jewish.
I made an even exchange.
Okay.
Are you better off with your deal?
Yes.
You know why?
Because they told me you don't have David who
Jesus Christ comes from the house of David.
You don't have to get married to a woman.
They'll just take his firm and give it to the girl.
And see what happens.
And if you know what?
I haven't heard that from Jewish.
I'll take that first.
What's your name?
David.
I'm Adam.
Nice to meet you, David.
So that's what I'm upset about.
All right.
I'm upset about it.
I'm about to trash.
Because it's literally hit me.
It's not a trash.
Yeah.
You know what?
This isn't as very park.
Right.
I mean.
You know.
A coin island left.
A coin island of 20 years ago.
Lincoln Road.
People hold their whole life.
Work hard.
Yeah.
To make money, to buy an apartment.
To open a business.
And then they have some staggy from Club Monica saying,
No, I can't leave my friends gay to see the bombs in the garbage.
Under the garbage under here.
Because California.
State line rule.
Say I can do whatever I want in Florida.
What the fuck is wrong with them?
I don't know.
And that's excuse.
Corporate.
Tell them, you know, Governor Jeb Bush is a redneck dick.
Okay.
And he doesn't go for this California state line bullshit with the state of Florida.
His state.
Don't tell him not.
Stop putting the blame on the German.
Stop putting the blame on the Jew.
You're deep, man.
I'm going to keep walking David.
Nice talking to you.
All right.
Listen, friends down the street.
I guess.
You find good places today.
You find good places.
It's all right.
There's one thing that's missing from South Beach.
And if you know business people that are interested, it's a Walmart.
A Walmart.
You know why?
The wing.
The sort of called wing.
Which tries to do the Walmart job.
But it's doing it.
At one point you did do it.
Which is a car, 20, 30 people.
Have everything.
We need a Walmart.
We need to get rid of wings of a Walmart.
You know, and hire the people that used to work at wing.
I'm going to pass that on.
Take it easy.
Okay.
Wow.
There you go.
Uh.
I think the most important message I got from our friend David was that there's an opportunity
for Walmart down here.
Otherwise, I'm not quite sure what we just learned.
I'm going to leave it all in here, though.
Because that's what it is.
That's what happens in real life.
People stop you on the street and start talking to you.
And sometimes you have no idea what they're talking about.
And sometimes you want to walk away from them.
Sometimes you keep walking.
And hey, that's what happens in real life.
That by the way, doesn't happen on radio shows.
If, uh.
If any.
Let's say broadcast radio program.
Run into that on their sound seeing tour of South Beach.
They would cut it out.
Because it was too politically loaded.
And whatever.
I'm leaving that shit in.
Okay.
We're here at the corner of ninth and ocean.
And we're going to walk down.
And we're going to listen to all the sounds.
I'm going to narrow it a little bit of it.
And we're going to listen to what people say.
And what people offer me.
Because you know what?
Let's go up to 10.
Because I want to get the full blown.
I want to go as much as possible.
And also between ninth and ten.
There's the tropical cafe.
Where the girls try to hustle you to come in.
And they look really cute.
And we're actually, I'm across the street from the top.
I'm walking up.
And I'm still on the ocean side.
And I'm going to cross over at 10th street.
And then we're going to walk down.
See, what are we at?
Yeah, it should be just about perfect.
So we'll probably be another 15 minutes.
We spent a little bit of time with our friend David there.
So with all this, with the sound stuff, the sound trip that I'm on today,
is the theater of the mine, which I was spoken about before.
If you've never been to South Beach, you're hearing all these sounds.
I know that you're hearing it because I have the head set on.
And I know that the microphone is great.
I'm really picking up all these sounds.
So this is good.
And you're going to just listen with me.
And in your mind, you're going to draw all these pictures.
And these pictures will be your pictures.
And they won't be anyone else.
There'll be unique to you.
But you know what?
It's your brain doing some fun work.
It's your imagination.
It's your creative juices flowing.
Completely the opposite of television, by the way.
I pointed again to the zen of the zen TV experiment on my weblog curry.com.
Please check it out.
If you haven't read it, do this because it will not disappoint you.
In fact, you're going to learn a lot about yourself.
And that you're not relaxed when you're in front of television.
You are actually working with someone else's pictures in imagination.
And it's very tiring.
And it's actually the equivalent of sucking on the cock.
A big brother is my friend Don would say.
This doesn't sound as we now cross over.
We're going down the other direction on ocean.
So on the left, I have tables.
And on the right, I have tables on the right.
Other people are going to try and hustle me to look at their menu.
And to try and give me free drinks.
Let's see if we score anything.
Okay, we're now at Cafe Med.
No tunes here.
Okay.
Well, here's the song, what I plan.
I'll pretend I'm looking at the food while I listen to the song with you.
Oops, must go on that.
Yeah, fuck it, can't hear it.
Let's walk out of the further.
Ooh, I want to get us to guard.
Hi.
You have a small cojuva.
Yeah.
That's good.
Yeah, how much is that?
$8.
What a bargain.
Yes, please.
With love.
I don't know why I don't do that way.
Let me take it up.
$1.20.
Let me change.
But.
No.
No more.
Let me take it up.
Don't just cut it through the plastic.
No more.
Okay.
Not for any dollars cigar.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Bye.
So basically it's not a real Cuban cigar. It's probably from Honduras or let me throw the plastic wrap around
There's something about and of course I'm not going to inhale this and it's not made by big brother
So it's not as cock I'm chucking on. It's not a very big cock either.
Where am I here? Where are the locus? No one's sitting at the locus.
Okay.
So we got a cigar and we're still cruising down. What is this? This is the...
Oh man. This is... Oh there it is. This is the tropical cafe. Oh it's so cute.
They're wearing all those nothing and what is what they are wearing is very tight.
And well we're passing out.
Ninestreet. Okay crossing. Ninestreet. I don't think we won't actually go down Lincoln that our friend David suggested.
We'll just walk down. This is the prime time, which is the next place we're passing here.
I think that I have the little jazz music for. I think that I have the head set on. People aren't going to bother me too much.
I think I'm preoccupied listening to a fricking podcast. But we're here. This is cafe Milano.
You're hearing some of the cars driving by people. They drive really slow here.
In fact, you walk faster than most of the cars because inevitably there's a car that's driving very slow
to show off the sound system and not just the sound system, but probably also the cool chrome rims.
It's too much sun. I can't really tell what this is.
It is a cultural melting pot if you listen to all the voices. So you are totally getting your own imaginary walk.
If I said walking by a sidewalk cafe right now, you're going to say, I was a woman looking at the menu.
It's a couple of talking. There's a waiter with a bad tie. Someone just dropped her silverware.
You're imagining all this stuff in your own little movie, right? Your own picture is essentially what you're seeing.
Even though it's more than likely completely not what is actually happening or what it looks like.
It's not the news cafe now. The news cafe is pretty much the place to have lunch. It's on the corner of eight and an ocean or deco, I guess. Deco drive, ever.
And they've night eight here the other day.
Now that we're such hipsters that we can always get a table, but we were just early for lunch.
Okay, don't kill me. Thank you. It's gross. Here we are now. This is what is this? This is wet willys.
What are you looking at?
It's like cops of a door wet willys to checking ID. Let's be something really wet willys in there. Got to check your ID.
Start light hotel.
Okay, and now we're just sea cafe.
Hi, thank you.
So that's the trick if you don't want to get hassled. Just put your head phones on and people won't talk to you or barely. She only said hi because it smiled at her.
Hi.
Where are we now? Oh, this is the Johnny Rockets. They're always playing good to them. They've put it playing right out.
Oh, chasing the sunshine man. Get down the night. Get down the night. Get down the night. Get down. He lives in Florida.
I'll hang out with Casey.
Pretty cool guy actually. He's reinvented himself several times. He's putting all his money up his nose.
Okay, we're now at building is called Avalon. Has a Chevy. I want to say it's a billaire. Is it a billaire? It has a classic car park that front.
Let's see, I think it's a billaire. It's definitely a Chevy. Well, yeah, I'm going to say that's a, it's a 57 maybe. I don't know my car is too well.
Man, the one thing though, there are women here that have legs that are so long.
Okay, we just crossed the next street. So we're at the majestic the Avalon Hotel 660 on Ocean and the next little sidewalk cafe we have here is Casablanca.
So we're lost a guy, walk a by trying to sell a CD or some CD.
I don't know what the office is. What is this? This is Park Central Hotel.
Park Central Hotel. You will recognize in pictures. There's a real old-time car parked out front.
What kind of car would this be? It's a Buick. Don't know what the model is. It's kind of like the gangster model.
We have a dummy in there, which is dressed up to look like Humphrey Bogart. And that's what people basically stand next to and take pictures. It's a very Disneylandish type of thing.
Right. So we've pretty much walked all the way past the sidewalk cafes. And I guess that would be it for the sound seeing Miami walking up on the guy here. He's also selling CDs.
What's your guy brother? It's that music from New York. And I think it's called the world.
What's your car? Do all live. Do all live as in two.
That's another guy walking there. That's your partner. That's my boys.
And it's not in no store, so that's why we are here for more in ourselves.
But you should have a boombox or something to play it.
I've got the headphones. I've got the headphones.
I can't put blasted off our headphones.
So you know, we've got anti stone on an album. We're on tour with her. She had a house of blows.
Really? He's opened up for 13 states throughout the US.
We've worked at ACON and got him on an album, hoody, Alicia Key, was dead fresh.
Really? Yeah, Jay would have damaged her.
But you don't have a record deal.
No, we're doing it independently.
By choice or you actually shopped it anywhere. You're trying to get it everywhere.
You're having a pass. You're having a pass. You know what? It's fucking blows.
You know what? You've got a website where you sell this as well.
Not yet. You've got to sell on the website. That's what you got to do.
So if I told someone I would really like this CD.
If I told someone I really like this and I wanted them to go buy it, where would I send them?
To Miami. Now.
How much is the CD? How much is the CD?
A couple weeks. Really? You know?
Do you know what the website will be called?
Yeah, it's right here. You're a Dimash Music Group.com.
So what's that's not up now?
No, it's an construction like we work because this is a new project so we don't update it now.
What's your favorite song of the album?
Do you play on this? You sing on this? You play on this?
Easy, breezy.
There's one with Andrew Stone. Andrew Stone is fucking normal by the way.
So which one do you like?
I'm checking it out.
Some music from New York.
Yeah, from Brooklyn. East New York.
On the East Coast.
Tell me.
13, yeah.
Eight, half dead.
Number seven. Well, I'm from.
You tell me which one?
Which one?
13.
Just one.
That's a heat.
Easy breezy.
Adam.
Definitely. I'm going to play it for my friends too.
Okay, do our live, right? Do our live even better.
Okay.
Cool.
All right.
Well, shoot.
Tell you what?
On a mix of scene right now.
See how much time do we have?
Oh, perfect. Let's play this song right now.
And that'll take us out.
You're going to listen to do our live from Brooklyn, New York from their brand new CD.
The official free lunch mix CD.
When the website is out, you can find it at www.redemptionmusicgroup.com.
Yeah, I'll put a link to that in the show notes.
Here's easy breezy.
Have a great weekend, everybody. Bye-bye.
We copy the bucket.
Easy breezy.
Talk to breezy.
We let you down.
We copy the bucket.
Get it boys.
Time in.
Make some air cramp up.
Turn them off as some tweeters can.
We kill the doors.
Look in. Why the F.L. Cali did G.A.D.J.
Go play whatever the hell we say.
Cause we keep messing them though.
We pick up messing the door.
All on alcohol, my sons to defend my health
I'm dead, they are gently, I could defend myself
While I hold my sons, you might not know my sons
They are all from the star, ready to die
I'm trying to get them ready to live
Papa's mother's ready, you kids
Pick that up on the comma, baby, blah blah
Show what's high here, this eye here, I hope they hear
I see how sneakers better hide to the coast is clear
Bending ain't no locus here, they don't listen
I'm on resouls and see, when I broke this here
Three, notice there is a focus here
Seeing the machines are both cold, the slope is there
Total recall for me, you heard it here, revolution never is an urban way
Beware y'all, easy, easy, don't talk to music
Related down, the play dance will be brought
I claim the same way, I'm the new star
We have to do like a mistake, you know
Easy, easy, don't talk to music
Related down, the play dance will be brought
I claim the same way, I'm the new star
We have to do like a mistake, you know
I'm casting, it's Adam Curry
Adam Curry
In the kitchen
All taking a bath
Onions are easy, listen
In the kitchen
All making me laugh
Morning, good night
Good night, in the night
In the kitchen