Daily source code, March 17th, 2005.
Transmators, we don't need no thinking transmittance.
Hey everybody, it's Thursday.
How you doing, everybody? I'm Adam Curry coming to you late today.
Much later than normal. It is your daily source code for March 17th.
It's Thursday, 2005.
Probably going to be a little bit short today since it's already 630
and dinner will be on the table before you know it, but still a source code.
And just before the show, I was working on two technical bits that have been bothering us here at the cottage for the past week or so.
One is the annoying blip that digital burp that's been taking place just before every single show starts.
I think I've fixed it now. I basically, a lot of people sent an email on how to, on how to work.
It's working, it's recording.
On how to set up the auto record feature, which I think is called,
the record sink, and hopefully it works.
Now I'm just trying to see if everything else is working here as a core in the plan yet.
Another thing I figured out is the buzz.
You're not going to believe with the buzz game from the buzz that was in my microphone.
Actually, let's just turn this down, turn down the music.
No buzz, whatever.
You're not going to believe this.
The power cord for my power book was actually crossing over on the floor was crossing over the microphone cable.
Wala, your culprit.
Just got a love figure in that kind of stuff out.
Hey, by the way, happy St. Patty's Day, everybody.
It is today, right? St. Patrick's Day.
A couple people said, hey, you should mention that.
I don't have anything really teed up or I don't.
Geez, I'm not even, am I even wearing any green?
Oh, no. What have you do? Don't pinch me, please.
I think drinking is very bad.
Check this out.
Yo, I got a fake, I need no.
You're going to love this, the mashup of the day.
Get tipsy over, it's the title.
I'll get a start.
3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 1.
Homeboy, it should be here.
We need to kind of pop it and we'll do this for fun.
You ain't got one to get you a better one.
We sound too dreadful.
You want a try?
Oh, your bones are both hard.
Everything's a stress.
And what's more?
Well, it's awesome.
It's fun.
This is great.
It comes before to give out to this day.
Stop dreaming, that's the sandwich.
Just a single man ain't trying to get rich
Little wasted on me, man, son of a bitch
Rusted it off, now I'm back again, man
Grew some oil, juice, man, you're some good bitch
I won't wait for me, cause I'm sparing that it's cheap
Nah, he on his side, man, son of a bitch
Just a bitch!
And what a pain!
What a pain!
Why a trying and open your mouth?
An eye!
We've got a job, got a life, got a forward door, and a faintless wife, got those nice
copper pipes, got an ex, got a room up for the night, I'm just such a kitch, what a prize,
ain't got a body like a battle, I love that perfect fruit, honest eyes, we got a
body email is only make serie of
searches, confuse..?
Yeah we've been looking for as many as couples introduced here, where we would
buy a job, get the basic things sold and we gonna buy it, in this
day.
I wouldn't be building any type of payments ever we couldcer, so there would be
Get tipsy everybody in the club get over it mash up here on the daily source code from March 17th, 2005
4 warned no big announcements in this show today. Maybe tomorrow maybe over the weekend
home just a little more power there for some reason I've been really busy today it's been
unbelievable and of course a lot of that is email if you sent me email you haven't
gotten reply once again someone overloaded on the communications front just
trying to fish all the important ones out of there because I'm really in the stage
of a company that I really like is when we're doing the contracts and putting everything
together and we have a number of contracts were completed yesterday and today which
means things are starting to take shape you know and I really do enjoy that and
so it's been a lot of emailing but certainly a lot of Skype call and I just
got to give Skype it's props one more time and these guys are the phone
companies unbelievable I have my own with Skype it seems like I have my own PBX now
you know I can I do conference calls add phone lines you know drop phone lines
you know be on one call and then hop off and put a whole conference on hold and
jump on another it's just great really it's great I even have this I bought a
Skype in number which now you can call me in Connecticut 203 unfortunately though
that doesn't work with the Mac version of Skype yet it does work on Windows
and I tried it out and it's very cool it actually just works you know so again
I think these guys have done it they've become pretty much the phone company so
what we're gonna talk about today first of all congrats to the lemon team 2.0
shipped yesterday looking awesome a lot of the features that we've been talking
about were put in there almost second I just got a Skype message here
that's my buddy Chris he's listening to a daily source code and Starbucks and
Sunnyvale it's a bit reminiscent of Starbucks and Surrey don't you think yeah no so
lemon is is the the iPodder that is cross-platform that works on both the Mac and on
Windows it's I think the team is now what is the team for people it's Martijn in Holland
got Andrew and Massachusetts Garth and Australia I'm missing one person I know I don't want
if I'm gonna do the credits I might as well do it right it's another person from Rotterdam
why can't I just I can't go up with the name okay so while well firefox is doing its business then
let me see that's iPodder I see if it's right iPodder dot sourceforge dot car
dot net that's it there we go let me just see I want to get the team right so yeah we go it's loading now
it's really cool by the way if you haven't seen their their homepage yet they've got a great
little what you call one arm band that's spinning and three lemons come up which is great
Eric that's it Eric from Rotterdam so Eric Andrew Garth and Martijn Feneroi did the design
user interface and then there's oh there's a content strategist mark I don't know if I've
met Mark or not I'm not quite sure anyway guys looks great it's a cross-platform
iPodder it's amazing it's so far it's working great I'm sure this stuff that we're gonna find is it
as as everything progresses and as as people start to bang on it but I like I like the cleanup
features those are really cool it's just good it's really an all-round great product
congratulations on on the release guys that's great that's great for the for the podcast and
community so if you haven't tried it yet going over and download the iPodder lemon
something else coming up is the skinny awards if you've not heard of them of this podcast the
skinny on sports we say T.S.O.S. it's Andy and Matt skin they're from up there away on the
left up a bit they do the faster 10 minutes on your iPod which is great this is a sports pod
cast I just love because it's tailored for me the guy who knows nothing about sports but wants to be
able to make conversation at the next cocktail party and it's not just news right it's Andy
Matt and they actually sit there and they discuss what's going on in sports and they're doing
an award show and I'm one of the presenters so that is on the horizon you can look out for
them not quite sure when the awards will air because they were still affirming up their presenters
list sounds just like the MTV awards but look for that skinny on sports you can find them in the
iPodder.org directory and some great news today I've been doing some experimentation with
as an Amazon associate we've talked about this where I put the Senseo coffee machine up
and then she currently have the iRiver IFP 799 running and now a couple days ago when I got
the new compact for the sound was it sound sound craft mixing board it was available as well through
the associate program I put that up dude I sold five mixers five mixers my earnings have tripled
in the past you know three days it's unbelievable this shit really works it's great you know and
and I presume people are listening to this show partially for podcast information stuff that's
going on and you know so there's a lot you know what's next microphone cable I have to admit I kind
of like selling coffee machines more than than mixers at least audio mixers but maybe there's more
it's great to see that this system works I can actually and by the way so you know I'm not
getting paid by anyone to endorse any product whatsoever or any service on the daily source code
except of course if you look at from a different vantage point I figure that people out there
who want to know what kind of year I'm using and have an opportunity to kick some back to the
person presenting them with that information it's working the the loop is closed it's freaking
work and I love it it really does it's cool I'm very excited about that and here's something that
has been brewing around for a while very early on when we started before the word podcasting was
invented and we were dealing with MP3s and automatically transferring them to ii pod actually this
this is a legacy issue from the ipod which later was moved to MP3 players have similar issues
and it's about the ii3 tags and I just want to see if I can bring up this email here
it's from bk I should summarize some of this although I put the whole email in the show notes
but I got to tell a little bit of the history about the naming convention of podcast so
when I get to complain the dsc-25-03-17 means very little to me and please could you put in
daily source code podcast for 314-2005 let me explain why we're not doing that the reason why
is that initially on the iPods and it's still that way on the iPods what you put in the title
field right we'll scroll but if you're in your iPod itself and you go to a playlist for
instance you could go to the daily source code playlist or maybe just you know your most recent podcast
it'll only say you'll only be able to read daily source code and it because it just cuts it off
you know it's basically a poor designer a bug whatever we want to call it in in the in the iPod so
if I if you have a long show name title it just won't be able to give you any data so we've
also tried you know doing the dates first and then the show name after that but the same problem
occurs because once you've done the date it basically will give you two or three characters and it's over
as to why we put the information about the about the podcast in the album it's for the same
in the album field on the id3 tags it's for the same reason if you put whatever's in the show
in the comment field of the id3 tags it won't show up in your MP3 player the only two things
that show up consistently across the board and iPods and MP3 players are the title and the album and
those two are basically what you want to see scrolling across the screen so that you could figure
out you know what you're listening to and this just no other way around it I mean the the whole
basically the id3 tags are our bogus for podcasting anyway podcast is not a valid
genre type at least in the id3 version two or whatever I'm a little confused and fuzzy on that
it will let me write them in the program that I use but it says hey that's not valid
which is interesting and it's all based upon music it was never intended for podcast so again
those are the reasons that we really did a lot of work and flesh this out early early on so I think
we've pretty much been through that loop and I don't see any reason currently to change those you
know BK is asking for some best practices he actually posted this on his on the site I'll put a link
to that as well but that's the reason why it's all about okay how how am I able to find out which
show I'm listening to by looking at a list doesn't work in certainly not in the iPod I river by
the way it's a much better job if you look at a listing of of files or podcasts essentially
it will start to scroll and you can even yeah man I river so cool you can modify the the speed
of the scroll and all that stuff but it was really done with iPods in mind so of course it's
it's to look for discussion but by the way I've seen some other very interesting uses of the id3
tag certainly of the album tag being used for commercials don and drew I think had MSMobile
calm in the album ID3 tag and it would just scroll across which it's kind of like RDS on the radio
so what it does fuck up and I completely agree with that it screws up sorry pardon my friend it's
screws up management in iTunes or however you're managing your podcast because you know yeah I'd
like the album to be it would make sense for the album to be daily source code that will be the
collection but you know it's we're kind of just cludging it into what's what's available maybe it's
time for ID4 tags or IDP tags I just don't know how that works but the industry standard is ID3 and
we're just kind of you know plugging along and using what we can at this at this point in time
so I promised you it was going to be relatively short and what's interesting to me
is I'm just looking at the eye river here it appears oh my god so I set up this sink right
the synchronization so it starts when basically it waits for sound and the once it hears the sound
it starts recording looks to me like when I shut up for a second and I don't produce any sound it
actually stops recording dude that's a configuration I have to look at and then it starts a new
recording when it hears something so this can be pretty interesting the way this is split let's test it
right now I'm going to be quiet and let's see if it shuts off yep yep one two one two one
totally shut off oh my god so I don't know if I can reset that somehow that's going to be very interesting
so now I also don't know how long I've been wait there's a oh man this eye river is they thought
about everything so it looks like I've been going for 12 minutes and 53 seconds of that possible
in total so it does keep a total of everything but it will quit midstream if you don't
provide it with any audio interesting so I'm going to have to work on that well hold on a second
then let's make sure that we provide some audio hold on so now I've got to keep talking because
I'm afraid it's going to like shut off don't want that to happen okay try this audio on
okay it's time once it's time for it to look with your on pull it hey on hi Adam this is
yet another hit test for you yeah I thought so and we're going to start right away this is number one
okay okay um I don't know let's say I just have to give up right away on that one number two
okay okay are you yelling at your iPod now do you if you're MP3 player you're
number three okay that one I know
uh abs now oh geez all right and this is answering number one what's this it's us
what I don't know ass away from ass what I don't know ass away from ass what
oh all right I was going to say that it's full note I was going to spend the night
oh it's too late for me it's too late now it's the third one
that's a great song yeah that's a great song yeah
oh all the boys here's Johnny yeah you go from uh number five's alive
and so number three in today's hit test whose Johnny elevards and that wraps up the
hit test for today well it's uh the same thing every time you can send feedback to hittest at
gmail.com and you can find information about the hittest and the separate hittest podcast
at young polettes dot-to-n-l that's j-a-n-f-o-l-e-t-t-n-l well Adam see you next time
for our next edition of the hittest thank you bye bye also I was talking to Andrew Brummit
he's the iPod 11 team today and he said that he had put the answers to hit test
was it 22 I think with the hairband the metalband guitar solos he put a spoiler out
he put all the answers up online and hopefully Michael Butler won't see it maybe this week
and we'll be the day that Mike and I finally hook up on on doing that uh doing that hittest
hey listen I gotta go it's uh because now of course I have to you know sew up all these files together
and make sure that it becomes one happy show and god knows it may sound like crap so my
apologies if that's what happened in the long run but I don't really want to re-record this show
that would kind of make no sense um tomorrow as I told you I'm slated for two interviews in
London one four uh as a very serious Dutch new show called to be from that which means two today
number that it's on channel too obviously uh so then you know the the Netherlands is trying
is basically catching up with podcast things it's kind of interesting how the press there has
have taken so long to to to really catch on and and really to print anything about it
Polo said dinner okay thank you be right there uh see perfect timing uh and part of that is
because the news was really focused on a lot of other really serious issues that are taking place
in the Netherlands um the murder of taeofonhoch uh the Dutch filmmaker uh there's been all kinds of
real real big tension going on um death threats to many politicians it's just it's not been a very
happy happy vibe and so I think the news is kind of dominated by that interesting though how
so much of the podcasting uh movement has come out of the Netherlands you know or actually um
I did my stuff in in Belgium but let's just call it actually I did do some of the some of my
attempts at coding the first iPod or script during my radio show and he'll were so more after
the show actually would do that and we're sitting around kind of decompressing and trying to write
two or three lines of code because they had a really nice fat pipe there at the studio and we
good to suck in megabytes of podcasts while I was testing uh sucking in RSS feeds but also look at
the you know there's uh the uh two people from the from the lemon team are uh are in Holland
what's Ed's uh mimic is another fine uh uh Dutch product I think Doppler as well I mean dude
this is there's a lot going on it's all in their enterprises backyard it's uh very typical I guess
oh one other thing that if you live in the UK and you've been reading the newspapers the big
governmental budget was presented uh it was in all the papers today and one thing that I keep reading
is that the UK government wants to go Dutch on uh rules for business uh let me just uh talk about
that for one second what they're referring to is the Dutch government's pledge to reduce um all the
laws and rules and often conflicting um processes that have to that are putting place for businesses
now I've started several businesses in the Netherlands um very few with big success and let me
tell you the number one problem is you just can't fucking do business there it is impossible there's
been no change whatsoever in any of these rules I recommend that you don't eat the horseshit
that it's working over there or that it's a great idea it's just bullshit to keep people believing
in the government these guys are going to be out when these rules are supposedly supposed to be
in full swing they'll all be out of they'll be in you know in great cushy little uh board director
jobs uh all over uh the world and they won't have to bother with any of that shit but that nothing
has trickled down whatsoever it is the worst business environment I have ever been in um and it's
it's it's crazy the minute you you you register a company blue envelope start coming in with you
have to pay this you have to talk to this person uh evaluated tax is separate from uh from normal
taxation it's crazy it's a crazy ass country and if you run a big company like diagio and you're
in there get your people out man I'm telling you get them out what do you think we escaped for
hey that's it I gotta go eat as you heard so thank you very much for this short and version
hope you don't mind the dropouts tomorrow um besides that uh that interview also doing click on
line with the BBC so I will uh take along the as Madge would say I take along the i-reathas with
my very expensive microphones thanks for tuning everybody tomorrow thank god it's brighter
comments at americancurry.com if you have a promo put it up online somewhere and just send me a
link to the URL uh because clearly sending MP3's is just not working it fills up Gmail and I
have no time to go manage my one gig of shit it's just not an easy interface to delete stuff actually
there's no simple way to say delete everything that's in junk it's not that I've been able to find
so if you've got a way let me know comments at www.curry.com the podcast feed and the latest
show in the archive the daily source code dot com thanks everybody i'll see you tomorrow on Friday take care bye
bye