POT show, choose the mothers, choose POT show.
Delta Sierra Charlie 2-9 or 3.
POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show
choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose POT show, choose
or came in and said, wow, I like this.
She does every single time I play a Grittles song.
It doesn't matter which one.
So I think she's got that, yeah, she's the radar is going off.
So I really need a town coordinator for my show now
because I've been trying all morning to persuade Patricia
to come on if she needs a five minute walk on here
on the show because I've got some audio feedback
from her for her from whispered pearls.
And as Grittles was playing, I yelled down
over the, over the banister.
And I got a very curt reply.
Yeah, I hear you.
Okay, she's on the phone with someone.
Hey, she doesn't care about the show, man.
Ah, so many interesting things in the news
that talk about related to podcasting
and media in general.
Trevor Carpenter sent me an article
which he says isn't about the music business per se,
but more about European publishing.
And he said, you know, it does kind of have the same vibe
if the music guy's the same as the publishing guys
and I'll talk about music publishing,
but I would just say publishers are printed, et cetera.
You know, Europe could be in for quite an interesting ride.
This isn't article from the Associated Press.
European publishers warn Tuesday, they cannot keep,
listen to this very carefully.
They warn Tuesday, they cannot keep allowing internet search engines
such as Google to make money from their content.
Quote, the new models of Google and others
reverse the traditional permission-based copyright model
of content trading that we have built up
over the years, said Francisco Pinto Blas-Samal.
No, Blas-Samal, the head of the European Publishers Council
in prepared remarks for a speech at a Brussels conference.
So it was a written response, I guess.
It goes on to say, this is really fascinating.
So I'll read this next paragraph.
It's fascinating to see how these companies help themselves,
quote, to copyright protected material,
build up their own business models around what they've collected
and parasitically earn advertising revenue
off the back of other people's content.
This is unlikely to be sustainable for publishers
in the long term.
Wow.
So what they're saying is that a search engine going out
and indexing content, which, hey, if they index my weblog,
it's essentially, that's copyrighted information.
It's on to creative comments, but it's copyrighted.
So, but I don't have a problem with it, obviously,
for obvious reasons.
But they're saying that that's foul.
That's a foul that you can't do that.
That you can't build a business model around search.
This is so un-really incredibly amazing.
This is coming from Brussels, man, from the European Union.
This guy is, I'm sorry, not the Union.
He's the head of the European Publishers Council,
but he was talking in Brussels, which is where it all goes down.
Let me see if there's anything else in here.
Last March, Ajahn's false press claimed the Google
News Service infringed on their copyrights
by reproducing information from the websites
of subscribers of the Paris-based news wholesaler.
It is seeking at least $17.5 million, 14.85 million euro,
and damages.
AFP says Google is breaking rules
on the fair use of copyright material
because it's new site looks similar to AFP subscribers on that's horseshit.
So there's a real simple fix guys.
You can put it in a robots.txt file
and Google won't index you.
Let's see if you like that as much.
If you don't want people discovering you,
like God would boneheads unbelievable.
Well, I don't think that's gonna hold up.
Which judge is gonna be the one that says,
oh, Google, you can't index information
because it's breaking copyright.
Who wants to take on that fight?
I really want to thank everybody
for thinking with me about the tattoo.
Since Christina got a tattoo on her just above her butt crack,
I might add.
I've been thinking of a tattoo myself,
not above the butt crack,
but on my, I guess my right arm.
And I've been getting some pretty interesting designs
that see this call for, oh, there she is.
Hello.
I was waiting for the doubt, he's not coming in.
Yeah, let me turn this out before you.
Where is it?
There you go.
All right.
Gee, I need a talent manager now.
Why?
Well, because I couldn't get the talent on the show.
No, I'm so busy.
People are phoning me, wanna talk to me.
Yeah, you're so popular.
I'm so popular.
I play that song the one you liked.
Oh yeah?
Do you know who it was?
No.
Groodle.
We have plenty of time.
Three songs.
Three times.
Every time we like it.
But it's a, I've played three different songs.
Each time, when I play the song,
when I come in, you come in and you say,
hey, I like that.
Well, so doesn't that tell you something?
Yeah.
I have taste.
Ha ha ha.
Cool.
I can still, I recognize them.
Speaking of taste, I received a piece of feedback,
some fan mail from whispered pearls.
Oh, you know, the two girls who were talking about,
that's, by the way, is the non-family safe portion
of the daily source code for time.
And so they sent some feedback and have a question for you.
So are you ready?
Okay.
Here we go.
Hi, this is Michelle from whispered pearls.
Hi, Adam and Patricia.
Thank you for responding to our podcast.
It's much appreciated.
And you know, Adam, I've long suspected
that you have an amazing cook.
But let's just stop right there.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I'm sorry.
Well, wait a minute, why are you laughing?
Because I just know because it's true.
Yeah, you love this.
Yeah, exactly.
Man, love to hear this.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
It will really make his day.
Christmas came early this year.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Yeah.
You want to hear that again?
We're just going to tell you.
No, we heard it.
Okay.
Thank you Patricia for confirming that.
No confirming.
I know.
That's what I said.
Nasty.
Indeed.
Very lucky to be able to put that in your mouth.
Oh my god.
You want to.
When Adam's not working.
You're so lucky.
I'm not talking.
No, I just.
Well, that's how we get you to stop talking.
Yeah.
So I just wanted.
I just want to.
I just want you to know that other people think you're very,
very lucky.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Oh, let me tell you later.
What does that mean?
Okay.
Let me.
Let me be a threat.
All right.
Here we go.
And, you know, I agree with you about the Patricia about the, um,
you know, strange men thing.
I did that a lot more in my youth than I'm doing now.
But she was talking about, um,
performing Felicia on strange men.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I couldn't imagine that.
Right.
I just didn't do that as often anymore.
Oh, thank God for that.
Uh, you can't keep a girl from giving a blow to have it.
It's just something that I'd love to do.
Ah.
Do you love doing it, huh?
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not doing it.
Okay.
I just want to make sure that you didn't have any interim comments.
You know Patricia, if you have any advice.
Uh, no.
How a large, breasted blow job.
giving loving woman can find a good man like Adam.
It would be very appreciated.
Thanks.
Bye.
I think she has all the qualifications.
Sounds like he doesn't.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't know.
It's, you know, the thing is, if I hear them talk,
but you know, it's especially because it's nice
that people can talk about this.
And there are probably a lot of people want to hear this.
Power to the podcast, baby.
Exactly.
And they want to get that off their big chest.
Of course.
But I always hate to to talk about that a lot,
because it makes men even bigger assholes.
You know, that's what I think.
I think they already think they're all that in a bag of chips.
They think they're so special.
So my thing, I am nice.
I'm always very warm.
I have a big smile.
I like to tease, but I'm totally in control.
And so my message is, don't, don't.
Yeah, I can explain that in detail.
Don't bring your guns.
Well, yeah, don't give them too much right away.
Just let them work for it.
Let them chase you.
That is the thing.
Make it very special.
Because if they think they can get it, just like that,
man, you're in trouble.
Let the balance of power as a whole.
Yeah, that's not good.
It's because men like women who are in control.
And they love to be controlled.
That is very sexual.
So I will never be the underdog.
I will never play the underdog.
You know that.
Right?
Well, what do you mean by underdog?
Well, I'm not the one.
The submissive one.
I'm the one in control.
I will say, Adam, lay down.
Oh, this is what we're going to do.
No, it's like, would you like a cup of tea?
Would you like to have sex?
Oh, oh, something happened to my sound.
Did you just lose it?
Yeah, I think so.
I was so lovely.
Did you have no sound?
Yeah.
No, nothing.
Why would you do?
I don't know.
I didn't do anything.
What are you hearing?
Subtash.
Shit man.
I'm back.
So yeah, that's what I like.
And my experience.
You know, I had very interesting men, very powerful men.
That's what they like.
So that's my experience.
I will never, ever behave like that.
It works both ways, by the way.
Because I didn't do anything for a long, long, long time when we met.
I made no moves.
No.
And then what happened?
I like that.
Yeah.
And then what happened?
Then what happened?
You made the move.
Yeah.
Yes.
But.
Guys, let me tell you, there's nothing like keeping a woman going from months
and then learning to speak to a woman.
First, I said you a lot of beautiful food.
Really?
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
A lot of avocados with shrimp.
Very good.
And lots of salmon.
I remember lots of salmon.
But I didn't go on my sushi.
Right away.
On your knees.
No.
In fact, no.
So that's my thing.
I mean, you know.
Okay.
No.
You can go shopping now.
Yeah.
He's shopping.
For your friend.
Yeah.
That's true.
Don't blow the surprise.
Oh, okay.
Okay, baby.
Thank you.
Well, that was, that was some very good advice.
Yeah.
Yes.
Well, thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
I like them very much.
Yeah.
They sound very good.
I think it's a great show.
I love listening to it.
I look forward to it.
They sound like they have big breasts.
Isn't that crazy?
Really?
Yeah.
I haven't developed that personally.
Both.
But one of them for sure.
Okay.
And it's got nothing to do with being thin or, you know, heavier.
No.
That's right.
Okay.
You're lovely for my brain, right?
Absolutely.
You know, we put my penis as close to it as possible.
I see.
Okay.
Bye.
Thanks, baby.
I love you.
Love you too.
Oh, they ain't no break the studio.
That's why.
Uh-huh.
Oh, by the way, huh, before you go, look.
Some people sent me some tattoo ideas.
Come on.
You got it.
Oh, boy.
Hold on.
Let me see.
Goal for.
Um.
Wait a minute.
Shit.
I think this is it.
Hold on.
Let's take a look.
Oh, God.
I have to re-log into Gmail.
I hate that.
Hold on.
See if it'll load it up immediately or if I have to do it again.
Uh-huh.
No, it's going to the inbox.
I'm afraid.
Oh, God.
Now the whole computer is.
You know what?
This happens every single way.
It might, it might fix it.
So whenever a picture comes near the computer.
Yeah.
I said, wings.
I want something cool in the middle.
I've got to open this.
Hold on.
Oh.
Pain in the ass.
Okay.
In the meantime, let me take.
Let me show you the next one.
This is from Frank Frank Jonah.
Yeah.
This is one.
Oh, this is one.
Wings with a little musical.
Is that a clef?
Is that what is that?
So.
The G.
G.
Yeah.
Look at this other one.
So everyone kind of got the wings thing.
They figured that out.
That's nice, isn't it?
This is with my head in the middle with an iPod attached to it.
Ah, thanks.
I don't think.
But this is nice, isn't it?
That's kind of cool with a little heart.
And it has, so it has a whole bunch of things in there.
Uh, and then Andy Armstrong sent one.
In pod we trust.
No.
Well, but it has PC and CC in there.
What?
Come closer.
Jump.
Jump to the mic, baby.
Jump up.
A little vagina with wings.
Very nice.
Okay.
I think you've overstayed your welcome.
Hold on.
Let me open this mic.
What?
Instead of that.
You know.
Yeah.
It's kind of cool though, isn't it?
But I like this one.
I really like the other one.
What is this one?
It's nice.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah.
You know, because of my father.
Because he's a great musician.
Oh, yeah.
It had a whole bunch of stuff.
But it doesn't really show the, I wanted the freedom of media somewhere in there.
I don't think.
Yeah.
It doesn't quite show that, yeah.
Is everything?
It has a heart.
Yeah.
I'll talk in front of the mic, baby.
Please.
No one can see it.
Well, but you already saw it.
It has a heart.
Yeah.
It has.
Well, let me try.
Looky.
There you go.
Can you see it?
It has everything.
It's nice.
It's actually up with that on the weblog.
Hmm.
On the end of the show.
No.
It's a look at it.
Yeah.
You're going to get a tattoo as well.
Huh?
You're going to get a tattoo?
No.
I don't know.
Why would you want that?
Okay.
All right.
I'm going on with the show.
Thanks, baby.
All right.
Bye.
Okay.
So keep in common.
And I'll shoot hold on the studios for an apartment here.
I'm trying it.
Ow.
Okay.
Got it.
Twist the G5 back into place.
There we go.
That's better.
All right.
The lovely Patricia, everybody.
Yosa.
Let's see.
What else did I have here?
Oh, I asked yesterday about
Lucien set up of Daily Planet TV.net.
And Frank again,
sent in this awesome link to Varus Software.
Actually, he sent a link to Wirecast.
And I think this is indeed exactly what Lucien is using.
It's very cool.
It's like a teleprompter,
but you can do effects and stuff at the same time.
It's very much a video podcast set.
So I think that I'll download that and I'll take it with me on the plain Saturday.
I'm going to San Francisco and play around with it and see what I come up with.
So that should be pretty cool.
All right.
More feedback here today.
Hi.
I'm this is Kevin and Beth from Dayton, Ohio.
We're here just to tell you about.
All right.
I'll admit it.
I'm one of the people who turned you into Apple.
We're having explicit content on your podcast.
But there's a big difference between explicit and offensive.
There's nothing offensive about
your show at all.
We both listen regularly.
What?
Eight ten months now?
Yeah.
We're dedicated listeners and Adam.
We don't give a shit.
What you say on there.
What you plan there.
It's all good.
Whatever the fuck you want.
But if we're going to go with what Apple's narrow definition of explicit is.
Your podcast should be explicit.
And that's the point I tried to make the apple.
Yeah.
It's Apple's problem.
Not yours.
They seem to go with what the recording industry has gone with as an explicit.
You say shit.
You say fuck.
You say dam in a song.
That song's explicit.
And then they enforce it arbitrarily.
Yeah.
This all started when a couple of weeks ago is listening to
Ignatian with Kevin Wright, Rose and Alex Albrecht.
Great podcast.
They got the same email that you got from Apple saying,
You know, hey, you need to mark your content as explicit.
They were completely dumbfounded because they'd swear two, three times an episode.
No fun, Adam.
But you swear ten times as much as they do.
And I don't consider you're swearing excessive.
But given that narrow definition of if you swear in your podcast that you remarked as an explicit,
your podcast should be marked as explicit.
Yeah.
And Apple just couldn't figure out the content of the email that the complaint was about them,
not about you.
Yeah.
You just, your show just made a really good example of how it was just arbitrarily enforced.
The only way you can report to them because getting a hold of apple is a little difficult.
The only thing you could do is you could say report a concern within the iTunes music store.
You're a reporter concern.
I say this podcast.
We marked as explicit.
And I explained.
I said, hey, you have a double standard here.
You came down a dig nation, but you've not come down on other podcasts.
And Adam, trust me, you are not the only one who says the occasional swear word,
but does not have an explicit tag on their podcast.
Yep.
So anyways, we just want to say, say whatever the fuck you want, we don't care.
You know, the explicit tag is not meant.
I don't even care if you have the explicit tag on there.
But it is nice to know, you know, we don't want our 40-year-old listening to the show.
Yeah.
But beyond that, we don't care what you say.
We're going to keep listening.
We love the show.
Yep.
We appreciate it.
We enjoy it.
Listen to it every day.
So that's it for us.
Thanks.
All right, Kevin and Beth.
You know, I wonder if there were any other people who registered to complain about the explicit tag.
If it was only based on one, that makes a lot of sense.
It'd just be funny to see if it was only one because yeah, you're absolutely right, of course.
And really, I don't care.
It's apples directory.
They can do whatever they want.
By the way, I think they're starting to lose their edge a little bit on the on what they what Apple dubbed the indie casters, which I still love.
Because they're really filling it up now with all kinds of mainstream stuff.
They're cutting deals.
All they're excitement is about television stuff for the video I pod.
That's really what they seem to be pushing.
So I strongly suggest that that you look at podcast,
dot com or indie potter dot org or pod cast pickle or.
You know, any myriad of other directories if you're really looking for something and want to make sure that you're listed properly there.
But hey, that's it's apples directory.
So, you know, they can totally do whatever they want to do.
It's just a little unfortunate that it's impossible to make everybody happy all of the time.
And, you know, add to that technical problems.
I know that they're having technical problems.
There's no other way it has to be something like that because, you know, all the things that are happening are not because, you know, they're sitting there reviewing every single podcast and you have some kind of magical process.
It's probably very, very labor intensive and very frustrating and.
You know, so be it.
So probably easier for Apple to do all of the mainstream stuff and do that really well.
And I enjoy that, you know, I and you know, and tie into the indie potters.
That's fine indie pod casters.
So, or, you know, give me the lost television series to buy and make sure that you show me that there's also.
Not one podcast, the official lost podcast with multiple.
There's one from Hawaii.
Maybe I think two from Hawaii that are lost podcast.
You know, link to that.
That's that's what you should be doing.
I think that's a, that's a really good idea.
And, you know, and thank God we still have things like the pod finder to steer people towards.
Although a very limited scope, at least steer them towards more independent podcasts.
Apple's doing their best. They know, they know what they've got to do and that's the way they work.
So they'll do it the way they can do it.
So let's not try to rely too much on them or Microsoft or Google or anybody else.
Right. I only on me got damage.
Interesting article a media week that I was pointed to that came out two days ago.
New study found the 12 to 24 year olds prefer their iPods over traditional radio.
This is according to bridge ratings.
According to bridge 85% said they would choose their MP3 players over traditional radio as their preferred option for music.
Survey response also preferred internet radio over AM and FM.
The study, which was, which interviewed 2,000 persons aged 12 to 24 was conducted as part of the University of Southern California's media lab.
How to make music radio appealing to the next generation analysis. That's a mouthful.
So you can read this yourself, but it does definitely show a trend.
It seems like a pretty small sample, 2000.
Again, I'm not a statistician, but maybe it's enough of a sample.
But I don't even need the study to know that that's where it's going.
And that's where being stuff like the pod safe music network comes into play.
That's where my daughter is now. Actually, she's tuning into podcast and she's going to artists websites and downloading.
Downloading MP3s that she likes and then she's telling your friends about them through instant messenger.
It just doesn't stop.
Hello, this is Nia Beta.
I've got something to tell you.
Hey guys here. Let's get ready now.
Let's grab a pod show.
What is this?
On the first day of Christmas, my iPod played for me.
Adam Curry's daily source code.
The second day of Christmas, my iPod played for me.
The time show.
And Adam Curry's daily source code.
There's no school.
On the day of Christmas, my iPod played for me.
I guess for one one.
The time show.
And Adam Curry's daily source code.
On the fourth day of Christmas, my iPod played for me.
History podcast.
Podcast show.
One.
The end show.
And Adele's year of joy.
The end of year.
Charlie.
Baby.
Yes.
There it is.
Let's put the breakdown here.
Okay.
One, two, three, four, five.
On the fifth day of Christmas, my iPod played for me.
Real days show.
History podcast.
Podcast show.
One.
The end show.
And Adele's year of joy.
I guess for one.
The end show.
And Adele's year of joy.
On the sixth day of Christmas, my iPod played for me.
Comedy.
I'm a D4 cast, Krill Cakes, Spray-O!
Here I am.
Here's the Rebond cast, Hot Cast for one one.
The showman.
And a pod father singing off key.
Singing off key.
On the 12th day of Christmas,
My iPod played for me.
These it can.
My spring pod gas rich as radio.
Media aren't a secret sexy in hash.
A very incarlin' show.
Harmony for cats.
Little cakes, radios.
History upon cats.
Hot cast for one one.
The intro.
And Adam for his daily source.
Merry Christmas, Adam.
At that day was Christmas.
Peace out.
Man, first the blow job story.
And now I get this Christmas truly has come early.
I got goose bumps, guys.
I truly got goose bumps on that.
Thank you so much.
It's, uh, I guess Ron from Grillo Cakes radio.
Completely pulled this together.
Um, let's see who do we have.
We had John and his wife Karen from the M show.
Rob from podcast four on one.
Jason and his wife Michelle from the history podcast.
Ron from Grillo Cakes radio, of course.
Clinton from comedy forecast.
Mary and Carla from the Mary and Carla show.
CC from CC Chapman from accident hash.
Franklin McMahon from media artist secrets.
Corey from red jazz radio.
Steve from life spring podcast and Bruce from the Zedcast.
Guys, thank you so much.
That was so, that really just blew me away.
That's fantastic.
You know, last year we got, let me see if I can find that.
Last year we did the 12 days of podcasting.
It was not, not the same production.
Hold on a second.
12 days of podcasting.
Come on, Google.
Do your thing.
Show it to me, baby.
12 days of damn if it isn't there.
Um, shoot.
Should we play that?
Yeah, let's play that.
Let's see.
This is what we did one year ago.
With a much smaller universe of podcasters.
This is interesting.
Oh, bad request invalid host name.
God doesn't that bite ass.
Oh, no.
Oh, wait.
Don't do that.
Maybe it's here.
This is horrible.
Okay, let me see if it's here.
Let's give another shot.
Hold on.
On the 12th day of podcasting, I potter fed to me.
12th conversations.
11 songs recovered.
Um, broken doors.
9.
Legos on file.
8.
Reviewed movies.
7.
Torrent seating.
6.
Pack of Hiny.
Boy.
4.
3.
Kufiko.
2.
Punks of Kasin.
And then closures in an XML tree.
There you go.
That was one year ago.
We have without a doubt.
Come quite a long way.
Judging on the, I should have played them in the reverse order, I guess.
Now, I love them both, obviously.
Both with the same beautiful intentions.
Wow.
You know, I was vibing on that.
Thank you guys.
I really appreciate it.
Hey, good news.
Slaw got the website up for pod save for peace.
That's the song.
39 pod.
Let me go to that side.
Well, what the hell?
Well, we're at it.
39 podcasters participated.
I'm sorry.
Pod save music artists participated.
Let me see.
Pod.
Safe.
Peace.
Org.
And here we go.
If every day we're Christmas is the result of a unique benefit project.
The song is a collaboration between 32 singers from eight countries.
A group collectively known as pod save for peace.
All brought together by the populous phenomenon phenomenon.
The, the, the, the, the, the of pod casting.
And the desire to pool their talents for a worthy cause.
A few causes make more sense of Christmas time.
Oh, and few causes make more sense of Christmas time.
The unicef, which aids children in need around the world.
The song was produced by Slaw and co-written by Orlando Pagan.
And the, the greatest part of the site that, that Slaw has got up and running here is that you can actually buy the song.
All proceeds go to unicef.
99 cents going, we're having tremendous problems getting into iTunes.
And I don't think it really matters.
And you know, if we send everyone to pod save for peace.org.
You can use PayPal or other methods to, to purchase the song.
It's a plain MP3.
There's no DRM or anything like that.
Let's, let's show, not just, you know, the world and unicef.
What we can do.
But it's also show the RIA.
I really believe in, in human nature.
But this, are you coming in?
Look, here's the website, baby.
You can see the pod save for peace.
You're on it.
Look, these are all the musicians that, where are you?
I just saw you. Oh, here you are.
Oh, nice.
I think I chose that picture.
You like it?
Yeah.
It's a nice picture, isn't it?
Isn't that cool?
Interesting.
What do you think about the song?
I love it.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's an earworm.
An earworm.
Mm-hmm.
Hey, you look cute with that hat.
Okay.
Fine.
Go in.
Doing the show.
Genius at work.
Yeah.
The help.
Love you.
Love you too.
Bye.
So here's the song that I'm talking about.
Pot save for peace.org or go over by it and support a worthy cause.
First winter snow outside my window.
Feels like that time again to me.
The mistletoe.
A Christmas show.
And the lighting of that famous Christmas tree.
All our shopping for them loved ones.
And making plans for Christmas feats.
Burning all goes by.
And the rain goes by.
And then we have to wait.
Another year.
We've got every day.
Christmas.
What a wonderful world.
This one free.
It will never be a proof.
We make all our dreams come true.
Every month we're every day.
It's time to bring out the good people.
I just look around now and you'll see it.
Everybody's nice and full of light.
And they get to those who aren't me.
And they get by every day.
Christmas.
What a wonderful world.
This one free.
It will never be a proof.
We make all our dreams come true.
Every month we're every day.
It's time to bring out the good people.
And they get by every day.
Christmas.
What a wonderful world.
This one free.
It's time to bring out the good people.
It's what we have, we will never be alone
We may call the trees on you
It's what we have, it's what we have
What we have, we will never be alone
We will never be alone, we will never be alone
We may call the trees on you
It's what we have, it's what we have, it's what we have
We will never be alone
We will never be alone, we will never be alone
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
that actually the play music are do report into what's at the BDS system and you know
so stuff gets does get picked up so hopefully we can get in there. I'm going to send
it to a couple of program directors slash program directors that I know because this song
is registered with AskCabby and my podcast has had permission to play it in their shows but if
it gets played on the radio then money comes in I think that's great so I don't go you know all
the profits proceeds from that will go to unicef. I can't say enough podsafe for piece dot org.
A couple more pieces of feedback one more podsafe tune them right here for today.
Hey Adam this is Eric. I have two bits of feedback about DSC 292.
One I was glad to hear you say that you know there's more to pod casting than music.
I run a fan base podcast about a sci-fi show and music plays a very minor role in it you know
sure the show is pretty much all discussion so you know I wasn't sure if you wanted feedback
from people that aren't music oriented per se and you know focused on the PMN and things like that.
The other thing is I know you've lived in Jersey or on the East Coast somewhere and I live
right outside Washington DC and I tell you the fox problem you're having over there we are being
overrun by foxes over here. You know I grew up in this area and I'd never saw fox growing up
and you know I recently moved back here a couple years ago and the foxes are just completely
approaching and you know plotting a takeover of suburbia so it's not just over there.
Also since I know you like to watch lost I would invite you to listen to my podcast
Firefly Talk which is all about a show called Firefly which if you're not familiar with it it's
it's a very funny Joss Weedon show he did buffy the vampire slayer. This show is a lot more mature
it's sort of a post apocalyptic sci-fi adventure with sort of a western flair to it. It's got lots
of guns and horse and if you haven't seen that show you should definitely give it a try so
anyways thanks a lot Adam for everything you're doing I'm a big fan I listen to you every day
and keep up the good work. Alright guns and horse? Hmm Firefly. I don't think I've come across
that anywhere does anyone know if I can get that on my skyside light that'll be cool I'll
definitely watch it based on that recommendation cool man appreciate it and appreciate the feedback
in general and of course podcasting is for so many different things so many art forms we haven't
even we haven't even thought about yet we're gonna get to all that here's a promo I just
really I love this promo remember I talked about the 12 to 24 year olds you know they're definitely
we'll cut inside the theater to our hidden camera man we'll be providing us with a bootleg
copy of the movie
hey and um doing promo for my podcast confused cask this is full of turkey day gas
episode one good times good times humans mumblings and most of all Paul's safe music
y'all from the pin and and we also feature sometimes if the co-hosts cover appears
room-skate stuff the most giddipping game ever these acts what the co-hosts things so Adam please
play my promo if you do thanks man lovey show confuse cask dot blog spot dot com back
c-o-n-s-u-s-e-t dot-b-l-o-g-s-p-o-t dot com all your teenagers belong to us
team podcasts kind of love hey well we're so off before I cut out of here also from the
music network
I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you
I'm so proud to be all of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of every god, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you you, I'm so proud of you, I'm so proud of you, I'm
I don't know why I'm a real person
There's music playing
Why can't you say yo
I don't do it all
I can't go mad
Check the movements
I've got a lot to do
I don't do it all
All of a sudden, do I worry what I said?
The music played in your room.
Man, we've called a lot of ground.
The only thing I didn't get around to was asking if anyone out there knows how ask,
and this is just a music business question.
So if you're a published artist, you may have the answer for me.
If you are registered with Ask Have Be Am I and you start getting airplay overseas,
how is that money collected?
And subsequent to that, can you as a foreigner, not a U.S. citizen or a resident of the
United States, can you register with Ask Have Be Am I and thus have performance royalties
collected in different countries through, through however it's done today?
Does that make sense?
That question?
Because that way, artists who are having all these issues with not being allowed to give
podcasts, there's permission to play their tunes on podcasts could be circumvented.
Excuse me.
If they were to sign up with Ask Have Be Am I.
So that's my question, do you or dailysourcecode.com, Adam at curry.com.
I will be back here tomorrow with a Thursday's edition of the Delta Sierra Charity Daily
Source Code.
Take care, everybody.
Pot Show.
The podcast, cool kids, go for.