Delta share a Charlie one nine or one.
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear since radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
It's Adam Curry!
You are a bitch!
Boo!
Oh yeah!
I apologize I'm a dick.
Oh dick, some respect.
Rocky stuff?
Oh yeah.
It's you.
What are you, what are you up to?
I'm in a dick.
Oh dick, some respect.
By the way, you're hearing that wild cherry sign.
I was like, what was that 1970?
You say 78?
Something like that?
Really think I give a shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit shit.
Oh what are you doing?
I weird in camera dick they are.
Touch anything sniff at all
You're a bad man! And you made me cry! I hate you!
You know, I'm an idiot!
You've been drinking!
Oh yeah!
It's the MTV!
It's the DVD!
What you just said is one of the most insanely idiotic things I've ever heard.
At no point, were you even close to anything that could be considered irrational thought?
Everyone in this room is now dumber for having left until it.
Oh boy.
It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
To the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky and crispy.
I like to think I'm flying into this jar.
I'm just kidding!
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It is the Daily Source Code today is the 8th of June 2005.
It was the Wednesday?
It was Tuesday.
I don't know, man.
How you doing?
Everybody?
It's another beautiful day here in Guilford.
It's curry cottage.
It's a little bit later than normal.
It's one, one, 42.
And the source code.
Music heavy today.
It felt like playing lots of cool pod safe tunes.
And I got another hit test, of course.
Young palette.
Doing his stuff.
How'd you like that opening, huh?
Brand new.
Although it's really old.
It's something I've played a while back.
No idea who made it, but I actually was meant kind of to scorn me.
But I know I kind of dig it now.
Just something new to start it off with.
Getting all kinds of complaints.
Oh, it's two minutes before you get to actually talking on the shows.
I'm skipping fast forwarding the opening of the show.
Great.
That's what those buttons are for.
And you can find them on the I River.
I have a interesting start of the day.
We're shipping horseback to Belgium to its original trainer.
Actually, it's being sold.
And there's a lot of difficulty trying to move animals into the UK.
But also out of the UK, it's kind of interesting.
Man, all kinds of forms and documents and stuff that you need.
In health certificates, I think they'd be glad to get one less animal.
Or one more animal out of the country have one less to deal with.
But apparently that is not the case.
As I said, lots of podsake music tunes today on the show.
A couple of promos, a young pull-out hit test, which of course is also always music heavy.
And I'm going to couple of things to talk about.
Got some great feedback to the yesterday show and the show notes and just want to chat with you about some stuff.
But first, an awesome mashup.
Get this party started.
The trip's Nirvana makes on the daily sucks horse coat.
Then on a Saturday night, everybody's waiting for me to arrive.
Sending out the message to all of my friends.
We'll be looking flashy in my Mercedes-Benz.
I got lots of styles like my gold diamond rings.
I can go from miles if you know what I mean.
I'm going to couple of things to talk about.
I'm going to couple things to talk about.
Party parties.
I want to y'know you know almost things that Megan said.
New that this was not Pod safe because it kind of...
created a little drop out there to render the entire recording useless.
I got a great email yesterday about that about the dropouts that I've been having.
Now I know it's definitely not audio hijacked pro because it tells you when it's skipped
something when it's had a dropout.
This is the program mega-sag that I've been using on the Mac when I'm not beta testing
cast blaster on the tablet, on the crap-lit.
Ryan Doer sent me a really long, very thoughtful email about the problem was, but the title
of the subject of the emails is, it's not your hard drive, I know I've had it happen to
me.
Here's the deal, it's actually a problem with quick time that is ancient and Apple doesn't
seem to be interested in fixing.
You're experiencing a lock-up of quick time when loading variable bitrate MP3 files.
Mega-sagged loads into quick-time player slots, actually a bit more complicated than
that but just think of each slot as a player in that quick-time player program, okay, I
kind of figure that.
So as a track is playing the next one loads, right, that's what mega-sagged does for me.
If it's in a variable bitrate MP3, the true time of the file must be calculated.
Quick-time is, unfortunately, not performing very efficiently and stops playback to give
more attention to the calculation, this is extremely irritating, not no shit.
And then he has a number of suggestions to fix the problem, of course, I can convert
to AAC or wave files using iTunes and then in Mega-sagged, I need to re-link the files
that I converted and remove the originals.
And then he gives me an email at one of the guys at Mega-sagged who will give me additional
suggestions.
Very cool, thanks a lot Ryan and it makes a total sense.
And if it's really just something that, you know, quick-time needs to fix, let's start
pitching about it.
It seems to work.
It only didn't even take us a year to get podcasting into iTunes, so maybe we can get
that fixed.
I totally understand what's happening.
It's just like one of those legacy things that lays around, but man, it's really bumming
me out when using programs on the Mac, so, and I know, well, what's his name?
Who's the head over there at Apple of Frank Casanova?
There you go.
Yeah.
All right.
The APB out to Frank Casanova.
Hopefully he'll hear this and we'll take action.
Or at least let us know what's happening.
It's a daily source code.
My name's Adam Curry.
I'm trying to do this every single day.
If you're new, welcome to the show.
If you're subscribed, thanks for subscribing.
If you don't know how to, head on over to iPodr.org or podcastally.com, and there's plenty
people who will help you out, or just hold off four or five weeks in iTunes.
It'll become very apparent.
I received another email a while ago from Young Lady Kay, and she was thinking of setting up
a podcasting business, and she and I helped her out with a couple things.
And she sent me the following message, which is really cute.
Adam Adam, Bob Adam, banana, banana, phoat Adam, phoat Adam, phoat Adam, phoat Adam,
Adam, hey, do I have to pay rights for the name, game song?
I hope not.
Anyway, this is Kay saying hi, and thank you so much from AskMyPod.com.
I really appreciate all the help that you've given me so far, and my RSS feeds are up and
working.
Thank you Adam.
You are the pod father.
Woo!
Anyway, I wanted to share with your listeners a little bit about what we do here at AskMyPod.com.
We are a positive podcasting group, and our thing is make them smile, because we think that you can do that.
You can go out, and you can enjoy the hell out of yourself, and help other people do the same.
So visit AskMyPod.com and smile in your day.
Okay, so we have six different shows.
The first one is our feature presentation, and that changes with every episode.
The current presentation is an interview with a happy angel.
Talking about how you can remain happy in a world of adversity.
How do you deal with all that negative crap you've gotten your day all the time?
Yeah, so far I'm digging this line up.
Fine.
What can you do about it?
PJKFC is where we interview up and coming bands and new music.
This is all pod safe music.
Again, we currently have an interview with J.D. from Sawser, a really hot band from Toronto.
AskBubb is an advice column.
You write in and let us know what your issues are, and we'll feed that through to Bubba, who works on our
staff here at AskMyPod.
That wouldn't happen to be Bubba the love sponge now, wouldn't it?
And he'll help you figure out your dilemma.
Happy news is where you can tune in, and hear the positive things that are happening around the globe.
Hookup is where we have really nice people, meeting other really nice people one at a time.
Tune in to hookup and see who's available right now.
That is something you have to hear.
This is a great line up for shows.
I'm totally digging it.
Extreme chicks features women who are on the cutting edge.
We have skydivers, secret agents, and all kinds of groovy stuff that we're doing.
Yeah.
We hope you like our format, and we hope that we're able to help people see things in a better
perspective and go out and make them smile.
That's our thing, and that's what we're trying to do.
And again, Adam, thank you so much for your help.
I'd like to leave you with us on from the Unrequited Loves.
This is Track One Off of their CD available on our PJKFC website here at AskMyPod.com.
These are the Unrequited Loves.
Make them smile.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Congratulations, and may you have many employees.
And you heard their adventure.
It's a daily source code.
Taking it out too soon.
Yeah.
It's going to be a new music Tuesday.
Now on.
It's hard to love.
I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you
I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've ever heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've never heard of you, I've not heard of you, I've ever heard of you, I've heard too, I've ever heard of you
He's all right, he's all right, he's all right, he's all right
He's all right, he's all right, he's all right
He's all right, he's all right
He's all right It's all right, he's all right
Don't be afraid, but you're all the greatest, just after the night it's all the way to the front of the walls
Don't be afraid, but you're all the best, and don't be afraid, but you're all the best
Don't be afraid, but you're all the best, and don't be afraid, but you're all the best, and don't be afraid, but you're all the best, and don't be afraid, but you're all the best, and don't be afraid, but you're all the best
Great..
We've got time here
All right, fucking quick time.
All right, okay, way to go, congratulations.
I was like a great little podcast network.
We should talk, girl.
By the way, thanks to JGNLA for the mashup today,
Pink with Nirvana, versus Nirvana, I should say.
Hey, yesterday I said something while I was narrating
the Steve Jobs keynote about, let's see, about an NPR show,
I think, called the treatment, which, of course,
I'd never heard, but just the, I said it was boring.
I didn't say it was boring, but I went, okay, so Steve Jobs
played with the source code and I said,
ask, I said, ask.
And then all the geeks in the house loved it.
And so they got a chuckle, and then the start of the treatment
was, I said boring, but I've never listened to the show.
I show, and but from what I see in comments on yesterday's show notes,
it is awesome and not at all boring.
So I apologize, I shouldn't have said it that way.
Certainly not without having heard the show.
I think I was just talking about what I'm seeing is the trend
that the, okay, so in blogging we had newspapers and publications,
magazines, et cetera, who were saying, well, bloggers are not
journalists, and it seems that with podcasting,
we're going to run into a reasonably similar situation
where the established media is going to say, okay,
we're professional and they're amateurs.
And this was very clear from what Steve Jobs said in his keynote,
and I refer back to yesterday's source code to listen to that
with my narration.
I think that a established media can either,
it has two choices really.
When something comes along that really breaks a business model
or is really something that shifts business in a very profound way.
And they can either extend or defend.
And it's interesting because you can also kind of walk in the middle.
You may compromise as in the business all the time for good or for bad.
And I think what the Apple is doing is compromising by saying,
okay, we're extending by offering podcasts
to come into the iTunes world, but we're also defending
by saying, hey, look at all these professionals
who are doing it.
So, of course, they're going to highlight probably one
to 2,000 professional podcasts.
Now, what is the difference between professional and amateur?
As far as I know, it's just whether you're getting paid for it or not.
It's whether you decide to commercialize that part of what you're doing
and take money or barter and products or something.
That's the only real difference.
It not to be confused with, oh, it sounds professional.
You know, even if you are a quote professional,
which means you're getting paid for doing what you're doing,
you can still be boring or you can be no good or have no talent.
Plenty of that going around in the professional world.
And the same goes for the amateur world.
So that's the only difference.
And actually, I think it's beautiful to put it that way
because once you understand that the only difference between professional
and amateur is getting paid for it or not,
it becomes very easy to see what a tremendous opportunity there
is in podcasting.
So I kind of like that.
Although I listened to Future Tense, which is John Gordon, I think.
He's in Minneapolis.
I don't have a clip.
It was actually, I was thinking of pulling a clip from it,
but it was so long.
It was the CEO of Audible.
The place we can download, spoken word, audio books for a fee.
I'm a subscriber, actually.
I don't take enough advantage of my subscription
because they presume that you're going to buy a book every month.
You actually pay for the book.
And I don't think the credits get saved up.
But either way, because they've been at it for a long time.
And I'm a believer in selling premium content as well.
But there, the CEO was kind of defending.
He wasn't really extending.
And what did tremendous opportunity?
He was really saying, hey, these are people with track records.
I'm like, you don't have to be good to have a track record.
You track records start somewhere.
So if I were an investor, I'd think about that.
I don't think the CEO has, he feels, he's definitely defending.
It's a long interview.
Please check it out.
Future tense.
I'll put a link to it in the show notes to the show itself.
He's really saying, well, this is not an iPod explosion.
This is not like DVD or we went from $30 million to $350 million sold.
He says that the explosion will happen, but that'll be much later.
And it's just like, man, ride the wave, dig it, you know?
I think it ought to be a perfect place to sell premium content.
And you should be out there scouting and you should be, I think you should be trying
to do deals with podcasters.
Never mind, I'm happy to do it for you.
So you've got a couple of workmen in this week.
There's no, they only work at like four hours, I don't know if that's four hours a day,
but four hours on what they're doing here at the cottage, they're basically fixing the window,
so we don't freeze the death there, doing some isolation, isolation, insulation, that's
what it is.
And so I got to talk about one of the guys and talk about podcasting.
He came up later and he said, hey, I got a question, you know, my cousin has an iPod
shuffle.
And I've got a Tashiba satellite laptop and I want to plug it in, I've got all the software
and everything ready to go, but it seems like his USB plug on the Tashiba is incompatible
with the shuffle.
I like that doesn't sound right.
I mean, it could be like one of those printer USB cables, no, it wasn't that either.
So he says it just doesn't fit in.
So if you happen to know if that's true or if there's some kind of adapter or, you know,
connector that he can put in, he said it would bring the kid over tomorrow, so I'll take
a look at it, excuse me.
Oh, guess what, that's deadly.
It's T property without a string on the T bag.
It's not the sense, say, oh, today, what else do I want to talk about?
I've got the future tense, I was going to talk about fame.
Yeah, fuck it.
That's, that was related to the audible thing.
Well, I will do that another day.
Today, of course, this new music Tuesday, I've just dubbed it that.
So let me see, where's the rest of my notes?
Crap.
I thought I had the notes for this shoot.
There's no fucking producer.
What is it?
We're going to play, here we go.
Unsaid band from Dallas.
That's what it was.
Screamin' relax out every time
Call the unit guy
Every time you find your ends in mind
Be get it but you get it from someone else
That this love thing means trust to me
I hear you whisper that you pull the windows down
I try to stop but my odds not stopping now
This is gonna be a tragedy
Please Mother say prayer for me with
To怕 that I gave you secrets
Just get the fake sniff mean time
Show it to me take it waver
You said this night could not surprise us
I made some tape in her eyes
I don't know if you're interested in the time I've never faced
Just don't know how they should
Just think of it, just think of it, just think of it
So, I know, just think of it, just think of it
Just think of it, just think of it
And if you're great though, be me
So think of it, just think of it
Sit down, just make it to be me
I take it down Ceachery
Make me, just think of it
They never say everything to me
Come on, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go,
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's do it, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not
sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, and if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can carry it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can, but I would be fine for this anymore, but I'm not sure whether I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I think I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'm not sure.
and perhaps you remember when I was on KFI in Los Angeles,
50,000 watts of clear channel,
humpin' and pumpin' wattage.
But I love your show,
and I wanted to say hi,
and I wanted to tell you that the diamond mine
is going to be back on the air on the internet,
and as an iPod cast,
and we hope that you'll support us,
we have been supporting you.
Thanks.
I've been thinking about things that you probably don't,
wasting time you said just to be definite,
what's the matter with me if you already know?
I'm alone,
sorry me.
I'm waking up,
trying to make something you need to bear,
but we're growing up soon.
Yeah, I might waste my time,
when we're growing up soon.
We're growing up again.
Are you listening to what I said?
Here we are again,
trying to make sense of this,
lost the reason we meant to keep down in the road,
on the road suddenly.
We're waking up, trying to make something I need to bear,
but we're growing up soon.
Yeah, I might waste my time,
when we're growing up soon.
We're growing up again,
because we're growing up soon.
Oh, we're wasting our time.
Yeah, I might waste my time,
when we're growing up soon.
Oh, we're wasting our time,
We're growing up soon.
when we're growing up soon.
Oh, we're wasting our time.
Oh, we're wasting our time,
because we're growing up soon.
Oh, we're wasting our time.
Oh, we were wasting our time.
Yeah, we're wasting our time.
Oh, we're wasting our time.
I'm thinking about parking your second bath,
then you're thinking about looking out.
Yeah, it'd be a such a perm.
Have I told you recently how much I enjoyed doing this? Oh man, what an awesome song
Podsafe of course throwing stones by tourists from Vancouver. They see their
listed on garageband.com. Of course links all of that in the show notes at today's
show. Before that was the band from Dallas, Eudacuz and his name is their name.
Red Light's a title that song, man. We should do this more often. We should do a
new music Tuesday every other day of the week. We could do a new music Tuesday on Thursday
every one of you. Oh yeah. Man, it's not often. Actually, I got to bring up iTunes here
because this is I didn't prep this. It's not often that you get an endorsement from somebody
that is so honest and so beautiful. But yesterday I got, it's time to light away the match.
Got an endorsement from Chris Rockwell from the Daily Download. That's the show that he does
it's a poop cast basically. Whenever he, it's time for him to go to the bathroom. He calls
that a studio and he takes his gear in there and he listens to it. By the way, the best time
in place to listen to this podcast is when you're poop casting yourself, of course. That
really gives you a monomono connection. And so Chris was talking about the work that he's
doing with Podsho and I just wanted you to hear it because you know, you know, when a guy is
taking a dump, he can't lie. It's like you're concentrating on it. It's about it.
Here we go. Life, you guys kind of hang in there, but life just got really busy and I just needed
to get, you know, caught up on a lot of things in my life and a lot of projects that I was working on.
And, you know, just to give me some time to where I could come back and get back. Yeah, it's pretty
down in the groove. All right. He tells us what you've been speaking of grooves. I have a brown fish
working its way out of mind. So let's get into the studio. See, there he goes. He's walking into the
studio. Sounded a little hollow and I'm not sure if I've screwed up something while I was away
or maybe my head said it's just a little funky. But anyway, last night for dinner, I had him and they
sell it. It's been pretty gassy today. So I'm not really sure what caused that. Maybe I had a
soy bar. Oh, that morning for breakfast. That'll do it. And that sometimes will do it.
That's a breakfast of that. That's for us. Well, so much to talk about.
I've received this. Let's see. First off, I wanted to talk a little bit about what I have been
up to. I've been working on a music database for Adam Curry's company, Pod Show. It's going to be a
really cool resource for podcasters, hooking them up with great indie artists. It really cool.
I'm not a very good programmer. I'll let you know that now. I love hearing that. Thank you very much.
Thanks, Chris. Keep on going, buddy. But I'm really happy with the direction this is going
and the vision that these guys have. Everybody talks about the corporations getting into podcasters.
No, so you know he's not lying because you can't lie when you're doing this. Oh, yes.
Oh, here comes. Oh, man. Anyway, my favorite part of the show. Even though, you know,
there's people seem to be against the pod show idea of becoming corporate. These guys really
have some great vision and really see more than just money. The whole money, you know, money to be made.
It's more about the community to be made. So really impressive. I'm really impressed. We're
working with these guys. Well, let's see what else have I been doing. So anyway, thank you very much,
Chris appreciate that that endorsement. And yes, that I was listening to this in the gym. Yes,
I've been for the second time already. Please, to take note of that. And during that piece,
but then also a little bit later on, I was laughing my ass off and people were like, oh, dude,
what's he up to? It was very, very funny show. I'll link to that, of course, in the show,
no, to be interested in hearing the whole thing.
Question one. How can all it become rich and famous? Question two. What's the meaning of life?
Question three. Where can I find a fun weekly trivia quiz podcast?
The answer to at least one of these questions can be found by visiting www.podquiz.com.
That's www.podquiz.com.
Yeah, was it? Of course, there is truly only one pod quiz. It's, you know, what it is?
Podquiz. What are you casting with Adam Curry?
Three, two, one. It's time for the interest with John Poeh.
Yeah, come on. Hey Adam, this is another hit test number 42 to be specific. And this one is also
recorded with cast blaster bed of 14. There's not much to tell about anything right now. So let's start with
the intro right away. This is intro number one.
Okay, easy one from movie flash dance, Michael Sunbello with Maniac.
And this is number two.
Okay, also easy for the MTV guy.
That's her burning by Midnight Oil.
And the final one is number three.
Oh, so my favorite. Van Halen run in with the devil. I think I got three for three today.
Fantastic. And you probably heard the Gmail sound. I just got a million from Mike
cast blaster Mike. No time for that right now because we're busy with the hit test. You're such a good
beta test. We're the intro. So this is answer number one.
It's an only Michael Sunbello. This is Maniac.
One point for the easy Michael.
From 1983, answer number one, Michael Sunbello. And this is answer number two. Midnight Oil.
That's our burning.
Hold and relax and buy with these awesome steam and party five degrees.
Patricia hates this guy. Thank you for singing. He has sex when I look his turn.
Midnight Oil. Answer number three.
This is the final answer. It's Van Halen and run in with the devil.
My life back there's no tomorrow. Yes, I'm living at our place like you.
One in with the devil Van Halen is answer number three.
Okay, and I'm a bit sit for a hit test number 42. As always, feedback is welcome and hit
test at gmail.com. And you can find the information about the hit test at yompolit.com,
the J.A. and B.O.L. E.C. dot com. And also check out the hit test podcast on the same site.
But thank you for listening. See you next time. Bye bye. All right, John. Thank you very much once again.
That sounded really good coming from the cast blast. And you want to figure it out that somehow
something's out of phase in my sound card. And people leave that shit.
Okay, and normally I'd stop the show right here, but this is the new music Tuesday. So
gotta play something sent to me by the potentate of pod safe. That's what Peter wants me to call.
I think it was the high priest, but a potentate apparently is higher than that. Make a few
in mind, it's orange park.
And this was the song that I miss. Do you think I'm making it? Do you want me to make it?
No, to sound, I think I'm your mind. Do that way, start it, make I'm your mind. Do that way, start it.
Someone said to me, look what I just found. No one's come in clean. They never make a sound.
I see you falling with this, what's the song that I miss? Do you think I'm making it? Do you want me to make it?
No, to sound, I think I'm your mind. Do that way, start it, make I'm your mind. Do that way, start it.
I always never wanted you to change your mind. The time that follows more and it needs you up and time.
I'll take back all the things that you were making, but I'll say goodbye, you say goodbye.
No, to sound, I think I'm your mind. Do that way, start it, make I'm your mind.
Do that way, start it, make I'm your mind. Do that way, start it, make I'm your mind.
Songs from the unknown, make up your mind, orange park on your daily source code, man. The music business really messed it up when they thought that, you know, by not letting us play their music on podcasts that they were doing the right things.
Stupid, look at all the exposure, we're giving it these great new bands, I love it.
That was fun, hope you enjoyed it, a little heavy on the guitar side of everything, but that was kind of the vibe I had today.
So I'm glad I could share that with you, hope you didn't fast forward through too much stuff, links to all of the songs and the promos that I played today are in the show notes, find those at dailysourcecode.com
You may want to leave a comment, you can do that at www.curry.com, or email is always welcome, don't expect it to be red.
I'm really trying to fish out the good ones, though it's very tough. Do you may able to do it a great job for me, Adam or Curry.com, and audio comments, also welcome here.
For promos, anything else you want to send me, submit at podshow.com, and send podsafe and podshow.com for podsafe music, and mash up, mash up at podshow.com.
Alright, that's it. I've got a lot of show notes to do, so for those of you who are wondering, I don't edit the show together, I basically do it all on the fly, just one take recording, and when I mess up, hey, there you go.
If I don't mess up, I'll do that.
Okay, so the podcast feed, of course, is a deadly source code.com, I think of this custom, or something else I was going to say.
Anyway, Patricia actually said, yes, they say, hey, it's time we do another podcast together, don't you think?
Trying to get it, taking care of, that should be fun.
I'll be back tomorrow for the Wednesday edition of the Daily Source Code.
You're listening to whatever you want to, just enjoy. Take care everybody. Bye.