Delta Sierra Charly 227
You're DJ!
I'm your DJ!
Your DJ has only just begun
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
Than the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
August 24th, 2005, your daily source code is on
The power of your head, though everybody
Earlier today, as promised, it is now only a quarter to two in the afternoon
So, I'm going to have a much more energetic show
I've actually created an outline
And I've got all my stuff all prepped today
Ran through the whole mailbox, lots of stuff to catch up on
The power of your head is coming
Boy, did we ever make a good decision yesterday
To not stay overnight and fly back this morning
Whether it's total crap, we've got high winds, we've got low visibility
And let your aim
As we say in aviation, the rock is wet
And I can't see it
So it's a perfect day to kind of
Mellow around the house, get ready for the big podcast
Complex move
Remember, that's the big, the big desk that was built for me
So I got to rearrange the room, get ready for it tomorrow
On today's source code, of course, I'm not saying music
Obviously plenty of promos want to talk about the promos as well
And some of the way that we're setting up hot show
And different avenues for you to get the word out
About your podcast that we can really start promoting these
And make sure that we can get those 100 million listeners
And when they do show up, give us some of the lessons too
I also want to talk about teenagers
Yeah, we got one, 14 that's turning 15 on Saturday
And I just want to spew some parental stuff about that
We'll get to that in a second
The first it's time to roll out a mashup
This is actually it's an agro one week on mashup.com
I think I mentioned that yesterday
So art has been sending me all the latest agro one mashups
And he also has following on and yesterday's source code
He has some ideas about how to get some of the creators of these wonderful mashups
So I'm going to keep you able to speed on that
He's going to send me all the plans
Here's turn out the car lights on the source code
Yeah, it's time to slow on only inside this bed
To blow a patch of it, my little slave was making it, it's good
We're gonna make it inside my head
It's gonna be your better run for it
That's the midnight
I'm running like a devil city
If you're wondering something
So easy to tell the problems
It's so easy to play a little breakdown
It's so easy to fly through a window
It's so easy to play with the sound
It's a bad, brilliant day
Because it can't be ready for a change
I didn't make it by the world
I didn't feel it
If it's half day low, if it's half as close
No, if it's willing, no
But as a midnight
I'm running like a devil city
If you're wondering something
So easy to tell the problems
It's so easy to play with the sound
It's so tough to get up
It's so tough
It's time to say the truth
When you hear that, you can't see you
I asked you on the book, tell me your name
Number two to the court
You can't do it on my whole life
I'm burning up, burning up, burning up
I'm burning up, burning up
You can't do it on my whole life
I'm going to come back and see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you see you when you
you when the you see you when you see you when you see you when you see sort of you and see me.
and see me then see me.
and see me.
you just keep me trembling
I'll open the next scene
and solve the time
you
turn out the car light
cars moving in stereo
versus Nelly Furtado's
turn out the light mashed up by Agro1
you heard it here
on the source code
mashuptown.com is where I came from
thanks to a dub art
over there and
very curious art
to hear what ideas you have
for against beer money
to the people or more
perhaps
and to the artists as well
who are all part of these
mashups because so much
fun
you know, it's such a
cultural thing
we have all these tools
we can mash things together
but we don't have any legal way
to share them
so any thoughts on that
would be very, very cool
apologies for yesterday's source code
for the iTunes
subscribers
you probably have it by now
so you have two shows
to listen to today
there's just too many steps
in the freaking process
to get a podcast up
you know
I'm uploading to three
different servers
creating
you know
making sure RSS files
are in the right place
and the naming conventions
this should be dragon
drop shit
I'm telling you
this is we actually have a
meeting today
where we're discussing
podcast
alice functionality
podshow
indie potter.org
how we're bringing it all together
and what pieces will be for listeners
what pieces will be for podcasters
and one thing for sure
when we come out with
with our full
blown offering for podcasters
it's got to be real simple
you know
I like the idea of just one button
boom
it's done
show notes are taken care of
they're posted
RSS feeds are done
uploads are done
and that's what computers
are for I think
right
that's
yeah I thought computers
actually were supposed to
make it life easier
I got to get back
into apple scripting stuff
you know
that's
which is of course
how the original iPod or script started
was just frustration
and apple script
actually
I just need some time
maybe the next trip
over to San Francisco
when I'm on
on the plane
I'll play around with
what does that thing called
it's
what is that new thing
in tiger
that
events or whatever
the events manager
anyway
it's
a way to create
apple scripts
simply by driving
drag and drop
and
probably with some tweaking
I'll be able to get some stuff
done so
that'll be just
for my personal benefit
I see we have so much to talk about today
on the way
promos
I want to talk about that
I run through the mail bag
because there's a lot of
backlog of e-mail stuff
that I wanted to talk about
also yesterday
yesterday's flight
which went from
ferrocs
in
nearby
Gilford
to Rotterdam
from Rotterdam
to Midasay Lont
in the Netherlands
and then that's when we decided
that we would go back
back to ferrocs
I've posted
my Bluetooth GPS unit
put it right up on the dashboard of the plane
I had my I didn't even talk about this
I had my MDA
with
what is that pocket
FMS
which is an open source
flight management system
which has
moving map
flight planning
it gets all this data
that's freely available
off the internet
which is the same way
jeperson
or any of those other guys do it
all the nav data
downloads weather data
for you
it's a fantastic program
it's open source
and it's free
I don't know
anything like
25 euros or something
to this project
and it's just it's really
really cool
you can run it on your laptop
you can run it on your on your
on your PDA
you can select maps
for the entire world
anyway
so I'm also able to
in this bluetooth
GPS unit
I'm able to record
my track
you know
the flight that I made
and if you load that into Google Earth
you can fly
the same flight path
that I flew
because you can you fly past
it's just me fast
the
has a big inhale
for instance
which is an airport
very well known airport
great navigation point
and you can actually stop the map
and then drill down
and go look at the airfield
you know you can see
we crossed over the English channel
so the next steps there
and I'm just trying to start
provide data
so people can do stuff with it
I would need easy way
to add photos to that
so what I'd like to do
is
just have some kind of application
where you throw a bunch of photos in
that wouldn't necessarily have GPS data
but would have time data
because GPS data in a GPS file
has the time as well
and it gets that time from the satellite
so you can sync that time up
with your camera I guess
and then it should know
where to just drop these spots in
so you can have hot spots
and pop up pictures
and
there's got to be something there
and then once you've got that piece
figured out
then I think we could actually move
over towards
combining that with the audio
from a podcast
and imagine how cool that would be
if you recorded the entire trip
and at any point you wanted to drill down
you could listen to the audio
as we were flying
or as we were just completing that piece
of the trip
it sounds like something that could be
one application all built together
and actually the MDA would be perfect for it
because it could take pictures
it can register GPS data
and it can record sound
wouldn't that be cool
to just be walking around
and then you
even if you don't talk
it doesn't matter
because only at points of interest
when you face it you take a picture
you'll be talking about it
and then you could just
you know bring that audio up
or something
there is a lot of cool stuff
that can be done
and I'm really getting into this GPS stuff
digging it totally
Who's your daddy?
Hey Adam, this is Aaron
and this is Cliff
and we're here to introduce
to you
the who's your daddy podcast
for two fathers
to discuss issues
facing fathers and family
we're tossing
a little pod safe music
some toy abuse
some tech and humor
yep
you'll hear two educated fathers
talk about things like
foreskin
we're going to read this
a little bit
a little bit like this
is to a little family
everyone is a medical thing
everyone has it except for women
what?
whoa
that I think is actually incorrect
not everyone has it
anymore
and
you have it so put the
and don't forget
Cliff's fatherly wisdom
raise your hand if you're
sorry
two married old sayers
and uh
the way to five years
before we had a kid
we realize we want to kid
I had jogging, two dogs, I had chunked him.
I think here your question is a horse or oh, I don't know if I thought maybe a kid
he said no horse, yes kid.
I think horse is actually a costume or the kids.
They'd maintain.
He'd be a thing sometimes.
You don't have to send a horse to college.
I got to subscribe to this show.
Let's talk.
But I right there was a sound clip that we're really gonna have to hear this again.
You don't have to send a horse to college.
So join us every week on the Who's your daddy podcast.
Thanks Adam.
Can you say goodbye to everybody?
Goodbye.
Pod Joe.
Content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
Hello.
This is Jack.
I just wanted to let you know that we have changed that year again.
You know, don't leave every door.
Jew cities.com.
Jack will spend that stray A.K.A.L.S.T.N.
A lot of people get mixed over and over.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Yeah, you know, actually I'm listening to the sound.
I think I changed something that I shouldn't have.
Hold on.
Let me just see if I can turn off this limiter here.
See what that does.
Hold on.
I turned this off.
One two.
That's actually.
A little.
Oh, it's a little worse.
Hold on.
Let me bring that back in.
This is interesting.
let's see, bright. There you go. Yeah, that's much better. Okay. Just messing around with the digital
workstation. I really love this box because I can basically use it in any situation that I might
run into. You know, need to plug in 3a 4 5 6 extra mics, need to plug in external gear, need
to record stuff, directly to the hard drive. The right now I have it set up in what they call
direct mode. So, it's outputting everything in any, you know, it's using the, what you call,
the stereo valve processor is in the chain there. It's just so incredibly cool. What I need is
it, I really need a flight case for all this stuff. I think I should have, because I know that
this is going to be a fucked up if I put this in my suitcase. I should have a flight case for the
mixer, for my microphone, what else should be in it? Well, of course, the mixer has an external power
supply they always do. Headphones, maybe even my fire wire drive in there with all the tunes
on it, you know, something like that. It'll just be an additional piece of luggage, but I think
it'll be well worth it to carry that around that way. It's not that heavy, but man, this thing
is really, I think it's perfect for getting the job done, if you know what I mean. Okay,
promo is going to talk about that for a second. As we start to build up the pod show network
and the pod show delivery network, in order to get your podcast out to the masses, the best way
for people to discover new podcast and to browse them is by listening to promos. Now,
there are lots of people making promos, but I'm just amazed at how many people say,
hey, you know, I've got a podcast, could you please mention it, which I'm happy to do, but, you know,
I don't have all the discretionary time either to listen to a whole bunch of podcast. Now, if you
can make a promo, which is exactly what it sounds like, you know, just tell us what the show is about,
you know, what's on it this week, you can make new promos whenever you want. If we, if we can
really all get into making promos, then these things can be pushed through so many different avenues,
you know, we can get them on the serious show for you in the pod find or an Apple's iTunes,
daily source code. I love playing promos, as you well know. And also, when you create promos,
make sure that you take the same amount of time you might put into creating the ID3 tags
in the metadata for your podcast. Make sure you do that with your promos. I was talking
to Peter about that yesterday. I can't count the number of times that someone sends in a promo that
says, you know, promo.mp3. And, you know, it really, it doesn't help because we're trying to build
databases of all this stuff to make it flow. So we really got to work on our metadata and work on
creating promos in general. Really, it's, it's well worth it. And it can just be spoken word,
you know, it doesn't have to, doesn't have to be an elaborately produced thing. They also shouldn't
be too long. You know, I think a good promo is anywhere from, you know, 30 seconds,
the two minutes, you know, kind of in that range. It all depends. You know, sometimes there,
one promo is more entertaining than the other. But it is going to be something really important
and really key if you want to promote your podcast. So we're also going in the, in the directory.
And of course, you know, we're about to reach out to all the node managers. We've got new tools
on the way. A personalized page for each node manager so that you can, you know, actually write
about, you know, the category that you're interested in, that you are maintaining. And also a way
to attach promos and to have promos flow through, well, we shouldn't make that automatic.
There should be, maybe we need a God wouldn't that be cool if we had a tag in the RSS feed,
which could be for a recent promo. We could create a promo namespace, I guess, to go along with
the RSS feed so that that could automatically be picked up. Oh, this is actually a pretty good idea.
Let's think about that for a second. Hey, babe. Yeah. I'm sorry. What's the number for the
taxi? Oh, because you don't have your phone. Oh, hold on a second. Excuse me. You're what?
Come over here. We can't hear you. You're hungry. Why are you hungry, girl? Why haven't
you eaten? I've eaten a yogurt because no one said me. You're talking to the mic and I'll write down the number.
Well, I need to say the mic. I don't know. You're on the daily source code.
Well, good morning. It's a lovely sunny day in England once again.
No, it's not. I know it was being wrapped. I was being sarcastic. That's why every morning
everyone. Oh, how are you? It's lovely sunny day. But yeah, it's raining. That was a really easy number.
Five six six five six six. I don't even remember that. That's an easy number, isn't it? Well, I'm off.
Okay, what time are you back? Um six. Okay. What? I love you. Do you look bad?
Come over here and say that again. Do I look bad? Well, why don't you say do I look good? Is that more
positive? No. Is that okay? You look wonderful right here. Now, what are you going? I'm going to the
bar to pick up my phone and then I'm going to the bar. Yes, I'm going to the bar to get dreaded.
Enjoy. Did you close my door? Thank you. Love you. Have fun.
Okay, she's not really going to the bar. She had some friends over last night and one of the,
one of her friends, I guess you watch as dishes in like a bar pub and they both have the same cell
phone and he accidentally took hers. But I did promise myself we're going to talk about teenagers
sometimes, man. You know, just what the way they talk back to you and I remember right and it's like
double, double edged sword. I'm just my mic because I remember so well my parents, you know,
saying don't talk back to us like that. And now I'm here and you know, I'm hearing my parents voice
come out of my freaking head. You know, it's like I don't want to be in this infinite loop. So I'm
like trying to change that. So my daughter won't have the same influences on her kids.
But man, sometimes you just want to stick those teenagers right up on the wall behind the wall paper,
man. Gosh, they can really get, and you know, this, like take that for it. You know, how many times a day,
my daughter says, does my hair okay? Is my face okay? You know, do you see any acne? Do I look okay?
Sometimes I just say, no, he looks like shit, you know, just a mess with her. And they just
know I don't. And it's like, oh, man. Anyway, a young woman coming into her own. And you're witnessing
it here daily on the source code. I didn't, I don't know if you knew what it would have gone on with
British airways. They had a strike, their caterer, a gate gourmet, went on strike for a couple of
some firings that I guess the union felt were unfair or someone fired a union member. I think the
story, because they were trying to organize some type of strike or some kind of action.
And so then the whole company just went on strike, which really messed up Heathrow Airport.
This was about, it was the beginning of our vacation. So it was like two weeks ago. And in that
two week period, British airways has not been able to feed their passengers no matter what
class you're in, it's just like there's no food, there's no drink other than water. And of course,
I've traveled with British airways. And I just received in the email a nice note from that I want
to share with you. Dear Mr. Curry, as you are a valued customer to British airways, I'd like
to provide you with an update on the current problems we are experiencing with our onboard catering
due to the unofficial industrial action by our Heathrow catering supplier gate gourmet. Although
British airways services into an out of London Heathrow continue to operate as normal,
we have limited onboard catering. There will be some catering provided at the airport prior
to the departure, however we are continuing to advise passengers, especially those with special
dietary requirements to eat before arriving at the airport. We do apologize in advance for any
inconvenience, blah, blah, blah, blah, like wow, you know, for British airways who really
He pride themselves on their service.
This is bad news.
Although, I must say, this unauthorized industrial action
did work.
I mean, this is something that really affects an airline.
I think it's extremely effective thing to do.
I would not fly British airways.
And there's a long haul flights.
Australia, imagine going to Australia, no food, no drink.
And you can't even get coffee or tea.
All it is is just water that's on board.
So, you know.
Thank goodness for Sir Richard and his Virgin Airlines.
And it looks like I won't be flying back to San Francisco
until September, which is good because I didn't,
I wanted to be home for Christina's birthday.
Be nice to be home for my birthday, which is coming up September 3rd.
So, I think that 12th of September, I'm going to go to New York.
We're going to do a couple days in New York.
Then I'll be out in San Francisco for about 10 days and looking forward to it.
Because stuff has hoppin' at the office.
C.C. Chapman was there.
I think he's still there and Chris Rockwell.
And, you know, I think everyone's just eventually going to come out and hang out
and we're getting stuff done.
Be on the lookout for it very, very soon.
Do you like great music?
Yeah, that's me.
I'm Chris from Rain Bucket.
My mother's so proud.
If you like great tunes, check out the Hoonik Podcast.
He's at hoonik.info.
That's H-O-O-O.
H-O-O.
And I C-K.info.
I-N-F-O.
You're going to love it.
Hi Adam.
It's Mark here.
I was on vacation recently and I've been listening to me all the shows back
in 2009, 2009, so I think it was 2-0-1 or 2-0-2, one of those two.
You're on about contacting you with anyone who's interested in getting into Podge.
And I have just begun to get into Podge, I think, of got a 50 megabyte limited web space
but no bandwidth, except for no, I can't do all of this feed on what I can, but I just
don't know how.
It's not well enough, it's very indexed, except for it.
So I'll leave my email address and Skype them at the end.
I hope you can help.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Email.
M-D-W-T.
Alright, Mark.
You know what?
I got good news for you because, essentially, very soon, we'll be hooking up through Podge
with all of that.
And as I said before, I really wanted to be incredibly simple.
You should be able to fire up cast blaster, put your show notes in, and just hit, you know,
publish this podcast, and it should all go.
Your show blogs should be arranged, your file uploads automatically, everything is all set
and you shouldn't.
I think you shouldn't have to pay for that actually, and that's what we're going to work
on.
Just going through the mail bag, guess it was, on one of my, was that one of my, no, it was
even before one of my drives in from Berkeley.
I was talking about the podcast awards, and I was wondering if there was a ceremony that
went along with that, and there is indeed a ceremony, which will be at the podcast expo,
be sure to put a link into the show notes to that.
That was the coming up really soon.
I thought that that isn't September, I think, or maybe it's later than that.
So again, I think it's, I still like the, like the surprise effect of not knowing who the
winners are before the ceremony, but at least there's going to be a ceremony.
It's that's pretty cool.
You know, while those promos were playing something really weird happened, all of a sudden,
my entire screen went black, and it had big white letters, and it said crime scene evidence,
and then that thing popped out.
I had no idea where that came from.
I don't know if it came from Megaseg or I have Omni Outliner open, but I was, I was like,
the weirdest thing.
After I record the show, I go back and see if that was something that was associated in one of
the promos.
That was a very, very frightening.
Other stuff from the mail bag, let's see.
Oh, remember I was at the Clairemont spawn resort, and I met a guy in the, in the health club,
as I was going to go for my floatation.
His name is Chad Dickerson, and he actually wrote about our brief encounter, and he put a pretty
interesting blog post up, so I'll post a link to that in the show notes as well.
What was that?
Oh, that's Christina's taxi.
It's working, you know, I like this feedback loop where you can bump into someone,
and then you say something on the show, and then he writes something on a blog post,
and then I mentioned it back in the show.
This is like the way radio is supposed to be.
Devon also, and this is referring to, this is definitely referring to our California trip.
Said I definitely write.
So I'm presently enjoying your family's vacation, diary, daily source code two, two, two,
but fill compelled to offer a slight correction.
MC Hammer's not from Oakland, but from Tracy, which is considerably inland from the East Bay.
It might be from Tracy, but didn't you have that huge house in Oakland, you know, the one with
like the waterfalls and 8,000 people on staff?
Something like that, I thought that was Oakland, and what's MC Hammer doing?
You know, the guy's got talent, you know, I know he went bust, but should have looked him up.
Anyone know what MC Hammer is doing?
I'm sure we could do some fun stuff in podcasting with him.
And also from the mailbag, this was a nice message that was sent in for the one-year anniversary
of the daily source code. I didn't get a chance to play it on the show, so I figured I
do it now because it's from two of my podcasting and life buddies, Ken and Squid.
Hey Adam, it's Cindy from the Ken and Squid show. Here's a special message from us to you in honor
of the one-year anniversary of the daily source code. Hit it, Kenny.
That's right. Right here on the Ken and Squid show.
Squid is going to take it all off, bro, and to grow some pasties.
That made me kind of hungry.
Somebody got me some pie.
And she's off. Oh yes, there she goes, ladies and gentlemen.
And say, this girl's friend given all your gots and asked the ticket, you're really not going off.
Uh-huh.
Look at those babies go.
Boy, I don't know. That puts the S in, squipper.
Excuse me, ma'am. Please step away from the window and put your clothes back on.
Oh, oh officer. I didn't hear you coming home. For the love of God's whip.
I just, I was just, uh, um, just thought it'd be good. Honestly, ma'am, I don't know whether they're
the issue of citation earth. Ask for your phone number.
I'm the anniversary, um, congratulations on all your successes during the past year and best
of luck for the future. Special Kenan's whip show love bubbles are headed your ways, sir.
And I'll be in touch as long as they have email from jail. This is a terrible predicament. We find ourselves
in on this auspicious occasion. But it was a nifty dance, Kenny wasn't it? Oh, it sure was.
Well worth it. That's what I say. Happy anniversary. Have an excited day.
Awesome. Okay. And they look great, squip. Thank you.
Yeah. We got to get, uh, that's another thing I got to put on the list. We got to get Skype
recording into cast blaster because I know how those guys are recording. Ken basically sits with
the, the other great microphone, but he positions the speakers that he's running Skype on around the
mic so that he's basically, uh, talking to Cindy through his microphone and then what he's
getting back from her is fed through the speakers into the microphone. So she sounds a little bit
muffled. Um, I was cruising around the pod safe music network the this morning looking for some
stuff. And you know what I like about this is what, you know, when you hear like when someone says
independent artists, I usually think about like independent rock, alternative rock, you know,
emo stuff. Um, but if you just go through all the genres and you, and you browse by
the genre, you can get some really incredible tunes. This one, uh, I kind of liked it.
Jennifer Halane, swallow me odd safe on the source code.
I won't let anyone put a chain in.
Swallow me swallow me. Make sure you chew it all out, because why go down can come back up, and I can't
forever and forever and well.
Don't play dumb, you don't fall in anyone, advice me until I was numb. Now the ice is melted down,
it's just in my day with heart. I'll always learn it, I turn off the flame,
you can't be drunk, I don't crush it with you.
Swallow me swallow me. Make sure you chew it all out, because why go down can come back up.
Now I can't forever and well.
Your prison is a sin, because while I'm shy, I will not die, so put them away, so we're getting out of the fly.
Swallow me swallow me. Make sure you chew it all out, because why go down can come back up.
And I can't forever and well.
You chew it all out, because why go down can come back up.
Jennifer Helaine swallow me. Pot safe on your daily source code, link to her website in the show notes for today's daily source code.
And that's it for the 24th of August, 2005. Hope you enjoy.
Keep those promos comments submit at podshow.com. Keep sending them in. Really need them.
We've got to expose more listeners to more cool stuff.
If you got pod safe music, head over to the pod safe music network and
odd safe music network.com or music.potshow.com.
And of course, you can always send me audio feedback out of my curie.com.
I'm a 98% now on the Gmail, so please don't attach MP3. Send me a link.
If throw it up on a server somewhere, and also when it comes to feedback,
I wouldn't mind if you put some metadata in there as well.
Use the ID3 tied. Don't just send me a file that says feedback for Adam.
It just makes life so much more complicated, and it shouldn't take much
a lot of extra effort to do that.
Thedysource.com is where you can find the podcast feed for the show. Hope you do subscribe.
And of course, there's www.curry.com.
That's the weblog, which is running a hell of a lot better these days.
Marcus has been rewriting responders because we've gotten so much comments
fab. And when you post a comment, it does take a resources on the machine.
If you're posting one every second, you're going to bring a machine to its knees eventually.
And it's all poker spanned.
Licker poker.
The penis enlargement. You know, all the basic good stuff.
Alright, that's it. I'll be back tomorrow with the Thursday edition
of your daily source code, more promo spots at music and mashups, and more.
Take care everybody. Stay subscribed. Bye bye.
Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.