source code for January 17th, 2005.
Transmators, we don't need no stinking transmators.
And good morning, good afternoon, good evening.
Hi everybody, welcome to the day of the source code coming to you once again from
Curry Cottage in in the affluence.
Suray, suburb, cold gulfed.
It's the start of a new week and we've got a lot of
lots of stuff to talk about on the source code.
All podcasts related of most of those.
Well, a new start, a new way to kick off the source code.
I've been receiving lots of emails from people.
Now is more and more people are coming online and enjoying podcasts.
It seems that the ID3 tags just aren't enough when searching through
whatever messed up playlist system your particular MP3 player might have.
So the request was, could you just start off by giving a little identification tag so that when someone hits
the play button, they know exactly which source code they're listening to.
Okay, fair enough, January 17th, 2003.
I keep forgetting that when you got headphones on, you can't take your glasses off because you
never get a background again.
Okay, there we go.
All right, 40 minutes approximately that is of all the latest goings on in the podcast
land and lots of responses to the previous podcast from last week.
The first thing I really want to talk about is the amount of response I got about my
easy jet experience traveling with Egypt.
In fact, I'm about to book another easy jet trip for this week to the Netherlands to do a couple
of a couple of meetings.
David Burgess said that he had a similar easy jet experience and he said polite, efficient,
orderly, although the playing was smaller than the Airbus 319 on the one that I flew on.
But I think this is, oh, he goes to this whole story about how people brought their own
champagne on board and how the students were all kind of cool with it and how the other
passengers were cool with it.
All of these, of course, in the production show, it's OPML file, which I'm thinking about
actually posting these in the blog post itself when I create the entry for Eves New Daily
source code.
Just probably need to format a little bit differently or polish it up so it doesn't look
so crappy on a web page.
But otherwise, you'll be able to get to all of those comments.
That's a really good one.
That's why I posted it up there.
Just been trolling through my iPod, I spent most of the weekend downloading stuff.
Of course, downloading automatically, transferring it to my I-River.
I got to tell you, I am completely an I-River guy now.
For some reason, it's just, it works better for me than the iPod.
It certainly is nicer because I have the old iPod, not the mini.
God forbid, not the micro or the, no, what was it?
It's the shuffle.
That's right.
David Letterman had a bit that I saw last night.
He had this little itsy bitsy, like an inch high by an inch wide mock-up of kind of like
the iPod shuffle and he said, look, Paul, this is the iPod micro.
It's like, yeah, exactly.
One podcast, even, that would be perfect, wouldn't it?
It's time once again for America's favorite radio show, the radio and such a subduct of Floyd,
brought to you by ductafloey.com.
This week, we join our heroes as a screen through time and space.
Yeah, you just don't get radio like that anymore, do you?
We were talking about Kennedy, the VJ.
On my last sounding tour down to Starbucks at Gilford and Matthew Bishop, of course, quite
active in the podcast community, checked in, he said, thought like, you know, that former
MTV VJ Kennedy now hosts the game show network show, friends or foe, yeah, well, she probably
has about the same amount of viewers as I have listeners to the source code, so we wish
her well.
It's just never was one of my favorite people, Kennedy.
God, gosh, we got so much to go through.
I have so many different sound clips and so many different things I want to talk about,
particularly about the sound seeing tour, because people are really catching onto this
concept and it's not just a concept that works when you're, well, I don't know, it works
everywhere basically and I was turned on to another podcast, which is actually, it's not
officially a podcast, it's a beer cast, now there are a lot of different beer cast, if you
look at the iPodot org directory, which I heard by the way that the iPodot org is listed
in the top 20,000 of most sites visited ever in the universe of the history of the
Incarnets, and where did I hear that, I heard it on, gosh, this is the problem, you know,
when you're listening to your I-river and open podcast that org for instance is something I
listened to a lot, I subscribe to that, but also podcast brothers and there's so many different
different podcasts that I just think, oh yeah, this is so great, I want to play a piece on my
show, I want to talk about it and what I want is a knob, you know, a knob where I can hit that
button, it remembers where it was, what file it was, let's me say something so I can, you know,
leave a little audio note to myself, that's gotta be possible, someone, somehow in the,
can someone hack that up in the firmware of the I-river please, I'll gladly pay for it,
make it happen for me. So here's one of those things that I did,
remember to put into today's podcast, this is the beer casting American tour,
you'll be interested to hear this because this is global maybe. Hey Adam, this is Greg from
beer casting.com, it's just right to let you know about the beer casting America tour,
which I am just about to kick off over the next few months. I don't know if you have ever heard
of one of our beer casts, but here's the scoop, what I do is I'm going on tour to a bunch of different
cities, all across the US, I introduce a bunch of new people who have never really met before
to what I call beer casting, podcasting with the buzz.
That's a great slogan. Podcasting with the buzz. Podcasting with the buzz, everybody.
That's what I, in fact, I wanted to call the Daily Source Code just that, the Daily Source Code,
podcasting with the buzz. Beer cast is essentially a podcast that I record live in a bar,
and then use all that RSS goodness to kind of get it out to the world. And I'll let people hear,
you know, what everyone's thinking about, all kinds of random shit from
why men are love cat fights down to politics down to tsunami, everything in between.
The tour actually just got started this week. It's going on. It was out in Worcester, Mass. On Tuesday,
hosted about 14 people out there. Also had a few people down in New York City doing it the same time.
Later on this month, I'll be hitting DC. Next Tuesday, the 18th, Seattle, Washington.
On the 23rd, Portland, Oregon, on the 26th, then goes on to February, and I'll be in Houston,
on the 7th, San Antonio, on the 8th, Austin, on the 9th. The second half of February,
and we'll go shoot down to Florida. Checking out West Palm Beach on the 20th, for Waterdale,
on the 21st, and South Beach, which you know, good and well. In the 22nd.
Seriously, though, the best part for me is not really the travel. The cool thing is that on
every city I visited or talked to or been to, it's somebody down there is helping me organize the event.
You know, they're getting people together to help me find location. I've been to some
most of these places, but you know, I've been there so long. So it's really great that people
come out of water work and they're saying, hey, you know, I love you to come down here to look
if you do it down here. March is, you know, kind of distant dream right now, but already
it looks like California is where I'm going to be. Getting people already sent it, you know,
and invite me to come do it down there. I'm really hoping that if there's any daily source
code listeners out there and one of these cities or someplace that they think it'd be great to do
one, I hope you come out, meet up, shoot me an email. Full schedule's up at www.bearcastin.com,
and you can check out some of the old shows and see how people are going to do it and what
we do and enjoy a lot of fun. You can also email me, graygetbeardcasting.com. Well,
well, thanks for listening and I hope you're a bandwidth get solved real soon.
Oh, great. Oh, please. Oh, the fucking bandwidth. It's killing me, man. It's fucking killing me.
I put a big post on my weblog today. Hopefully to get someone animated to come out and help me
before I start pulling up the curb myself to connect the last 15 meters. The last, you know,
30 feet or so of 50 feet maybe of wire. And when I listen to that, right, and I listen to as many
podcasts I possibly can. Most people, including my wife, my lovely wife Patricia, say, where do you
find the time to listen to all these? Well, actually, it's very clear where I find that time.
It's at Starbucks. Three hours a day is when I'm checking everything out. I'm not just uploading
and also downloading folks. But when I hear stuff like this, right, I'm thinking of myself, hold on.
We got to crank up the reverb here for a second. Ow, let's see if we can do this. Hello,
wait, that's the wrong. I'm doing the wrong thing here. No, I wanted to. Okay, let's see if I can, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, let's see. Okay. Hello. Okay. We are now turning the podcast transmitter towards
St. Louis, Missouri. Hello, and heiser Bush. Robert McColley and heiser Bush pay attention.
People are doing beer casts. A perfect moment to underwrite a beer cast. Okay. Let me, yeah,
there we go. Turn on the reverb. Just like, you know, there's opportunity out there. Anyone coming
into the beer space right now could own that in podcasting. And I certainly hope Greg has a good
time on this tour. I wonder what people are drinking. I'm certainly one that's going to be
subscribing to the show and listening to it. Okay, about the sound seeing tour, which is certainly
as you'll find out later on in today's podcast. It's not something that's new,
but it is something that we've kind of forgotten, you know, just sound. What does it sound like when
you're somewhere? In fact, there's a, the new Ray Charles movies coming out, right, with James
at Jamie Far from an living color, who was Jamie Far from Saturday Night Live. In living color,
I guess, right? Who does a fantastic Ray Charles? Absolutely blows me away. Can't wait to see
this movie, but there's a guy who, you know, from age seven, six or seven, I think,
only had sound. And we forget about that. And we forget about how much sound there is. And basically,
on the radio sound is all mushed and mangled into one, you know, big commercial block that kind of
flows towards you, not all radio, of course, but lots of, lots of radio. So people are really
catching on to these sound seeing tours. And I'd love to hear if other people are doing them,
and I'd love to, you know, go on a sound seeing tour of my own, not while recording, but while
listening to someone else. And I've got a lot of response to the last one, and so of course, I did the
my, my first sound seeing tour on South Beach, walking down the ocean drive in, in Florida.
The other one I did last was it Friday. In fact, I went to drop Christina off at,
near the high street yesterday. She was meeting up with some friends from school to go hang out, apparently.
It's pretty pretty harmless, I guess, for them to hang out here and gilford,
can't run into too much trouble. And Patricia called me and said, are you recording? You
should record that when you drop her off and what it's like? Good idea. I will. I certainly,
maybe she's just Mike Christina, and let her go on a sound seeing tour. Sound seeing tour gilford
has a 14-year-old girl. I'm learning so much. We've got, you know, that here in the UK,
so at her school, there are different groups of people. I'm not going to digress on this too much,
but we've got the chaves, and we've got the pikes. And I'm learning more, and more, I think I'm
probably more like a pikesy myself, but we're learning more about these groups every day as we settle
into the English culture. Anyway, so the number one thing people want to know about my
sound seeing tour is the setup. What am I using to record it? And I think that this is really key,
because first of all go through the elements, and then I'll tell you why these are probably the
right elements to use and why they're important. So the recording device is my iRiver,
IFP799. They're several different models. I like this one because it can hold up to a gig
of recording, and if you do, it's, I see I recorded 44 kilohertz on 128 KBPS. That's what I record at,
not what it actually gets sent out as, but I want to have a really high quality recording to start with.
And that's about a megabyte a minute. So if you do, you know, 40 minutes, you're going to be
pretty much around 40 meg. So plenty of plenty of space in there. What I like about the iRiver is you
can, when you put it into record mode, and of course you can lock it, right? So you put this little
iRiver into your pocket, and it won't automatically switch off. It plays the sound through. So
you can crank up the volume, and essentially when you have the earbuds in your ears, you're listening
to exactly what people will hear when they listen to the sound seeing tours. And believe me,
you hear a very different sound scape than when you're just listening with your ears.
So then what I do is I hook up my wireless microphone said. This is the kind, this is a
electro-eli shit. Hold on a second. Let me, let me just grab around my bag and make sure.
Yeah, that's a real good production.
Yeah, here it is. Sorry. I should have that. Prepared for you. This is the, okay, it's the
electro-eli CT-R-O. U-M-1-1-0. This is a set that we picked up, so there's many times before.
When we did a reality show to the Adam's family, and it's of course complete overkill to have
the transmitter in my front pocket, and the receiver in my back pocket hooked up to the
R.I. River. The advantage is this microphone is incredible. The way it picks up audio,
and it has a little lovelier, so you can just clip it onto your collar and no one will really
know that you're recording anything. The sound is phenomenal. That's what everyone hears. You can
hear everything around you. It has a very light compression in it. Of course, garbage and garbage
out. You've got to have the right microphone. This works for me. I'm sure that there are other
mic setups that will work, but that's what everyone wants to know. It's the electro-U-M-1-10
electro-U-HF transmitter receiver pair. Not cheap. I'll tell you that. I think I paid $2,000
euros for that, so that's almost $4,000 these days. Then what I do is I basically connect the
out of the electro receiver up to the input of the I-River, switch it on, and then I can listen
to exactly what I'm recording. Another additional benefit of this setup is that if you hold the
I-River in your hand, and you're left hand, for instance, and of course the wires are hooked
up to your head, right, and there's another wire running into your pocket to the receiver of the
microphone receiver, is that it looks like you're holding onto a cellular phone. Therefore, if you're
walking down the street, talking crap, you know, doing your sound seeing tour, people basically
won't look at you like you're some degenerate idiot, or the villager idiot for the
walking around talking to yourself. Alternatively, you can just keep the hold the cell phone up
to your ear, even though it can be off just pretending like you're talking into it. But I predict
that pretty soon it'll be normal, you know, people are doing sound seeing tours all over the
place, and it'll be a very normal thing to see in the city or village landscape. One additional bit
I would really love to have if it was at all possible. One additional feature would be GPS.
I'm so convinced that if I could connect GPS data to the sound seeing tour, that we'd have
something absolutely phenomenal. Better yet, wouldn't it be great just to have some kind of GPS
it is basically a connection with GPS, so I could do the sound seeing tour. I could, you know,
mark where I make a comment, and you could follow along with that tour, or alternatively,
you could just be walking anywhere, and let's say you had an iPod, an MP3 player with GPS in it,
and it would download GPS data, so let's say we had the sound seeing tour. God damn it,
I should register that domain name. What we're doing that, let me see if that's available.
Sound seeing tour.com, of course, what I would, my computer is not going to like me doing this
while I'm recording. Okay, before I upload the show, I'm checking God damn it, so you can't capture
that from me right away. I'll shoot. Now my computer is completely hoising out. Hold on, let me see if
Firefox will die. Go away. Go, please. Hide. Okay, great. So you basically upload your data. So let's
say I upload the data for a gilford, and if you're walking around gilford, then, you know, your MP3
player will go, bling, you know, we've got a message in this spot, and then I could, you know, click,
and then it would automatically bring me that or play that a sound file for me. Of course,
it seems like this would be logical to have it. Maybe we need to be able to put that into the RSS.
Yeah, there you go. So we need data that we can add into RSS feed along with the enclosure.
So, hey, there's another reason for a name space. Does anyone get what I'm talking about?
Where you can basically have these comments in space, so you could subscribe to sound
something like that. There's something in there that we got to work on.
And I've got a lot of comments and actually a real old fashioned
sound sing tour from the 1940s, but first a word from Patrick. Hey, Adam, this is Patrick from 80s
Airwaves, not a podcast, but a full-time online radio station dedicated to 80s music, movie clips,
and more. Now that you have your bandwidth, check us out as we broadcast live from a bonus room
over the garage at 80sairwaves.com. I just listened to your podcast on last week your sound trip
down ocean drive and south beach. I think it's the best podcast I've heard so far. You mentioned
two things that caused me to put this audio reply together. First, you mentioned how you're
involvement in the music business during the 80s caused you to miss a lot of the great stuff
that came out during that period. Our radio station plays a really wide variety of great music
from the 80s, not just the MTV stuff, but we throw in some scop, punk, rap, hair bands, more.
So I hope you'll check us out and let me know what you think. This could be your chance to
catch up on what you missed back then and Patrick got some cowbells. Second, you sounded pretty
stressed about the response to the interview with Madge from the East Radio person. Personally,
having survived cancer and radiation treatment myself and even having lost my father to cancer,
I personally like to tell people just to chill the fuck out. There are a lot more important
things in life to do than to get up tight about one person has to say about yeast infections.
So chill out people. That's it Adam. Keep up the great work.
Alright, Patrick, excellent. Thanks very much, Madge. Yeah, my mom has a sign on the her,
one of those old fashioned, what do you call it? My great grandmother used to knit them all the time.
Oh, shoot. A sampler is that we call it a sampler? And it's basically it's a crocheted or knit
type thing that hang on the wall and it has little slogan there like the one I remember is the road
to a friend's house is never long. But my mom has one and it's I used to complain about my shoes
hurting my feet until I met a man who had no feet. And yeah, that's obviously true. You know,
I'm bitching and moaning about my bandwidth but the hell of a lot worse that could be happening to me
or you know, could have happened to have been very fucking lucky in the past year. So
you're right, Patrick, there you go. We also just chill out. And by the way,
I've been listening to Madge's recent podcasts. The one about Apple about Steve Jobs keynote is
fucking hilarious. You got to listen to it. Absolutely fantastic. Okay, now let's go back in time
because we're going to listen to well, the introduction speaks for itself. Check this out. You're going to
love this. Hi Adam, this is Jim Widner. I wanted to tell you that first of all how much I've been
enjoying your daily source code sound scene tours. Your recent tour to Starbucks reminded me of an
MP3 file that I have in my collection. It's from a radio series that the BBC and CBS radio
put together in 1940 called London after dark. One of the programs featured CBS radio bureau chief
Edward Armerall standing near Trifagar Square with the air raid sirens blaring, giving listeners a
sort of sound scene of the area during the blitz. So I thought you might be interested in hearing
a clip from the program and I've included it here. I know we take you out of the streets of Black
Outland and downstate Lake Crescent-Shade region streets along south to be Avenue of here to
name into sharing crossroads London's Ken Panale and so to come down this way. Moving there is Edward
Murrow, known to you as Columbia's European director. Come in Ed Murrow.
This is the loudest where the noise that you hear at the moment is the sound of the air raid sirens.
I'm standing here just on the steps of St. Martin's in the field.
A search light just burst into action often in the distance. Man's single being slipping the sky above me
now. People are walking along that way. We're just at the entrance of an air raid shelter here and I must
move this kid over just to bits so people can walk in. I can see just straight away in front of me Lord
Nelson on top of that big column. There's no search light. Just square behind Nelson's statue.
That's like you listen to the traffic and the sound of the siren for a moment.
I'm in California. Tell your man's steps in front of me to light a cigarette.
There's some kind of those red buses around the corner. Do they look at the fire?
Just a few lights on the top deck. In this blackness it looks very much like a ship that's passing in the knife and you just see the purple.
That was another bus. More search lights come into action.
You see them reach, they have been to the sky in the cave. Maybe they catch a cloud and seem to splash on the bottom of it.
A little traffic lights here just a small cross on the Murrow's blood are now red. The cars pull up and
stop. I'll just ooze down in the darkness here along these steps and see if I can pick up the sound of
people's feet. Do they walk along? One of the strangest sounds one can hear in London these days,
or rather these dark nights. Just the sound of footsteps walking along the screen.
Like ghosts shot with steel shoes. Attachy goes up just in front and stops.
Just waiting for that red light to change to green hole a siren cloud.
There it goes and the cars move off. More search lights are in action.
We've not yet seen any burst of anti-aircraft by a little bit of them.
No parts of this doesn't necessarily mean that there are planes actually over London at this moment.
We've had these warnings before, of course.
Can you hear the siren just dying away in the distance now?
Near red one walks out of this shelter. The shelter there is the crypt underneath this famous old church,
just on the edge of the father's square. The crypt where in days of peace one was many women,
whatever to find a night's slagginger.
Industrial in all the steps of people coming up and to this old church.
And so that went on to hang out square.
How cool is that? Now you may have skipped past some of it because the quality was
well, 1940's quality. Man, if we come a long way with sound quality. But it's not awesome
that then people were blown away by that apparently. Of course they were. I mean,
geez, you were listening to an air raid happening over London, which was thousands of miles away.
And I presume that was live. I'm not sure if it was. But really cool to listen to.
And I really appreciate the MP3 to be able to play that on the source code.
I was going to say, oh yeah, by the way, if you are skipping past, I've noticed on the iRiver,
which is highly configurable, actually. You can adjust the joystick as to how fast it's going to
fast forward when you push it to the right or of course rewind when you push it to the left.
And it does give you the audio as it skips the longs. You can make it go at like 30 seconds of
pop at one second of pop. You can really change. I think it's like four or five different levels.
You can change it for skipping. So another reason to look at the iRiver, I should really get paid by
those fuckers, shouldn't I? Or they should at least fix the firmware so I can do more cool stuff with it.
Anyway, cool. Sound sing tours. Definitely something that I want to hear more of. And I've been
thinking about maybe something I should do is put a new podcast together where all of these
clips that I play or maybe clips, maybe even clips that I don't play is probably better.
Just a short podcast that I like. I can just kind of throw them into one bin and you subscribe
to that and it just brings you all the all the new stuff that I think is worth listening to.
That's something we can do. Oh, here that drunken voice again. That's one thing we haven't solved.
Yep, it's the latency issues. I think there's a, in November, there's a podcast
expo. We'll be held in California that I keep hearing about. I'm not sure. I think that the
podcast brothers are actually organizing that. But they're talking about a place where, of course,
podcasts, there's a come and meet each other. But also, where vendors, and I listen to the podcast
brothers at podcast brothers that org all the time, where vendors will be able to show off their
hard and software solutions for podcasters. Well, I certainly hope we have some by them because
we don't really have them yet, except for mixed cast live, which, well, it works only on Windows with
dot net. But there's so much, so we can do so much better with tools for, for making these podcast.
We really can. And you know me, right? I am the guy who loves the short podcast.
The legal underground word for the day is resend, which means you aggregate a null, avoid, or cancel
a contract, particularly nullifying a contract by the act of a party, to declare a contract void
in its inception, and to put an end to it, as though it never works. Not merely to terminate it
and release parties from further obligations to each other, but you aggregate it from the beginning,
and restore parties to relative positions, which they would have occupied, and no contract
ever been made. Source, lacks law dictionary, with pronunciations fifth edition.
All right, the legal word for the day is resend. There you go. See, that would be, we could do a
little format where you, you know, put together an OPML file of your shit. That's almost that.
That's a cool application. You could decide if you wanted the word of the day, the sound of the
day, the grout show of the day, or the legal word of the day. I'm telling you, we got a station.
It's very, very close. A couple of things I wanted to mention. First of all, I want to say
hi to Irwin of Irwin's podcast in the Netherlands. I'm not really going to extrovert a piece of
his show, nor do I want to extrovert pieces of all these podcasts that I talk about, but just
want Irwin to know that I listen to his show. It comes out almost every single day, I think,
or at least like four or five times a week. I listen to his show with great joy, not only for the,
you know, the song that he plays every single day, which he's usually is 60s or 70s,
oldies, oldies, too. But also he brings me up the speed within, like, what is it? Five or six
minutes of exactly what's going on in the media landscape in Holland. And I don't even read the
paper anymore. It's Irwin's podcast. I don't know what I'm listening to. I just want to say,
Erwin Iglarse de Frachnallia. Also been exchanging a lot of email with the bitties,
the civiest bitties. You know, my girls from New York City,
bittiesforever.com is where you can find out all about them and their music and we've played them
on the source code many times. There was a cover real special last Thursday, which I didn't
catch until the weekend, but of course, doesn't matter because that's, you know, that's the great
thing about it is your iPod, it will pick it up, you know, no matter when you do your iPod scan.
And it was great to hear them, although God, I chat, socks, it was really quality. And I know that,
yeah, there were apologies at front for the quality of that, but it was an eye chat conversation
between Canada and I guess New York where the girls were. And yeah, it's just not cotton it.
You know, Skype is far superior, but of course, Skype won't work properly on the Mac yet.
And what an incredible opportunity. I mean, the Skype guys could make Skype the podcast tool
do sure, you know, instead of call someone just record it straight to MP3. I hear,
ah, where's that? I had a comment somewhere, which I'll probably won't be able to play today,
because I can't find it right off the bat, but they also have a beta test of voice mail now.
It'll send you an MP3 of voice mail. So even if your computer is not connected, it'll store the message for you.
And then I guess you can retrieve it somehow. You know, so they've got all the bits in place.
And then of course, to be able to call someone who has Skype and do an interview or have a conversation
or conference in multiple people, I mean, it could be your own Gilmore gang set up, you know,
even though, well, look at the stuff that Doug K does. He's got, you know, professional mixing board,
professional audio, you know, phone bridge to hook everyone together. It could be done with Skype,
but I don't know, Skype just isn't, you know, well, maybe they're sticking to their mission,
which is probably a good thing. I am, by the way, about to order one of those Skype phones
that you hook right up to your network. And you can use Skype directly from that phone. I think that'll be great.
Considering that the Netherlands is one of the, except for Afghanistan, which, you know,
you don't want to call Afghanistan. You might want to smoke it, but you don't want to call it.
The Netherlands is the most expensive country to call in the world. What a racket the KPN has going on there,
huh? She especially cell phones and Holland calling them from outside the country, forget about it.
It's more than a pound of minutes. It's almost two bucks a minute just to call a cell phone
from outside of the country. Anyway, so the Bitties, a great interview on coverbill, check it out
coverbill.com, and you recall that when CBS evening news came to interview me in South Beach,
that I set up a little podcast for the interviewer, Sharon, Elfonci, and I used the list of
these Bitties. I want to be famous, which, of course, is the, you know, I thought about it, right?
It's the perfect song for the type of piece that I think they're going to make. So I think that
that probably works out just great for them, but it also gives the Bitties another boost and guess what?
CBS is called. They're going to interview them, too. So I cannot be more excited. I'm telling you
Grammys, onstage, Leanne, the girls, it can happen. It may not take that long.
And a quick pointer to Steve Garfield's video blog, Steve Garfield.com, if you've, I don't
think no Steve ever really got into podcasting. I think he's kind of, he wants to do video,
and he is attaching video as enclosures to his RSS feed. So you can certainly subscribe to it. I think
most of the iPodos will probably receive that as well, although if it gets really popular,
I don't know what's he's going to do for bandwidth, because it's a lot, well he's hosting it on his
dot Mac blog. But it's he's doing some interesting stuff. He's basically turning on the camera,
going places with his wife, and they're just hanging out and they're calling it a show, and you
should check it out. Steve Garfield test, Steve Garfield.com. And here's something cool I got in.
This is the kind of audio response I like. It's an interactive one where I actually have to stay
awake during the comment and play along. Hello Adam, Stuart Hunter here. I was really enjoying your
Miami podcast, especially the piece where I think you were in Dave's hotel room, and you were
challenging both Dave and Ron to recognize some music from the intro that you played from your iTunes
playlist. I really enjoyed that. Especially as I was putting my hand up saying, oh, I don't know.
I worked great. Okay. We got to do that more often then, perfect. I did think it was a little
bit unfair, because surely you were the music man of the 80s and 90s probably the most
knowledgeable. Of course, the showmaster always has all the answers, right? I mean, you know,
that's come on. Regis Phil did knows what the answers are in millionaire.
Person about the music of those times. So I thought maybe if she tried to reverse that a little bit
and challenge you on some intros. So I've picked a few little pieces together, and I'm going to play
them for you now. I'm not going to give you the answers right away, because if you don't get them,
I'm sure you will. I'm sure some of your listeners will email the answers. Okay. Oh, great.
This is cool. Okay. And by the way, I have not listened to the expressly. I've not listened to
the songs yet. So we're hearing this for the first time together. Let's see if we can do it.
Let's go. Let's hear it.
Oh, shit.
That from an artist who's still going strong had a big hit in the UK in the past year. Oh, shit.
Okay, I give. I don't know that one. That's the only clue you're going to get. Thank you.
Here's the next one. That's Robbie Williams. Isn't that the kids are all right?
I think that's Robbie Williams. I think I could be wrong. It was about to burst into song myself.
Yeah, because I thought it was coming up. That was the second one. Here's number three. Okay.
They're not named the band. Oh, these are 80s. I mean, I'm good at it.
A visage fade degree. Is that it?
Yeah, long, long, long, long, long. I think. Yeah, there we go. Okay, guys. I think I got that one.
Fizzage fade degree. Oh, we interrupt this test. Yes, dear.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Very quiet. Yeah. I was a layman. I was a long here and I had a bus comedy. Okay.
Okay, you're leaving now? Okay.
Is that she over there that's in my belt? What are you in here? Yeah.
Okay, I love you. No, close the door, please. Don't worry. I'll hear it. Yeah. I'll hear it. I'm almost done. Bye.
We have, okay, bye. Yeah, okay. Sorry. We now continue with the test.
Yeah, that's maybe the easiest one. Yeah, certainly had a great gun. They're of an option too. Yeah.
To guess what that was more. This one's a little bit harder. It's a good bit shorter because the
vocals kick in pretty quick. Okay. So you'll only have a few seconds here it is.
Lay all your hands on me. Short but sweet. Lay all your hands on me. Did not have too many hands on me.
Lay your hands on me. Thank you. Maybe a bit more difficult. Trying to think who they were.
Lay all your hands on me. It's like your hands on me. Whatever the hell we ever did it.
The next one will be very familiar to anyone from Australia. So this one should be fairly easy to guess.
John Farnam, you're the voice.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom. Yeah, this is good. All right. I'm feeling a little bit better about myself.
Yeah, I felt really shitty. We get it.
Yeah, that was easy.
Oh, a little bit more than 10 seconds worth of that song. So hopefully I won't get into any trouble
from the R.I. Oh, shut up. Of course you won't. Here's song number six.
What the hell is that? I guess the common thread and the interest on playing here is that the
bands themselves didn't have too many hits. Yeah, or I don't know if this one was a hit.
Is there one? I don't know, but so.
Of course, I know the song. It's 74. 75. It's a file track for me to guess the artist and no
points on that one, I guess. The shot.
Extra points.
Down. It's a wonderful wonderful life by, um,
wonderful wonderful life by, do I get half the points that don't I?
For wonderful life. Maybe it's by wonderful life, um, the wet wet wet or something like that.
This is harder than I thought it would be, actually.
Well, there you go, Adam. I hope you enjoyed the challenge, though. I did.
To be honest, I don't think those intervals will have caused you any problems whatsoever, but
so it was fun to play the name that tune. I hope the listeners enjoyed it. So
okay. Much of good night. Excellent, man. Thank you very much. I look forward to more of those.
Maybe not as long. Maybe you only do top three or so, but the stumped the podcast.
So now there's a, there's a segment for you on the Daily Source Code.
Podcrumbs. Number five is out with part two of my interview with singer,
Sawyer, Robert Birkwan. This is the second of four parts of our conversation.
It also features the song you're hearing now, Radio Church from his 2000 CD to this day.
You can find the show as well as last week's first part and all the podcrumbs episodes at our new home,
www.podcrumbs.com. No, it also the feed address has changed and is now www.podcrumbs.com slash
wayindex.xml. Thanks for listening. Okay, seeing that I only have a couple of minutes left on today's
show. I'm not going to be able to play Robert Birkwan's song, Junkman. I'm going to move that
over to tomorrow's show, but of course you can check out podcrumbs number five to get all the latest.
It's actually a guide that's some pretty decent tunes because I did want to leave you with a
couple of comments that came in regarding Andy Hertzfeld's comments on podcasting,
which we've spoken about. And well, a lot of people responded to that. Here's the first one.
Hey Adam is Jack over at Boundcast. Andy Hertzfeld. Last week I set up something with a
Riley to have him interviewed on MacRoll that one Wednesday. I go there. We sit out and right
before the interview he says, me, I'm not much on podcasting. I'm like, well, okay. And
why would we go on and continue the interview and get all the way done and he's a great interview.
And then I put it up on the site last night and the next thing I know I'm on the train coming home
and here's your show and you're like Andy Hertzfeld, interview. I'm like, oh, great!
This is fantastic. And no, it's the scene at an interview about how he does like podcasting.
I'm just blown away by that. So what can I say? And life's full of this quirky kind of ironic
timing. Hi Adam. This is Reed. I just wanted to say about Andy Hertzfeld and what he said about
I have a podcasting. Like I said, my blog, he's just doesn't get it. He's a kind of person who would have
said back in the early 90s that the web was completely unnecessary because HTTP is just a duplication
of existing things like FTP. What do we need to do HTTP for? Yeah, so don't worry about him.
Okay, he just got his head up his ass. Oh, don't say that. Okay, so that's pretty much the range of the
comments and how they went from left to right and many more in between. But then, I guess it's the
what is it? The Wizards of Technology? Do they, Mr. Mark and Digital Bill, I think that's who they
are. They, they caught Phil Schiller, who is, what is he vice president of Apple? He's the
number two guy. I think they caught him outside McRoll Expo and they got his comments on podcasting.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute. That was funny. Mark has got so nervous. They started falling
all over himself. Let's listen to that one more time. I don't mean to laugh, but I'm noticing that
now for the first time. It's all right. I sound drunk on my shows. Here, let's try that again.
And listen to him fucking blowing. Oh, no, I'm sorry. I got to go. I've got much, much more
to do over here. You know, I got no time to talk to you a little, this is it, guys. You know,
if you want to, if you want to get these guys, you want to have them look at you
serious, you got to trick them. And you need to have a microphone that has a mic cue on it.
You know, it needs a mic cue, so you look official. And it could say anything on there. As long
as it's a cue that fits up that mic, baby, that's one thing to say, oh, wait a minute, that's
some, and maybe a big windscreen, you know, with your logo on it as well. That is guaranteed
to not get that response. Oh, I'm sorry. I've got to run, guys. I've got to get run. I'm full
of shit. I'm hurt. I broke it. I'm right. I'm believable. He talks just like he does when
he's doing those keynotes when he's on stage. I think it's really cool technology. I think
I'm really happy a lot of people are trying out. This is really wonderful. Where's your
mic cue? I can't see your windscreen. Are you really an official broadcaster? He sounds like
a freaking robot. A fun way to get more programming on your iPod. Interesting. Interesting.
A fun way to get more programming, more programming on your iPod. That's a lot in there, I
feel. Oh, yes.
That's it for the source code for today, January 17th. As always, you can leave us a comment
at umadcurry.com or on the weblogcurry.com. Okay, tomorrow. What's we do tomorrow?
They can talk a little about South Beach. Some of the things that we discussed, of course,
you couldn't imagine most of the things we're thinking about are they commercial nature.
And I'm also going to think about working on that podcast feed of all the different clips I've
done. I quite sure I want to put that together. Oh, and of course, before I upload this show,
I'm totally going to see you sound seeing.com today. So by the time you hear this show,
you'll be registered to me. I hope. All right, everybody. Thank you very much for sending in your
comments. Keep it coming. And tomorrow, I'm another dating source code. Who knows? Maybe with some
broadband if those BT engineers can find it in their hearts to connect the last 15 meters from
the curb to the house. Take care, everybody. I'll see you tomorrow. Bye, bye.