Daily source code, 1-31-25.
Transmators? We don't need no stinkin' transmitters!
Get ready for the generation of rockin' world!
Autastic! It's Adam Curry!
And it's Monday, the 31st of January 2005.
The power of the Lord!
You just witnessed a major league crash here.
Hold on, what happened?
Shit, something fell off the wall, hold on.
The power of the Lord!
That'll show me.
Okay, that was the...
What was it?
That's the cheap trick.
Platinum album that I was given.
Just fell off the wall here in the cottage.
You know, hey, everybody, how you doing?
Brand new week. Brand new source code.
A little bit late today.
It's 5-20 in the afternoon coming to you from the Curry Cottage in Guilford.
Had a USA today photo shoot here today, which is why I'm late.
Sorry.
So, of course, with Patricia and I did yesterday's.
We spent all day cleaning up my...
The final room really of the house, which is where we stored all the boxes.
And the home trainer by...
You know, the sun, tan bed, and all that stuff.
And so we had to really clean up a lot of crap.
And stuff up to the attic.
And to just basically get the place looking livable.
And of course, I put up all my pictures, my albums, so that it would look nice, right?
And then the cheap trick just fell off the wall.
If I can have to take a picture of it now, because this is one of those.
You get like a platinum record for sale of more than, I guess, a million units or whatever.
And has little platinum cassette next to it as well, because of course we didn't have CDs back then.
Or we did, but they weren't really used very widely.
And that cassette has now, because of the fall, has kind of like shifted inside the encasing.
Oh, well, it doesn't matter. Hey, everybody, they have a body how you're doing.
Got a lot to do, a lot to talk about today.
I'm not feeling too well, actually.
Yesterday, I think...
Well, Patricia asked me to do some quick grocery shopping.
And I came back, which you wanted me to get some cookies as well.
And I got cookies, but I also found a...
Something like the English version of Fig Newtons, if you know what Fig Newtons are.
And I don't know, man, but those Fig Newtons, they're just sitting in my belly like 15 tons of bricks.
They're not moving.
So I have abdominal pains.
Yeah, what do you care?
Hey, first thing I want to do is thank everyone for sending in all these different versions of you don't own me.
Of course, the original by Leslie Gore, we heard that we've heard many times the one by the Civius Bitties.
We heard, oh, what is it?
Ross Poutina.
I have three more.
I'm not going to play every single one, but I do want to play one at least once a day.
So why don't we play this one, which is sent to me?
This, of course, was the revival of this song in the...
It was the first wives club when they actually sang.
And that's Bettmiddler, Goldie Hawn, and...
Rrr...
Hold on, do I have any of my notes here?
Bettmiddler, Goldie Hawn, and...
Well, shoot, I don't know.
But it's you don't owe me.
On your source code.
I'm not just one of your many toys.
You don't owe me.
Don't say I can't go with none at their place.
Papa, papa, papa, papa.
And you don't tell me what to do.
And you don't tell me what to say.
And when I go out with you.
Papa, put me on display.
Where'd it go?
I'm a friend.
You don't owe me.
Don't try to change me in anyway.
You don't try to be boundless.
I'll never stay.
I don't tell you what I'll say.
I don't tell you what to do.
So just let me be myself.
Papa, papa, papa, papa.
I can't go with none at their place.
And when I go out with you.
So just let me be myself.
Can't go with none at their place.
you'll know me, call it when we call you, tell me
shout out you'll know me
how about you to tell me
fordi-to-l
shout out you'll know me
how about you'll know me
From the first wife's club, Batman Alert, Goldie Haun, and I forget the third one.
Sure, you'll be able to tell me all about it. You don't own me on the daily source code.
So I've set up the Louis XIV now with multiple screens and I've got the breakout.
Everything has its place. You've got the breakout box. I actually did all the WDS networking of my airport
extremes. So now, not just the house, but the garden. And yes, if you set out to find outside my house,
you can absolutely enjoy the four megabit per second to Wi-Fi or the pipe, at least with Wi-Fi.
It's open access. So come on, y'all. Come on, have a good time.
The problem is, though, with the breakout box. It's like if I want to turn the mic off, I have to reach all the way over there.
See? So I've got to work on the ergonomics still of the quote studio.
Let's see. What did I do? Oh, yes. Wait a minute. First of all, since it's 530 here, I think that the sun has
gone over the yard arm. So I think we can really get ready for the show. I bought a PC, everybody.
I bought a PC for downstairs because Christina really wants a PC. That's really mainly due to peer
pressure. We've been talking about this before. And one of the important things is all the cool features in
MSN, which she doesn't have on the Macintosh. It's funny because I was talking to the photographer from USA today.
Well, he does. He's not from USA today. He's a photographer who was given the assignment by USA today.
And the first thing he said was, oh, yeah, on a PC, you can use the cool Nudge feature on MSN.
Like, yep, you got it. It's like drugs for these kids. So I had an interesting time setting it up.
I bought a cheap ass PC shit, a Packard Bill with a little 15 inch TFT monitor. So, you know,
the big box is stuck underneath the desk downstairs. And all those on top is the keyboard mouse.
And it's actually quite a cute little screen. And it's perfect for Christina. She loves it.
Had to install a Wi-Fi card. That wasn't too hard. I kind of remembered how to do it.
And getting the cabinet open was reasonably simple. And it's funny to look inside a PC again and say,
damn, there's so much room in there. So much room for stuff.
So what are my experiences with this? I have to say, the first thing you really notice is just a feel.
The feel of, it's like plastic. You know, a Mac is so, the finish is just so perfect, you know.
So, of course, you pay extra for that. But the PC experience of starting up is very interesting.
Because here you see that Microsoft and whoever the PC manufacturer has to be, it kind of like,
yeah, they integrate in a weird way. So the setup of your computer goes through part Microsoft XP setup for Windows
and part setup that the manufacturer, whoever, yeah, who makes the boxes, I guess, whatever they deemed
necessary. So I've got all these icons and shit on the desktop. But in all, really, the setup wasn't that hard.
Of course, it's impossible for me to figure out how to configure a network printer on this thing.
But it works. And another thing I noticed is the hard drive. Man, those things did crunch away.
It's just, I should record the sound of that hard drive. But I've stopped behind it. I've used it.
It's great, actually. And I've ordered the Skype wireless phone. So I can plug that into the USB port.
Won't work on a Mac. At least the wireless one that I'm looking at so that Patricia can then
call the entire world at her heart's content, mainly to Holland, which is, I think I mentioned this before,
the most expensive country after Afghanistan to call, particularly mobile. It's like, you want to
paint $2.50 a minute. Of course, that's with the exchange rate. It gets a little wackier. But
well over a euro. And probably about a year and a half, about a pound a minute. It's just crazy.
So the PC is, it's in the house. It's working. And really, I have no problems with it. I think I could,
you know, work on a PC just as well. Don't know about the audio stuff. And of course,
there's weird things that have happened that, well, here's one for you. I also bought a transmitter.
Transmitters, we don't need no stink in transmitters. A transmitter from the sky digital box
in the living room. And I bought a little flat screen for Patricia, for the kitchen. And so that has
a receiver. And between those two, there's actually a digital link. That's from one room to the next.
Works very well, although I found that it does interfere a little bit with the Wi-Fi. Or let's say the Wi-Fi,
and I have three base stations, four computers that are polling for the best signal. And this,
I guess Wi-Fi frequency-based transmitter receiver for the television. It's a little bit,
I could just a bit much. We got a lot of stuff going on here. Got an email about this new plug-in
for audio hijack approach. Someone's been trying to get me to try and see the email was from Greg Walker.
There's this free plug-in that you can use called the audio inspector. And you can put it in
at the end of your effects chain on audio hijack approach. Actually, I'm going to do right now.
I didn't dare start to show off doing this. I'm actually going to add this effect as we speak on the
fly. I think it'll work. Elemental audio systems inspector. There we go. Okay. So I don't know if that
I heard something click. I don't know if it changed anything. Apparently, this will keep your levels
together. I don't know if it's supposed to keep your levels at a continuous rate so that it kind of
keeps everything in check. Or if it's just like a monitor, a mood-long clear. It's in the chain now.
I can see a great spectrum analyzer. Lots of winky-blinky lights. It looks very cool. I just don't
know if it's what it's actually doing. If it's doing me any good. But it should apparently keep the
the loud bits not too loud and the softer bits not too soft. And you can find all the links to this
plug-in, which is great eye candy in the show notes for today. I've also been meaning to tell you
about this show that's been on for the past couple of weeks on channel 4 around midnight in the
UK. It's called Anatomy for Beginners. This is the most unfucking believable show I've ever seen.
They have a small audience. So maybe 30, 40, maybe 50 people tops. In just a small television
studio. In the middle of this television studio, they have an operating table, not with all the
gear. It's more like an autopsy table because they literally, every night, they take a cadaver,
which is French for dead person. And they discuss a separate part of the body. And they cut the
parts out and show them to you and explain what it's all about. And they've got this this doctor.
It was this guy who narrated to this British book. He's nice. He's just going through all the motions,
explaining what's going on. But this doctor wears it like this cowboy hat, like a black hat,
and he's kind of like a, he's a German. It's really, it's really quite frightening. But it's really
something that is just amazing to see. And once you get through the initial shock of my god, they're
cutting a body open. It's really fascinating to watch. The other day they, they cut out the entire
intestinal track from going from the tongue all the way down through the esophagus. Obviously,
all the way through all the bowels, which they rolled out. It was seven meters, which is 720,
what is that? 21 feet of guts. And they just rolled it out over over all these tables and explained
exactly how it worked. And, you know, they've cut open testicles, which was a very uncomfortable
show to watch. But man, this is something that they definitely should get on cable in the
states. Because once you get through the, as I said, once you get through the initial shock, it's just
fucking cool to see. And, and you get a whole new perspective on really what your body is about
and what's going on. And quite honestly, I'm freaked out.
Viget, have you hacked into the feed yet? Excellent. Hello, Mr. Adam Curry. This is Evil Mastermind,
Dr. Steve. I just wanted to give you a big thanks for mentioning the radio adventures of Dr. Floyd
podcast on your show, the daily source code. Thank you also for crediting it to someone else.
You fell for my evil plan, the spread lies about Dr. Floyd perfectly.
Now, everyone will think that the very talented PwFenton put together the radio adventures of Dr. Floyd
when in reality, it's those two talentless hacks, Grand Pachoco and Doug Bryce.
Now, no one will ever know that they can go to Dr. Floyd.com and find out more than they ever
wanted to know about the show. Because I'm not saying anything about it. What? No, I didn't
did I? We didn't do. Because you Adam Curry should have done all fidget.
All right, I guess I deserve that. Radio adventures of Dr. Floyd, Dr. Floyd.com.
Some cool college radio podcast happening here in the UK. I got email from Michael Rumble
one of that, you know, something great happening with podcasting and independent music in the
UK is at Cambridge University, although he lives in Wabridge, which is near Gilford.
He set up a podcast to showcase the best in this town that's town, not the university
in a way of independent music. So, apparently what's happening is they're doing podcasts with
local bands, with a playing MP3s of local bands, and also giving their gig schedule, you know,
where you can see them play, and apparently other universities are joining in. York University
set up their own podcast, and what else? To Cambridge, York, and then there's of course the podcast
you take UK. You should check these out. They're obviously in the iPodot org directory by now,
but also linked from the show notes for today. I listen to a couple of the tunes, and I think
I'll probably be playing some of that pod safe music from one of those bands pretty soon because
of some good stuff there, and it'll be even better, I guess, or we can get an interview with them,
maybe even record something alive since, hey, they're from my hometown. Hi Adam, this is Brian Reed,
from rebeldad.com. I just launched the Rebel Dad Radio podcast this weekend. He had to show talking
about stay at home fatherhood. That's the glory of the medium for me, the incredible narrow
casting. At any rate, I'm now trying to count the number of stay at home dads. I've got at least
two, there's me and Dan Class from the bitterspill.com. Should I be considering you a third?
Well, I don't know. How do you classify or qualify as a stay at home dad?
If I don't have a job, is that also stay at home? If I just pod gas at home?
And I would presume that stay at home dad means that mom is out working, perhaps.
So we're kind of stay at home mom and dad, but I try to pull my way. I really do.
So it sounds like a cool, a cool little concept you got there though, so I'll be tuning in to rebel
dad radio. Checked out the beta of iPodor 2 the other day and it's like really beta.
It's discovered some interesting things right away. I was working with Andrew Grummit, one of the
developers of lead developers of iPodor. Of the lemon team, I should say actually.
This shit's looking pretty good. There's still some experiential things that I'm going to
provide feedback on, but it's very, very nice. It's definitely getting together there and localized
in eight different languages, including Dutch my favorite, but of course there are a couple of Dutch
guys on the lemon team. So I had some problems on the Mac. My plan for for Wednesday, sorry.
Tomorrow I have CNN international here to do an interview me. But then I plan on trying out
the Windows version of iPodor. I plan on trying out Jay Potter, Doppler radio, and NIMIC,
and there's a couple others because it's just so much happening on the Windows side of things
that it's crazy that I haven't played with these. I'm sure that there's some features in there that
that others could benefit from. So what actually that's one of the cool things of the iPodor 2
is this, when you subscribe, it's very visual and it shows you all the different podcasts from
this new feed that you subscribe to. It says and it's visual with a checkmark. You can see that's
only going to download the most recent one. You can also just catch up buttons so you can say just
download the most recent one from all podcasts if you were a way of vacation or if you're bandwidth
sucked and you can only get some at Starbucks for instance. So really, some very cool features.
Although there's one thing, I got a call from a girl who was doing an article for
scientific American. So you think she maybe have some technical inclination. She said,
I don't have an iPod, so I don't understand where the shows are. I see that they're downloaded,
but I don't know where they are, so still some work to be done on that. But otherwise,
man, looking great, really fantastic, and hopefully I'll be able to check out the iPodor X
data, which is on its way as well. Great. We're coming out with version two of everything.
This is very, very exciting. I've talked about Ron Bloom before, a good friend of mine, who I
ran a company with from 96.95 to 2000. His dad, Aaron, passed away over the just before the weekend
at a grand age of 90, though, I have to say. And so Ron, of course, was going to Atlanta,
where he's from, for the funeral. And it's beautiful. I've known Ron for a long time. And every single
Sunday, he calls home to mom and the dad. And sometimes to other members of the family, and I'm
actually emulated that a little bit. And in this case, Aaron passed away in his sleep. So,
you know, it's just a beautiful, beautiful life, a fantastic, you know, it's, I think, falling,
if you go in your sleep, that's probably probably the best way. And I got an MP3 feedback from
Atlanta, which I actually, I Skype him, I said, dude, I really want to play this. Excuse me,
on the source code, because it really shows how you guys were celebrating Aaron's life.
And the fact that you called it a wakecast, it just really tickled me. So, I got this wave file.
The beginning is a lot of ambient noise, because this is at the wake, and there's a lot of people,
and there's clearly some drinking going on. But I just wanted to share this with the source
code listeners, because it probably is the first wakecast, if you want to call it that.
And it's, uh, it's a good listen, here comes.
All right, everybody here said hello. Adam, this is Adam. So, uh, here we go, here's Shaila.
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
Oh, great one. This is the lady's name, bitch.
Hello, Adam. This is Martha from Hot Latter.
I'm Adam, baby. Oh, that's the house. That's the room family signing off of the Z80 Wakecast.
So, uh, we miss you and we appreciate your kind messages and Z80s in a better place. We smile at all of it.
All right, Adam, talk to you later. We got to go eat some tissue. I was thinking about taking you on a
sensing tour of my plate, but there's no sushi left. So, uh, I'll have to wait till next time.
I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. Okay. I think that was actually done through an
AT&T recorded phone number. It showed up as a wave file, the first wakecast. And I put a link in
to, uh, to a page that was Adam Bloom, uh, Ron's nephew. Um, and so there's, uh, some, uh, some quick
time videos of, uh, of Ron's dad, which you definitely should check out. It's just cool to see.
So, the loop is complete. And I bet he is indeed looking down on us going,
what are you guys doing? Hey, uh, it's almost me guys. This is Simon Hodginson from
bizcast.co.uk. Just wanted to say great show. Also, just a wish you're listening to us.
A happy Chinese New Year. No, it's Chinese New Year on the 9th of February this year. It's the
year of the rooster. But if you're bumping Chinese people and you want to say happy New Year,
then in Mandarin Chinese, it's Shinyan Quaila. In Cantonese, it's Gong He Fat Choy.
Anyway, you can impress them with your Chinese now. Anyway, he plenty of dumplings,
light fireworks and other great Chinese New Year. Thank you. Gong He Fat Choy. All righty. Thank you
very much. Uh, always good to know. Some sounds seeing tour options. And I keep updating the
feed the sound seeing tours.com. Every single time something cool comes my way. So, if you
not subscribe, you might want to check that out. It's on the homepage of curry.com. It's also
under sound seeing in the ipod.org directory. I posted on curry.com a picture of the birth house
of PG Woodhouse, author and humorist who apparently was born in Guilford. And there's some
sounds sound seeing tour suggestions that have come in for Guilford itself. I'll read this.
This is from with this come from. For us from Lloyd from Perfect Path. Okay.
22nd is more avenue near Stoke Park was the boy at home of Alan Turing, without whose mathematical
genius we might not be conversing like this from Turing's machine. It doesn't know if there's a
plaque there, but Lewis Carroll is buried in Guilford up on the mount, which is the hill that I
see in the front of me when I when you walk down on the high street. There's a statue of Alice
and Wonderland down by the river. So that is some the first day that is reasonable. See, I've been
thinking either it's got to be a beautiful day or it's got to be a really, really shitty rainy day.
I just don't think my equipment is is is is good enough for that shitty rainy day, but I think
the real rain ambient noise might be cool. So one of those days either really shitty or really good
I'm off to do a sound seeing tour of Guilford. See if we can find the statue of Alice in Wonderland.
And I really screwed up a couple of times actually when I was talking about coverville,
Brian from coverville isn't indeed not from Canada. He's from Colorado just outside of Denver.
Why do I think that? I'd have no idea why I I'm sorry. I mean it's not bad to be called
Canadian, right? It's not bad. So Brian I was listening to the latest coverville show and he played
a version of I feel love that I had not heard before. You know the Donna Summerton and Patricia
actually walked in the office to damn. This is really good and I listen to the, oh man,
I don't have anything to drink here either. Let me just drink something out of the faucet.
I should have let the faucet run a little bit before I drank that. That was like pure copper coming.
I bet the color is now yellow. Hold on, I'll take you over here. I'll take you over here.
That's pretty clear. Okay, I just got the first mild full of nastiness.
So I looked in the show notes, one of the few times I've actually done that on a podcast,
but it's real handy on a music podcast. And and also heard Brian back announced it as the
Blue Man group with Venus Humb on vocals. Is that Venus Humb on vocals? And the Blue Man group,
familiar with them because I saw that they were in Vegas, I think, and I have a huge show there.
They probably have a touring version of it as well. And I'm kicking myself now that I didn't
go see them. We chose for like the new Cirque de Soleil. You know, I don't know, some kind of show
they were trying out. They're stupid because this Blue Man group stuff looks absolutely fantastic.
And I was able to find a video, which of course the podcast won't really help you with that,
but I found a video of this song. And it's like a theme footage, intercut with performance.
And I think it's from their show and probably from Vegas. Unbelievable. So I definitely wanted to
give the track a play because man, it's just like totally kicking.
The Blue Man group for Venus Humb. I feel love on your daily source code.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh-oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh-oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh. Oh, oh, oh, oh yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
You're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free
you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, your free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free, you're free,
Oh, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I
I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you, I can see you,
I feel love
Hi, this is David from the Audio Collective
Recently I've heard a few complaints about the Firefox browser being slow
Well, I've done some research and there seems to be a solution for the problem
As we all know, Firefox is a great browser
It's fast, it's less vulnerable to spyware and viruses and it has a wonderful pop-up blocking tool
With a few tweaks you can make Firefox even better
That's right, you can make it run even faster
Now this is a warning, this is not for people who are on dial-up connections
Only those people who have faster connections like DSL or broadband
This is actually taken advantage of a hidden option found in Firefox
Now to do this you must open your Firefox browser 1.0
In the address bar of your browser, type in the following about colon config
That is AB-O-U-T colon C-O-N-F-I-G
This will bring up a menu in your Firefox window
Next find the command line network.http.pyplining
And double click on that so the value equals true
Next find networking.http.pyplining.max.com
Dot max requests
Double click on it and change it from 4 to 10
Now what do these changes do when you're asking?
You're suited up!
The first one enables this tweak to happen
The second one is changing how fast Firefox can download the webpage
This makes it possible for Firefox to use more of your bandwidth when downloading webpages
Once again, if you missed it, here are the steps to tweak your Firefox browser
You must open your Firefox browser 1.0
In the address bar!
Okay, okay, I think we heard it the first time
Because you can always go back and listen to the instructions again
I did this, it really works
On macOSX significantly...
Sorry, it's the drunken sound again
Significantly faster
I really could tell of course
I made the mistake of setting it to 100 the first time
Instead of 10
And I was like, whoa, because of course I went to my regular porn banner sites
And the bandwidth was gone within another second
But yeah, changing that from 4 to 10 actually does work
Great tip and love the audio version of it
So I don't know if it's really effective
If it's easy to just go to the webpage as provided in the show notes
But it does work
I promised an update on the mixed-cast live beta
And then we talked about this, this is the Windows application
Which is built with .NET
That was modeled according to James
Well, the first email he sent me
You know a lot of
What this application is
Was designed around what we had talked about here on the source code
And I think with trade secrets as well with Dave
And he actually built this application
Which looks very much like a little mini radio studio
So we heard that I was wondering on the source code about how it was
How it was going, I'll just read this to you
I've been slowly adding people to the beta for the past three weeks
One of my get some gnarly bugs
I stopped adding people to the big ones are fixed
I've had five releases during that period
I'm preparing for the six which has been really busy on this man
He's probably doing this all by himself
There's a big job
Big change in the application are mostly configuration related
In fact the original demo that you link to is totally outdated
Oh, okay
Dude got to send me a new
A new
If you have a new screen grab or a screen movie
That's great, send it to me
Response from test has been very positive
Working hard to get the biggest remaining bugs squash before public release
I'm avoiding putting a date on it now
But he can say soon
And then James winds up saying let me know when your windows box is all together
I'll send you an invitation
Yes, I'm ready
I am red day
Of course, I don't have a microphone on the windows box
Shit
I have to go get off the by one
Or maybe if I get a webcam with the built-in mic
Can I use that too?
Well that worked
That's probably what a lot of people would use
And let's see
Last one here was a cute email from Andrew Grummit
We talked about him earlier
One of the developers on the lemon team
So sitting on the bus listing to another one of those name that tune segments on daily source code
There's so much fun
On comes a tune that I recognize and I blurred out
Can't explain that was the who right
Guy to see next to me turns his head and looks in me
Oh, I see
Yeah, okay, it was listening to a music trivia game
Gotta be careful, man
Oh shoot, where is my trivia?
I had trivia lined up for today
Hold on, that's weird
Didn't, I was gonna finish off with that
And I don't see it on my playlist here
Shit, now of course the Mac is
Can you hear that?
Listen to my Mac
Okay
Good, I don't know what happened and why I didn't load
Okay, and we're gonna wind up today's show
To fill out the 40 minutes with another trivia hit quiz
Hey Adam, this is a young poet with this week's hit test
Okay, three tracks, next to the first one
Wait, I hear cowbell
Wait, wait, I want to replace that girl back
I heard some cowbell
Fuck
I got to know about it
Next one
Number two
Don't waste my time
New shoes, jacked and grained
And number three
Scready Politi
The first time
I don't know, Scready Politi
With these, maybe
Something like that
There you have it
Okay, whoa, I love something
The answers, but first let me ask you something
Yes
When you've only played the test for yourself to test your knowledge
Or also if you think there are some kind of entertainment value in it
And if so, if it's a good idea to put this thing in a podcast
Of its own
Of course it's entertainment value
I wonder if you could share your thoughts about this
Well, I kind of, if you do, please pause this playback
To do so
I'm sorry
I have to pause the playback to do so
I don't know
It's kind of like the drum cadence of the day
You know, it's like, do you really want to drum cadence of the day
Podcast feed or you just want to hear it once in a while on the show
I think you could certainly make one available
But I'd love to keep receiving your hit test as well
And I'd hate to have to share that with everyone
Without doing it on the fly live
That's what I like the most I think
Because exactly what Andrew said
You're sitting there and you're like, Adam, you fucker
You know, of course you know the answer and I don't
I think that's that gives an extra dimension to it
Really
If not, there we go with the answers
That's what you can number one
Okay
Tom Jones and she's a lady
Yeah
She's all you'd ever want
She's the kind that I'd like to fault
And she's a lady
That was stupid
She's a lady
Who knows, she's a lady
Number two
That was, and people knew the benefit of the doubts
Oh, no, I blew it
It's the same fucking track as the waste my time
Oh, man
I got Screamy Politi right
That's all the same
And finally, number three
Come on
Screamy Politi
Yeah
This is the word girl
Word girl
Ah, man
Okay, so if you have to take
Artists and title
A 50% of the jams, or I got
Yeah
I got shit scores
So this concludes this week's hit test
I hope you had fun
See you in the next time, bye-bye
I can't fucking believe it
It fell off again
Oh, man
Let's start at the beginning and at the end of the show
Hold on
No, you better stay
God, I'm going to do that
I'm telling you, this place is possessed
It's like a poltergeist has been throwing
There's no reason why it should fall on the ground
None whatsoever
All right, everybody, that was it for today's show
For the 31st
If you've got a comment, it's Adam at Curry.com
Of course, you can find this show in the archives
at dailysourcecode.com
Leave a comment on the weblog
If you want, www. Curry.com
And feedback in MP3 form to MP3
Feedback at Gmail.com
So it's MP3 Feedback at Gmail.com
Okay
I'm tired
I see you all tomorrow, okay
I'm going to try new the show early
Before seeing end shows
Take care
Bye bye