Well, hi, everybody. I'm back. This is a special addition to the daily source code for Thursday, October 6, 2005.
I was so preoccupied with everything going wrong with my Mac that I completely forgot to bring you the job cast.
So doing this is a separate file, feel free to send it to your friends or whatever.
It'll be small enough. You can just download this and practically email it with somebody.
We've got a lot of stuff going on. We have four reasonably big projects happening out pod show.
And one of those like the pod safe music network.
And what we're realizing is that we're missing a critical, well actually we know we're missing a critical person in the organization.
We just really haven't been able to find this person yet.
So this is a job cast. It's an opening at pod show full-time position.
Anyone can apply. It's all about the experience.
This is really a job where someone has a very specific type of experience.
It's for in the Bay Area. So you have to come to the office. It's not a virtual job.
So if you don't live in the Bay Area then, you know, unfortunately, you know, just the speed that we need someone, etc.
It's just not going to work.
And what we're looking for is someone who has a lot of experience with the heavy iron of the world.
So we're talking about reasonably large hosting environments.
If you have experience with like multi-user setups, let me give an example.
Oh, for instance, like if you have example with setting up multiple mobile type web logs or WordPress or systems like that,
it's all lamp Linux Apache, mySQL and PHP, then we're looking for you.
And send your CV and a little bit about yourself. And by the way, I love it when people say here's what I can do for you.
I love it when you start off like that.
Send it to jobs at podshow.com.
J-O-B-S, jobs at podshow.com.
Feel free to see me if you want to.
But it'll go through through the correct channels if you send it to jobs at podshow.com.
We're looking for something for someone immediately to fill this spot.
And, you know, if we get to talk until you, I think we really excited about what we're doing.
And if you like hanging out in cages, in server cages, and you like, you know, talking border gateway protocol,
and you'd like messing around with lots and lots of users and user data and making stuff run smoothly.
Well, then we're looking for you.
So, jobs at podshow.com.
And thank you for listening to this.
Special Jobcast.