Delta shared Charlie two two three good morning everybody. Welcome. It is Tuesday morning
The date is the 16th of August 2005. I'm in Berkeley, California. Hold on. I'm just gonna be repositioned. I'm microphone here for a second
and
I'm off
Into San Francisco, 10 minutes past eight and
The girls are still sleeping and
I am well clearly. I'm doing much better
But also the vacation is kind of coming to an end here. Hold on. I'm sure. I'll crash. I think
As Friday, we're planning to go back and of course
part of this vacation was supposed to be a working vacation and
That part started yesterday really
Pretty exciting
Yesterday was the first day in our office in San Francisco now. It's not our
The office that we intend to have for good
This is a temporary office, but really it was it was quite cool to have just
Everybody kind of show up all of a sudden. We have a number of folks from the East Coast
Chris McIntyre from podcast Ali got a couple of people from
We just check what I'm doing here hold on a second after the Niga okay
A couple of people from out here people from Los Angeles. So it was like there was like
Eight people in the office yesterday
In fact, we have an office just blew me away. It was a total trip
rolled up at about eight thirty in the morning and
There it was coffee
Computers folks doing stuff very very exciting
So today there's two things on the agenda
One kind of flows into the other the first one is or the
The most prevalent thing that I'm doing today is we have a an update to our board of directors
Which is you know perfect we're just getting started and
Already we have a lot of
a lot of second
I'm not in a good place here with my car
We've got a lot of really really really cool things that are that are going on
I don't even know half of it because I've been so out of the loop. I feel really just
It's I think that's part of what I dealt what I dislike about vacation
It's being out of the loop on on anything really and not just
Having been on vacation, but really being completely tuned out because of this flu bug that we had
I feel like I've missed so much and then again
I was able to catch up with a lot of stuff
Once we got into
Into the Claremont resort
I was able to you know catch up with a couple of shows. I listened to the most recent Gilmour gang
Last night 86 minutes. I think it's just a bit credible amount
But what's really cool about this is you know if you're a listen to the Gilmour gang
Then you know it's like a roundtable discussion and it usually lasts for about an hour
What's Steve Gilmour has been doing recently and I really like this and I hope that
By now the rest of the gang understands if that's happening is he's basically the minute everyone's on the phone
You know the recording's already rolling and he just
Basically puts all that out unedited as far as I know it's unedited
And it's it's really what it's almost what the Gilmour gang used to be where people just bitching and moaning and talking about industry stuff
But really
You know much less held back for some reason
I'm not quite sure what it is about that, but it really really does work
And so they were waiting for Ron Ron Bloom to
To come on to the call so there must have been a good 20 or 25 minutes and then talk about all kinds of stuff scobal was on
But it's a very strong opinions about the pod show and serious
So you should definitely give that a listen
I'd say the I really like that those first 25 minutes because that was truly
People with their guard down and and it really
I don't think that any of the Gilmour gang members really listen to the show and I can't understand that
You know if you've you've already lived through the hour and a half that the show was and you pretty much know everything
It was said you're not gonna go back and listen to it
To the podcast more than likely
But I still have the feeling that a number of the gang members don't really understand that that opening bit that that first part is
Also being podcast
Maybe it's better that way because I just love listening to that
a lot of talk about pod show
about the
The interest that we receive from the investment community and not just the investment community from you know
Client of Perkins and Sequoia capital and Ram Shuram
People that we aggressively went after
Because we felt that they would be the perfect team
Help us grow our vision of pod casting
Well, I'm a second now. I have to I don't want to mess this up. I don't have a my typical GPS
Or even a never-law's in fact this car that I'm driving is a
For tourists as an SE it has absolutely nothing it's white to make it even
Add insult to injury
As no frills and I actually I kind of like it, but
Because it has no GPS. I really have to pay attention
Because you know, you know me jet boy
Without the GPS, I can't function anymore. Don't tell me there's gonna be a whole bunch of traffic this morning
That was not the agreement
Shoot
Okay, well, it's like we're already in some kind of traffic
So anyway, so that board update is today and
You know the update is great because there's lots of stuff and lots of ideas that we have and people that you know
We'd like to get in touch with which are and investors have all the inroads to
So I know that's a big big benefit and
Very exciting
To be moving in different circles these days got the apartment
Got all that squared away yesterday
Got a great apartment for one. I'm here in San Francisco which will be
Quite a lot. I'm sure
And hopefully some of the stuff that we ordered online Patricia and I did a big order
I think it was a JC pennies or something we ordered you know like a bed and and tables and stuff
Hopefully that's going to show up
Before we go back
Typical JC penny
Yeah, your order is in transit. I guess we have to call someone over there and figure out what's going on
And today
Patricia and Christina and Ron's wife Marta are gonna go pick up some more stuff
Both for my apartment also for
For Ron and Marta's apartment because they have actually relocated here and
It's very foggy today
This is not what I had ordered. I told Patricia. I said it's so beautiful
You even have palm trees out here Northern California
Which is true, but man foggy and chili
So I can't wait to really get back into the full swing of doing
regular daily source code
Can understand that I have obviously been splitting up my time between
Well being sick first of all, but also you know being with the family you know doing stuff together
Which is really you know what you do what we do want to do our vacation
Despite that some work is slipping in here and there
And that does eat into basically all the time I spend at home on
Pre-producing the source code
You know, but also other stuff like the pod finder. There's a new pod finder that came out today. I hope on iTunes
Dave Fox
hosted it this week
I'd actually plan on doing that even though I had relinquished all of my
Serious satellite pod show duties to other
podcasters
I was planning on doing the pod finder myself, but obviously it just didn't feel up to it
So Dave Fox who is he's the guy from the
He's the voice of pod casting it's Adam Curry
So I'm very curious to see how that turned out
So I've really cutting all at that time
And obviously five in the west. Yeah, that's what I'm gonna take here
Yesterday it was much faster. Why is it so slow? There isn't an accident or something
I have no idea really what the traffic patterns are in
San Francisco how many people live in San Francisco is it? I mean it certainly seems like a really big city when you look at it
but
No, it's a traffic okay. Let's see
It's traffic's moving
But I also want to get back to you know
Back to just into the fray of
Listening to what everyone's doing again and part of that is you really do need bandwidth
I found that still lots of hotel
connectivity is not really
Really good enough for the you know the type of subscription list that I have
And I'm running iTunes almost exclusively now for of the pod cast
I gotta say I'm pretty happy with it
But when you get into a a lower bandwidth situation
You do get broken download and you know that's really where
You know some of the some of the stuff starts yeah, I see buddy some of the stuff starts the fall apart
Bear with me here for a second
Trying to think if
I'm gonna crash into that mini van and I think if there's anything else it's really big that's that's been happening
I guess the the podcast awards I saw that I I want a podcast award for
Best produced podcast
Well, thank you very much. I presume that that is voted on by
By the audience
Was there ceremony or was there some kind of
Show or did just the announcements just kind of you know just appear. I was wondering about that
I like award I like awards
I like receiving awards rarely ever received an award for anything
But I do like it to
To be a ceremony number the wired rave awards
When I was up for was it's a
New technology or something and it went to see well
I forget it else was in the category with me. I do know that Mark think the CEO from blog lines
He won that it it was like there was no ceremony
Yeah, you you walked in and there was a like a PowerPoint switching through slides of the nominees and the winners
I like a ceremony man. That's you really need to have if you're gonna do it awards
Anything you got him you gotta go all the way
So maybe there's something planned for this podcast expo which uh, what is it now?
They can't be that far away maybe a month or two months away
So now we're coming up to the toll
This is kind of ziplong now. I like that
I'm not quite sure what this toll is for well obviously for some use of some
Road here. I'm just trying to think what the
Is it a
Wonder him all up
Get my cash here
There we go
Yeah, I see this is nice this is what New York traffic should be like
Beautiful
Yeah, I gotta have my tunes pump and early in the morning
Man my license plate is resonating with that guy's base
Good morning. Thank you. All right
So we're doing well then
Right so Friday we'll be gone back
Straight from San Francisco to London and I think the in-laws who've been staying at the house
Are ready to go home themselves. I think they're they're bored
It was probably stay a couple more days. I got a call-up wing command to William because of course
We flew them over on the on the 182 so I want to fly him back on the 182 and if I can
Work in a couple more hours of flying myself that'll be great
It's time once again. You know by the way the Carpool tunnel syndrome whatever it's getting better
It really is this still
In my left index finger is still a little little spots of numbness and and my my thumb is almost completely better
And that's I guess really just
Been through not
Yankees know yolks and just taking it easy so I'll be curious to see what happens when
When I go flying for a couple hours again see it if it well
I'm sure I'll feel it again. I'm sure some of it will come back, but hopefully progressively over time
You know just get better
Because I saw was it James Woods was on
I think it was on Leno or on Letterman and
He had something very similar
Where you know, so what happened with me is it was through the Yogiaki on the plane
While flying for that week and then of course
I fell asleep on my hand in the airplane for several hours not the one that I was flying but on the way to Miami
And what he had done is he had left his his four arms in one almost one position during a poker game
For I think you're saying 46 hours or something like that and he actually had to have his nerve
Cut out and reposition
Because of I guess the you know the pain and whatever the numbness, but his nerve was completely shot
And and I've heard lots of other people saying that you know eventually the only way you can solve this problem is through
An operation like now
First of all, I don't want to believe that second of all. I don't believe it. So it does seem to be getting much much better
Real happy about that now we're on the Bay Bridge
on the upper deck
which
This bridge has one way decks only so the
upper deck goes two surfaces go and the lower deck goes away from it and I can barely see it
It's all I can see the second portion of the bridge past what is it was at
Yerba Boina and Paradise Island kind of halfway through this bridge
It's completely in the clouds
That would be the foggy clouds
So it's I guess it's a very typical San Francisco morning
Then I don't know I'm gonna learn a lot more about it as I and now a new dweller of this city which I am liking very much
It seems like a real easy city to get around in
And just I don't know it's it seems convenient it seems pretty laid back
And it's pretty so I'm looking forward to being here a lot
I'm also looking forward to bringing my girls back with me
When when we have the apartments, I'll have our own place so they can have more of a base hang out
And get to know a little bit more about what's going on in the city itself because now it's you know where we're outside
And
So I'll probably do another quick update before we head back on Friday
Certainly if anything you know really cool happens
It seems like podcasting is just growing more every day
There's a I think I've said this before there's a whole new round of
I've pressed that is coming and that's because
It's still here you know podcasting is not a flash in the pan it hasn't gone away overnight
Publications are coming back interested in
Commercialization of podcasting interested in the glaring differences but it in a nice way between
Indie podcasters and mainstream podcasts
So there's there's plenty of opportunity for us to bring in more listeners
For more people to be exposed. I don't think there's a day that doesn't go by
That someone doesn't say send me an email saying hey, you know, I just found about this podcasting stuff
Usually it's through iTunes
How people tune into it so I think that we're
We're on a very very good track at this moment and you know as we start to wind down the summer
I think we're gonna see a lot of things kick up
Yeah
Oh, so I might have been my wife oops, well, I just missed it. Okay, so
I'm very bullish about everything that's going on and
Prepared to work very hard to see what we could take this
So as I have just about to take the free month street exit
We've been talking for about 20 minutes and I'll be picking up
Ron and Brian as we have a meeting in 930 in
Palo Alto
That's not a board update, but that's with the technology company which of course is why we're out here because if there's anything we're light on
You know, we know a lot about media. We don't know everything there is to know about
Technology and this is definitely the part of the world to come and get that so I'm gonna learn some more things today
And look forward to talking to you very soon as I said maybe
Before we go back if not certainly on Monday as we get back into swing of
A brand new source code so take care y'all and I'll talk to you soon bye bye