Daily source code, March 10th, 2005.
Oh boy, we got some stuff to talk about today.
I'm probably already overmodulating in your headphones because of it.
I'm not gonna be, yeah.
Let me adjust a little bit here. There we go, that should work.
It's the source code for March 10th, 2005.
I'm actually pretty pleased with myself.
I've been doing dual duty today, working with an entire team of lawyers who were in court
on my behalf today. That was interesting.
I always run the know that lawyers are talking to each other.
Both parties of lawyers are building you.
But also I worked on my setup here at the cottage.
You've almost had castle. It's starting to feel a bit like the castle.
All this gear all over the place.
So we're talking about the setup.
I got, you know, a mashup lined up and just normal stuff to talk about.
And it was during preparations for today's show that I noticed that I really had no more promos.
And I guess tomorrow will be my big suck to Gmail account dry day.
Well, that's second. Let me just ensure that I'm not gonna turn off the recording here.
So I hope you're enjoying the sound.
I've worked on this most of the day trying to figure out different ways to route audio.
And I have completely resorted to using outboard gear, which means boxes that are not native to software.
Although just about everything that I purchased certainly does integrate perfectly with my max running OS 10.
And if you hold on, I'll be happy to tell you all about it.
First, let's crank it up with a mashup for you off.
I mean, just easy top by themselves and be crying, right?
But now sprinkle a little bit of pink on top.
You've got the sharp dress party on this daily source curve.
So I hope you're enjoying the sound.
So I hope you enjoy the sound.
But I hope you're enjoying the sound.
So I hope you're enjoying the sound.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you're good, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
It's an unfortunate sharp dress party that was ZZU top versus pink here on the daily source code.
And hopefully you heard the sound was like kind of consistent now for the first time.
Let's talk about that.
First of all about my test yesterday.
I did the new mobile test where I jacked the iPod and the microphone together into a
single wire splitter that went into the iRiver as a recording device.
It actually worked okay.
I mean the sound was reasonably shitty on the microphone and sounded a bit overmodulated
and just wasn't quite coming through right.
But it also brought down the output volume significantly.
Until of course the iPod turned off and then, well, I got a lot of emails like the
following one.
This is from Axel.
Hello Adam, please refer to your regular hardware setup.
Please, I listened to the daily source code via my power book hooked up to my stereo
home cinema setup.
I thought my speakers were going to explode.
Please don't do this anymore.
It really sucks.
It really does.
One of the things that made daily source code stand out or did until yesterday was it's
a good broadcast quality.
Okay, so I do apologize.
It was, yeah, I was just kind of messing around and testing it out and that clearly
didn't work out too well.
Everybody complained about it.
So the morning after I dropped Christina off at school, I'd already done my homework
and checked out their website.
I went to Anderton Music, which is a really great music store in Guildford, not far from
Christina's school, actually, which was nice.
I went in and I bought, first of all, I bought a whole bunch of cables that match the
three and a half inch jack, the six inch jack, or whatever.
All mixes and matches of different types of wires and connectors.
In the music world, or in the professional audio world, they use different jacks than we
use on our computers and our headphones.
So I just needed some, you know, some adapter plugs.
Then I also purchased a soundcraft compact 4 mixer, which is, I had, I had spec this
one out before.
I looked at this mixer, I'm using it in a very simple setup, basically I'm just pumping
the microphone in and that is coming straight out, but it's better than any other mic
in version that I've used, you know, I use the breakout box.
These breakout boxes, even the fire wire, they just don't cut it because you get this
latency and this latency builds up and you just, you know, you just can't get rid of it
unless you, you know, re-regrab the interface and it just becomes unbearable after a bit.
In fact, doing the Patricia Pride podcast, it took us a good 20 minutes to set up and get
the levels right so that Patricia would actually, could bear having the headphones on,
listening to herself talk, she said, you know, it's slowing me down and it is.
I got used to it and, you know, now that I, that is gone, and I'll tell you how I solve
that, I'm really digging it.
So here's what I've done.
Here's how I've set it up and there's more gear to come because now I'm starting to
get the hang of all this and I'm getting pretty excited.
Basically, I have my wireless mic, the receiver is going into one input, a mono channel
on this mixer and the mixer is outputting a stereo signal which I'm putting into the line
in of my power book.
Now I had, why did I differently earlier today, where the output of my power book was
routed through the mixer as well and so I could play back stuff, anything on the computer
that I wanted to and then I could mix the microphone and that audio signal, I actually had my
iPod hooked up to it as well.
I could mix those together.
Now what happened is I really started to miss the signal processing.
You know, I work so hard on getting the reverb just right and, and, and getting the
equalizing just sounding right and a little bit of compressor and I've got all these great
effects in the computer that I'm affecting, I can't use in that setup.
So I'm piping the microphone now into the, as I said, into the line in through the
mixing board and I'm just using the hijack feature of audio hijack pro so that I can
use all of their effects and basically put a chain together and the music of hijack
that, as well, basically hijacked the line input and of hijacked the, the quick time
player which I used to play my, my little clips of audio or mashups and so I've been
able to process them both individually which is really nice and the recording I'm doing
on my iRiver.
I've decided this is a great recorder, because you just gobs and gobs of time, 17 hours
to record it very high quality sample rate and so basically it's just recording the,
it's getting its, it's input from the headphone jack on the power book and I just tried
out where I brought a Skype call in and I hijacked the Skype application as well so
I can process that so and then I, I can do VU meters for each individual channel so it's
finally starting to look and feel like a studio and that for a, you know, like a $100
mixer so I'm very, very happy with this setup currently and I'll keep you in the loop
on what I, I might even go for some external effects on the microphone that might be something
I could do, that might be cool.
Actually, I'll just give you a little demo here, hold on, let me decouple from the headset.
So I can actually turn this microphone off and now I have the other microphone on which
is my sure.
I need a mic stand for the sure so I can use it while I'm sitting down on the couch
so that's why I'm not using it today so I'm just using the, the lovelier so I'm
going to switch back to the lovelier, okay, I could make some, I just have it set up so
I could hit a button that turns the entire channel off so are we, are we recording now
is it working?
Hold on.
Hello, hello, hello, hello, yeah, okay, good.
So very pleased with this, with this current setup, I'm loving the no lag feature, that's
really, it really makes a difference, you know, I got to be honest, it makes a difference,
not having that.
Looks like we're still going to be moving towards external gear and I have received
hundreds, literally, hundreds of URLs to different portable mixers and there's about
three of them that pretty much do the job of just being portable, being able to add a
sound source and a microphone and then out.
So I could now essentially take my wireless microphone, my iPod and my I River and I could
do, and a mixer, a little mixer and I could do a complete mobile podcast, but of course
it's completely stupid because it should all be contained in one device, this would
just be one device that says here, give me, you know, jam a microphone in here or use
the built-in mic and if you want, you can mix in another line input, so if you want to
hook up an external sound source, but you can also write there from the interface, mix
in and be three.
I mean, it's software, I know it can be done, it's just, you know, I don't think we can,
we can't do it on the iPod because we don't know how to write software for it.
Maybe the Linux guys will get there eventually, but I think it's still quite a ways off,
but that's what we would need and it would be just perfect, you know, if we could do that,
really would.
So I haven't had the opportunity to email everybody back to thank them for all the links
to these portable mixers, there's quite a bit out there and, you know, the more I look
at it, the more I'm convinced that we will definitely be working with, you know, professional
sound gear from music stores like Anderton and Gilford, you know, that's, it's just
where they've got the stuff, they've got most of the stuff we need.
So I was even considering, I think I just said that, you know, buying an external effects
bank, I don't know, I'm just going to play around.
I really want to, you know, just get the best sound possible and I love the, the lavalier
microphone because it does give you a lot more ambience of the room, which I think a lot of
people like, you know, if you, probably just a shut up for a second here and I can actually
crank up the volume, you can even hear the TV downstairs, I would so loud know that my
mic is almost getting feet, I have a feedback on my ear buds, anyway, okay, so we're back.
Okay, so I did the mixers, oh, you were say today article, actually I should grab that,
we can talk about it and now that I'm not recording on the Mac itself, that's going to be a lot
easier. Because the processor isn't so overloaded that I can almost, I can just probably
end up with it in no life. I can use my, my browser, nothing slowing down and it's all just
happily recording away on the I River IFP 799. So the, what does it, music fans reach for the
stars? It's a pretty long article, but I guess kind of the gist of it is that what's happening
online and what's happening through file sharing and what's happening through, you know, groups like
what is it, association of music podcasting, the independent music feeds, you know, we've got
accident hash, we've got in some near radio, 300 with a $250 million radio show. I mean, there's
all these different independent outlets and podcasting, of course, is going to really, you know,
grab a hold in that arena that it's becoming more influential than MTV and, you know, kids are
making decisions on what they want to buy based upon different recommendations, you know, it's not,
it's not just the traditional channels, so there's a lot going on here, I'm really excited about that
because I'm pretty sure in the new venture, I've been telling you a bit about, that's one of the things
that I really look forward to, is helping people like, like the listidious bitty, you know, it's
perfect and I've, I've already been kind of doing some of that with them, you know, they're going
to be going out on tour soon. I actually did a South, was at SWSX, that's where they are right now
and they're doing their podcast and they're selling music through their, you know, which they're
retaining, you know, a large portion of the direct revenue. I mean, it's, it's really a good system.
We're getting to something here and, and, and mainstream media is starting to take notice,
which I guess is something they should be doing, so I'm just pretty, pretty jazzed about all that.
So you got an email here from Eric, Eric says, hey man, just curious, what exactly you do?
I just got into podcasting, you've heard that heard about you, so I've been listening lately,
but what is your daily job or career? I just started listening, can't really figure it out.
I'm on your site right now as well, and I'm trying to see what you do. I think you develop software
I potter, I believe, but just curious. Well, Eric or Eric, it's a CH is the way you spell it, Eric.
Um, well, first of all, thank you. I, uh, it's very, very nice of you to think of me as a software developer.
That's great. Um, my entire claim to fame is the iPodder script, so I think I appreciate it.
But no, I, um, I don't actually, this is all I'm doing right now. I, um, I had a, my previous
company, well, I had a couple companies in between with my previous company in the United States. I sold in
1999 with my partner, Ron Bloom, and, uh, you know, semi retired, although I, I was working on a lot of
similar stuff, actually, the podcasting, but completely in video and, uh, based on job-a-platform.
So what I did then was basically burn a lot of money. I've burned a lot of money in helicopters too.
But, um, you know, since, uh, July or August, um, this is what I've been doing, and I'm a radio geek
from way back. So I've been doing lots of radio, and this is so right up my alley, you know, the first
day I saw an internet connection. I said, ah, that's something we can broadcast over. And it was at the
wired rave awards that I hooked up with Carl Jacob, who I knew, uh, back then he contacted me
he was working at Sun Microsystems. And we actually, uh, started, uh, on ramp, uh, in the very,
very early days together. And he was out in San Francisco and, uh, the servers were in his apartment.
And, uh, I think it was when the 9600, uh, bought modems rolled around, that he, um,
transmitted an audio signal via the PCM codec, uh, from San Francisco to my, um, my home in New Jersey,
where I had a 64K frame relay connection, I believe, um, and it actually worked, you know, it was,
of course it was a single stream and it was really inefficient and it was pumping the bit straight
through, nothing like, you know, what, uh, it will not much later after that. We, uh, saw things like
was it progressive networks, which later became a real audio. Um, and, uh, you know, we were just
thinking back to, uh, to those days and now, you know, look at, look at what's happening. This is just so
incredibly amazing. That's what I said the other day when I realized that I was talking into a
little stick of plastic, like a, the size of a cheese stick, a cheese snack and knowing that after,
you know, a little bit of messing around on a keyboard and, uh, you know, some file transfers and
some clicking of the, the mouse that, uh, all these people would be able to hear this, you know, that's,
uh, that's definitely part of a dream come true. It's really, yeah, it's, uh, I'm digging it.
So anyway, so what am I doing now? Well, I'll tell you one of the things I'm working on,
is I'm working on getting the Gilmore gang back on the air because my weekends have been total
crap without the gang. Um, I'm, um, really, you know, I'm like totally bogged out about this. I've been
talking to Steve Gilmore, um, you know, have also been telling him a bit about our plans. And, uh, so
help me, uh, I want to get the Gilmore gang back on the air very, very, very, very, very quickly.
This is the hit test podcast. Yeah, test podcast featuring the hit test, heard on the daily source
codes. Hey, who are you on? Hold it. All right.
This is the opener of the hit test podcast. I'm working with a weekly podcast featuring an extended
version of the hit test with five intros for you to identify. And of course, I will be talking about
my favorite subjects. And that would be me. So check it out. Hey, y'all, let's dot to know that
J and P.O.L. E.G. doesn't help. And I'll just see you for the next hit test podcast. All right.
Time for Adam Curry to take the hit test. My goodness. I'm already tired.
Well, I Adam, this hit test number 21. Hey, uh, and this is the last time I will mention the number
because it's like it's very interesting for the listeners. Whoa.
What keep you proud? Uh, you're able to identify which hit test it is by looking at the file name.
So that will be enough. All right. This is number one. Okay. Here we go.
Once again. I got it. But I'm about to get ready. Okay. That's talking in your sleep by the romantic.
And this is number two.
Oh, once again. It sounds like a hairband ballads.
Wow. Now you've got me on that one, y'all. I'm definitely stumped. And the final one. Number three.
One more time. Try.
Oh, man.
Y'all. I think you've stumped me. I only got one out of three as far as I know.
Time for the answers. This is answer number one. Okay. That was romantic. That was romantic.
I'm here. The secret facts to keep talking in your sleep.
All right. Let's get to the number two.
Here it is now. And answer number two.
What was Boston? Oh, and a sunny styled Amanda.
Oh, but of course.
Oh, but it's the intro. It's like all our members, the decor. It's a nice, solid, sweet.
Can you read the man?
Okay, not entirely a hairband, so.
And Amanda is number two in today's hit test.
And this is answer number three.
It's an oldie by Sharon Brown.
I specialize in love. Oh, Jesus, you're kidding me. Oh, I never want to pray that.
I love this song.
Yeah, and this is really my kind of music specialized in love. Sharon Brown.
Well, this concludes the hit test for today.
As always, feedback is welcome at histest at gmail.com.
You can find all information about this hit test and the hit test podcast at www.yumpolets.nl
that's gannplt.nl.
Let us see you next time for another edition of the hit test. Bye-bye.
All right, buddy. Thank you very much.
Young Polette with his infamous hit test.
Well, what we're going to talk about. Oh, yes, I want to demonstrate the Skype phone to you.
I ordered this cordless telephone, which you hook up to a PC. Of course, it only works on a PC.
So I hook it up downstairs on the Christina's PC. And basically, it gives you a Skype,
it hooks up to your Skype account. So you have to be online with Skype.
And when someone calls you, it rings like a telephone. You pick it up and you use it like a telephone.
Which is just really fucking cool. And if you use it to call out, then you can go to the
phone book and it shows you all of your contacts that are online. You can scroll through and just hit
the dial button and it'll call them. Or you of course can use Skype out. So I immediately set
Patricia up with a Skype out account. And now she's calling all over the world that these wonderful
rates, which is a penny and a half per minute, which is just unbelievable. I mean, that price is
that's cheap. That's really dirt cheap. And now she's hooking up her sister's getting hooked up.
And once she's got Skype installed and all working, then we send her one of these Skype phones.
And then it can just basically call like they're using a telephone. And with this particular model,
you can plug it into the regular phone line. And you can choose which phone line you want to use,
and it'll ring for both for both incoming calls. So I'm telling you, man, Skype is going to be the
phone company. It's just amazing. I want to demo this to you. So how should I do this?
Well, first link, I'll tell you what, why don't I call downstairs, Christina's probably on the phone.
So let's just listen to the quality of it. Okay, I'm hijacking Skype now. And I'm going to ask,
this of course is a big, I'm going to ask Christina to come upstairs with the extension. You never know if a
teenager will do that, right? But let's see. So it should be ringing. Oh, it was ringing.
Hello. Hey, Sparky. Hey, Dad. Hey, I'm doing a podcast. I wanted to test the Skype phone.
Oh, what works. Yeah. Well, can you do me a humongous favor? Sure. Would you mind coming
upstairs and bringing the handset with you? Why? Well, so I can demo it. I want to let people here
the ring. All right. Hey, Dad. What do I have a whole bunch of people on my Skype list with the name
Gothenett? Uh, with the name Gothenett? On your Skype list? That's Mom's Skype list.
Yeah, I have no idea. Oh, my God. The name Gothenett? All these jeans and stuff in it.
I don't know. I'll take a look later, but you can just close that window. That should just be closed.
All right. Bring the phone. You want me to bring the whole thing with the plug?
No, no, no. Just you're on the phone now, right? Yeah. Yeah, no, just bring the phone up. Just walk
up and talk to me while you're walking. So I can hear you walk up the stairs. The sound is great. It's just like
a real phone, isn't it? Yep. Well, it kind of sounds like you're in a cave, like the back cave.
But it's all right. Oh, is this any better? Wait a minute. You're listening to me. I don't even know
how you're hearing me. Who knows? Oh, here you are. Hello. Hi. Oh, there's a little delay, isn't there?
Yeah. Yeah, hold on one second. Hang up. Okay, hang up. Okay. Now, I want to call you just so people can hear the ring.
Hold on. Take up. What's up? Cool. Okay. That was a thanks baby. All right.
I love you. Oh, can you close my door? My gosh. Thanks. Five. There you go. The Skype phone.
Inaction sounded pretty damn hot, didn't it? And, you know, the Skype out feature is just it's great. I love it.
And I haven't looked at the book yet, but I'm sure there's a way to even do the conference calls. And
oh, man, it's just so smart. And, you know, these guys are just cell and phone minutes. You know,
it's working. I totally, totally dig it. Hey, you got another mashup lined up for you. It's actually,
it's not a, it's not really a mashup more than like, well, it is, it is kind of a mashup. You know what?
It's not just a mashup. It's the king.
Give me another start.
Hey, all of a sudden, I mean, there are three, five, six, three.
Oh, man.
zenia.
Oh, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good
good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, very good, really good, good, good, good, best, I have love love, not only good, good, good line, good, good, good, good, good, good, my good, good, good, go, good, mmm, good, really good, great, good,
You deserve a chance, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, deserve it
You deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, you deserve it, deserve it, you deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve it, deserve
So, no more What today ?? I have a beauty sauna on the side ofup on my foot. I have something a little better to do taking pictures of ashore doubts fixing my rummaging around here Actually, I'm actually building another, just showing another source code?
So, anyway I've Newton Skype Sorry about that Right, you know what tomorrow? remember, Friday
I've been looking forward to the weekend And we've got some fun stuffed plans
And see, I think that we may even do another Patricia Pi podcast, I've kind of been
hinting that people like it so much, and I haven't received a couple of songs through
email MP3s and a like of stuff that Patricia has done in the past, and I think we'll
be a big surprise to her.
What's going on?
Yes.
The joke contains an old content that is brought to you by the letter 8.
This is the whip report.
Now, why am I going to play this for you?
I thought I couldn't sound welcome to the show.
This is the whip report on your host, my name is Whiplash.
Coming up later, an exclusive whip report first interview with Murphy, and how he
was about having his own law.
The interview goes okay, but if something can go wrong, it probably will.
Later, we'll chat with a man who has convinced that two poxikours are Jewish holiday.
First, at these top stories.
You should listen to that, the whip report.
Find it on ipotter.org.
Hey, by the way, the directory, I saw that Marcus was working on the static rendering, so the
directory is going to be a lot faster now.
Just about every single node has now been distributed, which is just great.
I'm still working on getting some people's opml working a little bit better, and pretty soon
I'm going to put in some interesting stuff for the node managers.
I'm going to give you a couple more tools to work with, so you can really build out the node.
And there's also going to be some money making opportunities.
But that's for another podcast, my friends.
I'm going to leave you with that thought.
I'm going to go downstairs, 12 past 7 p.m., see if I can help out with dinner.
And I will be back tomorrow to talk to you about the shoot.
Whatever comes to mind, I guess.
I'm going to come inside of acurry.com.
Of course, you can leave a comment on my weblog www.curry.com.
If you're looking for the newest show, all the archives, and the podcast feed for daily source code,
go to dailysourcecode.com.
Everybody I'll see tomorrow, take care.
Thanks for watching.