Delta's year at Charlie 228.
Quick and time!
DJ, are you done?
Your DJ has only just begun.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do you know what?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky grip.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Fantastic!
It's August 25, 2005.
It's the Daily Source Code.
And good afternoon everybody.
How are you doing?
Thursday.
We've done a show every single day.
This week, it truly is the Daily Source Code.
I'm amazed.
I'm just amazed.
It is about 4.35 in the afternoon.
Coming to you directly from Curry Cottage.
It's the Daily Source Code.
And this is the first official show in the podcast complex.
That's right.
This morning Mark and I think Stewart is his name.
His accomplice, his assistant came on over.
And we removed the home build podcast complex
from the garage, moved it all the way up to the bedroom studio.
And I spent most of the morning reconnecting, reconfiguring,
re-adjusting and taking pictures of my handy work.
It is absolutely phenomenally beautiful.
And it works.
It's so functional.
It's ergonomic.
It's systematic.
It's been kind of a weird day today.
It started off reasonably nice,
but wet.
And it just went really ugly.
And now it's like, look out the window.
A lot of wind.
But sunshine.
Alrighty.
We have quite, I always say that, don't right?
We have a lot to talk about.
But it really is true.
I got to cram all this into 30 or 40 minutes.
And I've got a couple minutes.
I'm going to see how long is this piece of the Zedcast.
I'm going to be check.
What is it?
Three minutes and fifty.
Six seconds of the Zedcast.
It's in counters, pod save music from Matthew Ebel.
And plenty of promos.
And we're talking about some geek stuff like GPS, GPS files.
And have a mashup for you.
See, where did I pull this one off of?
I think this was something that Peter Fadden put on the series show.
It's toxic shack.
Gelat on the source code.
See, you've paid it tight.
I can sign as a vote.
That's it.
Love, shine, there's a little place where you can get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get to get
get to get to get to get done it's that one
run
In
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, Yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah
Shut up, fuck it up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up,
shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut off, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up,
Jack happened in here, finally everything's all put together,
and I could not be happier with the way things have turned out.
Still kind of tweaking the sound a little bit.
And actually, I knew the sound was good enough
to use for today's source code,
because I've been testing back and forth with PW Fenton,
of Digital Flotsom, he produces the serious shows,
and we work a lot on sound stuff together.
And he sent me an email, he said,
oh man, it's sounding great now.
So that's good enough, because he uses a silo scopes
and stuff to check frequency ranges.
But I like to drive, drive everything really loud,
compressors and allimitors,
and chaining those together to achieve a certain kind of sound.
And I think I've got it.
So anyway, so finally the podcast complex is complete.
It's upstairs in the bedroom studio,
and I've got the Yamaha Professional Audio Workstation AW16G
right in the front, I've got my power book, my G4 power book
over on the right, and then on the upper shelf,
on the left, I've got the stereo valve processor,
on the right now, I've put the crap-lit,
which is, and it wasn't planned that way,
but it turns out perfectly,
because I can put the crap-lit up on this top shelf,
swivel the screen, because of course,
it normally, the screen can turn around
and fold over into a tablet.
So now I can actually read stuff off of that screen,
and I said, I level, and I don't have to use the Macintosh,
because it's conveniently located down on the right-hand lower side.
So it's just perfect, and I love standing up while I'm working.
I really do, and maybe I'll improve my posture
even one of these days.
So we're still tweaking the little bits here,
but I'm really, really happy with how it's working out so far.
Okay, what was I gonna talk to you about?
Oh, it looks like I'm not gonna go back to San Francisco.
Just yeah, it'll probably be,
we're gonna go to New York first,
then to Chicago, lots of advertising agencies
to talk to, lots of people are very interested.
I'm gonna do some interviews while we're in New York.
Got some of the phoneers tomorrow, actually.
Financial times, and parade magazine,
but I found, parade magazine is huge, by the way.
It's like one of the biggest magazines in the United States,
so, extremely excited about that.
Then we'll go to San Francisco,
and hopefully Patricia really got a lot of stuff together
for the Curry Condo in San Fran.
But we're still waiting for an order from JC Penny,
and we ordered that when we were in New York,
because that's like almost two weeks ago,
and I knew that one item had to transfer from another warehouse.
So I knew that it could last more than one business week,
but then I didn't hear anything for another week,
and then finally, an email shows up,
and there's no like, sorry, we're late,
or your order is ready to ship, or any pleasant news.
It was just to make sure that there's no fault
with your credit card, provide us with the billing details.
I'm like, what the fuck, you know?
I don't know, what's wrong with JC Penny?
I mean, they used to be really good with online ordering,
and now this.
That's just American credit cards in general.
There's, I don't know, it's whenever I use a European card,
talked about this before, it's never a problem.
The credit card company or bank never wants to double check anything,
and there's also no fraud ever on those.
Oh, knock on wood, which, of course, is exactly
what the podcast complex is made of.
Kids don't touch that time,
because now it's time for the Bobby Bucket Show.
Hello readers, it's Bobby Bucket with the Bobby Bucket Show,
a podcast for kids, parents, and readers of all ages.
If you love reading, then you're gonna love our show
because each week, we explore the best in children
in young readers' literature,
and we have a special section just for parents
to support their child's reading.
And we talk about things good readers do
in a fun and educational way.
And here for a sneak peek is my good friend,
Madam literatus, talking about the reading strategy
of making predictions.
Hello, it is Madam literatus.
Every so often read a stop and make predictions
or guesses about what is called
happen next in the story, they do this by using
both pictures and text and even connections
made by personal experience or text to text connections
or text to word connections.
You see good readers do not just see back in past
every way for me to come to them.
No, as they read their custody making meaning
by making predictions readers are playing around
with that meaning readers make those predictions
they read a little more and then they find out
if their predictions were correct or not,
if they weren't, they could sell them.
And they make new predictions.
So by making predictions, you're doing the following
with your mind.
You are connecting prior knowledge and experience,
focusing about the actual words in the story
and trying to figure out things by filling in gaps
in the author's writing.
Kind of like you are reading between the lines
or trying to read the writers' thoughts instead of just her words.
For the body bucket show, this is Madam literatus.
So come on over to BobbyBucket.com, here about great books,
great reading strategies, and celebrate reading
with books, music, author interviews, and more.
Television, we don't need no stinky television, we got a book.
Hi, Joe.
Content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
The actual real insider space is one place you can go.
It's one crush.
Join in and subscribe to the front seat feed
on the digital domain.
With the night cast, the WWE dot K&Y-T-H-T-W-I-C,
not come.
With the night cast, the everyday adventures of a modern-day
technocrat on the edge of real and cyberspace.
With the podcast for the Cybersitizen with digital views on tech,
cult, sci-fi, and the daily drag.
Point your pod catcher at our feed and learn how to chew tech
into your way of life.
The night cast upgrade from week to technocrat
and check us out at www.K&Y-G-H-T-W-I-S-E dot com.
I gotta tell you, I really love promos.
That's so cool.
So, you know, and then I hear these promos
I select them from a whole bunch of, well, I've got like,
PW and I have kind of like a system work to work out.
And then I hear them on the show and like, you know,
that sounds like a good show.
I want to subscribe to that.
It really does work.
Keep those promos coming.
Submit at podshow.com
and make sure you put the ID3 tags in.
Okay.
Please.
And don't name it promo.
Dot MP3.
Um,
if for the serious show on serious satellite radio,
every day we do four hours of podcasts
and podsafe music and mashups.
But put out and promos, of course.
But always, at least one featured podcast an hour.
And you can send all those, you know,
if you wanted to be played on serious,
send it off to submit at podshow.com.
PWFend and does a lot of the sifting,
well, does all the sifting through that, basically.
Um, and is always listening to new stuff coming out.
And so once in a while,
I'll stumble across something,
which, of course, I'll put on the podshow
and then, and then he'll alert me to it.
Because of course, I'm going to announce it.
And so I'll listen to this podcast before I even talk about it on the show.
And there's this podcast called The Zedcast.
This is episode number seven of The Zedcast.
And it's titled Close Encounters.
So, you know, Close Encounters with the third kind.
And there's a whole set up to it,
which I'm not going to play.
I'm going to play the part though,
when the aliens land.
Because, well, I'm not going to tell you why,
but it's, uh, it did have me laughing for sure.
Whoa!
Ladies and gentlemen, the sky is just turned up really a chain of fusion.
A giant mother ship.
He's coming out of the clouds.
It's enormous.
There are hatches opening on the bottom of the ship.
And there's pod-like crafts shooting everywhere.
It's unbelievable.
Please, gentlemen, I think we've made contact.
One of the pods is slanting right in front of us.
There's a door on the front that's opening.
And, oh, there's a beautiful bathing light.
And, and a beam.
So much humanoid, but it seems to be floating above the ground.
And, and behind him, several dozen just like him.
They seem pretty enough.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm going to attempt to get close enough
to these beings to try and communicate with them.
Hello.
Welcome to Canada.
We are people of Earth.
We mean you no harm.
Oh, I don't know if they could understand me.
People of Earth.
We have intercepted your transmissions.
We have analyzed your dialects.
And can speak to you in your own language.
How's it going, eh?
Good.
You said you intercepted transmissions.
Was that from our radio telescopes?
No.
We do not listen to the radio.
Was it television transmissions?
No.
Television is boring.
There's never anything good on me.
Uh, what kind of transmissions?
We have been tuning into your hottest sphere.
Oh, we are listening to podcasts.
That's great.
We are from the planet Zed.
And we have been transmitting our Zedcast to you for many months.
Oh, yeah, the Zedcast with Bruce Murray, right?
Yeah, but that's like comedy skits.
And he does storytelling and play some music.
Yes, you must decode it.
If you play it normally, it sounds like this.
Hi, everybody.
And welcome to the Zedcast.
But run it backwards.
And it is people of Earth.
We need our warning.
Well, why have you come to this planet?
We come to speak to the one called Adam.
Adam and Eve.
No, later than that.
Adam and Goyan.
Keep going.
Uh, Brian Adams.
Okay, this is getting annoying.
I will give you a hand.
Today, are you guys amazing?
Yeah.
Oh, Adam Curry from Podcho.
Yes, that is him.
We need his daily source code to program our events from
Unications.
Please direct us to Curry Cottage.
Oh, well, uh, this is Nova Scotia in Canada.
Uh, he lives in Guilford in the UK.
That's like 1,500 kilometers across the Atlantic Ocean.
No problem.
We will be there in 20 seconds.
20 seconds.
That's amazing.
How do you do that?
I have 16 million keypaps of spacecrafts throughout my ass.
And the next generation of interstellar communications in my ears.
So I guess you're flying into the future.
No.
I've been there.
It's not all that's cracked up to me.
Well, good luck on your journey.
Thanks for visiting.
No problem.
Stay subscribed.
Okay.
Set a love home fries.
Wow.
What was that?
You're your photon engine starting up?
No.
That's insane.
Oh, man.
I love it.
That's a great episode.
The Zedcast.
And if you want to know where to find the Zedcast.
Or anything else about anything you hear on the daily source code.
Just go to dailysourcecode.com.
Check the show notes.
Or the show.
The show notes are also always copied at www.curry.com.
That's also where I post the picture of the podcast complex.
So you can check that out as well.
And let's see.
Before I forget yesterday, pod save music.
I played Jennifer Halane.
And that's what's so cool about playing pod save music on a podcast.
Usually, I'll get an email the same day from the artist themselves saying,
Hey, thanks for playing the song.
And you know, always get to get to know a little bit more about him.
And it was actually Jennifer's brother who signed her up at pod save music network.com.
She'd heard about garageband.com.
But didn't know about PMN yet.
And this is actually something that's really true.
But most musicians, and not Jennifer, by the way.
Most musicians are just so lazy.
They don't want to go out and promote across all these websites.
Now, so they're probably writing songs and too busy with doing music.
So this is what you see happening a lot.
Barry Coral's brother also promotes her on the net.
So Jennifer wanted me to say hi to her brother.
And point out that he also has a podcast at frankwit.com.
So I'll put that in the show notes as well.
And I've been geeking out on this GPS stuff with the GPX files.
So, you know, I've been basically tracking my my flying.
And you can load those files into Google Earth.
And you can actually fly the entire route.
And there's also not quite sure how to do it.
But if you go to jeepster.com, that's G-E-E-P-S-T-E-R
or Gulf-Eko-Eko-Papa-Shere-Tango-Eko-Romio.com,
that's Koso's, one of Koso's many websites.
He's loaded both the most recent track,
where I flew to the Netherlands and back.
He loaded that into a Google map.
And he also did one for my USA trip.
And it's cool.
You can actually see the entire flight path that we took.
I really liked the one that we did on,
we went to Rotterdam Airport.
And then to mid-Azailum.
Because you can actually see the touch-and-go circuits that we were flying.
And they're almost all exactly the same.
It's really cool.
And although at Rotterdam Airport,
at the jet center, we parked to drop Patricia's parents off.
And we waited for, I don't know,
we had a couple of coffee or something before we left.
You'll see the track if you,
and I'll put links to all this in the show notes.
You'll see it looks like we were bugging all over the place.
But I think what happened is I just left the GPS unit on.
So it was recording every 15 or 30 seconds, I think.
And as I mentioned, it was IFR weather.
So the ceiling was like 300, 400 feet.
It was completely blocked out.
So I have a feeling that the GPS unit couldn't get
more than a couple of satellites.
And it was just every 15 seconds picking up a new signal.
And that's probably the inaccuracy,
if you're not a moving object, if you're just standing still.
And then, of course, it amazes me how those smart bombs hit their mark.
Anyway, so I was going through the Gmail,
and I found a piece of audio feedback from a couple of weeks ago.
But it's about the same stuff that we're talking about now
about these Google Maps and GPS files and how to integrate those
with podcasts and with pictures.
And I got this piece of audio feedback, which, as I said,
is a little late in being on the show,
but better late than never.
And it's still appropriate to the topic.
Hey Adam, this is JT from the FMlogicBox podcast.
And I was just listening to your latest daily source code
and heard that you were wondering about GPS and how to tie that
into MP3s and how to synchronize the video or the photograph,
and things like that.
Well, you may want to investigate the dot MP4 audio format.
I was just talking about that in my latest podcast,
number 22, and that should be coming out tonight
for August 5th.
But in any case, I didn't go into any depth on how to use that,
but, and I don't really know.
But it apparently allows you to add avatars and 2D,
and 3D animation and certainly still photos,
because it is the video format of the M4A file format
that is used in iTunes and for iPods,
and it's a higher compression ratio than the MP3 format.
But that would most certainly allow you to synchronize the,
pictures with the audio.
I think it would have to.
So I know that you didn't want to develop that on your own,
but you may want to pass that along to whoever you do want to do the development for you.
And I hope that helps, and thanks again for all of your daily source codes.
I listen to them every time they come out, as soon as they come out.
But I don't pain your sight every five seconds,
time to get them.
I just wait for it to be delivered.
So in any case, have a great day, and I hope you can get that working,
because I'm really curious about that myself.
Okay, so yeah, well thank you, JT.
I've got it figured out.
I know exactly what this should be and how it should work.
And if I liked what JT was saying, you know,
whoever's going to develop that for you.
All right.
So I do know that what I have noticed when you provide data,
when you are providing a stream of cool data like this flying data,
which definitely is, you know, it's interesting because, you know,
it's, you know, I was flying, you know,
and you can see certain things you wouldn't see when driving.
Developers do like that.
And it does get people's juices flowing.
So I'm going to continue to just, you know, make GPS data available.
I have, of course, had to get off my ass and out of the cottage to go to go get some data.
But I know, but the MDA should be able to do this.
Here's how I think it should work.
In essence, you want your one device and I'm going to say it's my MDA telefilm
because it has all this stuff built into it.
And you, you have a little application and you start the application
and it's doing a number of things.
The first thing is doing is it's recording audio.
And it's, it's recording audio, you know,
just like you would first sound seeing tour and the MDA can do that.
So, of course, you'd want to have an external microphone plugged in.
Please, that's not even necessary.
It's just recording audio.
At the same time, it's recording the GPS data.
That's coming out of the Bluetooth GPS receiver.
And it's basically, I don't know if it's writing
that was all to one file or not, but that's irrelevant.
So as let's say, I'm, I'm doing one of my trips.
So we're flying along and then, you know,
I'd just be narrating like any, but the hell is that?
Someone else's flying along.
I'd just be narrating like, you know,
like any other sound seeing tour or not,
doesn't matter because, you know, there's no penalty for the recording.
Then if at any point, I see something that's of interest,
I can take the MDA and snap a picture.
I was like, oh, I needed a sound effect.
I didn't have one.
I got these cool sound effects working on the Yamaha by the way.
Okay, so I'd take a picture.
Man, that sucks.
I like that one, that's a good one.
So I'd take a picture and it tags that somehow in this application.
So when I go back and I'm back home,
I synchronize my MDA.
It takes this data and what it should be creating is a Google map
where whenever a picture was taken,
there's a little flag so you can mouse over that
and then see the picture.
And of course, it could be some extra data entered there.
But at any point that in the path,
you should be able to click on the path and hear the audio
that was recorded at that point.
You see, because then you can,
it's almost like a museum tour and you can kind of determine
where you want to go in or want to go out.
Anyway, so I'm not quite sure how that would work
and I'm not quite sure what the viewer is.
It sounds almost like what have to be something
and flashed to make it work.
But I can totally see that being very interesting
and very compelling.
I can see business cases for that.
So if you develop up for Windows Mobile,
give it a shot.
Hello, Adam.
My name is Mark Anderson,
and I'm the host of a podcast called Shakespeare Upon iPod.
As the name suggests,
this podcast is about Shakespeare,
but there's a twist here.
There's been an undercurrent of scholarships
since the 1920s, in fact,
that has been looking at the life and troubled times
of a Elizabethan court poet playwright named Edward Devere,
who, more and more evidence suggests,
wrote under the pen name William Shakespeare.
Devere led an amazing and epic and very Shakespearean life.
He got into an interfamily war between his family
and his mistress's family,
regular Elizabethan monogues and capilets.
Devere spent a year touring France and Italy,
visiting the locations where many Shakespeare plays
with later be said.
Devere's sister was a temperamental fireball
who was wooed by a swashbuckler,
named Paragon Birdie,
and this courtship is spoofed
in Shakespeare's Taming of the Shrew.
Devere had his own problems with anger management, too,
when Devere was returning from Italy,
one of his servants are really ego.
Whispered hints of Devere's wife's infidelity
into Devere's ear.
This marital strife was played out throughout the Shakespeare canon
in plays such as a fellow,
much to do about nothing,
the Witter's Tale, and a number of others.
The list goes on and on,
of the astonishing parallels between Devere's life
and the storylines in the Shakespeare canon.
It just takes one shift of focus,
away from Stratford upon Avon,
and toward Edward Devere,
to reveal the astonishing layers of autobiography
to be found in Shakespeare.
The reason it hasn't been recognized before
is that people have for centuries been looking
at the wrong guy,
an entrepreneur and actor
from Stratford upon Avon.
The Shakespeare upon iPod podcasts
have been adapted from a biography of Devere
that I've written,
and that Gotham Books will be publishing
on August 8th.
The biography has titled Shakespeare by another name,
the life of Edward Devere Earl of Oxford,
the man who was Shakespeare.
Music fans may be interested to note
that one of the producers of Shakespeare upon iPod
is Chris Collingwood of the Power Pop Band
Fountains of Wayne.
So, now that the book is out,
I'm going to be repodcasting
the whole Shakespeare upon iPod series.
That's all nine episodes
from August through October,
starting with episode one on August 13th.
To hear Shakespeare upon iPod,
go to the podcast section of the iTunes music store
and do a keyword search for Shakespeare.
Or, just check out my book
and my podcast website
at Shakespeare by anothername.com.
That's Shakespeare by anothername.com.
On Show.com,
makes no claims regarding the quality
of its pod shows
or the sanity of its producers.
Listen at your own risk.
Hi, this is Jeff from podcastshuffle.com
telling you about the podcast shuffle show.
You know,
I was going to talk a lot about
what's the podcast shuffle show
but I think you should hear
from one of our listeners,
Bob Hayes from MotoGPOD.
He sums it up pretty good.
I finally got around
to subscribing to the actual podcast
in iTunes last week.
And it's pretty darn entertaining.
It's similar to Adam Curry's pod finder show
except that it has this great
indie feel to it
that I think I like it so much better.
It's not like it's amateur
or bad or anything.
But it just has more
it's more like
what I sort of think a true podcast should sound like.
Thanks Bob.
You can head over to podcastshuffle.com
and subscribe to the show
or you can find it in iTunes
by searching for podcast shuffle show.
Thanks for subscribing,
and I hope you listen in.
Oh.
Well,
harsh mind mellow.
It's like a daily source of code.
Like no,
it wasn't as like pod finder.
Only better.
All right.
Thank you.
Let's see,
what's the time?
32.
Okay.
Well, I'd say we have
to do some pod safe music.
Right?
Oh, that's right.
I have one more thing that I wanted to play for you.
And this is from Christopher Penn from the financial aid pod cast
who's his audio feedback is really nice.
It's almost like he sent me
pod cast that are audio feedback.
And the title of his message here was
the million listener march.
Of course, that got my attention when I saw that in the Gmail.
And I listened to what he's saying
and he's absolutely right.
There's an important event about to happen.
Or actually he's going to happen over the course of the next few weeks.
And very important as it pertains to pod casting.
Hey, and I'm Christopher,
the financial aid pod cast with some audio feedback
about the hundred million listeners march.
The revolution may be on,
but the revolution needs troops right now.
There's an army of millions moving into place.
And the next four weeks will determine
whether that army becomes slaves
to the big record companies,
whether they join the pod casting revolution.
That army is the army of millions of college students who have been away
away for the summer, away from ubiquitous broadband
and iTunes upgrades.
As they move in, they come back to school.
Pod castors have the chance to capture their hearts,
minds, and especially their ears.
In the times in school that out the maze,
so much has happened.
Things like iTunes, 4.9,
Hot City, Music Network.
Bruce Box said somebody heard the call.
Well, here's the call of the pod castors everywhere.
Get the word out to college students everywhere,
as they come back to school.
Tell them about pod safe music about pod cast,
about the revolution.
Get them involved.
If you're a pod castor, reach out and ask college students
in your audience to spread the word.
If you're a college student, spread the word to everyone you know.
College radio is ripe for music from the pod safe music network.
And college radio stations are always a needed great program.
Pod castor can fit the bill just as well,
on terrestrial college radio stations as online.
Finally, let the college students know that pod cast
isn't one way street.
Most students have the latest and greatest hardware
and software for school,
and garage vanda cast blaster,
only a couple of flicks away.
Point new pod guestors to podcastalley.com.
HotGest411.com.
And indiepodder.org.
Now you've heard the call.
Enjoying the revolution, bring your friends.
Thanks a lot out of.
Keep a great work as always.
Hopefully, in the formal weeks,
we'll have millions of new listeners.
This is Chris from the financial aid pod cast at
financialandpodcast.com.
Alright, Chris.
Thank you very much.
And you're so absolutely dead right on about that.
Millions of college kids
who'll be hooking up their PCs,
they'll be getting their high performance
band with together.
And indeed, podcaster perfect content
for college radio stations.
So that's right.
Keep them informed.
Keep wanting them towards all the cool places
to find out about pod casting.
Pod safe music now.
Matthew Ebel, Sally went down.
Got hit by a train.
Sally went down.
When I see my nut to the half-layer now
What's good like her gonna do?
Sattin' never made it to the road
Never saw the night never even heard the train coming
Sattin' I went walked on the track
Never where the rails took and never thought the love back
Sattin' not that she was doing right
But she went home early
But she never saw the night never heard the train coming
And landed here during the back
Sattin' never went down
Sattin' went down
Sattin' never went home early
At the scene before her
Keepin' down, walkin' on the track
Maybe they would just ignore her
But she kept her head down, she kept her head down, she kept her head down, she kept her head down
She didn't listen to the man who blocked her
Salade
No, no, no, no
Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Sal
Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salat, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade, Salade
Subscribed for tuning in and for bearing witness to my gushing over my wonderful set up
And let me know if it's sounding okay for you. I had to up the bit rate yesterday's bit rate got on messed up
Ah, there can be so many problems in the chain
Okay, so
40 minutes fantastic and
And so it's 515 now. The office in San Francisco is opened are two of my days about to be
It's so much fun to be too loud. We're still a little bit jet lag right away
We've been going to bed in two three block in the morning and of course
We would there's always been a reason to get up at nine so
We're pretty beat
It's almost time to go back
If you got a promo for your show that you'd like me to feature on the daily source code or on the serious pod show
Or in the pod finders in the office of mid and podshow.com
And you can always send audio feedback to Adam and curry.com
Please put your MP3 file up on a server somewhere and send me the link so I could stay below the
98%
My Gmail inbox
Daily source code.com is where you can find the podcast feed and the latest episode of this particular podcast
And my web log is www.curry.com tomorrow. Thank God it's Friday edition of your daily source code
I'll talk to you then bye bye
Show podcast stick it in your ear