Transmidders, we don't need no stinking transmemines.
Fantastic with Adam Curry.
Welcome to the daily source code for Friday.
And it's Friday, so you know what that means, right?
Now if you brought to yourself, yes, I know what that means.
It's Patricia waving at me.
Then, uh, just a full of shit because you don't have to do anything special on Friday.
Today we're doing a sound scene tour.
That's right.
Popular demand since we did that in Miami.
I'm sorry, whoop.
Did I actually say Miami?
Of course meant to say Wolf and South Beach.
Sorry about the crack and sound there.
Oh, oh shit.
Getting on my wires out of the car into my bag.
As we're going to take a little trip down to the town to the lovely town of a guilt-foot.
Which you already figured out, right?
Hold on.
Just putting all my...
Crap in.
Bye, love you.
She's laughing at me.
As usual.
Floughing and her silly ass husband doing silly ass shit.
Oh man, the plug are my...
Shoot, they're really sucking now.
The plug on my...
I River where I have the microphone plugged in is crackling.
Whoa, sorry about that.
Uh...
That's not good.
Because you whenever I just jostled a plug even a little bit,
it gives that crackling sound.
Let me see, is this...
It's been two minutes already.
Does that make sense?
Uh...
Okay, I'm going to suppose everything's working, okay?
And otherwise...
Well...
You know the consequences.
Of experimental shit.
Oh man, you hear that?
Hate this sound.
What is that coming from?
Maybe that's...
Ooh.
Hold on.
It's from the other side.
Oh.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Okay, hold on.
Let's see if I can fix this, okay?
Well, so how crappy did that sound, eh?
So, okay, it's the...
It is the plug-except that's on the receiving side.
Could I have the...
The wireless transmitter hooked up because of the great quality of the live microphone.
Everyone was real pleased about that when I used it for the south beach walk around.
Okay?
Um, so we are now in Studio A8, which we were only using today as a vehicle,
not as a studio recording device.
In the driveway, at the...
Cottage and we're back and up...
Getting out on our way down to Starbucks.
So, let's see.
Today is Friday.
It's January 14th, 2005.
Um, and as you...
If you heard yesterday's Daily Source Code, then you know that...
There was still no broadband here.
And it's not really easy-nets fault.
Uh...
A little beep for Patricia.
It's not really easy-nets fault.
It's...
It's British Telecom.
It's a surprise surprise.
It's the government run out fit.
It's fucked it up.
Um, and although they are really...
I mean, you can see their system working because I am a business customer, not residential.
Of course, a business customer in a residential area.
At the end of the road, as I was pointed out to me the this morning.
Um, they haven't really done a lot of these types of installations.
They've only been doing them for a year or less than a year.
The LLU, the local loop, unbumbled, which essentially means...
They're selling me.
They said, just selling wire, they're not selling an exchange or anything.
Because the other end of that wire is connected to easy-nets gear at the Gulford Exchange.
And so when something goes wrong in the installation process,
they don't really have all the...
Excuse me, all the bugs worked out yet.
As to where, you know, and how to resolve some of that.
So, as I said yesterday, the only missing piece now is the piece between the curb
and the side of the house where the wire that goes into my office terminates.
Um, we're talking no more than 30 feet.
Probably even less, but, you know, it's like...
Like, they keep talking about a surveyer that has to come out.
So, there's the veggies out of me surveyer, of course, is it?
I'm sure an English phrase in this case that means a guy who does surveyor work or whatever.
So, I just got to throw some wire in the ground and connect with the two ends and we're done.
And I know that easy-nets is already looking at the end of that wire
because it's connected to their gear and the exchange.
So, all they really need to do is, you know, just connect those two bits up
and everything should work.
I have half a mind of doing that myself.
Of course, that.
He's only going to confuse matters more, I'm sure.
So, today, at this morning, another guy showed up from British Telecom.
And he was there to install the line.
And he, basically, was the inside installing guy.
I said, well, you know, that part we got done.
Now, we need the outside installing guy.
So, I said, why don't you pretend that you just did all this?
Even though you didn't, it was already done.
And then, just, you know, put the paperwork through as normal.
Well, of course, it didn't sound like he was going to do that
because he was an independent contractor to British Telecom
and which means that he only gets paid if the work gets done and whatever.
So, fuck it.
I'm on my way to Starbucks.
And we're doing two birds with one stone here,
because we're going to do the Friday podcast, the Daily Source Code.
And we just check and see how we're doing.
Yeah, everything seems to be recording perfectly.
Now, if you were to look down at your iPod or MP3 player,
you would see that we're now six minutes,
18 seconds into the show.
Approximately that is because, of course, before I put the show up,
I have to put my little opening and closer stuff on there.
Just to, you know, make it identifiable.
So, you recognize the power of pure intellect.
So, now I'm on, we're at the top of the hill,
as I'm driving towards the parking spot.
It's actually, it's quite a production to get to Starbucks.
It's not, you can't just drive in a town parking you there.
You have to park and walk and you can't park in the town.
Well, you can park in the town of Guilford,
except you can only park there for 30 minutes at a time.
So, you have to keep running back every 30 minutes,
or risk getting a 60 pound ticket, which is over 100 bucks.
Not worth any podcast, I'd say.
At least not yet.
Okay, we're turning into the, so on the side of the hill,
there's this car park.
It's actually a number of car parks, which are quite good.
And they have signs on the outskirts of town,
telling you how many free spaces there are still left.
But usually when you pull up to the car park,
you have to wait until someone leaves,
and there's maybe a two or three car weight,
most of the time.
I see now that there's, let me see,
others plenty of spots up there.
It was really busy, busy Christmas season,
but I tell you, because we have one of those,
Guilford is one of those really idyllic kind of English towns
with a, with a Quaint High Street,
which, you're cutting that corner to close baby.
Careful, careful.
Ooh, man.
It's lady backing up into a parking spot.
That was very close.
Ooh, okay, you did it.
So basically, everyone from out of town comes to Guilford,
because it's totally, you know,
the Quaint Quality Street experience that you'd expect to see.
It didn't snow, unfortunately,
that would've made it so much better.
Okay, here we are.
You all have to watch out.
Here, I got to take it the other day,
for not being lined up precisely between the lines.
I got a 60 pound ticket,
because I was moved, let me see if I can make sure I'm inside the lines.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't want to fuck that up,
because they're serious about it.
You know what, though?
It gave me a real attitude adjustment.
I certainly paid attention to where I park now
and how I park.
You know, you know, basically,
oh, let me check.
Okay, I'm in line now.
It worked.
See, I don't believe in just little pansy-ass tickets.
If you want to teach someone something like
don't park at the handicapped spot,
make their car fucking explode.
They won't ever do it again.
You know, if it's at $20 fine,
like, I'll risk it, right?
It doesn't work that way.
Okay.
So now,
thank you.
We're going to go get a parking pass.
What?
Or pass, it's basically a ticket all by itself.
So, I am wired up in the same fashion.
I did in South Beach.
I've got the wireless transmitter receiver pair.
Transmitter in the back pocket.
Receiver in the front pocket.
Hooked up to my eye-river recording.
And I could do about 17 hours.
Probably even on the one battery that I have.
Let's see.
Two pounds in there.
They'll take us to 14.
Okay.
Three-thirty is more than enough.
Take it.
I love the way this mic records everything.
You can hear everything.
So, perfectly well.
That's what a lot of people commented on.
I don't think you just do this with any lovely or mic.
I'm not quite sure why this one works so well,
but I recall from when we did our reality TV show,
Adam's family.
How incredibly well it picked up conversations.
Even if one person was wearing the mic,
you could pretty much record an entire conversation with multiple people,
as long as they're more or less in the area.
Okay.
So, what you do is you get this little sticker here,
or the ticket essentially is a sticker.
You put it on the window.
So, you know what time you're coming back,
or what time you've paid till.
And they do check.
Well, yes, they do check.
Okay.
Okay, we're locked.
So, basically halfway down the hill,
that's where the parking lot is,
and I can see most of the town.
And what we're going to do is we're going to walk down,
cut through a little back alley,
and then we have to go through about half the high street.
I think it's just a great name.
You know, I should be living on the high street.
That would be perfect for me.
And then we turn left on the market street
and go into the Starbucks.
I guess what I'll do is I'll take it all the way in,
all the way through the ordering process.
It shouldn't be too busy today.
And then maybe, I don't think that had a couple things
that I wrote down in my show notes.
Let me see what I'm going to say.
And we'll talk about those as we're on our way.
Oh, yes.
If you haven't heard the Canon Squip Show,
which is a dustingmybrain.com,
Ken Clark and Cindy Camelari,
who used to work with me.
I think new ideas in New York.
They're doing a podcast.
I played bits of their show before.
To me, it's outrageously funny
because I know them so well.
And I know a lot of what they're talking about.
I think to, I think the last one they did
would work across the board for anybody.
But they had a special guest on which blew me away.
They had Dave Kendall.
And I know if you remember Dave Kendall.
He did 120 minutes on MTV.
He was really the postmodern guy before,
along before Kennedy came in.
And he was real.
Kennedy was such a fucking poser.
I'm not talking about John F.
by the way, but Kennedy the VJ Kennedy.
I don't know if she's not around anymore.
God knows what she's doing.
I didn't like Kennedy.
She actually, she fucked me up one time.
Really bad.
We were doing an MTV Beach House the first year.
And she had just gotten there.
And we were doing segments on wave runners.
And for some reason, she and I both got teamed up
to do a wave runner segment together.
And she thought it would be really funny
to, while I was doing a segment,
and thus completely unprepared for anything other than,
you know, the relationship to the camera that I was dealing with at the time.
She felt it would be really funny if she ran her wave runner into mine,
which she did, which is really dangerous.
Because, well, firstly, it threw me off the wave runner,
hitting the top of my thigh against the side.
And that has always been a problem area on my body.
It's basically the muscle there got damaged.
Not that it's something really horrible,
but you know, whenever I say,
whenever I, you know, that area is just sensitive still.
And that was, you know, 10 years ago, whatever.
I should have sued the fucking bitch.
Okay, we're now walking past the truck here.
We're on the high street, walking right into the high street, actually.
At the top of the high street is a statue.
I have to be honest, I've never actually read the inscription
to see who it is.
Of course, it's George Abbott, that makes sense.
Archbishop of Canterbury.
He lived from 1562 to 1633.
He was a Gilfordian and the Archbishop of Canterbury, George Abbott, of course.
Quite a scholar.
There's also the George Abbott School,
which is, actually it's the first school we try to get
Kristina into, but it was full.
You believe that?
So what I should do actually today is I should put the header graphic on
Curry.com back up and you'll see the clock of the,
what I have the plane right now is doing all that traveling
and the plane fly by header graphic on the web log.
I'm going to put the Gilford clock back up.
So you know exactly what I'm looking at at this very moment.
It's not too busy on the high street today.
Anyway, let me get back to Dave Kendall for a second.
So Dave, as it turns out, has been producing television shows.
I think it was, what do you say on the show was the fabulous vacation homes?
And he is about to go off for two or three months to Thailand to work for
an NGO, non-governmental organization, helping out people.
But not, not in the tsunami region in the north of Thailand,
Shang Mai, which I've been to.
I've actually been up a little further north Shangri,
which is, well, I sent it as the last town you hit before you go up
to the hill tribes.
I did a documentary there once and visited them.
But Shang Mai is a great town famous night time market in
Shang Mai. You can buy anything you can imagine there.
And it's the nighttime market, which makes it that much more kind of exciting.
I'll tell you what, since we're only 15 minutes into the show.
Why don't I walk instead of going straight to a D-line to Starbucks?
Why don't I walk down a little bit more with you?
So left and right, I'm walking on cobblestones.
And left and right, we've got sidewalk.
And I'll just see some of the shops here.
Give you an idea.
Jigsaw, Karen Millen, Ted Baker, Goldsmith,
It's a jeweler, River Island.
A T-buttoe, Clarks.
What do we have here?
Bennett T.
Moda in Pele.
Lush, fresh handmade cosmetics.
The phones for you, a lot of phones stores, a lot of mobile phones stores.
Mapping and web, another jeweler, DNA, Oasis, House of Fraser.
That's a big one.
It's a famous store.
Thorntons.
We're just book shops.
Sussex stationers, Russell Bromley.
Then of course there's the mechs.
And super drug.
Obviously boots.
The gap.
Lakeland.
Some of these you've got to recognize.
There's the Vodafone Store.
There's the Virgin Mobile Store.
And they're right now at the Angel Posting House.
Which is quite famous.
That's actually the place we stayed if you remember where I discovered that most of this
most of the town itself.
Now we live on Fort City.
Most of the town itself has a Wi-Fi blanketing the area.
And they actually have a Wi-Fi link in there as well.
But the lounge has been closed for the past couple weeks.
So I haven't been able to actually try that as a download and upload spot.
So.
What's that?
What is this?
What's in here?
Yeah.
It's the homeless magazine, right?
There you go, buddy.
It's too.
Thank you very much.
Okay, the homeless magazine, which, say, working, not begging.
There you go.
I like that.
So one pound forty, I gave him two pounds.
And let's see what's in chemical brothers.
One car-wise in there.
Business in Baghdad.
I think I know it could be interesting.
But chemical brothers on the cover of the big issue, which is the homeless magazine.
Well, how many homeless there are in Gilford?
I haven't seen any.
I don't think.
It's the affluent Surrey neighborhood.
We don't have homeless people here called Dennis.
All right.
So anyway, that was a Dave Kendall.
It was just fun to hear him again.
He actually worked at my company for a year or so.
What did we have?
That was before we actually had to go into the service business, which is, or we were still
doing stuff like the Grammy Awards.
And we had a lot of cool cybercasts that we do that we were doing.
Let's walk through them all here.
There's the next upper gallery.
It's what it's called.
So he did something called, what was it?
Was it alternate?
Alternate?
What was alternate is what we called it?
And he was basically producing content.
And it was really good at it.
We just didn't have any real way to capitalize on it at the time, which was really
a shame.
But he, of course, knows the UK.
And so I was listening to this podcast in,
and we were in South Beach.
And then I heard him say,
what the fuck is that?
I'm curry doing gilphid.
It's hard for people to figure out.
That's what I was telling the producer of the CBS Evening News.
He said, what are you doing in gilphid?
Because she'd actually been at the London Bureau for about eight years.
Linda, whose last name I'm not mentioning.
Even though she wants me to.
I want to keep her on the same level with the Donna and share.
So Linda said, what the fuck are you doing in gilphid?
Well, excuse me, did I forget to say that I'm boring?
And I like being anonymous.
And I don't think she really understood.
Okay, we've just successfully walked through the Galleria.
And now we're going to walk back up the hill on the other side of the high street,
which is North Street.
And this is actually where you can park for 30 minutes.
So we'll do as we'll pick up market street here.
To get to Starbucks.
Oh boy, it's great.
Whether it's about three degrees.
Sun is beautiful.
It's just shining.
So the temperature's kind of the same as when I'm used to.
We're Belgium and Antwerp and also in the Netherlands.
But, uh,
simply because a lot more sunshine here.
Of course, when the mist is in here,
it stays for a lot longer because of the way the countryside is laid out.
Mist really has a chance to just sit there and not burn off and not go away,
which is a downer.
If you schedule the helicopter flight at least.
Okay, the markets are actually open today.
I've got about that.
They put a market on the unknowns.
You can have flowers, they have Dutch flowers.
Dutch crescentalums.
Wow, two pounds, 75 per bunch.
You can buy that for a quarter of that in Holland.
Of course, Dutch tulips.
320, three pounds, 20 per bunch.
For 10 stems, man.
Expensive.
Okay.
This is, uh, I can't remember where market street is.
Okay, here's the, I don't know,
at the backside of the house of Fraser, which means.
The market street should be just around the corner.
And this, of course, normally, this is where you can park for 30 minutes,
but forgot, as of Thursday, midnight,
you can't parkly be towed because, well,
they build up the market on all those parking spots.
And it's, it's quaint.
Oh, yeah, every night.
Yeah, someone, I guess they're looking for shop lifters.
That was cool.
They got security guard talking.
I was walking, talking, describing what some kids look like,
who apparently are walking up.
Let's see.
They will get some action.
And again, maybe not.
Here's that store, the fashion store,
FCUK, which, of course,
is one of the more brilliant marketing
moves of the decade.
Because, of course, you just see the F and the K,
and you think, uh, that brand is fuck,
but it's not.
But it works because it's highly recognizable.
Okay, here we are in Market Street.
And there's, no one's allowed to drive here
until, uh, after 6 p.m.
and we're going to go into Starbucks.
And I'm just going to let you,
listen along until I'm upstairs and settle,
then we'll continue talking because I don't want to get confused
and think I'm a complete idiot,
which, of course, I am.
Here we go. We're inside.
Let's see.
There's no line.
Okay.
Hold on.
He is really cool,
that doesn't embarrass us either.
That's great.
Thanks for leaving me.
Hello.
Operational Grande for a here please.
Sorry.
And the answer to that, sir?
No, let me see.
Now, you recommend the proper set of brownies.
You recommend the chocolate-fudge brownies?
I'd have one for that, I'd have one.
Oh, I'll have to have one, then.
If you recommend it, absolutely.
Good sales job.
Just smiled so sweetly.
How could I refuse?
And it's so hot in here coming from outside.
Let's see.
Oh, the CDs for sale here.
Jazz impressions?
You guys like a record store now?
Yes.
How to tell you?
A lot of people keep asking us about some music that we play.
Yeah.
We play on a huge CD.
It's like about 200 songs on it.
They play random.
Yeah.
So they take selections of them and they make CDs at them.
Really?
You're like a big iPod.
Yeah.
There you go.
That's cool.
Great coffee.
And all that jazz.
A reether under her spell.
Jazz impressionists.
Cold train.
Cool.
That's it.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Great.
Oh, the chocolate brownie does look spacious.
I have to say.
Okay.
Over to the pickup area.
I've got to take my coat off real quick.
It's getting hot here.
Okay.
Let's see what's in the big issue.
Besides the chemical brothers.
tsunami.
Soul searching.
Sean Tillman.
Harmar superstar.
Of course.
Oh, that's cool.
This isn't actually pretty good.
This magazine.
Got lots of advertisements.
The condition is this.
Set up as a business.
And I want to give homeless people the chance to make an income.
Campaigns in behalf of homeless people.
It allows homeless people to voice their views and opinions.
To become a vendor.
You must be homeless or vulnerably housed.
Considering my.
Plumbing.
I may be vulnerable.
House.
That's from many people being houses.
One of the first days you're getting off the streets.
Therefore, a vendor needs to continue to sign a big issue.
We may allow them to.
Cool.
This is great.
What a great.
Brigade.
Great.
Great idea.
Chipsy radio station aims to hit the airways.
First in radio station dedicated to gypsies and the travel lifestyle.
Could be up and running by the end of this year.
Great.
Thank you very much.
That sounds like a podcast.
The gypsy and traveling podcast.
Perfect.
Don't see why that would be a radio station.
Doesn't make a hell of a lot of sense.
Have a radio station for people to travel.
Okay.
Put some nutmeg on here.
Yeah, what else do we cinnamon today?
Yeah.
Stick in one of those twigs.
And mush it all up.
Get 8,000 napkins from the dispenser because you know you can't just take one.
Right?
It's one of those metal dispensers that never worked right.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, we're now going up the stairs.
Great.
Lots of space.
Okay, I've successfully scored a seat near the electrical outlet.
Which is kind of like the big thing here.
That's what you got to grab a moment.
So, okay, we've made it up.
And there's a couple of things I wanted to talk to you about before we wind up today's show.
I'm going to get my laptop out.
And of course, my power plug.
So actually, a lot of people are here today.
It's really not busy at all for a typical day at Starbucks.
Maybe only 10 people up here.
That's why 10 people me Bob Dylan on the Starbucks iPod.
Did you hear that?
They're basically selling music because people hear the music they're playing.
Check it out.
Does that sound like podcasting or what?
Switch on there.
So they, you know, whatever, I guess they, they must have some kind of structure to ask about that.
If they have some form of survey.
Hey, I think we're not connecting here.
People.
There we go.
Connected.
Up.
Don't call home on.
See you, this is.
Lee Wilkins.
I'll leave them in the middle of my podcast.
You got to wait, buddy.
Yes, something to say.
I'm sure he's been calling me off and on for the past couple of days.
Okay, so I don't have my team mobile account set up.
I'm not going to make you wait while I do all that.
I did want to.
Whoops.
What happened there?
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
Do my Mac just decide to close down or what the hell?
Come on.
Oh, there we go.
Let's see what I wanted to mention.
Oh, I've got a lot of comments about Andy Hertzfeld.
I've talked about yesterday and maybe I came on a bit too strong.
Lots of people said, well, you know, you're probably right because Andy just told
didn't get it.
But also, they were saying, well, Andy's not like supposed to be completely with it anymore.
He's no longer an engineer inside of Apple.
I didn't want to come across as, you know, he's certainly no idiot.
He's a really smart guy.
And if I apologize if I went a little bit overboard on Andy, you know, on Andy.
Excuse me.
That wasn't nasty.
Another email I got, which was great.
This is from Nightwise.
He's leaving comments on each source code.
I, of course, he says, I hope you get your broadband fixed.
He says, you know, sitting outside in the car by yourself might make your neighbors think the following.
And I just want to share this one with you.
And of course, I'll put it in the show notes.
So, A, I made creepy stalker.
B, I had a fallout with Patricia and I've been kicked out of the house.
C, I am sucking the man that would be breaking my non-smoking pact.
D, a freaking geek that is not allowed to use his laptop in the house.
E, you're watching your region free porn collection.
F, you're on the phone with Madge.
Or E, all of the above and different combinations.
Well, you know what?
Except for the sucking the man, the non-smoking pact.
And the creepy stalker bit, I guess you're right on.
Although I haven't gone the phone with Madge yet.
Oh, fabulous.
And one other thing that I wanted to mention, which is his whoops,
and those that I river, which is a huge deal in the media here right now,
is the Kabbala exposé.
Basically, some undercover documentary teams have been, you know,
exposing this whole Kabbala movement.
This is the religion or the like faith or believing stuff,
spiritual stuff that Madhana has been such a part of,
particularly promoting it.
And you know, they're exposing, you know, all this fiction about it,
you know, this supposed in special water, you know,
comes from, you know, almost literally from the tap.
You know, all the things you would expect from expose,
and it's just like it's making Madhana look really stupid right now.
And I don't know if that's gotten to the stage yet,
but you can certainly expect that.
That's just something I caught last night.
And otherwise shoot, now we're looking forward to the weekend.
Princess is coming sometime this afternoon.
It's Christina's pony or horse.
Luke called me around the around 10 30 this morning.
He was just about to get on the ferry at Cala,
which will take him to Dover and then from Dover.
He drives to Gilford.
He's never driven in the UK.
Certainly not with a trailer with a horse behind it.
And he'll be driving left-hand side.
So we hope that God is with him and he drives safely.
And he'll be with us for the weekend.
And of course, that means we're taking the horse to the stables.
And he and Christina will be training all weekend.
And on Sunday, my sister-in-law and her daughter Ivana Roxy show up.
And they're going to be with us for a week.
So I'm probably going to take the opportunity as we have four chicks in the house.
I will probably sneak off to Amsterdam for a day and back.
Sometime next week, which I'm obviously going to coordinate with any other broad bend.
Work that is being done at the house.
I'm really hoping this works out.
And maybe I have to coordinate it expressly for that.
So I can go get some broad bend, you know.
Book another easy jet trip.
So I can go sit on the big pipe in the bunker.
Which by the way, it looks like we might have some potential buyers for it.
So fingers crossed everybody.
All right, that's about it for me for today.
I hope you enjoyed this little trip down from the cottage to Gilford.
You know, one of these days we'll do it in their first order.
And we'll go from Starbucks back up to the cottage.
Have yourself a great weekend.
Be healthy, be happy.
And I will talk to you on Monday with another daily source code.
Bye-bye.
Let's do the Incernet song because I love ending up with that.
Goodnight Incernet.
Goodnight.