Delta Shara Charley 201
Something remarkable is happening here. Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers
who've managed what you can hear since radio is invented. It's jumping into the hands
of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jar.
Yo DJ!
Your DJ has only just begun.
It is the 28th of June 2005. How you doing everybody?
Welcome to the Daily Source Code. This is the post mega crunch iTunes launch podcast.
Come to you from the lovely courtyard Marianne Hotel in Portland, Oregon.
It's the show that I love to bring to you.
I got to tell you what a day it's been. I am pretty free.
Now, that's for a number of reasons. The first one being, I've been flying all day.
Wow, I couldn't have planned it any better, you know.
We got this big mega crunch of bandwidth with the tens of thousands of new listeners
and subscribers showing up at our door this morning.
And what was I doing while I was concentrating on my flaps, my car heat, my angle of attack,
and all that groovy stuff the pilots have to learn. Because Friday I get my ticket.
Okay, don't have a lot of tunes queued up for you for the show.
Of course, this is another hotel room podcast, which means I'm on the wireless lab.
So you'll hear a little bit of extra room noise about normal.
And I'm using cast blaster, which you'll love this.
Unbeknownst to me during the nomdex keynote speech, which of course was also podcast.
Cast blaster was released.
That's right, there's a public bait and now available.
Just head over to castblaster.com.
Actually, it's pretty interesting because I agreed with Mike.
Cast blaster Mike as we call him around the shop.
It was of course lead developer on the entire project.
So the real test of cast blaster will be to see if I can use this thing in this live environment
because they had the whole idea for doing a daily source code 200 as a part.
Actually, as the keynote, the finishing keynote of nomdex 5.0.
So what you might not have known, if you were at nomdex,
actually had the love Mike clipped to my jacket and that was running into the crap lit through cast blaster.
And just the output coming through the headphones,
Jack was always being fed into the house PA system.
And I was very, very pleased with the results.
It really worked.
And I was able to upload the show just a couple minutes after the keynote.
Because of course, that's almost an automatic process now with cast blaster.
I'm really pleased with the outcome.
I'm very, very happy with what we have right now.
Of course, we're looking forward to implementing a lot more cool stuff in the cast blaster.
Obviously doing something about the graphical look.
Although I'm not displeased with just the standard windows stuff.
What I did know, is the one thing that I need.
And this is something we're going to definitely put on a separate development track.
You heard the daily source code episode number 200.
I, you know, with all the stuff going on on stage,
I couldn't really fade out the tracks that were playing.
So I think I played the mashup and I played some Rob Costlo.
And I just kind of cut it off midstream.
I, you know, to get your mouse over to click the fader and fade it down.
It works when you're kind of in a controlled environment,
but not in a live environment on stage.
So the next obvious thing to do is have a little hardware controller.
Or maybe even better yet.
And that's something I'll talk to Mike about.
Maybe some of the keyboard mappings can be mapped over to the,
to the player slider.
Like maybe use it.
I wonder what happens if I use the arrow key here.
Doesn't, oh my goodness.
Oh my goodness.
It already works.
Okay.
Just discovered something new.
Yeah, let me see if I can hear.
I'll play a bit of Rob Costlo check this out.
So now I can use the down arrow key and it basically fades it all the way down.
I used up arrow key and it fades it up.
That is phenomenal.
Okay.
Well, there you go.
So it's already been fixed.
Didn't even have to ask for anything.
That's great.
Thank you very much, Mike.
So daily source code episode 201.
This is the day that Apple launched iTunes 4.9,
which includes podcast and capabilities.
Wow.
Lots of stuff blew up.
Lots of stuff went wrong.
But at the end of the day, it is literally the end of the day.
It's 17 minutes before 12, before midnight, on the 28th.
I'd say the results are phenomenal.
This morning around 9 o'clock East Coast time,
all of iTunes actually came to its knees.
Now, we had sets and stuff up.
You probably noticed this thing called the podfinder podcast,
which is a co-production that we're doing with Apple.
And of course, all of the podcast featured in that,
we're intended to be hosted on a content delivery network,
which would have been Akamai I believe.
And Apple was going to take care of that.
Oops.
Instead of doing that, they basically pointed everything towards our servers.
Now, we already have sufficient pipe, but nothing.
Nothing at all for the onslaught that we received.
So we slapped on two new servers.
One of the 200 megabits of Dan with an hour kind of handling,
what's happening.
And also right now, it's a little crunchy,
but that's the good news, literally.
And I just looked at some of the stats.
Tens of thousands of new downloaders.
So we'll call those listeners.
And an equal amount of people actually subscribing to the podcast feed.
So I could not be happier with the result.
You know, bring it on.
The 100 million listener march has started.
So I'd love to hear more feedback.
I just had a glance of the email.
Looks like everyone's reasonably happy.
Of course, as all kinds of stuff with their directory.
And are you listed or not in the feeds?
And all this is going to start to shake out over the next couple of,
oh, next couple of days and probably next couple of weeks.
Because this was just people who were downloading iTunes and saying,
hey, I'm going to go.
I want to, you know, install this now and start using it.
But a lot of people won't get the upgraded iTunes until their software update runs.
And of course, they have to decide to install it.
So it'll probably be, I don't know what the run rate is on that for Apple's upgrades.
But it'll probably be another week or two before it's all fleshed out.
So in all, I think very successful because what no one really expected,
certainly not an Apple is the onslaught that podcasting was going to bring.
And it's not just the so-called quote,
indie podcast, which I thought was hilarious.
The Apple makes a distinction between a professional podcast.
There's an indie podcast.
But okay, you know, that's the way they want to call it.
That's fine, you know.
You know, they can call me whatever they want.
We know what we're doing and we know what our mission is.
And boy, do we have some exciting times ahead?
It's all good stuff, home fries.
The CC Chapman would say.
Come on, Rob, hit that last piano note for me.
Thank you.
That's what I was waiting for.
Whew.
Let me see.
What other stuff do we have to talk about?
I guess that's really it.
That's really what everyone is just all over is the Items launch.
Podcast Ali.
I believe by tomorrow will be providing anyone who's basically registered with podcast
Ali in the directory.
We'll be able to have an iTunes compliant feed.
We're working on creating subdomains so that you could have.
You could literally map that, which means there's no lock in.
So you could say, you would want to, for instance,
I could have daily source code dot podcast Ali dot com.
And that could actually be the default iTunes feed for you.
And of course Chris McIntyre over there is working on anything that will,
that'll make it easier for all of us to,
to basically provide our content.
And with this,
comes the very obvious path that we should be choosing as podcasters.
And that,
you
Okay, that was like totally weird.
I got a Skype ping and then all of a sudden just blew out my microphone.
Oh well, hey, that's what you get when you do stuff in a hotel room.
So anyway, the clear path that we have to get on now is,
is a bit torrent, I think,
to start solving these bandwidth issues.
And it's a completely legitimate use of peer-to-peer technology.
And I've been thinking about it.
There is a bit torrent name space.
And I'm not going to do it tonight because I really need to,
to get to bed because there's lots more flying to do tomorrow.
I was, I prepare for my check ride for my fixed wing license on Friday.
But I believe that we need to,
open up a dialogue with the aggregated developers about how to incorporate,
of course most iPodders and podcasters already,
understand bit torrent and already have it implemented.
There's just a couple of things I think we need to do to make that corner turn.
And I'm talking to lots of people.
Doug K from IT conversations has some really smart ideas about that.
And a couple of other podcasters who also are looking at lots and lots of bandwidth to be chewed up.
So that will be coming very, very soon.
And you know what, since it is late night,
we're kind of hanging out.
I'd say, we do a hit test.
We're just taking a hit test.
We're just taking a hit test with help.
We can reach you.
Hey, you guys, with your pilot.
Yeah, I'm this hit test number 45.
Hey buddy.
There's not much time.
So let's start right away.
You know how goes.
This is intro number one.
We're on the...
It's probably a...
Oh yeah.
I'm going to say,
Al steward on the border,
I think. Just off the cuff. And this is number two.
He was born Andrew Gold, Lonely Boy.
Yon, you're playing on my favorite songs. This is great.
And the final one is always number three.
Okay, I probably have mentioned this one a couple of times.
It's probably wrong again. It sounds like talking heads.
And time's up. These are the answers. This is number one.
So rough, y'all. From 1977, this is L. Stears.
Oh, the boy got it. Great song.
Okay, I get a boing for that.
All right, number two.
L. Stears, answer number one. And this is answer number two.
It's Andrew Gold. Oh, yeah. This is Lonely Boy.
Yeah.
And now, number three.
1977, an engine number two.
It was talking heads. And Lonely Boy.
And this is answer number three.
The talking heads.
What is this?
Once in a lifetime.
From 81, the talking heads. Once in a lifetime.
Well, that's it for today. By the way, all the clips you just heard and also the clips from the last couple of hit tests were all edited and created by Richard Richard.
Don't you know, he's been helping me out tremendously because of my lack of time due to the current circumstances.
That has to do with my current situation.
You can hear all about it in the hit test podcast and all information about that podcast.
So this hit test can be found at jompolet.com. That's J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T.com.
The address for feedback, as always, is hit test at jmail.com.
Well, Adam, I hope you did well. They were fairly easy to show you.
Should have done well.
Join us next time for hit test number 46.
So see you next time. Until then, bye-bye.
All right, young women, I get a little another boing there for at least getting the talking hands rise.
I don't know what the title is.
Okay, you know what?
I still have some pod show for serious stuff.
I want to record and then I want to get a good night's sleep.
Tomorrow, more flying, we're here in Portland at a little 80-bit airport.
It's called Aurora State, uncontrolled field.
And I did about two and a half hours of flying today.
Tomorrow, some ground school.
Then probably do about three hours of flying.
Then another three hours of flying, I think, on Thursday.
Then I'm Friday, the examiner.
I think you'll be doing my check right around noon.
And hopefully, if I've done everything right,
and I've got my head on straight, then I'll be able to get my ticket as we call it.
My wings for fixed wing for regular aircraft in addition to my helicopter license.
And it's kind of a weird time to be doing this.
But this has been planned for like nine or ten months.
And quite honestly, we've had our head so down and working so hard on just on so much stuff
and talking to people and we're working with a whole bunch of podcasters.
And I've set up before, if you're interested in looking what the pod show family can do for you.
Just drop me an email, add them at curry.com.
And we'll be happy to hook you up.
One thing we can certainly provide for you, which people start eating is bandwidth.
We're not like master buyers of bandwidth, so.
And I'm going to leave it at that.
So I will talk to you tomorrow, maybe a little bit of sound seeing from the skies.
And also, since I'm here in Portland, I'm going to go hook up with my buddy Ken Clark.
Probably no Ken from the Ken and Squip show also from the MTV Chronicles.
I mean, I haven't seen him in years and he lives here.
I mean, he's backyards.
So I've got to hook up with him.
Hey, you know what, maybe we'll do an MTV Chronicles.
We're both together.
I'll be going home.
That would actually be pretty fun.
So look forward to that.
Hey, let me know what you got going on.
Send it to submitapodshow.com.
If you got a promo or a podcast you want to share.
Got some pod safe music tunes.
I've been planning tonight, except for Rob Poslow, which of course is my hit newsure.
Send it off to podsafe at podshow.com and mashups.
Although I have a lot of them always looking forward to more mashups at podshow.com.
This program can be found at datingsourceco.com.
We can also find the feed to add to your iPodder or your iTunes at dailysourceco.com.
And of course there's always the weblog www.curry.com.
And if it's a little bit sun the sluggish side and it's kind of been and sluggish for the past
a couple of weeks we are getting all kinds of upgrades because we're blowing forward towards the future.
And I'd love for you to participate in the 100 million listener march because we're bringing them all in as an
enough podcast for everyone to enjoy something.
So, you know what?
Telling this dream is finally coming true and I'm extremely excited.
I hope you enjoyed it.
My friends, I will talk to you tomorrow.
Take care.
Stay subscribed and have yourself a great evening.
Bye-bye.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.