Delta Sierra Charly, 259 are good evening or good morning, wherever you happen to be.
This is Adam.
Adam Curry here in the Amstall Hotel in Amsterdam, the Netherlands.
It is the, as you can tell, the ambiance, you immediately get an idea that when I say that
I am now overlooking the Amstall River, it is actually technically, it is, I don't know,
I've got some wires dangling here.
It is past midnight, so it is a Thursday, October 13th, 2005.
I'm here on some business, which I actually, my business is the big part of my business.
I got some business, dammit, my business, B tomorrow, 930, I've got some appointments.
It's like legal crap and stuff.
So just, you know, stuff that you just can't schedule your life anyway, other, you know,
can't schedule around it, it's kind of inconvenient, but then again, isn't legal crap always
inconvenient.
So, whoo, man, there is a lot, a lot to go through.
First of all, let me say that I made a critical, critical error.
I'm not talking about the iPod video, we'll get to that later on.
Now, of course, you know about the power book, you know about the whole situation, you know,
that I'm basically working off of a firewire drive where I reinstalled most of my stuff,
and I was actually hoping that today, and I don't even know if new Macs were announced or not,
I mean, I've only seen news about the video iPod.
So, oh, I should, what we're doing that, I might as well just go ahead and surf over there.
I'm not recording on the Mac, and I will tell you why.
So, I, you know, I'd basically gone and rebooted my entire life, and I, you know, I figured out
all the pieces I wanted and didn't want to carry with me, and I reinstalled all my applications,
and, you know, so I figured when I, you know, want to run the road just for a quicky like this,
you know, I'll just bring the, just bring the power book and be able to record everything.
Wow, that thing does look pretty cool, the video iPod, I'm looking at it right now.
The new iPod, now playing music podcast photos, home movies, TV shows, music videos,
and it will give you a blue job, 30 gigabytes, 60 gigabytes, starting at 299.
Cool. And iTunes 6, oh, okay, so we have new iTunes, which means we have over 2,000 music videos,
hit TV shows, and more. Fucking brilliant Steve, absolutely brilliant, and you totally
did not expect it to come out now. But, man, you made a lot of people happy.
Okay, so, so that was all cool, right? And, and I've always got my, my little ear buds with me,
so I didn't need to carry headphones, already had headphones for the airplane, because of course,
I flew the, um, the 182RG. We'll talk about that as well. Um, and I sit down and, you know,
and we totally prepared for this video iPod thing, because of course, um, if you look in your iTunes,
and you're using iTunes, if not, you can grab this off of the RSS feed, the podcast feed.
I put a nice little daily source code kind of, uh, trailer thingy in there. Um, and,
you know, we've been waiting for this moment to have that, you know, when you have all this,
you know, cool capability, uh, excuse me.
I heard you say it. I heard you say senseo. I heard you couldn't stop,
couldn't help but think about it, could you? Um, so we've been waiting for this moment. We've been
waiting for the, um, uh, for the video iPod, uh, and have some content for it, uh, and this is
going to be very interesting. Um, wow, man, I really did not expect this to happen right now.
Glad we were prepared, but true. It even amazed me. I must say.
So this is where mainstream media will really get to play, and that's great. You know, um,
I've, uh, let's lots of TV shows and stuff I want to watch. I'm all for that.
Totally down with it. This is, you know, this is the Tvo capability of, uh, of what we've
discovered here. So that's pretty cool. Now, you know, um, we need more Steve Garfields, you know,
we need more. Kakyaos. Kakyao, my dear friend, the video wizard from the Netherlands who has made
me what I am today. And then I mentioned she's beautiful and so nice. Um,
so anyway, so yeah, I'm sorry. It's late. So I'm just trying to gather all my thoughts here. So,
um, I'm kind of thinking what I could do. All right. So let me get back to the problem at hand.
I like you really care about my thoughts there. Um, so I had everything all set up. I go to
record the source code. I've got mega-sag loaded, got all my software, uh, and I make the critical,
or I made the critical error that you can do all that, but you can't be reading and writing data
to a disk drive if it's on a firewire drive. So I'm basically, here I am asking my poor firewire
connection to pass data through of, uh, me recording, you know, so recording an MP3 file
direct to the disk at the same time, requesting files from that same disk. Dumb,
totally, just so incredibly stupid. So we can do a number of things. Uh, I'm thinking,
either I do some post, you know, because this is, you know, the cool thing about this of
court about podcasting is who cares, right, as long as we can, as long as we can hear something.
So what I'll do is, uh, we just, um, let's see, what I'll do, I'll do it with the old fashion
air bridge way. See, of course, you know, I got my love that even had new batteries and everything for,
for the, for the wireless microphone, new batteries. I'm recording on the I River now, by the way,
which, of course, is always the trusty backup. I almost thought to myself, right, when it
it pinched like this, it's time for a sound seeing tour. Uh, I don't like, man, it's Amsterdam.
It's like 12 o'clock. There's nothing going on. You know, it's, uh, it's a, it's a Wednesday night.
You know, things, uh, nothing happens in Amsterdam until probably at least two in the morning.
You know, and I got an early, an early call. So that's, uh, that's a, that's a no-go. Um,
so I was thinking maybe I should post edit the show and then everything you hear, uh, I'll kind of cross
over into the real sound file. I'll have to make that decision later. But first of all, for those of you
who didn't see the video, I'm just going to give you the sound of, of my little video, which is the first
kind of, you know, pod show vignette to run on the video iPod. If, uh, if you have one, and if not
certainly in iTunes 6, and I'm pretty sure this is going to work in iTunes 5 as well. Here, check it out.
Yeah, it's pretty cool. Room, uh, you don't get the full effect, of course, without actually seeing the video.
So I'm going to put that in as a separate piece of the feed. And, uh, let's see what we can do with this stuff.
Um, you know, Mads Weinstein videos have been showing up that she's been putting in her podcast
feed for a while now. Some of it's a pretty intense, definitely different there, Mads.
Okay, so, um, let's just talk about video iPod for a second because I was really blown away.
Oh, wait, the new iMac G5? Is that, uh, is that something that's new as well? That was announced today?
No, probably not. I think I have the new iMac G5, don't I? Okay. Yeah. I wonder is there a video available
of this? Did Steve do one of his famous, famous videos? Let me see.
Watch the new iPod ad, see the new iPod, and iTunes ad. Should we take a look at that?
Oh, Steve Jobs, the special web, I'm not going to watch the webcast with you. You don't want to do that.
I feel a lot like Mads Weinstein actually doing this. This is very much a, like a
Mads thing, you know, just messing around with audio and play some stuff. Let me see.
Oh, did I get a 404? That's interesting. I said, I wanted to see the new iPod and iTunes ads. I click on that.
And then it gets the page you tried was not found. Oh, that's interesting. How about the new iPod?
Okay, that one works. Let's take a look at it.
Got your eyes open? The bandwidth here, the hotel, by the way, is actually pretty good.
Okay, so this is a, oh, man. iTunes plus iPod TV. Okay. Uh, iTunes plus iPod TV ad featuring YouTube.
Yeah. Okay, that was brilliant.
It's transferring from a server called metrics.apple.com. Oh, the cool. Now that Bono is in a little iPod.
Make sure not actual picture. You might see.
Pretty cool. Wow, man. I can't wait. The content. That's what it's about. That's what's going to be so
interesting. Let's see if we can find out more iTunes. I overview. I really should download the new
iTunes. We got some other stuff to do. And I want to actually download some stuff and play it for you.
So the question is, you know, what kind of content is going to drive this mainstream content
without a doubt? I think that's great. And depending on the length and the quality, you know,
these are why these codex are also important that everyone talks about. You know, because the
small of the file size, the less it costs to actually send this out across whatever delivery network,
you know, these are going to go out. And this is, I guess, just kind of like a straight HTTP download.
So that's going to be very interesting to see how the economics of that work. You can bet that there's
a huge spreadsheet of apple, man, a huge one. And they're looking at bandwidth costs and customer
acquisition costs. And they're looking at, you know, what does it cost to run all those
individual tracks through their system and the billing? And this is a, and of course, you know,
the sales of new iPods, but damn, I mean, I think really that they lock up everyone's brain
almost with this. They must have been working on these deals for a long, long time. I can't wait to
download this thing and check it out. All right, let me try a few promos here. I'm just pulling
straight from the Gmail box. So, you know, your results may vary. Do you enjoy great jazz music,
musicians? Do you want your music played on the radio? Visit redjazz.com, your source for red hot
jazz, red jazz, hot casting and streaming great music 24 hours a day on redjazz.com,
and broadcasting every Sunday night at 6 p.m. Pacific time on KYOU AM1550 in San Francisco.
And this is a lot of good good jazz streaming stations. There's, there's still a lot of validity
to that. I like, you know, because I can't get the satellite stations. Unfortunately, I'd really wish I could
it would be, it would be really enjoyable to listen to. And of course, you know, our satellite TV
has all these stations, but I don't have it hooked into any stereo system. Kind of the drawback
of renting a house, you know, the cottage we're renting and we've kind of decided we're going to
actually we just had to decide we're going to stay there another year. We only do a year to year
least because we kind of want to figure out what we want to do. So, we're going to stay for at least
another year and then eventually, you know, I'd like to build the house of my dreams. But
that's for another podcast. So, this morning, ticker seen at a school horrible traffic.
Oh, man, there was a couple of cars overturned on the A3 motorway, actually on the inbound to
Gilford. And there's really only one main drag to get to Gilford and even if you go off the beaten
path, that that fills up with its seconds because it's so windy, twisty, you know, great English
countryside roads. And great for motoring. And so, you know, it's just the traffic was horrendous.
Christina was really late. We even called the school on our way and the school knew about it because
lots of kids were late. And Wind Commander William and actually one of Patricia's cardiologists
Eric Frittent, yeah. He's, he's also a FAA medical examiner and I had a medical test scheduled
with him in Antwerp this morning. And since William, the Wind Commander was bringing the
Cessna over from Antwerp to pick me up so I could fly it back with him. He brought Eric over,
his apartment is literally right at almost at the airport. And it's a great guy, 68 years old,
cardiologist, you know, really interesting guy, pilot for many, many years, just built his own
airplane. You know, it was kind of cool. But I was late for, you know, meeting them. But, you know,
they just had some breakfast, bangers and mash, of course. It's just like bigals, man. I'm telling
you, this Farrow's airport is just beautiful. It's exactly what you want from your
small English airfield. Hopped in the Sessna, off we were pretty cool. You can fly, we flew
it to flight level 5, 5, so 5, 500 feet. And in the UK, you can fly VFR, so visual flying rules above
the clouds. But we also did some IMC flying, so basically you're in the clouds, you're flying
on instruments. And that's where that kind of, you know, weird vertigo thing kicks in, which is
what instrument flying is all about, you know, is where you think you should be, you know,
leaning the plane towards the left, where really, you know, you could be in all kinds of attitudes.
And that's basically what happened to JF Kennedy Jr., you know, he got into weather where
that a lot of experience and freaked out on the instruments. And before you know it, you look
up at the sky and there's a sheep there, you know, except it's your upside down, you're about
to crash into the into the meadow. In this case, it would be a boat probably flying over the English
channel. So that worked out pretty well, actually, you know, and hadn't flown for what maybe
six weeks. So, you know, at the beginning, thereafter take off and William was doing the radio,
which really takes a lot of workload off of the pilot, obviously. You know, I was, I felt like
the plane was like a mile ahead of me, you know, I'm still doing everything. But then,
you know, as we kind of, I stabilized a bit and, you know, got to, got the hang of it again.
And, you know, remember, oh, yeah, small inputs on everything. And it was good. We were flying,
you know, and we were on the total control of London radar and telling us what to do. And it was,
yeah, it was a good trip, went to Antwerp, went over to Eric's place, got my physical, my medical
snive, the first class medical again, or an extension there of, so good for two years. And then
William and I went flying. And we went to mid-Azailant, which is in the middle of the Netherlands,
kind of lower middle, I would say, on the, on the sea. And that is actually the airport there,
is just a stone's throw from Cas Blaster Mike's place. And he had heard, I guess, yesterday on the
source code that I was going to be flying, he knows that I would sometimes do touch and goes there.
So he had sent me a message saying, hey, you know, let me know if you're going to be in the neighborhood.
I called him, I said, dude, we're definitely going to fly over. I'll do a couple of touching
goes and if you're there, we'll have some coffee. And, you know, the, so Cas Blaster Mike, who makes
the Cas Blaster application, he really, it's the whole development of that. I mean, the guys
really, quite brilliant at, at the software that he's put together and wait until you see this
next release where everything's done in software and, you know, the hardware is no longer
dependent and zero latency. I mean, it's just rocket science stuff to me at least as a user.
And boy, am I kicking myself that I chose to take the, uh, the power book, sorry about that,
and that I chose to take the power book instead of, uh, the craplet because I could have
happily done a great show on the on Cas Blaster. So, you know, in the continuing war of how
Mike is going to get me to use Cas Blaster all the time. I think I've learned my lesson here.
This really, this really bites him actually holding the love microphone here. It's like holding
onto a peanut in front of your face. You know, it looks dorky too. So, uh, there he was, Mike,
he wrote his bike over from his house and, uh, and he had his, you know, he's a ham radio operator,
of course, uh, and so he had his little, uh, receiver and he had been listening to us on the frequency
doing the touching goes. And, uh, and of course, uh, even though they only charge me for four,
I probably did about eight touching goes on one of the landings. But, uh, we got down walked away
safely, so it's all good. Uh, and I was cool to see Mike, you know, and then just hang out for a
little bit and had a quick bite to eat and then, um, I went off to the tower to pay for our
fuel and, uh, and for, uh, you know, the landing fees in Europe. You have to pay landing fees,
which is, you know, pretty weird for a US pilot to what won't really recognize that,
unless you're a transport pilot. Uh, I said, well, you know, William, why don't you take
Mike up? Now, Mike is never flown. Uh, I think he actually flew one song like, you know,
some city hopper type thing, but he did not like it. And he's, you know, uh, you know,
Mike's the kind of guy that will go to England on vacation and he'll drive, okay, and he'll take
the boat or the train and put the car on the train or whatever, but he doesn't fly. And I said,
well, man, you want to fly? And I want to, you know, I want to have a quick trip and, uh,
said, yeah, well, so you got to sit up front, you know, so that's, and of course, William was there.
So, so, but I'm not going to sit in the back. I'll go pay the bill and then, uh, you guys go fly, man.
I, that guy had a grin when he came out of that plane. Uh, I know that he's probably, you know,
downloading a flight sim right now, you know, trying to, I want to fly some more. Uh, it is quite
addictive. Yeah, it's quite addictive. Um, okay, Doki, let me see. I had, uh, I did do the show prep.
It's just I couldn't load everything in the way I wanted to do it, obviously.
I got a hit test from, uh, from Yon Polette coming up. Uh, thank you very much, everyone who,
everyone who sent in, uh, the Unix command, man, this is so geeky. You know, I said that there's a
way that you can make programs on your Mac, uh, have more processing power assigned to it.
It's called the Nice Command, and I said, well, I think you can only start it up by typing Nice,
and then the, you know, the path of the application or whatever. You have to set a, a variable for how
nice you want it to, to be or how nice you want the system to be to that application. Um, oops,
no, someone's typing me, who's this? Okay, I don't know what's up with that.
Um, shoot, where was I? Oh, man, roll back the clock. Okay, uh, on the nice thing,
there you go, I can hear you yelling at me saying, about nice, okay, get on with the damn Unix talk.
Um, so you can actually re-knice a process, and I'm sure someone will be more than happy to put that
information in, uh, in the show notes for today. So you can, uh, figure out how to do that. It's, it's,
kind of, it's really, it's more advanced stuff, but it does kind of go to show. And that's what I really
like about my Mac is that you can do that kind of stuff. Um, man, you know, I, I don't have my,
uh, I don't have my, uh, my regular MP3 files with me either. I really messed this up. My pre-production
on this trip was absolutely horrible. Not to mention that it falls, um, in line with the, uh,
with the board meeting, and it's just like I did not want to be here. I really wanted to be back
in San Francisco for this week. So, okay, what we'll do while I look at some stuff and see if I can
find, uh, hold on, tell me I've lost that as well. Yeah, see if I can find some of these other
promos I lined up. Why don't we, oh, this is a good one, hold on. Oh, that's quite a difference between
the way I normally do it and what you're hearing right now. Yes, I have it. It's lined up. It's
Yonpula. Oh, yeah.
I am this is a new hit. It's this number 65 already and there is not much time. So if you don't mind,
we're going to start right away. Okay, this is number one.
Okay, that sounds to me like super tramp and I'm going to have to say look my girlfriend,
a breakfast in America. Number two.
It's like, it's like extra hard because I can't really hear it through the shitty sound. I give up on that one.
And the final one, number three. Come on, I need a word, ring my bell. I know the second one too.
I just got to hear it again and time's up.
This is the answer number one in today's hit. It's a song from 1989. It's super tramp.
This is super school. Oh, school.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh yeah oh, oh oh, oh oh oh, oh, oh, oh, no better than ever in the world.
I love the second floor
Yes, I think you've seen me
You hear something, lady, baby
So, baby, baby, baby
Just don't cry, baby
Enter number two, Susanne Fagas
And this is the third and final answer
Oh, baby, wonderful, I'm 1979
Can you tell me what?
Bring my bell
Remember this man, this was the jam
I know the great song this time from just to be 48 years
I need a ward
And rate my bell as a third and final answer
In hit test number 64
I need a ward
And rate my bell as a third and final answer
In hit test number 64
And this concludes this hit test
I hope you did well, Adam, I also hope you enjoyed this one as well
Again, great music, lots of different kinds of music
To keep it a bit striking
Okay, as always, feedback is welcome
It's a usual address hit test in gmail.com
And you can find some info at that usual place
www.yompolet.com
Also, the iTunes links are to be found there
So please use these links if you've got advice and tricks
And then you've heard one of the hit test
Well, thank you for listening until next time
Again, so getting the usual story at the end of the hit test
I don't know when the next one will be created
And will be played on a daily source code
So there will be an next time, so until then, bye-bye
You know, I think that we have safely established that
This air bridge audio link bites ass
This is no good
God, I was trying to position the microphone to get it
You know, sound a little less like sharp
Like cutting into my brain
Because I'm wearing the earbud
So I'm wearing exactly what you're going to be hearing
When you look depending on what kind of earbud you have
Of course, oh my god, that was nasty
Okay, young, thank you very much though
It was nice about it
It did definitely get me in the mood
And it made me feel good, man, when I hear those tunes
Ah, it's the soundtrack to your life
Flashing before your eyes, I need something to drink
Let me clip you on again, oops
That's right, I got to take everything with me
Great
So for those of you who are listening to the daily source code
On serious satellite, kind of 103 serious stars
And thinking what the hell is this?
This is podcasting, it's a total mobile concept
Not only on your end, but also on my end
I'm completely mobile, let's see what let's take a look
What do we have in the Amstel Hotel
Mini bar
Well, let's see, we have a tubalaron
Oh, that's Don's Favorite
Don does nasty stuff with tubalaron
I don't want to say that
And we have a very chic, very nice actually
Body opener
Beer can opener, nice knife
It's almost like a full leather than there
We have Coke classic Coke light
Two of those, smear enough typical stuff
I was like to look at the juices, you know
So they have German juice
Made from fresh Germans
Fyinger, orange and soft
Nehobens fyinger
So that's orange juice, so we have
What do you mean?
Team flushed in soft, full soft
Multivitamin
Ten, full juices
And there's a two-latten soft
And another round of the soft
And we have Americano, Pringles, original and paprika
And we have a very expensive looking nut
And by the way, if you sometimes live from many bars like I do
You soon learn that the nuts are
Outradiously expensive
It's just nuts
It's exactly what it is
Got myself some Pringles and got myself some
Evian here
Okay, so anyway, and by the way, I'm sorry about yesterday
I just didn't work out having
Just couldn't do the source code
Literally, you know, with
By the time we were done flying
I mean, look at the quality of the problem, right?
Check this out
And if you had the munchies right now
Do you be going like, man
Dude's got some Pringles
Then we went from Midasiland to Hilversum
The Hollywood of the Netherlands, that's where they have an airport
Grassfield, but which is really convenient
Because you can, it's basically the same distance from
Skipple airport with all the traffic
Certainly that time of day, which is the main airport
You can land there, you can land
I'm just grabbing right there
You can land there, that's general aviation
There we go
But Hilversum is a lot more fun, because you can't
You probably aren't going to get a lot of permission
Do touching goes at Skipple Airport
But you can do lots of touching goes at
At Hilversum
And that's a couple of those
And then they have a little clubhouse
They're restaurant, so had a beer, waited for
Taxi Erics guide to come pick me up
And take me to the hotel
So really, but you know, with the hour that you lose
And time difference
Are really, it didn't get into the hotel
Until like quarter eight in the my room
Of course, my reservation hadn't gone through
Expedia, of course
You know, you'll always see that happen, right?
So I had to figure all of that out, and that just
Yeah, it was a bit of a pain
And then hopped on the Skype, I've called home
I've spoke a great length to one of my dear friends
It's funny, because it was not really funny, but I'm here
And spoke to her, and she lives in the Netherlands
But we actually had our whole conversation on Skype, which was kind of trippy
Kind of strange
Excuse me
Right, so
We have at Pod Show
We have meetings
The meetings is more like kind of like
We all get together, and we certainly can do it now in the configuration of the company
You know, we don't have too many people before it gets a little overbearing
People just, you know, and we have one big open space, so it's real cool
So we all kind of, you know, get together
It's either a business meeting or a technology meeting
And you know, everyone will present what they're working on
A lot of, a lot of been over here, obviously I'd dial in
And we do a video actually just use eye chat, and that works really well
And I got to tell you
We got some smart, some smart people doing some really interesting stuff
Taking, you know, the whole idea of podcasting and what you can do with it
To places that I just never thought of, although
Actually places that I have kind of been bumping into here and there
Let me give you an example of what I'm talking about
Do you remember that, the promo I played the other day for the
Mary and who was her name?
Let me go to my show notes, that's where I'll be able to find it
Hold on a second
I might even have it, no, I don't have it in my browser history
Okay, okay, let me just go to the daily source code wiki
It's gonna tell me that immediately
So these two 20 year old girls get to the name in a second
And I guess 20 something or whatever
And what's really cool is that they do a podcast and they do it on a Mac
Well, how do I know that? Well, because they also recorded on video
And they put that or they have a separate feed for that
And it was like, wow, you know, that's pretty cool
But what was going on was was actually more interesting
They were commenting on another podcast, which they were playing back
And stopping at intervals and laughing about, oh, here it is
Of course, Mary and Carla show, I'm sorry, Mary and Carla dot com
And you know, and I was kind of being a warrior of warrior
Looking in on, even though they sometimes were talking to me as the listener
And actually to the camera at some points, which was even
Trippier to see
And it was kind of like they were having this, you know, this
Conversation with like four people, the two of them and these two other guys
And they were actually playing that snippets of their show
And I was like, wow, you know, this is like
It's kind of like a hyper linking type of thing
Although no one else can follow it, which is a bummer
But you can kind of understand the thread, you know
And you just jump into it and they've done nine or ten shows or something
So I kind of fell into them into full steam
And I guess this feud or whatever, you know, it's kind of
Dissing back and forth and it's interesting
It really is
And I've seen some really interesting behavior and tagging
That is really in my mind is saying that podcasting is going to be more than
And of course this is no secret, right?
We always knew that, you know, you could have
You could do a podcast like a radio show or
It can be a book, you know, look at Scott Sigler or it can be
You know, an exercise, work out routine, you know, like
Marina's podcast, you know, it can be so many different things
And even I often without a doubt get stuck in the idea of
You know, it's going to be one, there's going to be a show and
You know, go to many people or a set number of people
Or maybe to know people and you have advertising
You don't have advertising and what is advertising?
You know, an advertising can be podcasts
I mean, when you start to really step back a little bit and see
What people are doing online and how they're using applications
And how they're using instant messaging and how they're using voice over
IP and I think that this is a part of it and it fits into a
much bigger puzzle that in a way Apple is trying to figure out
If I, and I was actually, I did just look at the
At the Apple page for it goes a little bit further
Yeah, so it's the iTunes page, right?
Now, of course, what Apple has always done has
Work this concept of eye life where, you know, your photos
And your music go together and so it was photos music and then
But what else do they have?
A movie, of course, with eye movie
And, you know, what happened is it turns out that
Really having one, one piece of software and
Clearly one device takes care a lot of a lot of your
entertainment necessities.
There's my eye count telling me something here.
So, you know, the, the iPod does photos,
Items does photos, does music, does video.
So it's all kind of coming into one device.
And if you look at the iPod economy of all the add-ons and
Snap-ons and plug-ins that you can buy for the iPod,
I mean, it's becoming a pretty pretty interesting little box.
And of course, it's beautiful, which is nice.
Now, that's not to say that there aren't tons of great other
Devices out there running an open source platform, etc.
But, you know, it's a beautiful device.
I just can't help but say, you know, I like beautiful things
It looks really nice and seems to be affordable.
So, just like what Apple is doing with, you know,
With this integration of all these different things.
So, too, does podcasting and video casting have a place, you know?
And I just, I got to think about it.
This video thing is, like, it's so intriguing to me.
There's so many different things you can do.
And, you know, how many content creators are there?
And is there a simple type of content creation,
Which can be, you know, for video, which is easy as plugging in a microphone
Into an eye-rever and then uploading the file, you know,
And holding a microphone in front of the speaker and doing that kind of stuff.
You know, is there going to be an equivalent to that in video?
And is there going to be entertaining?
Will it draw an audience?
I must say that somehow short videos do it for me.
Sure, either a music video, which I like, but, you know,
If it's like a performance, what we did MTV, we used to call up a performance piece
Where people are dancing or whatever.
That's not really going to work on the small screen.
So they have great examples here.
Actually, I can see on the page, Bono up close,
Singing Madonna with her Vogue, and her Vogue stands.
Okay, so that's going to work, you know,
But, oh, in the complete Stevie Wonder digital box set is also out.
Oh, man.
I bet Steve Jobs announced that today as well.
Hold on a second.
Let's see.
Oh, man.
You know, I'm such a Stevie Wonder fan.
Let me see.
I'm accessing requests could not be.
Not currently not available in the Dutch store,
But it is available in the US store.
Click Change Store to view this item.
Oh.
I can view it, but I can't buy it.
Oh, okay.
So the rights haven't been cleared for the Netherlands yet,
Or the European Union.
189 bucks.
The complete Stevie Wonder.
That's what it's called.
Wow.
That looks good.
Okay.
See?
Already it's working, right?
You just saw me get marketed to.
I was looking at something completely else.
So Stevie Wonder, I clicked on them.
Unfortunately, they can't give it to me because I'm in the wrong country.
And that's not.
It's not that iTunes knows that I'm in the Netherlands, by the way.
I've just had my, my Mac account that long.
It's still on my, my Dutch credit card and my,
Actually, my Dutch address.
Which I don't own anymore.
Fantastic.
Okay.
So that's what I've been getting from these updates with the, with the team.
And it's great because we're also getting to know each other.
And, and we're sparring with each other, which is,
Oh, man.
Have I longed to do that again with smart people and,
You know, talk about concepts and,
And we had, well, this was great.
We had Andrew Grumman out for a couple days.
Andrew Grumman, of course.
Well known from all of his development work on iPod or lemon.
He's been there from almost day one with the,
You know, after this whole thing kind of got started.
Definitely pretty.
Well, shoot, I was talking with,
In fact, Andrew was in Amsterdam with Dave Winner as funny,
because I remember describing to him distinctly.
I bet he'll remember this.
And sometimes Andrew does a podcast.
And I'd love to hear his recollection of this.
We were in Amsterdam.
I still had the, the bunker.
And so we hung out there for a little bit.
They weren't traveling together,
But I think maybe Dave invited Andrew over.
I can't quite remember how that went.
But we were, and this is, you know,
There was no podcast in there.
I hadn't written any script,
But there was all kinds of things floating around that
I remember saying what I want.
Because remember now,
I built the first iPod or script,
Because I couldn't get anyone to do this.
And I was explained it well.
But I said to Andrew, I said,
I really want, like,
Black hole, you know,
I want to, you, you,
If you make an MP3 file,
We're even thinking about how you do that them.
But you just drag it into this hole on your desktop.
And it goes away.
And anyone who's subscribed to it,
They can pick it up.
And I want a place where the stuff comes in.
And I want to go straight to my iPod.
And so as basically describing the functionality of iPod,
Or an aggregator, of course,
Which I didn't come up with.
But an aggregator with enclosures.
But, you know, the whole experience.
That's what it's about for me.
It's going through to the,
All the way through to my, at that time, iPod.
Funny.
I just remember something else we talked about in that conversation.
That, and this is probably, you know,
This is, here's a place where the iPod,
What is it called?
Is it called an iPod?
Does it have a separate sub name?
Like the iPod Nano?
Does it have any?
Was it just the iPod?
The iPod?
Hmm.
It just says the new iPod.
Okay.
Poorne.
Poorne is going to be huge.
Huge.
I, you know, the porn guys are just going,
Holy moly.
And, you know, what I believe in two personal porn.
I think that's, that's definitely going to happen.
It is.
And, isn't it time for a hot or not application on your iPod,
By the way, don't we need that?
I mean, video dating, subscribe to the video dating feed.
Oh, man.
Yeah, that's the kind of stuff that's going to be cool.
And, you know, and that to me is also a version of podcasting.
I think it's just, it is much broader.
And, by the way, it doesn't mean that it's, you know,
that there's any less love or, or more or whatever.
It's just, you know, we're only beginning to understand the massive changes
that are taking place in, in our media landscape.
And, actually, not even doing the source code today.
And, just, you know, flying and taking my mind off it.
When I, when I was done flying, it's just, it's like a whole bunch of stuff
myself out.
I didn't even know about the release of the, of the new iPod yet.
But, you know, we're seeing something very different,
which is going to affect a lot.
We've talked about this, what's happening with music.
This is very much like another evolution of music.
And, I guess if you look back at it,
the stages of, you know, of types of music,
pretty much always go hand in hand with the technological
innovation of some sort.
Okay, I don't know all of them, but let's take the 60s.
A lot of it was based on distortion.
You know, I'm sure that there were some parents saying,
how can you listen to that crap?
Look, it's over-modulated, the guitar, and what is that sound?
That's a guitar?
It sounds like a cat screaming.
That's right.
I see electric guitar, baby.
Papa.
Daddy-o.
And then, of course, we had synthesizers brought us disco, new wave.
And, by the way, it was cool then.
And we just heard Anita Ward ring my bell.
That works for me, still.
Then, what do we have after that?
Well, remember, the Fair Light God Braun should be a part of this podcast.
I think he had one of the only ones in weight.
Was that the Fair Light?
Or do you have something pre- Fair Light?
Actually, 10CC started doing samples.
Was that thing called the melatron or something like that?
They had loops of tape, and you hit the tape, and the sampled play on the
actual loop of recording tape.
And that really spawned all new types of music and sounds.
I remember when everyone would be jealous, because it was always Quincy Jones and Michael Jackson,
who would get the new DX7 keyboard, which had samples in it.
They would be the first ones to cut a record using the samples that were built inside the keyboard.
So, all of that goes hand in hand with technological revolution.
And also the distribution of it, along with that came AM radio, FM radio, MTV, which of course,
meant cable, satellite, and it really affects how everything comes together.
And I guess it was kind of foolish not to think that radio wouldn't have to come along in some fashion.
And what is it going to be?
Maybe more questions asked than answered in this particular daily source code.
But I'm really happy.
I'm happy about what I'm seeing.
This just opens up.
Seeing it actually seeing this video iPod system, we're on the right track.
And I think you all know those of you that are clued in, those of you who are starting to see it,
I mean, PDF casting, yeah, that could happen too.
I mean, our version of media and what it means to us and how we consume it and how we make it is changing.
Check out the Mary and Carla.
See if you can get that video, the video cast.
Look at how they're using the computer.
And I don't want to feel that girls like you're being over-analyzed, but I just love it.
I look at my daughter, 15.
And I see how she's using the tools that we're created with entirely different purposes in mind.
And they're being used for very interesting purposes.
Particularly that webcam shit parents.
You got to make sure you know what your kid's doing with a damn webcam, okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow.
Okay.
So we've almost gotten through the time that I wanted to spend today and everything that I think just about everything I want to talk about, kind of a free form flow of ideas with a little bit of classical music in the background.
I hope that came through.
I apologize for the sound quality and for the lack of, you know, the usual bits and bits.
But sometimes it's kind of refreshing just to just to, you know, do something different and get it all off, just get it all off it all off of my mind.
Just a brain dump on you.
I hope you don't, I hope you don't mind.
So tomorrow, court crap.
And this will be the podcast for Thursday.
As I said, it is technically Thursday here.
And then I'll be back at the cottage.
My sister is arriving tomorrow at the cottage.
So that'll be fun, Tiffany.
I hope I can get on the podcast, which will be the thank God of Friday edition of the daily source code.
So that said, if you're just listening to this for the first time, you can subscribe to the show in iTunes or you can go to daily source code.com and find out everything about it and the podcast feed, etc.
Add them to create.com feedback, audio feedback is welcome.
Just throw it up on a server somewhere so that, you know, I don't don't attach it to the email if you can't.
If you can help it.
And I'll be back tomorrow.
Wish me luck.
It's going to be fun doing my business stuff.
Talk to you Friday, everybody.
Bye-bye.