Delta Sierra Charney 2-8-6
Timmy, you see that?
Holy information you don't yet have!
Adam Curry!
$16 million worth of airplane trapped to my ass!
And the next generation radio content in my ears!
We don't need no speaking gritty!
I like to think I'm flying into the future!
I guess it is Adam Curry!
One, two, three!
I'm counting on you!
Yeah, sure!
Maybe it was Thanksgiving, but that doesn't mean that we're going to skip our Friday celebrations now, doesn't it?
I don't want to!
Stop down, drive it around from Gilford, the Curry Cottage!
This is the Daddy Source Code, it is Friday, kick it off with Josh Woodward!
Incoherent!
How you doing?
This illusion broken but you know it's intense!
Holy truth!
You hear like an explosion!
And the smiles on all the faces of the children
of just a moment that we lost in the police!
Are you trying to keep it falling tacky with the number of it's wine?
Will it bounce or break?
There's some on the sidewalk!
And a sticky hushes weasel dim in the corner of the brain!
Now it's time to live away and look for me here!
Oh, it's clear it's not nearly twice as big!
It's out of reaching heavy as a brick!
Well, it's quick to make a noise and no,
you'll rub our gun and all the elements!
Getting so much water and the tea!
Oh, it's clear it's not nearly twice as big!
It's not nearly twice as big!
What you say I don't want to say to me
What you say I want you to say to me
I can't be your world I can't be your world
I can't be your world
Joshua would work in co-harons founded on the ultimate mix podcast
And shuttle went over to the podcast piece of network and picked up a copy
Excellent song kick off today's source code
Okay, so the power was off earlier, hold on a second
Everything sounds like shit now
Oh man
Hold on, let me see if I can get some boost back
Does this help?
I have no idea what I'm doing
Okay, well, it sounds a little bit
I don't know if it's my voice or if it's just nasal and general or whatever's going on
Doesn't matter
How you doing? Hope you had a great Thanksgiving
Oh man, it's really, it sounds crappy
Damn
I don't know if I can get over this
Hold on, let me try, let me try doing that a little
Put a little bit of low end, a little more
I'm missing something in the mid-range somewhere
Oh wait a minute, maybe that's it
No, that's down
It's so hard to listen to your own voice
And then think if you see if you can get the settings right
So it sounds right
Okay, I don't think I have much more to do
And now the secondary headphones aren't working
That's nice
I was in gun invite Patricia up to talk about some TV stuff
Oh man, the reverb is all over the place
Ah
Okay, never you mind
It'll all work out in the end
So we didn't celebrate Thanksgiving yesterday
In the United Kingdom
In fact, I think it's as Aaron Hastings email
The US Independence Day is when the Brits celebrate Thanksgiving
It's funny because people called me from the States and said
Hey, happy Thanksgiving, are you celebrating?
You got your family
Well, we don't have any family that lives here
And I said, you know, it's not really like a holiday over here
People don't really celebrate Thanksgiving
They said really why
So we'll do you know the story of Thanksgiving?
Yeah, you know the pilgrims and we sat down
Uh-huh, but do you know the whole story?
Like, you know, the year before that
At the pilgrims, it basically shot the bird at the UK
At Britain and left
Oh yeah, yeah, that doesn't make a lot of sense
Exactly
So amongst all of this crap, what I did figure out
Because it what happened as the electrician came over
And finally fixed all the lights and all the stuff that's wrong here
And I discovered where that mysterious hum was coming from
God, this sounds so horrible
I don't know what to do about it
I really don't
I wish I could make myself sound more just better
Um, the horrible hum was coming from Patricia's jewelry cabinet
Which has built in dimmed lighting
And I really only discovered it by accident
I was sitting in the studio the other night
And Patricia was ready to go to bed
So she turned off the dimmer and also like, wow
The hum just went away because I had the speaker still on
But there was nothing playing
And that's how we figured it out
And so that's the one thing he didn't fix
Fix everything else
So the washing machine works the lights in the bathroom
We're working
And except for my entire mixer being a deprogrammed
Everything else is pretty cool
Help this is from Matthew Kneeble
Hey Adam, this is Matthew Eble
Podsafe musician and self-abound stone or super geek
Hey, a while back you would mention something along the lines
Of a podshow polusa
Some kind of concert or tour with a bunch of podsafe artists
Like me and the brother love chance
And all the other people that have been popping up on the podsafe music network
Is there any truth to rumors that something like that is in the works
Because you know I've already got my bags pack and the posters printed up
And I'm waiting for the tour of us to roll up to my house
My roommates are starting to get annoyed that I have all my internet on the front lawn
So let's get rolling with this
Anyway, something else
My roommates mentioned to me recently that she had been hearing your name
Obviously because I play the daily source code a lot
She'd been hearing Adam Curry hit Adam Curry this and the podfather that and Adam Curry
And she knew you were on MTV back in the day
And that kind of thing
She recently admitted to me that every time she heard your name
She pictured Kurt Loader
Yeah, is that a bad thing?
Get back to us on that
Anyway, that was a good idea
It's a kickass show and I'm looking forward to the next episode
Thanks a lot
Oh yeah, and don't forget to check out my new album, Beer & Coffee
Oh yeah
You see how quickly I snuck that in there
You see it's the old slam and plug trick
That's what it is
No, that's not okay
Of course not
Are you crazy?
Are you nuts?
Go slap her around for me, will ya?
Let me see
The Curry Cruiser
We're supposed to pick that up yesterday
Actually Eric came over yesterday on the Thanksgiving celebrations
To pick up the A8 driving back to Holland
Actually he came over the day before he slept over
And we're supposed to pick up the Curry Cruiser yesterday
But international bank transfers
Since you know my money is in other countries
Take up to four days
And that's what's happening in the UK
And if you do it from the States no problem
But if it comes from any other country then the United States
You can take up to four days
I don't know maybe the screen to see if I have al-Qaeda ties or something like that
But it really sucks because we have no car
Patricia got caught yesterday in a hailstorm
Oh man
It started hailing and I'm sitting here in my big green chair
And the minute I thought to myself oh man
I hope Patricia doesn't get caught
And that because she'd walked to the hairdresser
She was walking back
And three seconds later my phone rings
I can hear this
Oh my goodness
So we have no car
But Louis from the Jack dealer apparently is going to help me up
And hook us up with some car for the weekend
If the money doesn't show up today
And I guess then by Monday it'll be in
Ah, that was
Let's see
I'll tell you why
Why don't I roll out a boatload of promos here
I invited Patricia to come and talk about some television stuff
We've been watching
So hopefully she'll have a nice cup of tea ready
And even though the headphones don't work
I've got a proper mic set up for
So let's see if we can get her on the show
Stay tuned
Hi, this is Mark of the website
RateMyRap.com
RateMyRap.com is a website
Where unsigned up and coming rappers
Can upload their MP3s for free
And people will rate those
MP3s anywhere from
Totally whack the platinum
RateMyRap.com is also a podcast
Where we will feature the guest wrap
For the previous month as well as
New up on the site
And maybe some picks up my own
So check it out
RateMyRap.com
Peace
Secure a taste
Potential internet scuba geeks
Are you ready to dive deeper
Into your video I pod
PodDiver TV
The video cast is on air
And online
PodDiver TV
Video companion
PodDiver radio
On previous episodes of PodDiver TV
We covered diving World War II
Jarvin Uboats
Rediving with spinner dolphins
Diving special forces combat divers
And diving with yours
Issue effects
PodDiver TV
The video cast
On future episodes
We will cover
Shark diving in the Bahamas
KDiving in the UK
So submerge and subscribe
To podDiver TV
The video cast
On your host
Jokegoza
You can find podDiver TV
On iTunes
Search under scuba
Or check out our website at
www podDiver.com
Attention
OPML
The managers of planet Earth
This is a public service announcement
Could all OPML lists that you maintain
Please make sure that any entries you have
At point to an RSS feed
Have the valid
Type equals RSS attribute
Without this attribute being used correctly
The functionality of the directories themselves will suffer
And we don't want that do we?
We want to make everything better
Please visit the OPML guidelines at www.OPML.org
Flashback
I thank you
For your patience and attention
Hey Adam
Is this the sound of vegetarianism?
I just wish that we could all be peaceful
And harmonious like the little bunnies in the field
Or is this the sound of vegetarianism?
Yes
Neither Adam
The sound of vegetarianism is Vegcass
The Veggie Podcast
Vegcass brings you the full Veggie Spectrum
Every show packed with a range of Veggie theme on it
You'll hear in depth interviews with leading vegetarian experts
I hope that there's a 75% of all new emerging diseases came from
Raising animals for
Thought provoking news from the world of science
And the headline is chickens
Think about the future
Visits with vegan entrepreneurs
Developing tasty new products
I'll do three minute promo
That's a bit much
The world is in a flaming whole of real
But I'm here to ask you all to listen to my podcast
If the world is up, the world is up
If the story is still true, now come the place to share your love
Ciao
Okay, Curry, good cue and way to go, dude
Let me see if I can hear Patricia Holna
I'll open up the other microphone
I think she's still talking on the phone
Damn it
She doesn't care about the show, man
She just doesn't care
You know, all this pod safe music stuff that's been going on
And just the whole creation of the pod safe music network
And all the fantastic energy that's taking place in and around it
Has why does it sound like I'm talking out of my ass?
Uh, uh, one, two, one, two
God damn it, this sounds like shit
Hello, hello, hello, hello
It sounds horrible, what is going on?
Why doesn't it one, two, one, two, three, one, two, three
I don't know, leave it something like that
Okay
So with all this pod safe music stuff that's going on
I've discovered something
Actually, I'm able to now finally rediscover music
I'm learning things about music that I didn't know before
I have a whole new appreciation
I used to be, um, I wouldn't even back in the day
When I was just in encased by the hits
Which would be during the day at MTV
And then on weekends I'd do a shift at Z100
And you know, that's really, you've got the hits
And you're head then man, let me tell you
Um, then, you know, just it was hits all around me
Continuously
And for some reason, you lock off portions of your brain
They become numb to new stimuli
And if it isn't, you know, if it isn't something that
I don't know, it's very, very hard to explain
It's taken me years at this point to get out of that
And it actually was like a whole deep programming process
It's so hard to explain
But finally, now I feel that I'm so liberated in just my listening
Forget what I can do with podcasting
And, you know, I could go on about that forever
Obviously, but just as a listener enjoying music
Listening to other people talk about music
And then hearing that music and being able to go and download it myself
I'm going to play it on my own show
And I don't know
And also Patricia keeps walking into my, into the office here
More and more frequently saying, hey, that sounds pretty cool
You know, it's just something is going on
There's a real excitement in the air
There's just something tingling
You can feel it in your fingertips, you know
So, as well, for the, the pod save Christmas song
Which now I'm going to call pod save for peace
I don't know why, but
That's catchy, isn't it?
Pod save for peace
And proceeds go to UNICEF
Music for UNICEF, pod save for UNICEF is better
Pod save for peace sounds so good though
Okay, well, you know, help me out the side there
Maybe we'll come up with a new one as we go along
So now I'm hearing different pod save artists who have podcasts
All over the place
Talking about the vocals that they're doing for the song
Here's a piece from, uh, what is this?
This is from a Derek Miller, I used from his pod
Kind of like the backing track that's loud provided us
To sing along with
That's not what the final version is going to sound like
It's just me with a backing track with some guide vocals
So here you can give a listen to my high, my low, together
And then the backing track
Uh, hope you enjoy it, sounds kind of weird to start with
But here we go
What if every day
We're Christmas
What I wonder for well
This would be
We would never feel blue
We'd make all our dreams come true
If Christmas
We're every day
The low part
The member Patricia was saying about how it
It was not the right key for her
Listen how low Derek has to go to hit the notes
He's really hurt
We would never feel blue
We'd make all our dreams come true
If Christmas
We're every day
All right, together
What if every day
We're Christmas
What I wonder for well
This would be
We would never feel blue
We'd make all our dreams come true
If Christmas
And if you're ready for it
Here's the music
Here we go
All right
Everybody know
Christmas
Excellent
All right, so I can't wait to hear this
I finally got the proper tracks into slow
The ones without the reverbs
He could actually do something with them
With the tracks that Patricia did
And I think his cutoff date is today
That everything is supposed to be pretty much done
Oh man, I cannot wait to hear the final product
I think December 1st
It was like his drop dead date that
Brother Love told me that
Really looking forward to it
All right, let's play some
Some other pod safe music here for a second
This is
I don't even know where I heard this one
But
Even though it's long
Which of course means you can skip over
But I suggest you listen to the whole thing
Because it really builds in a nice way
Patricia walked in on this song
And she said, hey, sounds a bit like Bowie
Well, she could know
This is beggars town
If we come
What am I supposed to spice
Even I believed
All my lives
But I found no one
Now I'm biting my own tongue
I'm not off to rights
But once again I'm wrong
So brought the blame on me
It doesn't matter anymore
You say the damage has been done
I see I love what's already flow
In beggars town
Now I'm dismatized
Everything I know
And love
I was hoping I could forget
You are a new list to me now
There's no cure and I'm addicted to you yet
Who can have depend upon
To get me out of this
You've got the sweetest smile
There's such a poison's kiss
My hands are shaking with rage
It's too late now to negotiate
For all the love has turned to hate
And it seems without a trace
For the blame on me
It doesn't matter anymore
You say the damage has been done
I see I love what's already flow
In beggars town
Now I'm dismatized
So this is what we are
And this is what we've been through
I've been nothing left to give
I give everything ahead to you
There's no cure and I'm addicted to you
There's such a poison's kiss
In beggars town
I can just hear Jason Kelcanus yelling now at his iPod
I want to hear only the talking bits on the daily source code
I don't want to hear all the mash up
Ten on all the bonsai he think he and the promo
I want to hear all that
Dude
It's called advertising
I'm forcing you to listen
Get through all the crap to listen to the good bits
That was a hollow horse from the pod save music network beggars town
Music.podshow.com
I was talking actually not talking but I was emailing with Chris Rockwell
From the daily download
Dude when you get another poop cast
Yes, so many poop cast fans who just can't believe that he hasn't posted a new show
And such a long time
So he's leading the charge on the development of the pod save music network
And I said, you know, when do we think we're going to have a lot of these pieces up
We've been talking about and he said, I'm thinking Christmas
Wow
So I sure hope so dude
That would be awesome if we could have it by the new year even
I'd be extremely happy
Speaking of pod save music networks and feedback here from Ken Irman
Yo Adam
I've been spinning the power steppers from the pod save music network
And Colin from the van sent me an email to say thanks for the spins
You know how that works right?
If you're a pod cast when you sign up of the pod save music network
Then you report that you played the song
And then the pod save music artist receives an email that you played it
So we had exchanged a couple emails
Then I got an email from him to which he attached to station identification piece
He recorded for me with a sweet singer and everything
I didn't ask him to
How freaking cool is that you can hear it in the promo?
Actually the promo was really long
No way it wasn't that long
Is this the right promo?
Am I thinking of the right thing?
Hold on
Oh
Oops
That didn't work
I just clicked on the
No, that's not what I wanted
Hold on a second
Is this the promo?
Yo, it's Ken Irman for the bragging job I'm showing
By the name of staff, I groggy job with that TV
Where you can check out some of my TV shows that I've been producing
Some of my photo shop work on my thicker photo stream
And of course my pod cast
Or I play a light back track
Because I'm a laid back cat
The coffee's always fresh in the music's always pod save
I'm doing my best to make pod cast that I want to listen to
Interesting and real enough to enjoy with rich sounding music
Like I can listen to while I'm thinking out in cold monkey mode
A sort of iris spied me long
Should music to generate a single single review
Yeah
Yo, I've been spending power stuff for his baby long cow voice
Danger to the shut-ups
Danger stronger just getting a shield
And you know what?
And it's one of the things to be judged right
Sound good you
Come on by the groggy job at dot TV's website
Check out a couple episodes to the groggy job show
And by the way, I know I got to finish the squirrel 100 TV series
Everyone's been bugging me
The very second I had two hours to spare
I will get the next episode out of the door
Yo, got her run, talks in
Bad
So it goes on to say
The pod cast community is freaking cool
Two months into it, I've already been meeting so many really nice people
I really feel like I've joined the community
You bet buddy
Thank you so much for being point man and lightning rod
I don't know if that's good
Alright, peace shot
AKA
Croggie Java
Lots of feedback about
We were talking about with
Yeah, I was talking about Christina
How she's so forgetful and
Doesn't seem to respect a lot of from mom's stuff
Neil Gorman sent me a beautiful email
He said he heard some of the
What's the right word?
I'll say issues you're having with your 15 year old child
I wanted to take a moment and send you a thought
I went through my head as I listened
Even though I don't have any kids in my own because of my job
I'm around lots of teenagers on a regular basis
I work with lots of troubled teens
Who come mainly from the west side of Chicago
Many of them have been gang involved
Abused, participated in violent crime
Or lost control over the lies because they
Became dependent on drugs and alcohol
To feel normal
Quote
To function
I'm not talking about smoking a little bit of weed
I'm talking about much more serious stuff
Anyway, I just wanted to say that if the main problems
You're having arc Christina being forgetful
Or absent minded
Hey baby
Thank you
Hey
Hello
Hop in front of the mic
I was just reading that email
You know what?
I'll tell you
Hey
No, despite the way you have a microphone
I do
You have headphones that work
You knew I was coming
I told you
Yeah
I was invited for tea
Yes
I was just reading that email
The guy I said
You said
The main problems
You are having with Christina being forgetful or absent minded
But where she put stuff
You put your shark clearly doing a great job of being parents
Christina is very lucky kid to have you both
Wow
Yeah, that's nice
And we are because last night we went to the parent teacher conference
Yes
And
Didn't we actually one point say
Are you talking about the same girl?
Don't touch your breasts
No, I was itching on the nipple
Uh-huh
Yeah
No, we actually
A curry
See you
Yeah, I see you
All right
Same curry
And they said yes
She's just lovely girl
She's delightful
She always has a whole more done
Her coursework is great
I said you said
When is she doing that?
She seems to be on the computer
The whole time
No, she's doing both
My microphone sounds like ass
I don't know what happened
When they did the power
Everything
Yeah, it was a big nasal
Is it nasal?
Hold on
Help me out here
You know how to listen to this
Okay, that's better
One step
One, two, one, two, one, two, one, two, one, two
Nipping it
Notes
Is that too much high?
That's gone now
Oh no, two, three, four
Hello
Hello, what's wrong?
Hello part is gone
Yeah, well I can bring that in
Hold on
One, two, three, four
Yeah
Two, three, one, two, three, four
Ok
No, it's still fucked up. Like somebody said, how do you sound? You sound okay? I sound okay. I don't have talking for you
No, it's I don't know what it is after they how's that one two three one to this too much low in there
One two three four how's that one two three? Yeah sounds a little bit boy
You sounded over modulated. All right
Anyway, so that was really nice. Yeah, we were all kind of around like big talk. Yeah, and you know what what I really liked
What I heard um was that they said every every teach you said that she was so polite
And again, I said see you
And you know I'm proud of that yeah, no kidding. I'm very proud of that you know for decent people
I guess so yeah, yeah
Hey, uh, he's dead George Best. Oh, really. Yeah, yeah, he went for me. That's just a united one of the best to footballers in the world
Yeah, wasn't he involved in it was he involved in some scandal
He was always a football scandal
Yeah, because it's the drink. I
Yeah, it's the drink. Hey, and the the pubs are not open 24 hours a day here in the UK
So they're expecting a huge binge attack like the I don't think so I don't think that's it's gonna make them that much difference
He's like I don't get it because I don't get drinking at all. No, no, we don't get it at all
But but like we were um we grew up with Amsterdam and the brown cafes and everything and
I remember that of course there were people, you know sitting in a cafe
We call it the brown cafe. It's a pub
The father said need to like go get your father, you know
I kind of go get him from the pub. Yeah, so you always had those people, but
I don't know I we never had that problem of I never heard about the word binge drinking in Holland
Did you ever hear about that? No, and especially not the kids
I don't think the kids are interested in Holland no in in in
Maybe split but not no, I think but not even that no
You never hear those things. No, no
Anyway, geez, I need a lot of cheese cheese. They're in the cheese cheese in the pothots
And a friend she's so kill you before the the weed will
Friends, right
Man, you know in Holland they eat french fries with mayonnaise mayonnaise. Yeah, that will do it. Yeah, it's good for you people
You know what they call a
A quarter pounder in France
Yeah
What was it right out?
I think it was the right out. I was just telling I was some talking to Rob
We know the
Gossip journalist in Holland. He was friend of ours. Who's a friend of mine? I don't want him writing anything
No, no, he's not writing at the moment
There are no good magazines. He wants to work for
But I was telling him that I enjoyed
English TV so much that we had
I'm a celebrity you get me out of here. Dude now hold on a second
This is a national
It's a national happening everyone's talking about this and I must say when television is good
It's really
You know it works because everyone's sitting at home there so that's it's I'm a celebrity
Get me out of here. They throw all these well, you know
A used to I think it start off with really be celebrities, but now it's just it's interesting people
People that you don't really it's not they're not peace celebrities. Oh, they started off weed
Not a celebrity. See that that's not interesting. I'm not interested
So who do we have we want to be first first? I started one right
But it's it's a two-week program right every night at airs and every night they have but I don't think that they did that in in
In English I think in Holland
They started off with we'd want to be you know
Cowards because the most of them are cowards and not going yeah, like us
Well, and they asked everybody
Yeah, I wouldn't go. We know I we wouldn't go not for the Dutch one. I don't know for the English one. No, you're in it. Oh five
You wouldn't survive. What are you talking about? I would survive. You spoiled. I would sir. Yeah
No, so I wouldn't survive. What we have to explain is so if people do they have them in the in America? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, but they
But they go but this the historic there anyway here in England very interested people very interesting
And oh, it's interesting. I mean and this time they had a Carol
That's here. Yeah, Margaret that's her daughter right and they also have a way they have more the Jimmy Osmond
Yeah from long-haired lover from Liverpool little they call him little Jimmy Osmond. He's a sweet guy. He's so sweet bless him
Yeah, he's really nice. That's what he says oh bless and then there's the cute chick from there
From neighbors the Kylie want to be yes with Kylie kind of a time very nice girl another woman and I don't know
So a couple of we don't know but very nice. Oh one from the the singing group blue
Ugly guy from the little overweight guy. I didn't see it. That's not the same thing, but okay
No, it's not ugly. Yeah, he said he spit heavy it and then that's really what I have remember him. He's not one of the cute guys
Not depends on what you think it's cute. Okay. He's not my idea of a cute guy. All right, so
But it was fantastic, that it wasn't it really was because first of all this heralthatcher
Because they were you know they record continuously and somewhere in the middle of the night
Which which does get broadcast on on sky at least. I don't know have a channel that's all night
There's a couple tonight. Second night. They were there. They were there. Carol Thatcher
Had to take a pee in the night. So she rolls out of her bed which is like a sleeping bag kind of on the ground
Yeah, and she just squats there where they're humongous boys, but and she doesn't she didn't even
Wipe or dry off anything and she's called back in the bed with the same white butt
And so it's back. That of course is when you talk imagine all over the papers
So yesterday and quite a spread it is but she is she is really an iron daughter or something because
Yeah, she is absolutely not the freight. I had the bushwacker trial and the other girl other woman
I don't know her name. What is she like a theater actress or something? She seems like that. Yeah, I don't know. Oh, she is she is
She was an emeraldale. Oh, so guys. She was in yeah another so there's something yeah
So they both had to do the bushwacker trial where you have to eat stuff and it started off with what they started off
I can't remember what they started off with
What was the first thing nasty oh worms? No, it was no worms no that was later on. I can't remember what was first or something like that. Well amongst the delicacies which they ate
We're fish eyes, which okay that that's all right. That was not too bad. What are milder
Come out of dead bodies
Oh
I don't know what it's called
maggots maggots maggots handful of maggots one of these humongous caterpillar type things. It was alive
Oh, they had to eat a cockroach cockroach
Yeah, yeah, they had cockroaches and then kangaroo penis
Yes, and kangaroo testicles
That was that I couldn't even test them. They get points for that and then they do and then they
Anyone who eats kangaroo dead stars and every star is a meal because they're starving
There's so hungry that you're kangaroo dead
So two of them were sitting there and I have to say that Carol was now she was great she was so brave
She just picks shit up and just ate it, man
And you could hear a crunch a cockroach
Like that a couple times she almost puked
Yeah, she gags a little bit but then what what was so funny was and then the other woman had to eat a the kangaroo penis
Just a tip yeah, just a tip and she was very tough and
So she to a piece of and she said
But when she was done she said can I have a sip of water? I have to get that penis
Taste out of my mouth
It was very funny. No, it's almost said what does it taste like yeah, and she said like ass
And then someone else then say how does she know what else taste like
Yeah, we wonder
What would you be in the the kangaroo penis? No, no way no, I would have eaten that I would have eaten the penis
Yeah, I can't even eat a blue cheese
Really, no, no, no, but it's fantastic you know how I I don't like that you don't there's the you don't put anything in your mouth
No, because we were listening to the two ladies on the internet
Yeah, talking about penis whispered pearls. Yeah, yeah talking about penis. I think I want to I want to do a deal with with that podcast
Because
You know, it may not have got the desire to affect on you
For one penis to the other penis. Yeah, exactly. Yeah
I've so I started playing this podcast right in the middle somewhere and the butcher says are they talking about your penis?
Well, because it was good. Well, it was good
They had they were talking about the most perfect
Yeah, she had a home about it about the penis very serious. Yeah, and I said to you
Are they for real
Yeah
So they're talking about their relationships about man about penis is about the giving about penis
Low jobs, and I don't know and then more about penis. Yeah, and how how important it was for them to give blood
I said come closer hands give them like a blood
And and I was I was amazed because I
Don't understand
What well she was talking about giving strange man, you know, that she was
So into if she even if she didn't know the man just giving them a blow job right away
You know, are you saying this is not a good thing? I don't think so with whole others listen
Where was I? You got it and I'm really okay with that. I'm really I'm
I'm sure guys really didn't notice this about the old photographs of Betty Page, but I did
I wasn't
Then we're gonna close okay
So just so you know what's on the agenda still keep
Then he'll get into his Cadillac and drive away
What does this her fantasy cock
I want him to start suddenly by taking me out to dinner at an ocean side restaurant
Is her fantasy? I don't drive me home
Eat my pussy wall fuck me
Make my pearl like a feeling goddess
Make time stand still
Wait, where's the
I know and she was in tears and she's funny. I interviewed her. I don't know if I find it perfection of it. Oh, here it is. Here it is. Why mouth
Not yours
We both die or something. Okay, here comes
They are talking about those famous bronze penises of rock stars
Reop shining glimmer
Yet shining brighter than any of that was it that was it yeah yours the perfect cock
The cock that all people should create that's what I can mean and say are they talking about yours
Yours perfect in size and shape and smell
I thought if your cock puts items others to shame
The head of your cock instantly inspires lust
Is that the one that's a sign of my mouth
Not often enough
Yours that I would suck every day if I could
Yeah, you wish
You know, I don't want anyone sucking my penis
I'm sorry. I'm just not
I like it but that it's not you know, I got other stuff to do
I'm just like I'm busy on
Yeah, like today
No, but hold on a second. I was in between
Showering and shaving
Right and what did I say?
What did I say? I said no, I came in I said oh you're clean
You have your towel around you. Yeah, that's lovely because that's what women want to see
Right and ice-clean man, but I had it coming out of the shower
But I had it a six-day beard
He said it doesn't matter if we're not interested you weren't interested in my beard
Okay, yeah, well, so I
Said can I touch it?
Yeah, and I let you touch it and
Yeah, but then you said
What is this?
Not good right anyway, so something something to suggest I said oh, honey, please can I can I exchange it for
You coming on the show? Yeah, I gave it up for the show. Yes, you did
Yeah, yeah, but I said it's not like I'm giving it up because I can still cash in on it
I can cash on later
But we're talking about these some vintage
Yeah, okay, and
They are a little bit
Very saturating about this think I was happening with myself
There's a noise gate on it and when you don't talk then it cuts out
What's happening with my sound down it
So yeah, okay. Oh, you want to hear the magic sent in this thing that I wanted
Did you hear this yesterday?
I heard it. It was loud enough. Yeah, oh my second
I want to share it. It was funny though. Well funny. It's kind of you know, she's really angry
It's so Adam it's mad listen while you're
busy kissing Apple's ass and licking Steve Jobs balls talking about how wonderful
Enjoy as it is to pay a dollar 99 for a song for a television show you can watch for free
I'm telling you he's talking about lost. I I watch it again this morning
I love it. I love that you can download that for a nine nine. You can't get it here
That was so good. There's still an episode is one. I'm totally hooked. Yeah. That's like a works vision
I've been very upset with Apple actually and I as some of my discussions with you about
Apple have been tongue-to-cheek talking about Steve Jobs's high pants others have been less tongue-to-cheek talking about how
Steve Jobs doesn't care about gay people because he doesn't seem to concern himself at all
with putting a gay category gay lesbian kind of let me just say one thing about that
I mean he needs love no, but I mean it's like if you do a game lesbian category
Doing a directory of anything what happens if if all of a sudden you saw an iTunes again
Lesbian category and you're a transsexual
You know then what do we need we need a transsexual category? Yeah, I think this should have a sexuality
category. I don't know if they have that in iTunes
It's maybe yeah, I mean
Add a gory on the iTunes music store now
My beef with you with Apple today my video website and same films.com
Which was the first
video blog to be some scribble via RSS
Has been removed from the iTunes music store with no explanation whatsoever Apple did not answer in queries asking for an explanation
This is ridiculous and
Unexceptible completely my video blogs have been very very politically oriented there is some
There is some nudity no, but it is marked explicit as
Instructed and has always been marked explicit
So what's the problem and why is there an explicit tag if it doesn't matter and if any right wing Christian crazy
Person who doesn't like freedom of speech complaints about it. They remove it. Is that what happens? Where's the explanation at a minimum?
I should get an explanation
But anyway
The moral of this story is that the iTunes music store for podcasts has in my mind become irrelevant
Particularly for video blogs first of all. I would encourage anybody who's been screwed over by the music store to send
Adam at curry.com and email so he understands
These are numbers of people that have been removed and and
Basically fucked over by Steve Jobs and his highways did pants
Now secondly, I would like to recommend to
Comprehensive
Video blog directories that do not censor that I enjoy very much number one is me fedia
me fedia that's M E F E E D I A and vlogger
V L O G D I R these are both comprehensive directories that do not censor
Political or artistic content. I've had it with the iTunes music store only presenting network garbage
That's not what podcasting is about that's not why we started this podcasting movement and the apple can go fuck themselves and Steve Jobs too with your high pants
Go bet make your belt one notch tighter mother fucker you're dealing with match wine steam and get used to the fact that we consumers can speak out now
You
Look, oops, look match, match
Calm down. Yeah, really calm first of all calm down
You know
Don't you undone? Don't you see what's happening? Don't you see that this is
That apple is not interested and that if you're all about you know, oh, this is podcasting
This is no restarted for this stop relying on fucking apple
That's what I don't understand. You know, it's like look we're building an entire listener and viewer interface
Over at Pod Show, you know, let's get some of your ideas so we can make it better. You know, don't rely on that
Jesus and by the way, this is not people always think that some big evil plan that apple is out to fuck everybody
It's not it's like the shit doesn't breaks doesn't work
It's fucking technology and they've got three people working on it
You know to handle all of this stuff or maybe they have a couple more, but not very many and then people people this is same thing with with with Pod Show
They think that we're evil
Yeah, of course because you know, we don't we you know, yeah, we do think yeah, all right, and I do stuff
We don't do the traditional way of all as do a crush release. Let's do a crush tour
You know, we like to build shit get it out there and make it work
I think that that and then I think there's more behind it. Yeah. Oh well, there is of course
I mean
Yeah
So so that you know, so imagine like yelling at Steve John did I hear that yesterday
Yeah, it was through out of the house
Fuck you
But it's not so unnecessary. You know, it's so unnecessary. Fuck him. It doesn't matter
It's like everyone is like you know without iTunes podcasting won't exist all of a sudden
You know as if if you if you wanted to find a podcast about a particular topic. What would you do
When you just go to Google and say find podcast about
What would you want to hear a podcast about me? Yeah
Oh everything actually it's just people talking about everything
Okay, yeah, but be anything right so you're dealing give a shit of it's a particular topic
No, so maybe you'd say I want to
I always want to learn something right, but there's something that I don't know so
So what would you do if you wanted to go find a podcast where would you go?
Why would I go? Yeah, would you come ask me? Yeah, yeah, that's exactly how it works. That's the whole point
I'll ask and I'd say try it. Yeah, you're a department fan. Thank you, baby. Yeah, yeah, of course
Of course, of course that's how it works and not like oh let me go to a fucking director. Yeah
Yeah, you know, it's like oh, I don't I don't believe that's not the way I don't do that when you want to find what's on TV
Well, good show. How do you do that? You ask me yeah, exactly see
See
I'm talking about
She needs some angel kisses who match yeah from a woman yeah, you know for the time yeah, of course
Yeah, he's a lesbian so I'll give her some angel kisses on her back on all the way down
And she feels weeks oh, yeah, but I think so all the way down. Yeah, oh
Can I watch? I don't know if match one
Okay
Can I think else I got some of I've got some other shit I can do
We just think we have to talk. I don't know. I don't think there was I already talked about the car
We don't have that yet. No, we have no car at all. No, and then again our bikes are gone. Yeah
You know Christina. That's I wonder if he was raining and cold until can we can we use our
You know as as good Dutch people we had bikes in the in the garage
Because we bikes in Belgium and in Holland and
Which is not possible here because it's too too steep into
How it's it's possible?
Yeah
Hard attack so the boy said can we use your bikes you'll get them back tomorrow?
Yeah, that was too much
Well, it was more than two months ago. Yeah
So we have nothing right now. So I went to the hairdressers yesterday
I already told the story and I walked. I already told the story. I thought I was you're gonna tell the story again
No, I'm not I'm not I'm not I was so proud of myself
Can I say one thing your hair is very cute? Yeah. Yeah very cute absolutely. Oh
Okay, I love how you take off. I had a thank you so much
Darling oh
Really, of course. Darling. Yes, thank you. Let's play some music baby
This is
Oh, this is that Mike viola
No, no, no, no, no, I'm sorry. This is the butterfly catchers
Yeah, I don't know where I heard it, but I liked it a lot of course it's from the Potsay music network. This is
Wake up on the daily source card
No, no, just a time
Get up and fight
Don't you realize we call this a set of world of life
Who's here I am
I'm coming to say that
Even if you don't want to be safe
Well, you're right
I'll come to get you
We know my life just for this day
You're so excited
I know you've been trying just trying to make it through the day
You didn't love you
Don't let that cry
Believe it baby, where can I say
We know
Wake up to me
Stand up
Stand up and shout
You didn't have so much you can't fight me
Where you are
I'm back
Thank you so much
You don't seem to realize
So amazing
You're so excited
Don't you realize
I'm coming to say that
Even if you don't want to be safe
Yeah, you're right
I'm coming to get you
We know my life just for this day
You're so excited
I know you've been trying
Just trying to make it through the day
You didn't love you
Don't let that cry
Believe it baby, where can I say
We know
You're so excited
I know you've been trying
Just trying to make it through the day
And you belong to him
I'm coming down to crying
Believe it baby, where can I say
When I see it
When I see it to you
We come to me
Believe it
You don't like this kind of music
No, I know
Never this, she has a sweet voice
I like this kind of freak you
The whole thing
So I angry, angry chick with the guitar
So bands
Yeah
You don't like that
That's okay
For
Big finish
Okay, all right
Sounds a bit Irish
Could be a bit of an Irish
That's true
Okay, baby, so do anything else or should we
This is a longer podcast than normal because you drop by
Oh really
Well people love it hearing you
Yeah, it's the soap
Yeah, oh, dude
I'm cold and this house sucks
I
Come to winter
I told you
No, what did they do for the past six months have been working on this house
And what difference is it?
Or maybe a little bit but it's a little bit different
Yeah
Because because the last time yeah, because the last winter
I we could feel the wind blowing
And okay, well has the blow on that hard
Yeah, you just wait
They don't happen
There's a lot blowing but not the wind
Okay, dokey dokey
Okay
All right, so we go what are you going to do?
What are we going to do? What are we going to do?
What are we going to do?
Let's have another cup of tea
Yes, we'll now go a little bit
Oh, yeah, so we don't have any fire logs
No, and we can't go out
Because we don't have the power to get fire logs
I'll just go up to the
Get some woods on the chop something up
Chop it
Okay
It would
All right
I have to take this my signature sign off
Uh-huh
Oh
Okay
All right, I love you
I can love you too
Bye
Another pop show pop test
Stick it in your ear