don't just share a charlie one nine or nine or
nine or
that would
the two podfathers sitting next to each other
oh and their shaking hands right now
to hear the crowd is very very happy about that
16 million dollars worth of airplane
strapped to my ass
than the next generation radio content in my ears
we don't need us thinking
crazy
I like to think I'm
flying into this journey
fantastic
hey everybody how you doing
coming to you from my hotel room
this is
daily source code episode
one hundred and ninety nine
and that can't be a coincidence
my friends
no no no no no I've really
I've been in my hotel room
what time is it now
it's ten past eight
I left the conference
of course I'm talking about
nomdex
I should probably
restate for
not everyone knows exactly
what's going on if you just
tuning into the daily source code
but there's a conference
in progress right now in Seattle
which is
nomdex five
which is organized by Chris
Perillo and Ponzi
and there's four hundred
attendees here and speakers
and there's some really
fascinating beautiful stuff
happening
and
tomorrow I have an interesting
task
I'm doing a keynote speech
and when Chris asked me if I wanted to
the keynote for nomdex I immediately said
yeah of course I do
and
I would have thought that
the keynote speech is the first
speech of a conference
but in this case it's
the last speech
and Dave Weinner actually did the
keynote speech
this morning which was the first
speech
and I've never done one at the end
of a conference
but now everything is starting to unfold
for me and I'm starting to understand
what my role is and what I'm
supposed to be saying tomorrow
and I did tell everyone hey
I don't know what I'm going to talk about yet
because I want to attend the conference
and I have figured it out
which of course makes this daily source code
rather difficult
because
I don't want to
you have to understand the situation
so
I've got a really nice room
as a great hotel
it's beautiful
it's not large but it has everything
it's got a table near the window
and I'm overload
I'm looking out into the street
so I'm not looking towards the water
side
but that's okay
I'm not looking outside much
and there's a table there
with a lamp
and I've got my
my Mac
I've got my Craplet
which I'm actually recording on
and cast Blaster
which I think
tomorrow we're going to open up
a time limited beta
or something like that
I haven't really been focusing too much on it
so I'm just kind of letting that go
it's course
but that's something to hear
you know there
although I am really excited about it
and I've got papers all over the place
I've been writing down notes
I was actually just
watching the
MSN Channel 9
I'll just call it a podcast
it's video
but I'm going to call it a podcast
Robert Scobel did
basically a
reiteration of what Dean told us today
what Microsoft is doing
what he told us at the conference on stage
with Microsoft is doing with RSS
and that moment stuff
really just started to click together
and I got all kinds of
just all made sense
it really did
so I'm very excited about
now preparing for my speech for tomorrow
which I'm not sure what time it is actually
well I don't really look it up
it's at the end of the day
and so I'm probably going to just stay in
and order some room service
and just kind of vibe on through it
and I'm really motivated
really excited
because this is just
just hit me
and let me see
I had a couple notes
I want to talk about for this
podcast
I want to kind of remove the
earbuds for a second
let me see
see this is all the stuff I want to
talk about tomorrow
oh
you something
I did learn something
I learned a little bit more about
techno-radi today
I've never really paid much attention
to techno-radi
I'm not quite sure why
but I'll figure that out eventually
but I really
I was just interested to see
how we were doing
what were the messages that we were sending out
what was the main topic
what is really going out
into the world
from these 400 people
and just typed in
Nomdex
and techno-radi
and I got like a lot of blog posts
and lots of audio and video
and pictures
and
eloquent descriptions of what's going on
very exciting
we're doing a great job
certainly doing a great job
and so now I hope to be able to kind of wrap it all up tomorrow
so that we have a mission
and we can go and go
go forth and do something with all this energy
that has just been
has descended upon
Seattle
which I'm starting to understand a little bit better actually
I've been here several times
on business to Microsoft
and I understand overnight
and I think
I'm on, I was at 4th Avenue
and like Spring Street or something
and so I've been able to walk around a little bit
and have, yeah, it's very nice
there's some beautiful parts of Seattle
I'm really enjoying
it's great to be in this city
for a particularly for this event
I think that's it really
I don't want to, you know, use it too much here
time this is actually very short
six minutes
but
most of the attendees
for nomdex
probably
are going to
or maybe
but you're probably hopefully
you're hearing this
because this is as much for
the nomdex
participants
as for
regular source code listeners
but of course I'm hoping that
when everyone's back from the
I think it's the Yahoo party tonight
that
that everyone just has a quick listen to
the source code
and that are really excited
about tomorrow
it's going to be lots of great
panels
and discussions
and
it is a kind of a good flow
of going in and out
you know, you can walk into a
it's a kind of basically
it's one big room
but there's lots of space to kind of talk
and there are rooms
where people can set up
and can record stuff
and everyone's recording a podcast
that's really amazing
I just wish I had more time to talk
to everybody
because
I actually
pretty much know
everyone who's here
it's
I know that I've
exchanged email
with just what everyone
has come up to me and people come up
and say, you know,
hey, how's Patricia?
How's Christina?
How's the dogs?
How's this?
And, you know, they know about my life
and it's really
it's a great experience
and I also know
often a lot about their lives
Okay, I think that's all I had
on my list
because I'm going to move this all over
to the speech
for tomorrow
and of course
that was what I started
off with
this is episode
number 199
something really just feels good
about tomorrow
because of course
I'll be recording my
nomdex
keynote
as
a podcast
it will be
daily source code
number 200
so that's just good karma
I'd say
wouldn't you?
Okidoki
let me just
me know over here
to the crapplet
with that
I will
see you all tomorrow
talk to you all tomorrow
if you're not in Seattle
look around
on techno-radi
to see what
what people are saying
about nomdex
and be prepared
because I think tomorrow
we're all going to
really figure it out
and be blown away
so
take everybody
another pod show pod guest
stick it in your ear