Daily source code February 8th 2005.
Transmeters? We don't need no stinking transmeters.
Autastic! It's Adam Curry.
Hey everybody, how you doing? It's Tuesday, February 8th.
The power of the door.
Once again, coming you from Curry Cottage, it is the Daily Source Code.
Well man, I've got some stuff lined up for you today.
I could not be happier about a couple of bits of news that I received today through email.
Time here in the UK and Gulford is 1224.
Once again, I'm back in the big green oversized ugly chair.
I've got everything all set up.
I actually have my second mic standing my just in case Patricia decides to come in and give me some shit about yesterday's hit test on.
Man! Thank you very much for all the great emails that I've received about not even recognizing one of my wife's biggest hit
songs. I figured out what the problem is right away. It was 1981 and I was either in between doing pirate radio broadcasts
or I think I might have been in college for that lost semester in West Virginia.
Okay, coming up today we have some technology stuff to talk about about iPodder and about
a podcast recording tool, have some pod save music and also some not so pod save music.
Why you might wonder why why well it was brought to my attention today and then I'm so excited about this.
Oops. That was me bringing up Firefox. It was brought to my attention today
that ASCAP which of course is the American Society of Composer's author and publishers have
put out a license for podcasts. Yes, this is apparently was effective as of January 1st. I'm not sure when this
license agreement came out. Of course, a link to the license agreement you can find in the
show notes for today. I'm going to read you a couple of parts of this because I'm just so excited to see
a word that didn't even exist barely half a year ago. Now show up in legal documents and
good legal documents, not the kind that say we're suing your ass. Here it is. The ASCAP
experimental license agreement for internet sites and services released 5.0 was designed for sites and
services that perform ASCAP music in a non interactive manner. What does that mean? You might ask.
Well, non interactive means that users cannot select individual songs or posted songs,
song collections unless the performance is not more than 60 seconds in duration. So first of all,
if you play anything for instance, young poet with his with his hit test would be less than 60 seconds.
Although I think the answer sometimes it goes a little bit longer than that. But he would not have to
pay a license. Okay, almost second. I'm going to have to sit with my T here because we're going to
talk about this for just a couple of minutes. This is exciting shit. Okay, examples of non interactive
music, that music uses that qualify for release 5.0 include. Here comes music that is embedded
on one or more pages of a site or service such as a flash intro. Okay, that makes sense. By the way,
you know, if you have a podcast and you're using an opening theme song like you just heard my
rock money enough. Now, rock money enough. I don't think I think the copyright is pretty much
inspired on the rock money enough. But it's a remix, right? So someone else performs a music and
if they're an ask cap member, they deserve to get paid for it. Second, webcasts of live performances
and here comes. Here's the one. Radio broadcasts or podcasts. Now, they hi-finated podcast. I'm
not quite sure why, but I'll just read that again. Radio broadcasts or podcasts that do not
offer a playlist program guide and do not make advanced lists of the songs contained in the programs
available prior to their transmission. And finally, song samples are excerpts that are not
more than 60 seconds in duration. So if I reread this one piece, okay? Radio broadcasts or podcasts.
I love seeing this show up on the ask cap site that do not offer a playlist program guide and do
not make advanced lists of the songs contained in the programs available prior to their
transmission. So I think what that means is show notes can't contain the title or any
information about the ask cap song, which is kind of makes it, I understand what they're doing
this. So I guess you can't search it and then apparently pull out that one particular piece of music,
would be quite an interesting technological feat actually if you could do that with a podcast.
I think, yeah, I guess technically it is possible if you had the time codes and everything you
might be able to suck it out, but that's I think that's kind of a technicality, but okay,
so that means you would not be able to list the songs in your show notes. And of course,
you have to pay some money. Now, this is where it broke down for me because I immediately was like,
whoa, give me the license. Let me see what's going on. I downloaded the non-interactive 5.0
license agreement. Hello lawyers. I know that you listened to the show. I've received many
an email from you and had conversations. Some of you, my friends, some of you aren't. Some of you
were my friends before you lit a gate on the other side. We need some help from lawyer. Hold on,
what's that? That's the neighbor. What is he doing? Is he sharpening his throwing knives?
Hmm, lawyers. Yes, I know that lawyers listen to the daily source code. Please help me out,
help me understand what this license is. As far as I can tell, if you have no revenue on your show,
that means you have no sponsoring or advertising, no money coming in based upon the show,
you pay $250 a year and that's it. You can play any ASCAP license music on your podcast.
If you do make money, then you have to pay a percentage of revenue and that's where we've got
really complicated. They have like three different schedules and examples and my eyes fucking glazed over
when I saw that shit. So they're far from understanding what we need as podcasts, which is just a
fairly simple license. If you're a lawyer, please, I really, I would appreciate so much if you could
look through this document. Again, it's linked from the show notes. I think it is legal actually
to point to the license from your show notes and see if you can figure it out. What does it mean?
What exactly do we have to do? And I'll say right off the bat that I think I saw like 15% so if I
understand just in general terms, if I say I make $100 a month in advertising on my podcast,
I would have to pay $15 to ASCAP if I played music. Now the question is, if I just have an opening
tune, which presumably would be more than 60 seconds, of course, that's your way out, right?
If you do it list less than 60 seconds. Or if you play maybe one song of the day,
do you still have to pay the full amount? I mean, the scheduling, as they call it, the schedule
of how you pay for this performance ride is just fucking complicated, you know, and I'm not a lawyer
and I plead all lawyers who are listening, please help us out. And as easily as possible,
please record this in MP3, send it to MP3feedback at gmail.com. So we can all understand and we can do
this in a fair and safe manner because wow, you know, I'm not looking forward to playing Britney Spears
or anything like that, but I totally would love to share some memories of old tunes with you guys.
And I know that you would love to do it as well. And I think it would be really, really good for
podcasting. It would be great for artists who have big back catalogs who are selling them
through their own website, for instance. It could just be really, really good for the music industry in general.
And, you know, the terms are, of course, debatable, but the fact that it's shown up now,
hold on. Oh, yes. The fact that it's shown up as, as podcasts on a license just is such
such good news. I'm incredibly happy about this. So today I'm going to be playing a couple of
what we would deem non-pod-safe tunes. And I'm just going to think that it won't be a problem
for me to, you know, add this on to whatever payment I'm going to make. Because of course, I'm
going to pay the $250, right? So as of today, I'll just consider myself licensed,
licensed, armed, and licensed is what I think. And it's good because I was talking the past two shows
I've been talking about Michael Jackson and how I believe that he's being framed in this particular
case. I've met this man a couple of times. He comes across this very polite, although freaky individual,
but, you know, what's normal? I'm normal sitting here, smoking, drinking, yapping into a microphone.
And it's just whatever you consider normal. But I think he's totally being framed and what's worse.
What's much worse is that we're completely forgetting about the musical profit that Michael Jackson
is. He said something really interesting on that Haraldo interview on Fox News. He said,
I think Haraldo said, well, you know, these days it's hip hop, it's rap, it's, you know, there's all kinds
of different musical styles. And you're still kind of what Haraldo was basically saying he was
being nice about it. He was saying, you're kind of still stuck in the 80s and 90s, Michael.
You know, you haven't really upgraded your sound or whatever. And Michael said,
you know, Haraldo, cultural change, style will change, fashion will change, but music stays the same.
The songs always remain. And that's kind of the theme of today's podcast, but I also want to
make sure that we don't forget the musical genius that Michael Jackson is. So let's kick it off
today with Don't Stop till you get enough. This is your daily source code for February 8, 2005.
You ready? Crank it off.
Just rise in the air.
Good luck tonight.
Hey.
Hey, Adam.
It's Richard Land全warchorid.com
I'd like to point your listeners on something real special,
On February 15t.
Then it will be possible to listen to you in real life
on the topic of nero costing and also in storage media.
But I think the nero costing part
part in combination with podcasting can be quite interesting. As far as I know, the first
opportunity for weeks or even months that people can see you live and there's something
interesting as well. The conference is for free. So I'll suggest your podcast listeners to
sign on and there's this special website which can be found on November in the
Mike-congress.nl. That's November in your Mike-congress.nl. And I think it's quite
interesting conference and I suggest the podcast listeners who live in the
Netherlands Belgium or maybe even Germany can join this conference on February to
15th and the location is called Happy Days. And what I did see but I'm sure that's
just a coincidence that the founding partner is Grandmasterview. You see you on the 15th
I will be speaking there as well and I will speak about business models for podcasting and stuff
like that.
Richard that was created completely with Nick's cast live. Sounds good although it's just looking at the
meters here at my output meters. Looks like the left channel was a little bit lower than the
right channel. I don't know if that's a problem with Nick's cast live or not. You can hear that
Richard had all these little bits mapped keys and he was firing him off and the sound actually
was really good. I don't know if there's any processing sound in Nick's cast live but it's pretty
impressive. Nick's cast live.com download that sucker. If you're looking for something to create
live podcast with on the fly this is not something you record you used to record and go back and
edit this is for kind of life performance version of the podcast which is the way I do the
daily source code. Adam Bloom sent me some tunes. Yes he's related to Ron and I just wanted to
share this with you because he's so fucking crazy to hear this version of an ACD C2. Here's Hasing Dixie
on the source code. Oh by the way you're allowed to sing along if you know the words.
Probably the first time you could understand that. I'm not going to plug in your own electric guitar
and the jamblers are fast with scenes. She kept motorclaims. She was the best damn woman that I've ever seen
she had decided that I still and we no lies out in me out in America that I've eaten more than
their share. Had me fat for a year. She told me to come but I was already there. The walls were
shaking. Earth was a curtain from mine. We were shaking. We wasn't making it in here. She made
all night long. Give me a tear you made. She made all night long. Working double time must have
looks in the light. She didn't want to catch it. She kissed mine all night long. No lies just
a matter of health. Made a meal out of me. Come back for my own. Had to come down to taking
movies around. Now I'm back in the rain to take it. Let the swing and the walls was shaking. Earth was
a curtain from mine. We were shaking. We wasn't making it in here. She made all night long. I have
mercy on the years. She made all night long. You're able to make it in here. She made all night long.
Got it now. I'm standing here. She made all night long. Yeah, you should make.
You're able to make it in here. You're able to make it in here. You're able to make it in here.
Yeah, you should make it in here. You're able to make it in here.
Oh, god, oh. Hey, Adam and all the daily source code listeners. My name's Travis Hoffman
and I'm the proprietor of the Ponderplace podcast. What's the Ponderplace podcast you ask?
It's a place where I take a look into the tales of the odd and moronic found in everyday life.
So exactly. What kind of tales of odd and moronic behavior am I talking about?
Well, there's always like how we just own cheese. How come you never see any metal sports?
How can you get 130% vitamin C in the orange juice? Why do they always hide the Valentine's day
candy and health information underneath the candy? Is it impossible to blow your nose well driving?
Do those blizz greens of death on one nose machine? You'll have to be that annoying.
Is lots of hair pigment threes on old people with their web turned signal on well driving?
Does everything need a four-none date these days? Why do charming compare toilet paper to pillows?
How come in Walmart? There's a mirror for your car that has a rhinoceros in it.
They show on your love by spinning or doing your pets really showing love at all. How exactly do you puff?
Puff rise and pump bleak. The secret service just hasn't blown anyone anymore. It's really not that big of a secret.
I think it'd be funny to put strawberry milk on an empty petal business model and just drink a lot.
How come mallwalkers are so dangerous? I think it'd be funny if that grocery store had sales on can do it.
And then hung up from the ceiling just out of reach two words, nerped car.
How come scientists have kept calcium and sodium yet? Why do you need a careful of your own?
Sorry. I get kind of carried away sometimes.
If you're curious about these pondering and many others, be sure to check out the Ponderplace podcast at www.
Travishopman.com slash ponderplace. Thanks. And back to you Adam.
Yeah, I'm tired. I'm tired. I'm tired.
Oh, I'm tired.
With your own polo.
I know.
Hi, Adam. Hey, young polo, I take you with a hit test number seven.
Alright, buddy. Again, I've lined up three tracks for you.
I bet you have.
I hope you're ready.
Yes, this is number one.
Don't forget to buy my wife in there, okay?
Oh, Charlie Wattley.
Oh, it's Chalamara, Charlie.
It's, I think it's Charlie Wattley.
I'm looking for new.
Look. Listen to that cow.
Do I hear a cow though?
And this is number two.
Yes, this is a Dutch group.
Frog with your fruit.
Swine bits.
No one else will know that outside of Holland or Portugal.
Your Dutch, you probably guessed it. Big hit.
And the last one. Number three.
Hmm, yeah, I know this one.
This is uh, Alice and Moier.
Oh, my head. Alice and Moier. It's all sung out.
Oh, cry.
I'll cry it out, I think it is.
And these are the answers.
And so number one.
It's Charlie Wattley.
And she's looking for a new love.
I hear a cow though.
I need a cow though.
I'm really, yeah.
Charlie Wattley.
The former singer of Schalemar.
See, I see a lot of people.
I knew love. This is number two.
We're going extra points.
It's a Dutch track.
Yeah.
It's Frank Weier.
And the song is titled, The Swatch Vits.
I should tell the listeners that this guy married
Amanda Redington.
She's a UK TV presenter and his hero wondering.
It's a nice guy, Frank.
So really good lyric in this.
I'm not white. I'm not black.
I don't think white. I don't think black.
I think in the color of your heart.
I don't think white.
No, it's Frank Weier.
And Swatch Vits.
Black and white.
Something in line of don't think black.
Don't say white.
But think in the color of your heart.
It's answer number three.
All right.
Allison.
It's Allison Weier.
And she's all cried out.
I'll cry it out.
The grass is gone and you'll be
baby.
I'm gonna keep it as I run
and hear the short and the narrow.
I'm not thinking anything.
I'll be yeah.
Also a great lyric to this listeners.
Oh yeah.
You took a whole lot of love and for a handful of nothing.
It's great.
Great young.
Excellent.
Oh my favorite songs.
Man, they made some good music in the A.E.
It's a bad hair.
Crad out with answer number three.
And this hit test.
Number seven already.
It's going fast.
Well, I'm still still working on the air checks.
You can't have too many of those.
Still searching for a piece that I can use in the hit test.
If you've got one, please send it to hittestatgmail.com.
And that's also the address to send your feedback to hittestatgmail.com.
If you want to download this edition of the hittest
or earlier episodes, you can find them at www.helpat hands.nl slash hittest.
So that's www.helpat hands.
That's an L slash hittest.
That's it for today.
See you next time for another
edition of the hittest. Bye-bye.
Thank you very much, young.
Excellent.
As always, the hit test.
And I forgot to put the site in there.
Yesterday in the show notes, it's in there today.
Hi Adam.
This is Kevin.
And if my voice sounds a little bit familiar to you,
but you can't quite place it, let me give you a hand.
It's time for Adam Curry to take the hittest.
I'm just one of the fellows that post over at radeogaddy.com.
And I just wanted to drop in and clarify
key things because I've noticed a few people have heard about the site
through you and other places and have come by and made requests
and been a little bit disappointed and not understood why.
And so I thought I might just drop in clarify
key things and help people get a little bit better response perhaps.
I first think to understand is that radeogaddy.com builds itself
as free voiceovers and more.
The original intent was to help low-power non-profit radio stations.
Exchange voice work so that, you know, if I have a station in the mean guy,
you know, you don't hear my voice all day long.
I'll have other people do voices like I have an Australian fellow
on my little home station that you'll hear.
A few clarifications on what things are voiceover talking.
If you ask for a voiceover or a dry read,
you'll probably get that filled pretty quick.
Somebody will just read what you type in and do give them a script.
Tell them what you want.
Just saying drop by my website and check it out and get an idea what I want.
That's not going to get a good response.
So say clearly what it is you're looking for.
And what style?
Upbeat, newsy, mellow, laidback, however you want to phrase it.
Next, a jingle.
Jingle has singing.
We do not do jingles.
You don't want to hear me sing.
That's all there is to that.
A sweeper or a produced element is what a lot of people are asking for.
And I want folks to understand that you have to have the stuff to make those.
And a lot of guys do not.
And you have to have the time to do them.
There's a lot of work involved in that.
So occasionally somebody will find something they think is a challenge.
Like this one I did for a game's podcast.
I'd rather like it and just kind of proud of it and enjoy doing it.
We're not talking your dad's video games.
So that's an example of a produced sweeper.
But as I say, not everybody's time to do that.
So if that's not what you get, please don't be disappointed that nobody answered.
Sometimes your post gets knocked down the list and just gets missed.
I hope this explains things a little bit and that folks will drop by and check things out.
And I enjoy doing the stuff for Yon and for you and for the hit test.
And I did not know about your podcast before, but now I'm enjoying listening.
Take care and I'm sure you'll be hearing me often because I don't think Yon and the hit
test are going anywhere anytime soon.
So this is Kevin, known over at radiodaddy.com is power FM saying now back to Adam Curry and the
Daily Source Co.
Awesome. Awesome. Thank you very much, Kevin. That's great.
That's clarification because I've been sending people over to radiodaddy.com without really
thinking too much about what the implications of that could be.
And perhaps we need to do something specifically for podcasts for that.
And I'd certainly contribute and you're right, creating sweepers and bumpers and jingles and stuff is hard work.
And usually I wound up paying people significant sums of money to do that for me is a guy in
New York, Dave Fox, WX Fox on the run.com is his site and he does, I actually have an exclusive
arrangement with him for for Europe when I do stuff on, you know, traditional radio and television.
But if you have a little bit of a cash and you want him to produce some stuff and he has the
time too, he is absolutely the best. But when it comes to a community-based thing like this,
yeah, I'd be happy to, you know, happy to cut some liners. Maybe, well, you know, we should think
about that where we can do if we can come up with some kind of central resource because the idea is
great. But, you know, maybe radiodaddy.com should be for a little, you know, for a different audience
than the podcasters. But the clarification was excellent Kevin, I really appreciate. And of course,
I appreciate the sweeper and the bumper for the hit test. As do I appreciate,
young pull-out putting that together every single day, I really appreciate that. Don't forget,
on Thursdays, we have our trivia Thursday, I have, oh man, I have such a big,
yeah, I got a big, you know, I was big. I have this Beatles-based trivia, I've got another
lost in translation trivia, I've got him here, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
five, seven, yeah, seven different trivia to us so far. And of course, there'll be, so let's
make that eight with young pull-outs Thursday edition. All right, almost, well, actually, it's
40 minutes, so I could end it here, but Christine and I were in the car this morning. What I,
when I tend to do is, I got my iPod running overnight and the iPod has plugged in, so, you know,
true to form, I pick up the iPod, jack in the iPrip and on the way to school, which is about a
15 minute drive in the morning, sometimes a little bit longer. Then we listen to whatever's come
through, whatever the latest podcasts were. And this morning, we heard this awesome mashup,
which I just wanted to share with you. So, you know, you can end if your walk is over,
if your commute is over, you're at the 40 minute mark, you can save this for later,
or you can listen to it right now, but I guarantee you, I guarantee you're going to want to crank
this one out. YouTube versus lyrics more, it's called calling on a Sunday.
And I told every group you go make it all happy night you're right next. I'm on a walk from the other house
and who the hell he is. And it's called a joke, I make it to my new meet in. So take your time, grab a take a week, I'll move to see you.
And I will now make you introduce me to my new people, see my name is Leverich's mom, baby, and I truly mean it.
For the past, I'm the future from the new women's and you can't help but leave it, you can read it, pay to it,
and you'll need to live a life, or see it's won't be in this more baby.
I'm a blessing, I'm a girl, see you, and I think, oh, that's time to get your dinner, baby.
I'm never running from a challenge ever, bitchy, bitchy, you know, rap, all the time we got that can't move in.
You have to see me do my best, son, I'm two fingers, play it too, not the two, show the wounded man.
I have a rumor, you may begin to feel the music, your feet may never be true, the music ain't love, be the screamer, baby.
All in a zone, every group you go make it all happy night you're right next.
Call it up to all, every group you go make it all happy night you're right next.
My life's a combination of my past achievements,
with a lot of heavy lifting, a lot of teeth breathing, a lot of courage,
a lot of times, a lot of mixed feelings, a lot of love, a lot of love, a lot of love,
you throw a lot of reasons, hang, bring out, I'm about to paint it on the mistreatment,
hang, bring out a little backstage, try the wiggle, me, you, hang,
forgot about the flowers, you underneath the crowded streets, drop in between the crack team,
a chap, hey, hey, fallin' like I like it in the kind of signal,
and you can pass it to my ticket, you're in the Masaliga,
you think I'll never hang head up for money, stop dreaming,
you think I'll never stop, hold baby, now you're richer.
I won't stop till I feel my known stop breathing,
I won't stop till I feel my heart stopped beating,
I won't stop speaking this weekend next weekend,
I won't sleep singing, I don't stop singing,
buy a freeze and I keep the fireball free,
no, man, won't break this from the metal times,
swimming, baby, call it up to all, every group you go make it all happy night you're right next.
Call it up to all, every group you go make it all happy night you're right next.
Call it on Sunday, it's, uh,
YouTube versus lyrics born at the end of the Tuesday source code.
Alrighty, oh, man, so, uh, 10 after one,
gonna have some lunch with my wife and, uh,
shoot this up to the bird, that would be the server, right?
That's it, feedback at amaccharry.com or for audio feedback, MP3 feedback at gmail.com.
Keep it all coming, and of course, I'm expecting lots of lawyers to be emailing about this brand new
license that we found. So, please send that off. And of course, you can find all of the source codes,
data source code.com for the archives, the latest show and the podcast feed.
And, uh, if you have a chance, you can also check out the weblog www.curry.com.
Thanks for tuning in. Thanks for subscribing. Thanks for downloading. I really appreciate it.
I'll see you tomorrow on the HumphDeadish Network source code. Take care everybody. Bye. Bye.