Well, hi, everybody. Welcome to the Daily Source Code coming to you from Central Park
in New York City. It's Saturday, it is 115 in the afternoon. Today is the 16th of April,
2005, and it couldn't be a more beautiful day in the city. This is one of those picture
perfect moments, and I've kind of got the right mood for sitting here on a bench central
park on the west side, actually. That's I see right off of Fifth Avenue, and so that's
the loud was at 57th Street. That's kind of where you enter the park across from the Plaza Hotel.
And the sun is shining, I'd say it's about, oh, just a guess, probably about 75, 76 degrees,
is it a slight breeze, which just makes it absolutely beautiful. Sun, of course, is bright,
and it's the oasis in this madhouse known as madhattan. This is actually one of the few places
in the world where I don't feel self-conscious about talking into myself, which I'm not. I'm talking
to you. You listening to this in your computer, or maybe you have it in your ears. You're listening
on your MP3 player, or perhaps you've got your FM transmitter blasting on your car radio. Maybe
you've burned this to a CD. That's all completely valid ways to listen to a podcast.
A couple of things, I mean, well, we're at a start, right, and I'm a little bit fuzzy because
definitely went to bed way too late last night. Had one night to catch up with a couple of friends,
and I'll talk about that, but that's, I got to go back, was it three days now, back to
Thursday. Yeah, Thursday, right, when I went to Denver. So I'm just going to try and
wrap up a little bit of the week here in New York and talk to you a bit about what's been going on,
and some things you can expect in the next couple of weeks. Actually, I was planning on having
Ron Bloom do a strategy cast with me. Excuse me, this is a fine cup of Chino that I'm
sipping here from Angela's Rock and Roll Delhi. I'm actually looking to look at this cup for a second.
We are crazy about great food in Rock and Roll, 1428-6 Avenue, right at the park, open seven days,
we deliver, and we cater for all occasions. Corporate accounts, welcome. But we were just so wiped out
from from the week, and last night, Ron is here with his wife, Martha. They pretty much,
if Ron is out of town for more than a day or two, then she always comes along. They used to live in New York,
so she got plenty of friends. And she's been kind of taking care of us every night, making sure
that we had a place to eat, and that we were everything. We were taking care of it just so sweet.
And last night, she said, no, we're going to go out to dinner, we're going to have our last dinner
New York, and I looked at Ron and I knew he was so fucking fried and I said, dude, let's just chill out.
It's actually went to sleep for an hour or two before my friends showed up around 1030.
So let's go back to Thursday. Thursday, Ron and I flew out for a day trip to Denver.
And this is kind of funny because we did this trip 10 years ago, almost to the day, probably.
We flew out to meet with Glenn Jones. Glenn Jones is the founder, and I guess he still does.
I don't know if he's the solo owner, but it bears his name, and I think he pretty much is the guy
calls all the shots of Jones cable, and Jones cable owned a lot of cable networks.
And at that at least 10 years ago, he did. And we went out at that time to talk to him about the
internet. And I don't remember all of them meeting, but I remember a lot of it, and I think that we met
with some other people primarily, you know, like his managers and or what you might call
to tenants and pitch this idea of the internet. And at the time he was certainly interested.
He's a, either a techno file. He's very interested in technology. He has, well, and he kind of
have to be, if you're a certainly 10 years ago cable, even though it may have been perceived by many
is trench diggers. You know, there's a lot of technology that has grown up within the cable business.
Just look at your cable mode. And you know, that was not something people were thinking of 10 years ago.
But I think Glenn Jones might have been. And although he was interested at the time,
we were looking at that time for investment. He didn't take any, and he wished us well,
and that went very well, as far as I'm concerned. So we had the opportunity to go back and talk
to about podcasting, and he was very well prepared. But you kind of got a, and I really wish
like I could have done some sound seeing, and maybe one day I'll go back, and then I will do some
sound seeing of the offices there, because it's, you know what it is? He's really an American dream
come true. He's a, really the epitome of an American entrepreneur. He's, you know, he's got
his beautiful offices there in Denver. He's building his legacy, which is Jones University,
which is a university by a satellite. He was, he actually, he was just starting that 10 years ago,
and I'm not quite sure how it's doing, but I think it's doing very well, just looking all the
uplink dishes that are in the scattered amongst the grounds there. And he's also a major contributor
to the US, the Congress, the Library of Congress. Is that right? Library of Congress?
Oh, here comes a little squirrel. Hey squirrel. How are you doing?
There's no tame here. Hey, hey buddy. Just walking right back.
And so we, we didn't do a tour of the building, because it, not that much had changed, but
what has changed is he sold all of his physical assets. I think he's pretty smart, you know,
where people are saying, now you got to buy cable, but one more cable stations, you know,
consolidate and he's saying, nah, it's over. He's selling. He's getting, he got rid of it all.
He's rebuilding his empire in cyberspace, his virtual empire. He's doing, excuse me for a second.
Perhaps I should have warned you. He's doing a building systems and all kinds of
interesting projects. But he basically has a big water cache, and he's investing it. As I said,
he's building his legacy. And my question of all of his assets, but he's heavy into radio,
and he's very interesting. He knows a lot about it. And he's not a, not an extremely young guy.
He's 74 years old. It doesn't look 74. But he's got to set up, you know, he's got,
right across his offices. He's not quite sure what the name of the airfield is. Of course,
not the main-gen airport. There's not an airfield, like five minutes across the way from his office.
And he's got his, his hawker 800 jet there. So this is the guy that many guys would like to be.
And he has his inner sanctum inside the office, and that, you know, it's kind of,
what is it like? The real beautiful shiny wood kind of French 18 layers of lacquer.
Just phenomenally beautiful with a library dining room area. He has a bedroom there if he wants to crash
out, you know, the private inner sanctum. He also has, and this is so cool. He has a war room.
We didn't go in at this time. Remember, 10 years ago, it's, you know, you go through these
security revolving doors, only one person at a time, and, you know, you really can't get in or out
without, without him, you know, the retinal scan type, the wheel, which is just, it's showy, but it's,
it's cool, you know, if you're going to build something, you're going to build a war room,
build it anyway, and there he's got, you know, just topped a bottom monitors and, you know,
the theater seats, and he can control his entire empire and monitor everything from there,
which is, you know, the kind of the, wah-ha-ha, I'll give you a white kitten to pet to what I
sit in my war room. But really, now the nowadays, it's a use for his, for his Jones University.
So, you know, you kind of want to bring each other up to date, you know, what you've been doing,
and he served lunch for us, and it was Ron, myself, Gary Schoenfeld from Media America, who I started
on-ramp with 10 years ago, before Ron joined, and I think Gary sold his company to Jones,
and so he's a member of the InterSanctum. So, you know, we were kind of talking, and they were
sort of, what, what do we get? We first got a nice, pronged cocktail, you know, the jumbo shrimp,
and then the main course was this, just, I, I, I, I, I, I, in fact, I actually said, you know,
Glenn, I got to tell you this, this, this, this beef, this meat, it's just so wonderful. It's so
the texture, the flavor, and I knew that they, I saw on the balcony of, uh, of the offices,
of the office suite, that, you know, there was actually a barbecue, and they were, they'd barbecue
this lunch for us at the office, go figure. Um, it's just wonderful, and he said, well, that's
because it's, uh, Buffalo, and I never had Buffalo before, but, oh, man, it's just, what a great
taste, and your knife almost just falls through this meat, you know, like butter almost. So,
so we're in this, this, this, this meeting, and again, it's in the InterSanctum, and, you know, it's
very chic, and it's, uh, it's very plush. And all I could think of as we're talking, and, you know,
catching up on 10 years of history is man. Chris Rockwell from the Daily Download would love to
experiment with Buffalo, you know, what comes out the other end after you've had Buffalo.
So that was my, my private little joke moment that was going on there. Uh, so then we, uh,
and we actually talked for quite a while, and then after that, we had a, uh, a presentation, uh,
for several executives within, within the company, uh, to talk about, you know, what podcasting is,
what, uh, where we feel it's going to go, what could be done, what the opportunities are,
what the industry needs if we really want to turn this into a medium, which believe me is money,
but was really exciting. First of all, there's some very smart people there,
know a lot about radio and understand the current, uh, dynamics of the radio industry and,
and have dreams that have wishes, you know, man, if only we could do this, and I think they got
really excited every single time they figured out exactly what they could do. Um, um, one of the
things that was exciting to me was, uh, in fact, talking to a couple of people from Jones University,
they immediately glammed on to the power of, of podcasting, uh, in the scholastic system, and
something that I'd like to bring up, if you haven't heard of it before, if you haven't seen it,
a for about, oh, man, I think almost five years now, I've been running schoolblocks.com,
and schoolblocks.com is a free weblog service for anyone who's going to use it for scholastic purposes,
so that can be teachers, students, uh, administrative personnel, professors,
anyone who was going to use this for an educational purpose, uh, is welcome to open up a weblog at schoolblocks.com.
And, uh, it's not, you know, the fastest service in the world because, uh, well, it runs on one
server, which is as tuned as possible, you know, but there's a lot of support that goes into
at Marcus Mowler, who's been working with me for, uh, for as many years at least, um,
maintains that 24-7, make sure the server's running provides support to people who kind of fall off the edge.
It's, it runs on a vanilla server, so sometimes shit just breaks and fucks up, and, you know, that happens,
and stuff that, um, a user can't even fix. I don't know if you've ever seen that with a vanilla site,
where somehow something with the calendar and you switch over, or you switch over to the next month,
and I'm not quite sure how you can get into the situation, but it can just break, and then you get this,
or error at the home page of your weblog. So he fixes all that stuff regularly, and it just helps people
when they don't quite understand. Um, we have a donation button on, uh, on all of the
school blogs, um, a PayPal donation button. I think that I've received a whopping total of,
maybe $500, and now probably $1,000 and five years, but that's not what it's about.
It's, uh, maybe it's, we'll just call it one of my ways of, uh, of contributing back.
Um, but they completely understand, uh, the power of, uh, of that interactivity. And you know,
that was something that started in my daughter's class. And if, if you look at the traditional
student teacher relationship, her, her, I'm going to say her, um, fifth grade class. That is with the
Peter Ford or teacher. I talked about this in blog about it many, many times. Look up Peter Ford.
He's one of the true heroes behind this project. And, um, if you have, you know, if a teacher
says, okay, here's your assignment. I want you to write this, you know, story or paper or whatever,
then the student will write it and we'll hand it into the teacher, you know, basically saying,
okay, teach here it is. And, you know, here's my effort towards you because you're really writing it
for the teacher and maybe not for anybody else. Now if the teacher said, if the assignment says,
you know, write this on your web blog or write some blog posts about this topic or create a project
outlined for this, uh, for this assignment. Um, then it kind of the dynamics change because not only
will the teacher be able to see it, they'll be able to see it as you're writing it perhaps as
edits occur. Your peers and the classroom will be able to read along and check it out. And, uh,
as well as your family and friends and anyone else who give the URL to. So, all of a sudden there's
an audience and then the dynamics are writing and reading and the interactivity between the two
with comments, uh, really changes the way, you know, the work is done. And, uh, I'm not an educator.
I, you know, I don't know anything about teaching. Uh, I wasn't too brilliant in school myself,
but I've seen the results and I've seen how incredibly motivated kids got, um, to be a part of
something like this. And, essentially, the podcasting part is, you know, we can add just a few
bits to it and, you know, you can turn all of these, oh, I don't know how many thousands of school
blogs are already created. You know, they all could be podcasting. They could be podcasts, uh, show notes
and, uh, and podcast feeds. And, we talked about all the different kinds of opportunities there.
And, uh, I think that something might come out of that. I'd be very excited to see if we can, uh,
set something up, uh, particularly with Jones University, who knows what else. So, let's see,
then we flew back, we flew coach. I mean, I can't, I just can't bring myself anymore to pay for
business class or hire. I think we've talked about this a couple times, uh, the price is just so
fucking outrageous. It's just, you know, it's not normal anymore. And what do you get? You know,
you don't get any real extra benefit, a little bit of legroom perhaps, but, um, you know,
what we're talking about, three and a half hours. That's not too bad. And it was an Airbus A319,
you know, my favorite. I love the Airbus. That's what easy jet flies. So, I actually discovered now
that I could take easy jet for a longer period than, uh, than the regular hour that it takes to get to Amsterdam.
So, in total, I was on easy jet for seven hours, uh, easy jet on, uh, United, uh, back and forth
from Denver, uh, for total of seven hours. Uh, and it didn't kill me. I wasn't too bad. We did
investigate an upgrade, which is going to be $325 per person each way. That's as screw it dude. Well,
let's drink $700 worth of wine and we get back, which we haven't done. So, I guess we did pretty good.
I was something else I was going to say about the two. Oh yeah, United is the only airline
by the way. Uh, and as far as I know, the only airline, uh, ever in the states to have a, on channel nine,
they, uh, they do from the flight deck. And essentially, you're just listening into the comms on the radio.
So, you're not actually hearing the cockpit, but you're listening to whatever is the, uh, the, the,
the captain and, uh, whatever is heard up on the flight deck on the radio. So, you can really follow
along air traffic control, um, on the way out, uh, there was only music on channel nine and I said,
I asked the, uh, flight attendant, you know, can you please ask the captain to turn it on and
say, no, this captain won't do that. I don't like what the fuck. What are you afraid of, dude? You know,
afraid that we're going to hear you screw up or something like that? Who told on my battery
pack almost fell out? Um, but the way back, um, I was able to track us all the way from Denver,
from Denver to, uh, let's see Minneapolis. I think it was Minneapolis first.
Minneapolis, then Chicago, it was Chicago Minneapolis. Uh, there's my topology for you.
Cleveland and eventually, uh, into New York. Um, and I hadn't really had a chance to
really sit there and listen to air traffic control for, you know, the big guys, uh, because usually
I'm, um, you know, much, much lower altitude. We're talking, like, between, uh, 500 and, uh, and
4,000 feet versus, you know, flight level 35. Oh, it was like 35,000 feet and higher. Uh, but I could, of
course, follow along the knew what they were talking about. And, uh, that was quite enjoyable. Uh,
that made it, especially because Oceans 12 was the movie and I'd already seen that. So, uh,
I was, uh, I was kind of cool just chilling back and just, uh, kind of, uh, flight. It was,
you know what it was? It was basically a sound seeing tour for me. That's what it was.
Shitty quality, of course, on the, uh, in the, in flight entertainment system, but it was a total
sound seeing experience, uh, and I, and I really enjoyed that. I think it was anything funny that I
heard them talking about on the way. Not basically, they were just asking for ride reports, you know,
well, how's the chop, which means any turbulence? And, uh, if there's turbulence, the
pilots will pass that on to air traffic control. And, uh, you know, they can change altitudes accordingly,
uh, to kind of avoid it and make the flight for the passengers that much more enjoyable.
I knew, I know there's something that I'm forgetting to say about, uh, about the flight back. But
anyway, so got in back to LaGuardia, we got in late, completely fried. Uh, so that was the, the first
source code that I wasn't able to be able to cut for the week because of, uh, just total fried
ness. And I wanted to say something about the elevator cast. Um, so the responses that I received to
it, uh, were overwhelmingly positive. Uh, it seems that this theater of the mind and, you know,
what's going to happen next and, and just being there and closing your eyes and listening to, you know,
whatever I was doing or describing as we're going through steps, uh, is very compelling to people.
Uh, and I personally, I'd love to hear lots more sound seeing towards, I love listening to
bicycle mark and, you know, match-wine steering going to target, you know, trips me out. Um,
but some people made some very, a very valid point which I hadn't thought about. Um, it's one
thing I guess to be walking around and have kind of a, a background of noise that you can listen to
and follow along with. It's another thing, well, actually, and also, and I feel that if I'm in an
elevator and, you know, that's a public space and if people are talking to each other while I'm
standing there, then, you know, that's okay. That's a part of background noise and, you know,
if someone just, if we just strike up a conversation, I think that's kind of where maybe I did go a
little bit overboard, uh, because essentially I'm, I'm recording people illegally, uh, or
without their knowledge. And so I talked to, you know, the extra who, um, who was waiting in line
for her shot at, uh, being an extra. Uh, there was the auditions. Uh, on the, the WB, uh, pilot
for, what is it, the new WB show, the prince? That actually isn't very cool, uh, to do that without
someone's consent. Uh, yeah, it's cool to talk and ask people for someone questions and say,
hey, what's going on, but it's, I guess, not cool to, to put that on a podcast. There just really
wasn't thinking about it. So, uh, there's a good point there, and I, and I won't do that, uh,
again, purposely. Now, if I'm just sitting here on the, on the bench, and someone would sit next
to me and strike up a conversation, I think I'd probably talk to him for a couple of minutes before I'd
say, you know, by the way, this is being podcast, uh, but purposely going out probably wasn't okay.
And, and one of two people mentioned it, and, and first I thought, I don't know what's that
shit, man. And then I thought, no, that really is kind of a good point. Although, um, it's happened to
me in another context. I was, um, at the BBC, um, a while back. Remember I did the BBC sound
seeing tour, which I announced I was doing it at that, at that point, so that was cool. And I said,
hey, you know, I'm, I'm recording all of this. And that's, uh, uh, uh, that was for click online.
And, uh, a couple days later, um, uh, the pieces from the interview that I was doing on camera,
showed up in a piece on BBC.com, uh, in a technology piece, which, by the way, I like, I like,
was written. I thought it was pretty funny. Uh, Koso wrote that. He's, uh, from the blog cast,
VLUG. Um, but he didn't tell me that he was going to, you know, because he was basically sitting
next to the camera next to the person interviewing me. Uh, he didn't tell me that that was going
to be written up into an interview as if we had sat down and we're doing an interview. And it was
kind of surprising. Um, and also, and, and the thing that was really surprising to me is that on
camera, um, uh, I was talking about podcasting, you know, a camera, of course,
camera, exactly what the question was. But then I said, as a joke on camera, which is a totally
different context, I say, you know, I really should be knighting for this stuff. And when you, you know,
I was doing it to the camera, you know, doing a play to the audience who would be watching if they
were to use, I don't know if they used that in the, in the, in the, in the, in the piece or not.
But I did that in a very different context than I would have done it with someone who was doing a
written piece. And so when it showed up in writing, I was like, oh, well, that kind of is taking
out of context. So, oops, the trash cart passing by. So it was taking a bit out of context.
And I was surprised. And, you know, and, and I, and I, and I really said, oh, memo to self, you know,
got to be careful about stuff like that because, uh, if you don't know that you're being recorded
in a certain context, it can come across pretty weirdly. And so that really struck home with me
when people said, you know, hey, dude, maybe you shouldn't be recording people without their consent.
Just, I mean, forget the legal standpoint. The ethical standpoint is more important. And I received an email
from Dave Slusher, uh, who pointed out to me as well. And I got a degree. So I appreciate you guys
sent me straight on that one. You're totally right. Okay. So now we're at Friday. Friday we had
planned to kind of spend time in New York. Um, um, we have a relationship with Bear Stearns,
which is a big banking company. Uh, there's, uh, they have a private banking, basically it's people
who who help you spend your money. And, uh, Ron and I are both clients there. And, uh,
it was certainly by no means, you know, the most important clients on the block. But they're very,
very nice to us and set us up with a conference room and facilities whenever we're in towns.
We basically can have an office. Um, and it's, it's so cool. They have, um, you know, of course,
the, you know, banks are basically big, um, databases, you know, that would have database operators.
And those would be the, the traders and people who are using the system. That's what it is. It's all
about systems. And when banks merge, you know, the offices aren't important. It's merging their
incredibly large data systems together, uh, because, you know, there's computations that are
being made. And we did some work at a previous company for bankers trust and the derivatives
division. So I learned a lot about what goes on in banks. And it's, it's all about computers and
data and how fast it can be calculated, computated, how you can apply models and predictions
and it's risk management. Um, so of course, you can't just, you know, jacking to a network there.
And if you think there's no Wi-Fi networks believe me, um, uh, uh, so they have a conference room for us,
which actually has a separate DSL line coming into the building. So it's a very convenient.
Oh, I just remembered what I was going to say about, uh, about our flight from Denver. Um,
it's, it was, it was about security because, you know, it's now still at New York, every single,
office building you walk into, particularly if it, uh, if it has a bank in it, um, there's the equivalent
of airport security that you go through and your pictures take. And interestingly enough, by the
same Logitech setup, you know, that is used when you come into the country. So there was a big sales
job there, man. Someone really made a bunch of dough on, on selling the, uh, the security equipment.
And then, you know, you put your bag through a scanner and, uh, you know, it's all basically,
I think, just for insurance purposes. But I wanted to point out that it is now illegal
to carry a lighter or matches on board of any, uh, US air carrier. Um, and I was,
it's actually, I think it's been illegal to carry matches or lighter in your bag or your check
baggage for the past 30 years. Nice cigar here. Let me get that cranking. Um, but now you
not let allowed to even have one in your pocket, uh, which sucks if you're carrying like a really
nice lighter, uh, because they'll confiscate it. And, uh, you cannot take it on board in any way.
And the reason for this is, uh, the same reason we're taking our shoes off, ladies and gentlemen,
uh, the genesis of the lighters is because of the one guy, uh, and I'm not trying to downplay it,
you know, who tried to set off an explosive device in his shoe. So the way to make it, so apparently
what the transport security TSA has decided is that the way to eliminate that risk besides taking your
shoes off and having those examined is to not allow you to like anything. Uh, which of course makes
sense, but you know, why don't we just, uh, take your fucking grain out, okay? So you can't think
and can't do anything and then just leave all the damn checks to for what it is, you know,
then we don't have to worry about it. It's getting pretty fucking frustrating. And now, uh,
the news reports are that, uh, although we've, you know, we've hired and are paying for 45,000
people at, uh, airport security. Um, we're pretty much not that much more secure than we were before,
yet, duh. Um, um, and, and so now, uh, I think, uh, the administration is saying the solution to
that is to put more technology in place. So again, I'm just for a temporary lobotomy, so that you
can't think or act like a terrorist. I guess that's the best solution. It's pretty fucking tedious.
It really pisses me off. It's a, I just hate being lied to when it's snow job, you know, it's like,
it's marketing and has nothing to do with security. You're not any more safe, um, going through
the current security than you were, you know, 10 years ago. It's just not true. So in once
a do something, there's plenty of ways to do it. And by the way, you can still fly down right through
the New York corridor with, you know, with a lightweight aircraft or an aircraft you want, you know,
you, it's just don't think that just because they're taking your tax dollars and spending it on
people in, uh, in white suits with impressive looking logos that is really any more effective.
So Friday, um, we had a conference room all set up at Bear Stearns and we had Brian,
Brian Longus. He haven't met yet. Brian is doing, doing operations for us at Pod Show.
He lives in DC and he came up. It was a mess because of the trains, you know, the, the high
speed trains apparently have faulty brakes. So they're, uh, checking them all out and that just
really messed up the train systems. He, he was coming in a lot later. And I got, well, first of all,
I got a call from, um, Dave from Rolling Stone Magazine and he wanted to do an interview and I'll tell
you that, uh, Rolling Stone Magazine when they call, you know, he kind of want to make some time
for him. It's, uh, it's an influential publication and I was just delighted to hear that, uh,
that the, the journalist, um, had worked at Sonic Net back in the days when, uh, we were just
starting up on ramp and, uh, we were actually looking at Sonic Net. We were pretty jealous because,
you know, those guys had some great funding and they were doing all kinds of cool content later.
I think that actually was, it was sold to MTV, uh, and we were doing Metaverse.com and the vibe
and cyber sleaze and not making a fricking dime with it. Um, and we essentially, uh, in order to
create a business, started doing things like that, but uh, worked for hire for companies like
Anheuser Bush for Budweiser. We built Budweiser.com and, um, and Reebok.com and did a lot of fun
sites that at the, at the time had a lot of entertainment. It was related to, uh, activities the company
was involved in. So Reebok, you can only imagine, you know, we went to lots of games, interviewed
superstars, like Shaq, for instance, who had signed up with Reebok back then, uh, for Budweiser.
We went to a lot of their sporting events and we did, uh, cyber cast, which meant, you know,
like, see you see me streaming video, audio recordings of, you know, anything we could get our hands on.
And, uh, that was, uh, those were really fun days actually. So he had grown up with, uh, the internet
and, uh, and had witnessed all the, the going commercial part. He's actually written, uh, a book.
Now, forgetting the title, uh, but it's the story about, uh, the guys that id software,
who created Doom and Quake, and now he's writing another book. And, uh, so we, uh,
walked a bit on the streets, uh, talked about, you know, the potential of podcasting,
certainly in relation to music, which I'm getting really excited about, what, what we can do with
pod save music, because the more I'm exposed to what's out there.
New York is a great place to get exposed to all kinds of pod save music, because this is where
people come to try and make it, you know, it's, uh, this is where people are playing in the clubs,
waiting to be discovered. He, uh, pauses you here once in the while, it's been taking a
sip of coffee or a choke on the sea guard. 31 minutes into this. I'm going to try and keep it at
40. Uh, and I, uh, I kind of squeezed him in because I received a call when I got in, uh,
late Thursday night from Denver. There was a call on my voicemail from a music industry legend,
his name is Harvey Leeds. And if you've heard us talk about the Ken Clark and I on the MTV
Chronicles, heard us talk about, uh, Steve Leeds at MTV. Harvey is his brother, and Harvey has been
an epic, uh, which is now Sony records or epic Sony records for 30 years. Um, he was there at the,
the very beginning of MTV, you know, when, you know, when no one knew how to promote a video,
promote a band through a video. He's always been, uh, in the promotion part of the record industry.
And he's, uh, he's just, he's a great guy to know. I mean, he's extremely well-loved, extremely
connected. Um, he knows how to, you know, and he loves the music, you know, he'll, he'll fly a million
miles in the baggage space of an airplane just to see a band play that he really believes in and
and he'll promote the heck out of him. He, he does a great job with that. Um, and he, uh, called me and
he said, you know, I don't want to talk about podcasting, you know, can you? He, come on over. And
come on over means he invited Ron and I to lunch in the Sony club, which is, this is kind of funny.
This is on the, oh god, I don't know, it's what it's like, the 40th or 50th floor of the Sony building
it's 55th and, uh, a Madison. And it's a, um, what kind of, it's kind of like an observation deck,
only it's one big restaurant with multiple rooms. And it's only for, uh, the big, important meetings.
It's, yeah, every band has this as well. It's, you know, when, when either just before you're about
to sign the big artist or if you want to celebrate or, you know, if anyone's doing a big deal,
then you take him up to the Sony club, that is if you have enough pull, right? If you got the
juice of the cloud to, to, to be allowed to eat up in the Sony club, uh, then you, uh, then you go up there
and it's very classy and chic. And I've been there, I was there 10 years ago, I think with Sony,
it was that it was the hardware division. I'm not quite sure why, but I was invited up there,
you know, personal waiters and butlers and, you know, everything's just right in the food is, you know,
prepared personally and there's all different types of kitchens and and cuisines and you name it.
It's impressive. And it's fun, you know, it's fun to do that because you can, when you're up there,
you look out the south side and you can almost reach out to David Copperfield's three-story penthouse
apartment, you know, we can basically see him walking up and down his own house. That's kind of
funny. I don't know, the wind is picking up a little bit. And Harvey totally has the juice, you know,
you can, uh, everyone is like, hey, Harvey, how you doing? The waiter is, hey, Harvey, how are you?
Usually table Harvey, you're like your usual iced tea, Harvey, you know, and as I said, you know,
if you can be in the industry that long, certainly at one company and he's worked with every single
artist you can you can think of and he knows them all personally and he has this little kind of like
cubby hole of an office, but it's just it's a shrine to 30 years of music history piled up all over the
place and I'm sure he has five times that size somewhere stored away, he just filled with crap that
that he can't put in his current configuration. And I'm trying to think which part of the story I want
to tell first. Yeah, well, so basically what he wanted and the meeting was not just with Harvey,
it was also with the vice president of new media and his name is Corey, Corey Luellen. Yeah,
vice president of Epic Records, New Media, that's just getting his business card here.
And what it is is, Harvey was saying, you know, dude, I've been listening to these podcasts.
I want to podcast, you know, I want to like promote and there he is, right, Harvey promoting stuff,
you know, he's he's they're all these records that have to people that so many probably don't
even know these signed these artists, you know, and he's like, I kind of want to promote and
want people to catch your buzz. You know, Harvey is the guy that when he has new band he wants to promote
and one way to do that is through getting them out in front of public, you know, get them playing
for people. Then, you know, if he finds out whichever act is performing somewhere and he'll basically
beg and plead and do whatever to get one of the newer acts to open up for the successful big act.
And it was pretty interesting because he isn't the kind of guy that's thinking about lawyers and,
you know, RIA, even though he is essential part of that wheel, he just wants to get good music out there.
And we went through a couple scenarios and we talked about, you know, why not a lot of RIA
music is being played on podcast. And we can't put a couple of really interesting ideas,
some of which would have landed us both in jail and made us beautiful cellmates. I should
anyone decide to come down on us. We also can't put some really good ideas of ways to promote
basically pod safe music and, you know, some other ways to create sign-off and put some
and basically trying to create ways to make some or as much as possible,
available for use in podcasting. It really is just a just a question of legality.
Which is the same I learned for satellite radio. Here's something I learned.
Satellite radios, although not entirely regulated the way it's restory or radio is regulated,
does have to adhere to the digital millennium copyright act. And part of the stipulation of the
digital millennium copyright act because it does involve digital streams and downloading or a version
of downloading from digitally digital copies. Let's put it that way. It's that you cannot,
on satellite radio, you cannot play more than two tracks by one artist or I think from the same
album after each other. So there has to be a separation there of, I don't know exactly what the
separation is. It's hours or channels or whatever, because then essentially the theory is that if
you didn't do that, you could cobble together the entire CD, which of course is ludicrous.
I'm sure people could do it, but who the heck is doing that? Some, maybe, all, probably not.
And so there's, you know, if you want to do like the, what should we say? If you want to do the
Bruce Springsteen tribute hour or Bruce Springsteen's coming out with a new record and you want to
cut up an interview with Bruce Springsteen with, with tracks with a new record, it's either you
can't do it or you have to get an actual sign off for each individual project and Harvey is one
of the people who can sign off. So we had a lovely lunch. They had pineapple slushies just perfect.
We sat in a nice, you know, curved little booth and a couple of observations. First of all,
the lobby downstairs. So you have the Sony lobby, which is, I don't know, it's, you have the public
space down in the Sony building. You get up in one elevator bank that only goes to the Sony
music lobby and that's basically where you enter into the Sony music realm and you have to
check in and, you know, it's a security check once again. And the elevator doors open and it
looks like a hip hop convention. There must be 15 different hip hop groups. Some of them
cutting a video, others just walking around with cell phones. It was a madhouse essentially and
everyone had to wait in line for their name to be taken down and it's like four or five reception
is just, you know, going out at all the time and then they have to call up and the way they're
doing it because it was, you know, just so crowded and like everybody was there. It seemed like
everyone there had a record deal, it was cutting a record deal or it was going to be the next p-ditty.
You know, it took a while and what they do is they take down your name and then you wait and
then they call out your name really loudly and then you pick up your badge and then you can go through.
And it's a madhouse and we're like it's exactly one o'clock and so I call up to Harvey's office and
talk to his lovely assistant and I said, you know, we're down in the lobby, it's a madhouse so
we're going to probably about 10 minutes late just let, you know. And Simon LeBon is standing right
in front of me, Simon from LeBon from Duran Duran who on Wednesday night I think sold out the garden
completely sold it out for a concert and he's standing there just like like us two Joe Shmoans
waiting in line and you know, the guy says, okay, what's your name? It's his Simon LeBon.
You had a picture ID and he says, no, I don't, you know, because, you know, maybe he didn't, you know,
in Europe, you don't have pictures on your driver's licenses and I don't, I guess he didn't have his passport with him.
I've learned now to carry my passport with me and, you know, and then so he's waiting and Simon,
you can just see he's like, oh man, he's getting impatient, but he's taken it with great stride,
but it's not like the old days, you know, where you'd have a real vibe and it was cool music playing
when you come into a record company and, you know, people were zigging and zagging and getting
shit done and now it's just like this huge corporate marble piece of shit structure and he's
Simon LeBon, you know, and he's a, to me, he's still a superstar and he's being treated just with
as much disrespect as the rest and then they call out his name Simon LeBon so he could pick up his
past to get in and then Harvey's assistant came down and actually got us and walked us through
as that was kind of cool, I got a better treatment than Simon LeBon, so that was one thing
that I noticed right there, I'm like, you know, man, this is really weird, you know, this is not
the type of image you want to project of a hip swing and company that knows what it's doing
and is really going to, you know, is on the cutting edge of music, take another sip.
And as we were upstairs, I always, first went to his office who went up to the Sony club, I noticed
that the Sony club is fraying at the edges, my friends, it no longer, the other carpet isn't
well, the carpet's probably 15 years old by that this point, it's fraying, you know, it's just,
it's not as, they had, you know, it's decaying, it's slowly decaying and we were the only guys in there
that were talking about music, all the other tables were lawyers and, you know, the discussion
invariably at points is we're talking, then Harvey would lower his voice and say, you know,
the lawyers, because that's the culture of these places now, everything is being run by lawyers who are
just trying to figure out who can get the most money from each little piece of music and it hit me
then that these record companies, they're already, they understand the long-tail concept and they're
already applying it, you know what, hold on a second, I want to, the spot where I'm sitting right now
is now longer in the sun, so let me just move over two benches to get in the sun like, hold on
all the benches, by the way, have placards on and we'll read a couple of them to you,
a memory of Benjamin and Estelle Wachtell for Carol E. Holtzmann, in celebration of her 80th birthday
with love from her grandchildren, Brooke Alexandra Jackman, a shining star with a radiant smile,
compassionate, intelligent and beautiful, always loved the joy of our lives, didn't live very long,
82878, of course 9101, wow just hit me when I saw the date, let's sit on this one, shall we?
Wow, I just got a chill, I didn't recognize the 9101 because European date would be 11901,
quick reflection there people, okay, so now we're sitting back in the sunshine,
I was talking about the long-tail concept,
the record companies, at least this one, I presume the other three at this point, whatever it is,
they're totally applying the long-tail concept, what they're doing is they're just, you know,
and so the long-tail concept is, you know, you can have, let's say, one record that will sell
10 million copies, doesn't happen that often anymore, or you can have 10 records that sell a million
and that's what the record companies are doing, they're just signing up hip-hop groups for
predominantly, I think, or at least that's what I saw on the lobby, left and right, given
him shitty deals, you know, the first deal is always shitty when it comes to record companies,
you get nothing, you'll wind up with nothing, you might get a little advance, you can go buy some
bling, but that's pretty much it, and they just pump them out, you know, and each one, if they
can sell 100,000 copies, that's a million bucks, you know, and they just keep cranking it out and
cranking it out, and what they've done very successfully, which seems unethical, and you could argue
about that, is they've just set it up so that if there's no more sales, you drop them, just drop
it like it's hot, drop it like it's hot, and you get rid of it, and then just let them disintegrate
into nothing, you know, that's what the record business has been really good at, because the
record business is all about contracts and laws, et cetera, and a little bit about the creativity,
and so that's what's going on there, you know, while the big guys are upstairs fighting about
every single penny and trying to squeeze blood from a stone and, and therefore, hampering the
distribution of music and hampering, in our case, the discovery of music, that's what podcasting
is bringing, I think, is ways to discover new talent, discover new artists, new music, new creative
people, that's being stifled, and then doing that themselves, and bully for them, you know,
let them do whatever the heck they want. Harvey is, of course, the guy who gave me four CDs of
new stuff that no one has ever heard of, particularly sushi su is a name of a girl, I think it's a
girl or a group who he's, he's really nuts about, and he has given me the personal Harvey
leads permission to play that on the podcast, so I'm going to do that when I get back to the cottage,
I'm going to listen to the CDs, and if I like it, I certainly will play it.
46 minutes, let's start wrapping this up. So here's what I learned with all the meetings, and we've
done, you know, I can't just can't even physically tell you about everything because it's just so much.
First of all, New York is great, New York is kicking, New York is alive, and people are,
to me, people are just here to get shit done, they're excited, everyone's trying to help each other
in business, that's always kind of been that way, New York, but to me it feels like this city is
really bounce back. I hooked up with Rick Kalman, the audio guy at MTV was my first,
our Patricia and my, our first friend in New York, he was the guy that when we actually started
on the same day, I think at MTV, he started doing audio, and I started, of course, on air,
and but he'd been in New York for a while doing radio, and doing all kinds of various types of
jobs, and he was the first one that said, hey, come on, let's go out to dinner and he took us to a
show, which was simply what I think was playing at the Beacon Theatre, and he was just nice and
been friends for almost 20 years now, and we lose touch, and then we hook up again, and he came
over last night, and we were talking about podcasting, and actually, of course, I said, Rick,
he hooked me up, you know, I haven't had anything to smoke in like a week, and he said,
no, he's now working for Division of the New Jersey Police, where, of course, he has some
tests that he has to take regularly, so he doesn't smoke anymore, but he invited one of
two of his friends over who were kind enough to bring some of the holy herb along with them,
and one of them was a musician, a nice girl, Shelly, and did I say that right?
I'm spacing on the names, and she was showing me where she has her music uploaded on her
myspaces.com, they called a weblog, it's kind of a weblog, or you can set it up as a weblog,
and that's kind of her community, that's where she gets gigs from, it's how she hooks up
with other musicians, she produces and records all her stuff at home, it was a nice fire trek,
truck going by the park with a police siren, and we were, you know, there's like three people
in the room, and we're just hanging out, it was very much the American party, you know,
like, you got a bottle of coke, you got some potato chips, yeah, we got a party, and we're just chilling,
and we're talking, and we're hanging out, and we talked about podcasting, and everyone had read about
or heard about it, but really hadn't heard of podcast, and so I played a couple of four,
I played a bit of East Radio, played a daily download, played some digital slots, some
Catholic insider, you know, I tried to do a nice mix of, as an example of all kinds of different
stuff, and of course, they were blown away and just loving every single moment of these podcasts,
and that's one of the things I really learned while educating people about podcasting,
because that's a big part of what I'm still doing is, you know, teaching people
within the business community, you know, what it is, how it works, where it's going, what the
potential is, what can be done with it, you know, and that varies from, as we've talked about,
from the educational system to advertisers. It's the same thing I did 10 years ago, and that's
exactly the same thing, so then it was like, you know, people said, what's this internet thing,
and now they've kind of got that, and they know what an MP3 player is, or at least an iPod,
and so in explaining this, again, I'm realizing that we are not by a long shot doing enough
to get people listening. All of this talk, all of these, you know, tools that are being put out there,
is really for podcasts, there's, and for people who are already podcasting, and maybe for people
who have a real drive to podcast, but want a better tool, what is not being done, and this is,
of course, going to be the part of the secret sauce of podshow.com, is people are not helping,
the listener, people need to learn how to tune into these things. You know, for me,
my contribution to podcasting, or what is now called podcasting, was really creating,
you know, the radio receiver portion, making the experience seamless. You know,
people that have been recording programs, call them radio programs, or audio blogs, or whatever,
and putting them up on the web on HTTP servers for years and years and years, people have been
attaching those to RSS files ever since Dave Weiner and I met, and he created the enclosure
element in RSS 2.0. You know, that's been done, but what really made it happen, or at least what
was the spark, I think, was the magical part, and I still call it magic, and I intended it to be magic.
That's why my original iPod, or when I wrote it, was invisible, it was a script, you know,
ran in the background, there was no player, no playlists, no organizational tool, it was just,
you know, just go download this and put it on my iPod. That was the magical step, was removing,
eliminating the waiting part, or any intervention, which gives it the illusion of a radio,
a transistor radio that you pick up except the differences, you know, you don't have to
tune in to find something, or, you know, or tune in at a certain time to listen to something
that you want to, you know, you have the control there, your fingertips, and within a very
short amount of time what I'm noticing is that it's gone beyond the MP3 player. It's beyond the box.
People are hooked on the shows, on the content, on the creativity. That's what's going on,
but we need to help more people learn how to listen, so when it comes to
subscribing to a feed, it's still way too difficult. We have to do a hell of a lot more to help
people learn how to receive and listen. We have to help listeners. We have to grow the listening
audience, and I think there's ways to do it that go beyond the organic nature of it.
Particularly because there's so many different ways that you can enjoy great audio.
You could, you could buy it from audible, if you wish, you could, you know, that's a
service that people know how to use, you know, that's a reasonably simple system.
You should be able to get it from the iTunes music store. I'm not saying that you should have to buy it,
you know, that's the business part of it. I'm just talking about the ease of use.
It would be the most beautiful way is if you had an MP3 player that had everything built in and you
just, you know, click and select and you don't have to do any cutting and pasting and, you know,
or if there's a, you know, if you want to subscribe to a show, you use a barcode scanner. I don't
know what the hell it is, but there's a million more ways to make this easy, because I think for
every one person that is subscribed to a podcast and listening to it and enjoying it, there's
10 that have fallen off the edge and have not figured out how to do it. Mainly because of it's still
unclear, you know, and it's what's this little, why don't orange XML icon? Yeah, there's millions
of people who understand what it is, but there's hundreds of millions who don't.
So, part of the, the overall mission of podshow.com will be for listeners. In fact,
our slogan is going to be, stick it in your ear and we're about making it easier for people
to find the shows that want to listen to and actually listen to them and no matter where they
are, no matter what system they have and there's going to be a lot of promotion in that and
a lot of marketing and getting podcasters exposure. That's the way, you know, that's, that's the
words with any of these kids are cute chasing their mom with little sticks. So cute.
Oh, maybe it's their nanny who knows. So that's an important part of the mission of podshow.com,
and that's what Ron and I were going to talk about in a strategy cast today, but that's going to
have to wait until next week when I'm back in the UK at the cottage and we'll get on Skype,
because that is one of the things we promised each other to do. It's definitely keep podcasting
between the two of us so we can, you know, shit, how can you run a podcasting company in whatever
sense of the word it is without, you know, podcasting yourself. So I hope everyone with an
or company will be a podcaster or will do some form of podcasting. And of course, that doesn't
have to be the salilicoid that I've done now for the past 55 minutes, which is way over my budgeted
time. But then again, hey, Dougie, how are you Dougie? That's German Shepherd. That's way over my,
my budgeted time for a daily source code. But of course, it's the weekend. So what the hey?
Okay, so that will be my final thought for the day. It's
as if on Q, let's probably run hold on. No, it's not wrong. Okay, another call.
I'm going to wrap this up. It's been great in New York. I'm going to be back pretty soon.
We're going to sit here. Actually, I'm going to be back in at the cottage for at least a couple
weeks. Patricia is, see, she's going to be away May 12, 15th. I think 12th of the 15th. She's going
to 3-8 trip to the south of France. So of course, I'll be home with Christina for that. This week,
I believe, with a little bit of luck, if the weather holds out, the wing commander is picking me up
at Therrokes, which is about 15 minutes from the cottage, with the, with the Sess No 182RG,
we're going to do two days of training. I'm going to fly on Tuesday. We'll make a channel crossing.
I'm going to stay overnight and then we'll do more training on Wednesday and then fly back. So
that'll be just a little bit of relaxation. Get my mind off of, get my mind off of podcasting and
work and the world the issues for a little while and just chill. And we'll be announcing some
of the exciting deals that we've put together. Great ways for people to tune into podcast,
to find podcasts, to listen to them, to really build some more momentum and excitement. Because I
do see that still as my mission as a part of what we've created here in the podcast and community.
So now we've, we've all got shows and we're creating and we're tracking probably about almost
5,000 now at iPod.org. Popularity is going nuts. Popularity voting on podcast alley in other places
like that. It's just phenomenal. But we have to expose this to more people and make it simpler for them
to find out about podcasting and listen to podcasts and sample podcasts and and start to understand
what it is and evangelize. Another part of that is meetup.com. That's another great place but
shouldn't just be for podcasters. It should also be for people interested in podcasting and finding
out what it is and listening and finding out how they can participate. That's, and I think that's
really the way it goes. Because I asked the girl last night who was at our little party
saying, okay, so you have myspaces.com, how do you find people? She says, well really, you just
usually, you, you, someone tells you about it, you look at their myspaces, weblog. And this is the
way it goes in weblogging, right? And then, you know, you'll join as a friend. So that's kind of
the social networking aspect of it. You'll join with your own weblog. And then, you know, you'll
find more people and people will find you. And it's how they find you. Well, usually buy your
picture. You know, so everyone has beautiful pictures of themselves and sexy pictures and you click
on it and then you hear their music and then you get information about them and you see more
friends there. So that's kind of the viral aspect of it. And that's how it should be going with
podcasting. And it could not only can't work, but it is working. It's just we have to make more
of that available. And that's not just going to be tools and, you know, create, listen, synchronize,
you know, that's not it. That is part of it, but that's more for people who are already podcasting
and already in this medium that we're trying to build. And remember, we're still building this.
So if that means, it's funny because Dave Winner is written on scripting news and had heard
him say it in a podcast recently that the quote is, Adam Curry has sold out to the dark side.
And I'm not quite sure what he means. I haven't sold anything out.
That I'm not quite sure if you split that up sold out. I mean, that's like an artist and musician
selling out, which basically means going commercial. And the dark side, I'm not quite sure what the
dark side means for Dave Winner probably means mainstream media. So I'm not, you know, my action
so far, I don't think have shown any selling out of anything. Certainly not anything we've announced.
And I don't know what the dark side is. I don't know. Is the dark side Microsoft? You know,
I don't think so. I think the people of Microsoft are very intelligent and are very smart.
And you know, is that the big record business? No, I don't think so. That's Harvey League, you know,
guys who would actually love to podcast themselves and are trying to make it so that we can use
RIA music. These are all just people. You know, I think that's, you know what, if something
Dave sent me in a private email once, he said, why do you take it up the ass from the mainstream media?
And because, you know, I do a lot of interviews when someone wants to, and actually haven't
done a lot of them recently, I've been rejecting a lot or not even responding really to the emails
for requests because just I don't have enough time in the day to even go through my regular email,
let alone all these requests. So I try to fish out ones that I think will be beneficial. We'll get
the word out there, get people understanding how cool it is and how you can tune in and how you can
listen and what you can expect and what you can get. And if that's selling out to the dark side,
my friends, then so be it. I'm proud to be doing it. So this has been the daily source code for
April 16th Saturday in the park. That's a great tune by Chicago. I'll have to play that when I get
back to the cottage. Atimentcurry.com is where you can send your responses, where you can check out my
weblog at www.curry.com. And daily source code.com is where you can pick up the podcast feed to
subscribe to this show when you can always find the latest one to listen to it right from your
computer or the archives. Take care everybody. Next time we speak, I'll be back at the cottage. Bye-bye.