In the source code, my third is out by h and h.
Oh I wonder why, why, why, why, why, why?
And this is one DJ, you don't want to fuck with.
Cmondado!
Hey everybody,
that once again some studio stages.
This is the Daily Source Code coming to you from just outside
the BBC studios.
To be precise, that would be the Southern Counties radio studios of the BBC, located
at Surrey University right outside of Gilford.
Oh man, I'm really pumping the tombs here.
I got so many great responses to the past two days doing the podcast with St. Christina
yesterday and in the kitchen the day before that I figured well.
Maybe I just try to get my act together and do everything on remote or on location and
just carry everything with me, which of course has me now carrying around tons of wires
and my iPod and my iPod and all the gear that you need as well as my show notes in paper
form.
So it's the third of March, 2005.
So the first thing I want to talk about is this interview that I just did.
I've been here to the Southern Counties radio studio where they have an ISDN set which
is basically a little mixer and a bridge that connects two studios together and have a microphone
and some headphones.
Kind of like some stuff that the equipment I think dates back from the 70s, it's pretty
cruddy stuff but at least it works and I've been here several times whenever the BBC
wanted to interview me and today it was and I've actually, I've said no in the past couple
of weeks but this was for BBC Radio 4 which is I guess it's the pretty much the premiere
like talk station for the BBC and I know that my neighbors listen to it and I'd love
for Marion and Jimmy to hear me on Radio 4 so they'd know what the hell I'm doing and they'd
finally could put some clues into place just to why I used to sit outside in my car in
halfway between their driveway and the next neighbors sucking off bandwidth you know and
what all this pod iPod stuff is about this pod casting so and let's see I was interviewed by
you just see here I was interviewed by Rosie Goldsmith and this will air on April 1st can you
believe that I mean April 1st that's like in a month is when they're going to air this I mean
gee whiz anything could happen between now and then that was uh I kind of surprised me at the end
there let me just hit the the hold button here on the i River so that I don't accidentally
stop the recording um if he was kind of confrontational you know talking about uh it was actually
it was pretty much a version of uh of you know mainstream media press saying web bloggers are you
journalists and their pajamas who's kind of like well this is all amateur radio stuff and uh you
know do you think you'll ever get professional I said well excuse me I've been broadcasting since
I was 14 I'm a professional you know I've been paid lots of money to do radio programs and I'm doing
you know my own creative thing uh only I'm doing it you know in a different distribution mechanism
and there was something wonderful and I love it when when journalists report us do this and uh
you know it's never gonna make make the air and you know I should have started the recording of
today's source code while doing that interview but uh I knew there would be no way to get both
what they were saying and I was saying so I figured I wouldn't do it but um what was the question
let me think if I can I want to I don't want to miss a quote around this um she said um oops that's
my uh my i-trip basically stopping okay I see when the iPod shuts off then the i-trip of course
has no juice um she said well you know there's a reason for oh no um so unlike professional
radio broadcast where there's a production and there's an editor and there's this whole process
which of of course is uh is necessary and I said well why is it necessary why do you need all that
she said well I'm not going to answer your questions okay that's fine so um anyway we've got a
got a ways to go clearly so I'm back into car as you can tell I'm flying myself let me uh
put the sheet well darn through the whoops through all the wires here I got my headphones I got the
microphone but we do want to be safe let me see if I can position this mic a little bit better for
y'all as I'm driving trying to find a good spot to put it so we have a maximum sound okay that's
probably good there um yeah take a look my show notes because what I want to do is I want to
back up it's actually gonna be quite a job to get out of here I wish you could see where it is
it's really inconvenient and I have to back this mother load boat of a car through a very narrow passage
way so just bear with me on this for a second and of course there's cars parked on all sides just to make
my life a little more interesting okay let's see this is one of those where you actually have to do
it on driving your mirrors okay we're doing good and there's some whoops some audible help from
from the a8 the technicians at Audi woo this is tight so basically it's saying you are very close to
obstacle sir okay so I'm looking good looking good whoops I mean I should shoot I wish I should
I got to bring my camera along for these rides you would not believe how tightly packed this is
this parking lot so now I'm probably gonna hit a little curb here as I back it out
okay I actually have to now back down the hill in reverse because I can't turn around my goodness
for the attitude the BBC has you'd expect that I have a little better facilities okay
right oh okay so now I'm going down the hill in reverse you know what the screw it I'm going to go
open see if I can turn them there all right while I'm doing this let's go to our first track today
which I've got cut up here on the iPod which we're gonna play for you now through the
stereo system so the great mashup that I found I thought you to enjoy it it's uh
rather unusual version of let it be enjoy for a couple minutes
let it be let it be let it be let it be let it be let it be let it be let it be let it be let it be
let it be let it be let it be let it it be jelly
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let
go, let's go, let's go, let's go to the seats, go, let's go, let's go.
All right how many different songs did you hear in that Mashup, huh? No woman no cry,
a little bit of chili peppers in there and of course let it be by the beetles and as you
You can tell I've taken to mixing longer tracks right in so that, you know, you don't
just hear car noise the whole time, but you actually hear the track.
Now I'm doing that in post-production, which is only necessary because I don't really
have the required setup, the right tools to do it live.
I've been looking desperately for a little battery powered mixer that'll just take
a microphone and then, you know, hopefully with maybe a little bit of effects or
processing or at least some, some equalizer settings and then one, but preferably two
line inputs and then of course I wanted to have a headphone amplifier and it would
have to have an out so that I could route that to my recording device, which is the
I River IFP799 and then of course I wanted all in one box that I can just take with me.
Now I have all kinds of things strapped together and actually on the way over I was thinking
about this, maybe there's a way to combine all this in one of these smart phones, maybe
a trio or perhaps a Microsoft smart phone because what I'm looking for is the following elements,
I need to be able to record my voice, I need to be able to mix in MP3s with that, you know,
and literally in real mix, right, not recording from the speaker through the microphone,
but you know, some little software actually has to be built and it would be even cooler
if you could add to that, see some of these phones have Wi-Fi and it's so that I could
actually hook up to a network and perhaps utilize a handheld version of Skype.
Give me that and I'm your man, I'm telling you, I mean, how hard can it be?
I think that there are handheld devices out there that have all of these elements, we just
need to kind of strap them all together and please don't make me go learn, you know,
dot net or visual basic or some crap like that to get it done, surely there's some developer
out there who's thinking, hmm, maybe that first Apple script that turned an iPod or maybe
something there and I could go create something cool that people use as well, so, you
know, don't wait around, I mean, Microsoft say what you will but they certainly provide tools
for developers, so, you know, let's get cracking at, I mean, I wouldn't need my computer
anymore if I could, if I could do it all on one device, but I have to, you know, and by
the way, make, you know, hook up the buttons on the phone so you can, you know, map them
to like starting a track or open up the microphone or something like that and if anyone
out there feels they can develop this application, you know, I will be your number one
beta tester and I will certainly, you know, take it around the block for multiple spins
to, to make sure that it's, you know, that, that it's, it's matching the requirements.
Let's see, so, and also, it'll be great if I could have an outline on that for my show
notes because now I just have a piece of paper with basically a screen shot of my outline.
And one of the things I need to talk to you about that I wrote down is, Libsin, just
what, Libra is indication, they're a podcast, infrastructure provider, I guess, place
where you can go drop your podcasts, they give you some file management, your RSS feed is
created, you get a little show notes blog, really quite simple.
And I mistakenly said that their pricing was, was a little bit too high for the, for the
small amount of data that they were allowing and I received an email about that, which,
of course, you can all retrieve from the show notes at dailysourcecode.com or from www.curry.com.
Essentially, they have unmetored bandwidth and you're paying for the storage for the number
of files.
I think you start like it, five bucks for storing 100 megs worth of files, which is probably
good, in my case, for about five shows, but of course, you could, you know, move one
off archive at somewhere else or whatever, but the bandwidth is unmetored.
So, I was mistaken about that, which makes that actually much more, you know, much more
attractive proposition.
And if anyone out there has knows about networking, maybe you can explain this to me.
I've, it's been, people have tried to explain to me that internet service providers or hosting
companies that have a tremendous amount of data traffic that is being requested from their
network that is actually a benefit to them if they can provide that.
So, whereas you might think, oh my gosh, you know, all this, this traffic that they're
sending out, only cost gobs and gobs of money, it is my understanding, and again, I'm
not quite sure how it works.
It is my understanding that that is actually advantageous to a web host provider or an ISP
who provides, who actually is hosting those shows.
I'm not quite sure how it works.
I don't know if it has something to do with peering agreements or, you know, whatever it
is, but if that is true, I'd love to know how it works, because they know that stuff
that happens up in the so-called cloud is just really, really fuzzy.
I just, you know, I'm not quite sure I understand.
So, Adam McCree dot com if I'm just siren, let's come it up, let me see, is that it's
coming closer?
Is it here?
Oh ambulance?
Okay, I'm sorry ambulance service.
Okay, now I see, this is where I got to go over to my iPod again, and I got to line up
the next track.
Oh, this is great.
I came across this on openpodcast.org, and it just blew me away.
Let's listen to this little history lesson, which will actually help us, perhaps, understand
the future somewhat.
You're not fully matured in 1933 when Armstrong invented FM radio.
They developed a receiver and a transmitter to drive it.
They could tell the difference between lightning electric motors, atmospheric interference,
and the radio broadcast itself.
So you'd think that his employer, RSEA, would jump to the new technology.
Instead, they did everything they could to kill it.
Why?
RSEA owned two radio networks in BC Red and in BC Blue, and some of the biggest radio stations
that served large areas of the country.
The stations that were protected against interference from smaller stations.
FM stations would take away from NBC's power of position, so they sat on FM, and Armstrong
ultimately killed himself.
It's happening again.
The big players, the phone companies, the terrestrial broadcasters, the old-line media
rights holders, see their monopolies ending and their playing dirty, and it's only the
beginning.
Bill South told Lafayette Louisiana that if Lafayette utilities lay his fiber, Bill South
will pull its singular wireless call center out of the city, and the jobs along with it.
Texas Legislator Phil King, rich from big media corporate donations, is introduced
to Bill to keep municipalities from installing broadband.
Vonage is complained to the FCC about a rural telephone company who has blocked voice
over IP on its internet connections, presumably, so that you'll use their phone instead.
In Republican Senator Ted Stevens of Alaska, voted against a bill that would extend
in decency regulation to cable, but he has told the group of broadcasters that he might
be changing his mind.
That's the latest way to support terrestrial broadcast owners.
Make the competition illegal.
If you dumb down cable and satellite radio, you get the same shit being shoveled over
the air.
Get ready, because direct internet delivery is next.
A Los Angeles radio station owner petitioned the FCC last year to regulate XM and serious.
Sal the Vines said he wasn't anti-free speech.
He just wanted a level playing field, but the FCC's Powell sentiment out and said since
kids can't receive satellite without their parents entering into an agreement, it just wasn't
the same.
So where are we?
Vonage once the FCC to regulate Lex who regulate content by making it legal the
block ports used for VoIP.
The FCC hasn't decided that when yet, but has told Sal of Ian, that satellite radio
gets a pass because kids can't get it.
Kids can get podcasts.
In fact, they're more likely to get them, so VoIP may not be the only four-liter word
they regulate.
And who benefits from all this?
Legacy providers in Big Media, who loses the public and the poorer you are, the more you
lose.
I really like Lawrence Lessig's take on this on his wired podcast.
Governor Ed Rendell last year signed an anti-manusable Wi-Fi bill in Pennsylvania.
This is a pretty hard thing to sell, and he had to exempt Philadelphia because half the
poorer neighborhoods would probably get no internet if it applied to everybody.
But the gov dusted off that old socialism argument, which proves how far these guys are
willing to go to take away from the people and make it look like there's some higher
purpose in it.
Lessig really skewered him on it.
For if you look closely, you'll see that the communist menace has infiltrated governments
everywhere.
Ever noticed those free photons as you walk the city streets at night?
Everything about the poor, street lamp companies run out of business because municipalities
dain to do completely what private industry would only do incompletely.
Yeah, yeah, but we're all preaching to the choir here.
And most of the folks who remember the last time arguments like this were used are dead
or dying.
This is Adolf Margeau speaking.
If the Visionski or Molotov had been sitting in Congress during the past six years, they
could not have voted against the unemellican activities committee more consistently than
did Helen Douglas.
If she had had her way, a swarm of pro-Soviet turmites would still be knowing away
at the foundations of our government.
And now Mrs. Douglas hailed by the Communist line press as one of the heroes of the
area of Congress, this contesting for the seat in the United States Senate against Congressman
Richard Nixon.
One thing you can be sure, every communist and California will vote for Mrs. Douglas.
Now let's prompt them and tell you the votes for Richard Nixon, a man who is dignified
the House of Representatives by his presence in his actions.
People who cannot learn from history are doomed to repeat it.
But that's just my opinion, as plagiarized from George Santa Ana.
So I'm not quite sure who created this.
It's podcast 1186 on openpodcast.org.
Voight is a four or voice over IP is a four letter word by PBC Liberal, excellent piece.
Enjoy that very much.
And by now I've actually arrived home.
So I'm going to see disconnect some stuff here and we're going to go inside.
We'll continue from there because I have the same playlist.
Now of course I've got to figure out how to carry all this stuff at the same time.
Let's see.
I've put the receiver side in the eye river in my pocket transmitter.
We don't need no stink in transmitters.
And the other pocket over here.
Okay, well, let's slap the iPod in there.
Show notes.
Okay.
Is that tight squeeze?
There we go.
It's not a very nice day today.
Put the mic as close.
What are we doing here?
Oh hi, Pussycat.
Hello.
What's wrong?
Baby.
What is there?
Here.
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong?
It's a beautiful like Siamese cat.
Let me pet him.
Oh, he looks okay.
There's no collar.
I wonder if he belongs here.
Maybe he's one of the neighbors cats.
When you're making such a racket about baby, you make such a racket about.
Okay, seems very friendly.
All right.
Maybe just wanted some attention.
So we'll leave him for what he is.
Let's move on.
You can hear the wind.
Not only is it cold, but the wind is just flowing down off the downs.
Hello.
I'm podcasting.
Yes.
Hello.
I hope it doesn't finish off.
BBC 4 confrontational.
Yeah.
So this is all just amateurs.
Excuse me.
I think I'm pretty damn professional.
I've been doing it since I was 14.
And I've been paid lots of money to.
She.
That's not the point.
She was just saying podcasting is just amateurs.
Exactly.
That's the face I made.
I hear a lot more amateurs on there.
On the radio.
Oh.
And I went through this whole thing and said, you know, what?
Why?
Why does this appeal to?
It's fine.
Shoot.
So why does this appeal to people?
I said because we're living in a world of fakeness.
Yeah.
And we're tied to fake.
I said, pick up a women's magazine.
Look at Kate Moss with her to get the Rimal London look.
Yeah.
So she's wearing eyelash.
Fake eyelashes.
For selling mascara that makes your eyelashes look long.
Yeah.
And her life sucks.
Thank you.
Thank you, dear.
Oh, shoot.
I got a major crackling side.
Yeah.
What's she hanging out with that Pete guy?
That drug addict?
Yeah.
I think he's over now.
Hey, we're in jail.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to go upstairs and finish.
I don't know what's going on here with me.
I hope you're not hearing that.
For some reason.
I'm getting major interference.
Hold on.
Maybe.
Just a minute or the receiver.
Maybe it's just all the frickin' frequencies being used throughout the house.
So I'm going to have...
There we go.
It was the transmitter.
Probably hitting up against something.
I've got three Wi-Fi hotspots in the house.
We've got cordless telephones.
We've got wireless transmitters for...
Or transmitter pair for the television, the kitchen.
Shoot.
So, you know.
We've got to think that that's got to have something to do with it.
Okay.
So, I think I should be able to bring up my playlist here of stuff that I was playing.
Yes.
What was I going to do next?
What's our time frame here?
Okay.
10 minutes left.
Well, then, of course, we've got to play the final countdown.
Your president at his best.
Turn, turn, turn.
Evil is real.
8 years.
It is a totalitarian political ideology to do it.
Proceed with consuming zeal and do it.
And without conscience, do it.
Bring them on.
tyranny and terrorism dot dot.
I'm George W. Bush and I approve this and I want to share with you.
Carry representing the geneticism, resentment, and terror.
Made long ago on the day of our founding.
We affirm it again today.
Do it.
I am determined to simmer in resentment and tyranny.
Prone to ideologies that feed hatred and excuse murder.
Bring them on.
There can be no separate peace.
Violence will gather and multiply and destructive power.
Bring them on.
Each attack is designed to demoralize our people and divide us from one another.
The worst locomotive and raise a mortal threat to it.
There's a mindset that rejoices in suicide.
Do it.
Insights murder.
And celebrates every death when we release the shock truce of a hateful ideology.
Army to threaten the peace of the world.
Bring them on.
Thousands of dangerous killers.
School in the methods of murder are now spread throughout the world.
Like the ticking time bombs.
Set to go off without warning.
America is a friend of the Muslim crowd.
Terror, terror, terror.
Violence, tyranny is not surrender to the country.
Your enemy is ruling your country.
Do it.
We're living together.
But still it's farewell.
And maybe we'll come back to burn.
Who can tell?
Like there is no one to blame.
We'll leave it grow.
Will things ever be the same again.
Do it.
It's a fine no-to-one.
I believe in the solemn duty of the American president.
It's the district punishment for imaginary crimes.
We celebrate the reign of hatred.
The existence of permanent turning.
The possibility of permanent slavery.
We have led many have joined.
And America in the world is a complicated mess.
The wise excuse of America's strength is to advance the continuing danger of terrorism.
And all of this has confirmed one belief in the end.
We've come this far.
Our tested and confident nations can achieve anything.
Eight years of more dark violence will gather.
Do it.
Bring more.
We're in front of the map.
Evil is real.
So not really intended.
There's a political message more than an interesting mashup.
And good editing job on that with the final countdown.
By that wonderful Swedish band.
You heard, remember them?
You know, I was, see what, oh.
I got to skip a couple of things here just because of the time.
Gmail mentioned the Gmail have been down a couple of times, which freaked me out a little bit.
And I got to email about that that perhaps it wasn't that they were down, but they might be performing an upgrade.
Because now it seems that Gmail is working on more browsers, including some Linux flavors of browsers.
So maybe that Gmail is doing upgrades, which is great.
I'm still a big fan of the service.
Some information about Father Roderick.
We've talked about him.
The Catholic Insider.com.
He has not actually gotten Vatican Radio to start podcasting along with his podcast.
Deep from the bowels of the Vatican where no journalists has ever gone before.
Catholic Insider.com.
I can't, I can't listen to that podcast enough.
I really, really dig it.
And I got some email from a Dutch listener because Father Roderick is a Dutch priest.
Who's been podcasting from the Vatican for the past week or so.
Turns out he's been active online for quite a while.
Actually, he's been found in the Star Wars realm.
He seems to be a geek.
A Star Wars geek.
Which is cool.
And it makes total sense.
And I still get a kick out of him saying, oh my gosh.
Let's see.
Oh, that's right.
The blast on the past.
The buddy of mine, Larry, who I met many, many years ago, is now up at Microsoft.
And is working in the Xbox division.
Larry, why don't you come on in?
Thanks, Adam.
Hey, this is Larry.
Her better known as Xbox Live's Major Nelson.
If you want to know what's going on with the future of gaming,
there's no better place than the 2005 Game Developers Conference,
March 7th through 10th in San Francisco.
Not a game developer.
Can't make it.
But you still want to learn what the new trends are in gaming.
No problem.
Soon into my podcast at majornelson.com, and you'll be on the inside.
Plus this year, I'll be podcasting Jay Howard's keynote speech about the future
of gaming unlocking the opportunity.
For more information and complete details, check out majornelson.com.
Now back to the Daily Source Code.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Ooh.
Nice Xbox sound there.
So at normal.
Yeah, I wouldn't just go and pull out stuff like that.
But I love the fact that Larry put a promo together and had it open ended.
You know, so I could toss to him and he toss back to me.
And a place where you can pick up promos, which I think is actually,
it might be something cool to look into.
If you like a certain show, podcastpromos.com has been created,
where you can essentially drop off a promo for your show,
and pick up promos from other shows.
And it's kind of like a radio daddy type of exchange,
where you can exchange a voiceover work on.
This is just purely for promos.
More information about that in the show notes for today's podcast.
On daily source code.com.
And now time for...
Yeah.
There you see my thinking cap.
First, there have to put my thinking cap on.
Come on.
It's time for Adam.
I'm curious to take the hint to us.
With y'all.
Pull it.
I had him.
Hey, y'all number 19.
All right.
Let's keep it short and simple.
And this is...
I'm on for that.
I know.
That's easy.
That would be...
Odyssey going back to my roots.
Ooh.
Within the time limit even.
And this is number two.
Dubler?
Something like that?
I don't know.
And this is number three.
It's hard.
Easy.
Time guns.
Haven't some funds.
Gotta be George Michael and Andrew Rizley.
And wham.
Two for three.
I think today.
Time's up.
Answer number one.
It's fun.
Yeah.
Going back to my roots.
And we played this one to death on the pirate radio station.
Back in the release.
Running for race, huh?
There you go.
And so there you go.
We're back to my roots.
Yeah.
Do somebody come back.
Odyssey and going back to my roots.
And answer number one in today's internet station.
And this is answer number two.
I never would have guessed Johnny
Johnny gave a hood force later
One thing in a new addition with Bobby Brown
I'm saying duets with Stacey Lattipo
I never would have gotten out when you're too tough
I'm just so bad I'm just so bad
Johnny gave an answer number two
and this is answer number three
George Michael, together with Andrew Richley
back in the days that they were called to win
This is Young Guns
Hey, Saka
We're gonna get extra points for knowing Andrews name
And Pepsi and Shirley singing back a vocal
We don't know and try
All you could say
What's the point, George?
My fiance
Yeah
When
For third and final answer and Young Guns
Well this wraps up hit this number 19
Again, I hope you did well
And I thank you
Better than most days
Welcome at hit there's the Gmail.com
You can find information about hit there's the end of the hit there's practice
at www.yumpolets.nl
Let me see you next time for number 20 of the hit there
Bye bye
That's our second or fourth lobster
What is that?
Thank you very much Young Palette
As always for bringing us a little bit of joy
During the podcast
A little bit of brain teasing
That's it for today's Danny source code
Just under the 40 minute mark
Tomorrow I'll be back
And I've asked Patricia to go and find some of her CDs
Turns out they're actually here in my office
So I kind of picked them the other day
But I think it's time to play some of her work
I could talk about her career
That's going to be fun
So hopefully I can get it all together
To do that with her tomorrow
Oh shoot no wait a bit
Tomorrow I've got to go to London
Maybe we'll do it over the weekend
And what I'll do then is I'll probably do a podcast from London
As I'm being interviewed by Dutch television show
Which is kind of like
I'd say on the level of like Charlie Rose
You know so it's really intellectual
So I'll have to dress it really nice
And smartly and have Patricia be my hair
Hey Adam and Curry dot com for the feedback
And of course for the podcast feed
And the archives is dailysourcecode dot com
Or leave a comment on www.curry dot com
I'll see you tomorrow everybody
Bye bye
You