It's your daily source code, show number 180, something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear since
radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
That's right, it's show number 180 and it's Friday everybody, thank God.
I've actually had to restart the show three times. My Mac has been acting up like a mother fucker.
I don't know what's going on. I think it's something to do with the file system and
they can say trying to rescan stuff and God knows what's going on.
Basically, I've crippled everything, turned off file sharing, turned off the
Incernet on the Mac and it's working so far.
Knock on wood, will you please for me?
I don't want to start all over again.
So the past couple days have been a dreary in the UK.
Of course, this show coming to you from Kroy Cottage in the effluent London
suburb of Guilford, actually more a city.
And today this guy's decided to open up, so it's raining and it's perfect for the weekend.
Although I am off to the sunny west coast once again, we're talking about that today.
Also, I'll talk a little bit about the pod show on series.
I've got some excellent pod safe music coming up.
Of course, some promos and awesome email.
I really have to talk about the Eurovision Song Contest, which happens tomorrow night
as the finals being held in Kiev this year.
Last night, there was a semi-final for kind of all the loser countries that
were below the fold on last year's show.
Also, in order to participate, they had, I think that they had to pay like 150,000 euros
just to participate.
It's really fucked up.
I'll tell you all about this Eurovision Song Contest later on today.
Let's see.
What else was it going to happen?
It's just all kind of stuff going on.
I'm a little bit tired.
It's been a long, long week.
Finalized the first week of the pod show on series.
So now I'm ready to relax for a day before I get on a plane and listen to
8 million pod casts at 8 miles high.
Literally.
But first we got a mashup for you.
It's DJBC.
I'm fine.
When another week makes, what's opera doc on the source code?
Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, W
Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 3, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, Wabbit, 1, Wabbit 2, Wabbit 2, W
Kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit
I'm going to kill the rabbit, oh mighty, I thought the world will be quiet at least, how can you do it, my darling, why are you asking?
I will do it with my speel in magic helmet, your spear in magic helmet, magic helmet, magic helmet, magic helmet, magic helmet
magic helmet, magic helmet, magic helmet, magic helmet
kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit, kill the rabbit
Who are they'all are blameton?
I've killed the rabbit too little bunny, poor what a weirde
No, what did you expect in an opera, I had the ending?
Oh man, I love that.
Fantastic.
I could tell you that DJBC, you know, I don't know what he's doing, if he's doing drugs,
he'd better share some of that because he's got some great stuff going on.
It's a daily source code on a Friday, show number 180 as calculated by the people who track
that kind of shit.
I have lost count so long ago, we're going to pick it up, this is officially show number 180.
Want your promo or your pod safe music featured?
Well...
Godfather, forgive me for troubling you with such a trivial matter.
I have come here to pay you tribute, and to ask you for a small favor.
I have a pod cast that I believe most people would find enjoyable, but I'm having trouble
reaching these people.
Podfather, you are a man of great influence.
Please, Podfather.
If you can find it in your heart to help me promote my pod cast, please tell me what I must
do to gain this favor.
Well, my son, it's quite easy.
Really, just go over to iPodon.org submitted in a couple of categories that you think
would fit.
Podcastali.com, another great place to submit your pod cast, or if you want to play it
on the source code, or on the pod show on Syria satellite, send it to submit at podshow.com
if it's pod safe music, send it to podsafe at podshow.com, and if it's a mashup, like
DJBC's been doing, send it to mashup at podshow.com.
It's been great.
I've been exposed to so many new podcasts and promos with a serious show.
It's just been fantastic.
There's plenty of room in those four hours a day, so send in your stuff.
Hello, this is Franklin McMahon from Media Artist Secrets.
Are you a creative artist?
Are you a musician, writer, director, designer, photographer, animator, or just someone
who is exploring a lot of different creative fields?
Well, we have podcasts for you, oh yes.
Media Artist Secrets is fast-paced, easily digestible, and low-car podcasts filled with ideas
on how to gain the inspiration you need.
You're creative, fine-tune your vision, advance your skills, and share your creations
with the world.
The show's main goal is to get you rolling, get you activated creatively, but where
your creative career is now, and getting it to where you want it to be.
Oh, and it's fun.
Did I mention that?
Oh, yes.
It's fun.
So, drop what you are doing.
I'm not literally, but go to MediaArtist.com and get the latest episodes while you're
in there.
We can also check out our inspiring articles, the video tutorials, pictures, and much more.
So if you've only subscribed to one podcast this year, maybe two, two this year, make
sure one of them is MediaArtist Secrets, that's MediaArtist.com, any DIA, ART, IST.com.
If you want to be a star and your great stuff creatively, this is the place.
What's the secret?
Find out.
Listen today.
Alrighty.
Um, a couple of guys I met at the LeCipiusBitty Show at Joe's Pub and New York are
going on the road and they're going to start podcasting it and I believe it kicks off
today.
May 16, 2005.
Welcome to the Dutch Hupto podcast.
This is a test podcast to see if the system is working correctly.
So Friday, May 20th, I'll start a daily podcast covering a two-week road trip across
the USA.
See you then.
Alrighty.
For more info on that podcast, check out the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Radio sucks.
Listen to pod pirates.
I had a, I'm Johnny Fickery.
How about playing this promo?
I want you to sign up.
Whoa, sorry about that, Adam.
Once in a while the pod pirates get a little, uh, out of control here and, uh, you know,
sign up and I can do about it.
Anyway, as I was saying, my name is Johnny Velcro and I'm the host of pod pirates.
And twice a week, we try to bring you the best independent music.
And we try to add a little bit of humor.
Some people call it humor.
Some don't.
Fuck them.
Anyway, uh, you can reach us at jvilcro.blogspot.com or gestures tier.lips.com.
Or you can go to podcast alley and, uh, look us up and we're there.
So, uh, give us a shot.
Give us a listen.
You like what you hear?
I promise.
Yeah.
Later.
Okay.
Promises promises.
Alrighty.
That sounds cool with me.
Uh, look at in the email.
I got some fantastic email yesterday.
When I was, uh, like 15 or 16 years old, and I was really into radio.
This is just after I had started at a pirate radio station in Amsterdam called decibel radio.
I was 16 years old, um, except I had an, and I was a totaled wee nerd, excuse me,
since I say, oh, my goodness.
Um, not popular at school, but, uh, once people found out that I was actually John Holden,
that was my air name on the radio, I suddenly became very much involved.
And John Holden, of course, was a big black guy from the States who drove a hearty
Davidson through the, uh, through the streets of Amsterdam.
When in reality, it was me, the gauky little teenager who wrote a moped.
Um, but one of my heroes at the time was Scott Shannon.
He was, um, let's see at the time he was on Z100 in New York.
And he had really crafted the, the zoo format, which was very popular in the 80s,
which, of course, is, you know, um, there's so many different rip-offs of it.
But it wasn't so much the form, oh, yeah, no, I have to say, was the format of the show,
you know, and they had, you know, the Claire, the news guy and news guy.
The news guy, uh, Jonathan B. Bell, who was community services director,
and then they had coach Mike for sports, and then there was Ross Britten, who was the sidekick.
But Scott Shannon really had an uncanny sense of timing.
And, uh, but he also knew how to really break it down and, uh,
and use music to really portray a sensitive point.
And one thing, because I, um, well, get to that in a second.
One thing that I learned from him was, you know, you should let the room breathe once in a while.
You know, silence can be beautiful too on the radio, and he was really good at that.
And not a lot of people have, you know, who have recreated the zoo format
have really glomed on to that, and it doesn't all have to be, uh, a rim shot.
Um, so after Z100, he went to, well, first of all, when I started MTV in the States,
um, I did a personal appearance at some mall somewhere in Jersey.
And, uh, a part of that appearance was also Scott Shannon.
So I was like, oh, man, big fan of yours and have been, you know,
ripping your shit off and translating it to Dutch for years.
And, uh, we exchanged the phone numbers and turns out that we actually lived, like,
one street away from each other in Montclair, New Jersey.
Um, then he got me basically started on the radio in the States,
and helped me up with the right people.
And this was just about the time he was leaving to start something called
Pirate Radio in Los Angeles, uh, which didn't work out.
Uh, just, uh, for a number of reasons, I thought the idea was pretty good,
but it just didn't quite work out the way he wanted.
So Scott moved back later, um, and has been on WPLJ, 955 in New York for the past 14 years.
And all of a sudden out of the blue yesterday, I get an email, which is an all upper case,
all caps, which is very typical for, uh, old school radio guys,
because that's how they type all the liner notes and all the, you know,
basically whatever is typed by, you know, someone like Scott Shannon,
it's going to be right on the air.
So it does sometimes, uh, help to do it all in upper case,
just because it's easier to read.
Uh, so I just want to share this with you because I'm so, I'm so happy,
and so proud, really, to have received the team and I say,
my god, man, I should do the Scott Shannon voice.
My god, man, you're seem to find a way to make something happen.
I love what you're doing.
I'm still put putting along in New York doing the morning show on PLJ 14 years.
Now my daughter's going to be a sophomore at the University of Virginia,
and we live in Purchase, New York.
I read that you have managed to hold your family together all as well.
Send me your phone number.
Let's talk Scott Shannon DJ USA and your former neighbor.
I love it.
That, that really, that made my day.
That is just, is cool.
So, um, hopefully, um, next time in New York,
it won't be this trip, uh, it's either tomorrow,
which will be Saturday, maybe Sunday, uh, someone else has invited me
to stop by the house over the weekend, um, up in like San Diego, I think.
Uh, so I may go earlier, but I won't be back until probably Thursday or Friday,
and I don't think I'm going to have a chance to stop by New York.
At these days, it's pretty wack.
You know, I'm, I'm booking tickets all one way,
because you just never know what's going to happen.
And of course, you know what happens when you get, when you book a one way ticket, right?
Uh-huh.
You get that big quadruple F stamped on your ass,
and you get searched and searched and researched,
and supplementary search.
Man, it's just ugly.
Hey.
Hey, Tom.
Hey, buddy.
Okay.
Yeah.
Right on.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
That's a very good question.
Actually, um, we're still contemplating how to do this.
Um, we think that's going to be a couple of different versions.
Um, currently cast blaster, which only works on Windows, by the way.
Um, saves your podcast locally to your hard drive.
The next obvious step is what we're creating now is so that we have an API,
which is, um, it stands for application programming interface.
Oh, God, this insane was hitting me today, folks.
Um, and which, of course, will open up to other developers of podcast recording software.
Or if, you know, they have recording software already, it would just be a,
a reasonably small addition to add that in to be able to get whatever you've recorded right up on,
on, um, on podcast or come, uh, you know, as your own podcast with your own podcast feed,
and you don't show notes, et cetera.
But we are also contemplating a release that will enable you to, uh, basically use the software
with any hosting service that you prefer.
So, uh, don't have an answer yet, but we'll very soon as we're about to, I say,
what does it like two more weeks, maybe, maybe less.
Uh, we'll be going to a much wider, more public beta of cast blaster.
So stay tuned for that one.
Next.
Yeah.
Well, let's talk about Bitcoin for a second.
I saw a beta release that came out yesterday, which is now, uh,
what does it the tracker list, uh, bit torrent, which means you no longer have to have a server,
set up with special software, uh, to basically, you know,
hand off the information on where to download for all these individual bit torrent, uh, clients.
So in theory, you could basically bake all of them.
I mean, I know that most of the, um, most of the iPodder software out there already understands bit torrent.
So I don't know if they have to upgrade or, or put anything in it,
probably not put any additional software in or change the software to work with this tracker list system.
I haven't experimented it with it yet, but it seems like something that we might even
bake into cast blaster just, you know, to have it there.
Of course, the, the real problem is, you know, are you going to do multiple feeds for, um,
uh, for your, for your pod, you know, for your podcast feed, one with bit torrents and one with
regular web downloads and, you know, what happens, uh, if someone just clicks on a bit torrent link.
I mean, there's all kinds of things to be considered because as you know, really of the,
the iPodder traffic that I'm seeing, it's really only 20% of the people who are actually
listening to the show a lot of them are probably.
And if, you know, let me know how you're doing it, but I think a lot of people are downloading
the show when it comes out and either listening to it at their computer or they're dragging
over manually onto their, onto their MP3 player, not quite sure.
Um, so, um, I don't know.
I'm very interested in, in bit torrent.
Uh, it would be very cool if, if indeed we could turn that corner and make it work.
I'm just not sure how and, you know, that's like, guess that's what happens is once you
establish something so firmly, which you've done that with podcasting, you know,
people are going to, you know, they get used to it.
It's used to a certain way of working.
So I don't, I don't know if there's like a, under the covers way,
we can make that happen and make the switch and the hand off and so all of a sudden,
not, but I would certainly love to hear from my techy geeky friends if they have any
ideas.
And third.
Oh, okay.
I don't mind.
I'm not, you know, there are lots of people who sit in the first class,
which I only sit in first class these days from upgraded, because I just, I, I think,
don't think it's worth it, but since I travel alone, I often do get the upgrade, because
these flights continuously.
I'm not one of these people who hates screaming children, not at all, not at all,
but man, there are some arrogant motherfuckers who do, I tell you that.
What's this now?
Oh, yeah.
This is a, a long-form problem.
We're back when, when we didn't have to think, come on,
and don't be sick.
The boys on the bar, let me in and on,
on the banks of Chuck Creek, Chuck Creek.
Hi, everybody. This is, uh, this is Dave from Chuck Creek.com.
I just wanted to send out this note, because if you're not listening to Chuck Creek,
you're really missing out, because, you know, on our show, we make,
our own music, we make our own comedy skits, we make our own, whatever it is,
we need, you know, we do that, and we do it for you guys, and it's, it's all for you to
listen to, and we do it from the heart, you know, and, and here's a song,
I think this is from one of our first episodes, maybe one or two or three, and
it's one Gary wrote, and, uh, it's one that I really believe in, and one that I
thought, uh, probably his crowning piece, uh, and it's called,
I don't give a fuck about that toaster, and I wanted it to do not.
Well, you said to me, I think it was this morning, with this really, really,
really disgusting, don't in your voice, it sounded as though you were almost joking,
I'm a great big ball of friend, oh yeah, so anyway, you yelled at me with this disgusting
voice, that sounded like you were choking on a great big ball of thumb, and you said,
why don't you fix that toaster, it's always burning, burning, burning, burning
my toast, and I thought you were talking about your toast, but then again,
you were talking about your toast, and I should have known that because your voice was so
awful, yes, it was awful, and it made me sick, and I, I don't even know how,
to fix a fucking auto-steer, anyway, but then anyways, you came up with that amazing idea,
so we are in the trunk, after we planted all of our vegetables in the garden,
we had like peas, and spinach, no kinds of other shit, it was quite the word glow,
it was quite the word glow, but then it was back to your idea, we got in the trunk,
my big trunk, my big trunk oh yeah, and you're idea wants to go to the coffee and don't
just shut, we've got so much, it come in, because I wanted a coffee, just like you and I wanted to get my mind,
I've got a fucking toast, and I wanted a donor, and who cares if your toast gets burned,
I don't give a fuck any more about fucking toasters and burnin'
I love to have a donor with you, because we planted all kinds of vegetables and it was a long long day,
okay that's just one example of how hard we work for you, and I want you to do me a favor if you enjoyed that, send an email to Gary,
because in all the hundreds and hundreds of people that have heard that, have downloaded our show, not one person has emailed him to congratulate him about that song,
so I'd like you to do that for me, it's Gary at chubcreek.com, thanks for listening everybody.
So that immediately makes me want to have my own theme song, you know? I'd love to have one.
If you're sitting around strumming the guitar then make me a theme song, I'd love that, I really would.
Okay, let me see a couple of emails I wanted to talk to you about, this is from Ronnie Roach, great name, by the way Ronnie,
says, hey Adam, I've been to subscribe to the Daily Source Code for a couple of months, now I love it, thank you very much.
By the way, if you just click on the show every single day and download it and put it on your MP3 player manually, it can be an automatic process.
Go to iPod or not to org and look for download iPod or go to podcast alley, and there's all different forms and versions that can run on anything from Linux to Mac to Windows,
what does it, Windows, mobile, I mean there's all kinds of iPoders, and it'll just basically you subscribe to the show,
whenever there's a new one it'll automatically show up on your player, which is very cool.
So back to Ronnie's email, I'll live on the outer banks of North Carolina and my wife and I helping out with the program that encourages youth to learn about aviation.
If a fifth grade student completes the program, they get to fly a sess now over the right brothers memorial.
I was wondering if you would consider coming to the area for one of the first flights or the right brothers anniversary celebration, seeing how you're a celebrity in all,
and also a flight enthusiast, I think would be a great fit.
Well, I already had some more correspondence with their Ronnie, that happens in December.
Boy, what I love that, are you kidding me?
Have you awesome to, you know, during the right brothers celebration, the guys like invented this shit?
Yeah, that would be very, oh, by the way, there were people who flew before the right brothers and I guess, you know,
there's a whole invention thing.
Another one from Brian Deamer, yet a story you wanted to share.
He says about a month ago, he was shopping at the Apple store in Soha Manhattan when a woman with a video camera asked him to answer a few questions.
He said, sure, did his thing and then went home.
Well, he says, last week I got a call from a production company in LA, Apple might want me to be in the next commercial.
How cool he says.
So on Monday, Apple flew me to Los Angeles first class with about 50 other Mac geeks first class.
We all had a casting call and about 30 people got picked. Unfortunately, I wasn't one of them.
But the lucky ones are filming as we speak.
We all received a free iPod shuffle 512 for our time and it was great and a great LA experience.
I'm excited to see the new commercials.
I know every single person who'll be in them.
All in all, it says pretty good Mac geeks story, thought you would enjoy.
Yeah, and I always wondered if they were actors or if they just picked people off the street.
But apparently, if you see someone video taping in an Apple store, could be your shot at fame.
Maybe the next round right after they do this one.
Eurovision song contest. That's the final thing I wanted to talk to you about.
This is something that's been going on for probably, I think it's 30 years.
There's a consortium called Eurovision.
It used to be, and I think it still is, all the public broadcasters from each different country in Europe.
Once a year, and they had their own semi-finals and pre-rounds.
It's the precursor to idols, obviously, in their own country.
And then they send off a delegate.
That delegate will compete against delegates from all the other European countries in the union for the best song.
Now, mind you, it's about the best song, not about the prettiest dress, the best outfit, the wackiest stage show, or the best singer.
And it's always been a very, very political thing.
For instance, the Netherlands, where I live for a long time,
will probably always vote for Belgium, who are their neighbors.
And the Belgians will probably vote for the Netherlands.
And then you've got a whole bunch of East Black countries, which, you know,
I think we created 20 more countries since the wall came down.
And they all kind of vote for each other.
It's also culturally, you know, you just may have more affinity with a song that sounds a little bit like,
you know, it's from your hood or from just around the corner.
And because these broadcasts were so long, they decided to chop it down, and if you'd lost,
or if you didn't make the top, I think the top 20, top 15 or top 20, I can't remember,
maybe it's even the top 10.
Then you weren't allowed to participate in the next year's show.
Unless you go through a special bonus round, which was held last night in Kiev,
that's where the finals will be held tomorrow night.
And I believe actually, they have to pay 150,000 euros or something like that.
It's very complicated.
And really, it's, it's a lot, right?
And mostly these countries take it very, very seriously.
In the United Kingdom, Terry Wogan, who does wake up with Wogan, it's a morning show,
which has been very successful for a long time here on BBC Radio 2.
He has a very dry British just fun sense of humor,
and he does the voiceover on the telecast.
And it's funny.
I mean, you're literally wedding yourself because he's just taking the piss out of every single contest.
And except, of course, for Britain's entry, right, if they actually make it into the final round,
which I think they are this year.
And so we watched yesterday because Glen is Grace, a Dutch girl who we know,
who actually had an unreality TV show, Adam's family two years ago.
And she's a fantastic singer.
The resurrection of Whitney Houston, I'd have to say, just really good great song.
Well, she didn't make the cut last night, which was, it surprised everyone, actually.
Even, it wasn't Terry who did this particular round,
but even the voiceover on the BBC was like, well, you know, Holland didn't make it in.
And I think this has far reaching implications.
I believe that the Netherlands, and I was reading the newspapers this morning online,
I think the Netherlands is saying, what the fuck, man?
You know, this is the way we're getting treated in Europe.
We're definitely going to vote no on that referendum coming up next week,
which is about the European Constitution I've talked about this before.
If the Dutch say no to, you know, and this Constitution is, yeah, it's about liberties and freedoms, etc.
And, you know, work rights and shelter rights and you name it, human rights, basically.
But it's really about who has control of, you know, of what in the European Union,
which country has the most to say?
Is it the guys who put the most money in, is the guys who have the most population?
You know, how does that work?
Very complicated set of rules, and it doesn't sound very clean to me at all, at least from what I understand.
But, basically, all the members have to vote, yes, and say that they're for this,
and the French are coming up on June 1.
If the Dutch say no, the French could say no, and that could basically, you know, put the European Union back in the freezer,
which, I mean, that's going to affect everything.
It's going to affect economics, it's going to affect trade, it's going to affect a lot of things.
So it'll be very interesting to see.
And I truly believe that the Dutch who were already very disappointed with their own government
and probably going to vote no, just to punish their government, who, of course, you know, they all want, yes,
because they want, you know, to see the expansion mainly for economic reasons,
and which still have to be proven yet, I have to be fair.
I think the Dutch are going to be really down on the European Union right now,
all because of this silly ass song contest.
And, you know what, one of these days I get Patricia back on, we'll do another PPP podcast,
and we'll talk about her days participating in these song contest, which used to be very common around Europe.
You don't see him anymore, other than what's happened now with the reality type based television programming like idols.
That's kind of the only, the only thing we have left, but it's not really a national thing.
It really used to be, it's our country, and we want our country to win, and, you know, the whole voting thing and the call-up.
Hello, Moscow, may we have your votes, please?
Ah, so exciting.
Okay, how are we doing on time?
33 minutes perfect.
This is a song that CC Chapman turned me on to.
CC does the accident hash podcast.
You can find it at accident hash.com.
He's also working with us on setting up the pod safe music network, which I'm really excited about.
We've talked about that a couple times.
This is a guy whose name is Chance.
You can find him in my name is Chance.com, of course you'll find all that information in the show notes.
It's not entirely pod safe.
It would actually work very well on Coverville, because as long as you're paying an AskCap or BMI license, then it's all taken care of.
And you have permission by the guy himself, Chance, in this case, who doesn't have a record label, you know, he's independent.
As long as you have that permission to play it, then it's okay, but it's kind of borderline.
But the song is great.
It's, I think, I calculate the song is 21 years old by now, but it's still, it just, it kicks ass, particularly in this version.
Here's Windows Cry.
And the most striking reasons for this, that you late, that you between me and you, you just leave me standing.
Alone in a world so cold.
Maybe I'm just too demanding.
Maybe I'm just like my father to go, maybe I'm just like my mother.
She's never said it's fine, never said it.
Why do we scream at each other?
This is what it sounds like when does cry.
Touch if you will, my stomach.
Feel how it trembles inside.
You've got the borderline as all tied up.
Don't make me chase you.
Even though it's a pride, just being standing.
Alone in a world so cold.
What so?
Maybe I'm just too demanding.
Maybe I'm just like my father to go.
Maybe I'm just like my mother.
She's never said it's fine.
Why do we scream at each other?
This is what it sounds like when does cry.
I'm just too demanding.
Alone in a world so cold.
Maybe I'm just too demanding.
Maybe I'm just like my mother.
She's never said it's fine, never said it's fine.
Why do we scream at each other?
This is what it sounds like when does cry.
Touch if you will, my stomach.
Feel how it trembles inside.
You've got the borderline as all tied up.
Oh, ho, oh, do, oh, do, oh, do, oh, do.
I think it's the accordion at the end,
that really doesn't form it,
that's a great chance when dub's cry
on the Friday edition of the Source Code.
Alrighty, so, that's it.
I will be on the road Saturday or Sunday
and of course, Source Code's coming your way.
All this week, don't forget,
got the pod show on serious your promos are very welcome and please don't forget
your ID3 tags when you make a promo mix it so much easier to put the show notes together
so I think today we'll finally have the show notes up for the pod show on serious
we can find that at serious.podshow.com that's s-i-r-i-u-s serious pod show.com
this particular podcast can be subscribed to if you've got an iPodder
download one of those fine pieces of software and subscribe to the feed at dailysourcecode.com
you can leave a comment there as well or send me something through the email item of curie.com
or if you want you can leave a comment on my weblog it's www.curie.com that's pretty easy to remember
know isn't it? all right some of those promos submitted pod show.com more pod
music is welcome podsafe podshow.com and your mashup smashup podshow.com all right i'm going to
get this up get it rolling i'm going to hang out with my wife i'll see if i can take her out to
dinner tonight before i leave again for the wild blue yongo but it's all good stuff maybe
wrong i should do another update a strategy cast well together in a sample system that would be
kind of cool yeah i'll ask what we can do that and i got some cool ideas for another source code
which will involve Skype stay tuned for that soon here on the source code have a great weekend everybody bye bye