Deadly source code for Tuesday, April 26, 2005.
Yo, DJ!
Hi, yo, Joe!
Next day, yo!
Yo, DJ, has only just begun.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Can you do this?
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking turns, man.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's Tuesday.
We're at the cottage.
It's a fuzzy cast.
Everybody?
Fuzzy cast.
Because I am extremely fuzzy.
Hold on a second.
We just make sure we're not clipping on the microphone there.
Everything else set up.
Yeah.
We got the sleep in a bit.
Christina wasn't feeling good.
So they let me sleep until I recorded it.
10.
There's normally I take Christina to school.
Which I was a little worried about the levels here.
Hold on a second.
I'm seeing some one-two.
Okay.
Let's just make sure we adjust all that perfectly for you folks.
Yeah, normally I'm up bright and early.
Take Christina to school.
Get the papers.
Get the coffee going.
So I've kind of skipped overall that.
And the first contact, almost the second human contact I had this morning,
was with EZNet.
My internet service provider.
Once again, crap going on.
You're not going to believe this.
Yesterday I got a phone call from someone from technical support.
It sounded like an engineer from EZNet.
And he said, and this was what was weird.
He said, hi.
So we're all out of four megabit.
We're just going to hook up to SDSL.
Okay.
Whoa.
It's like an engineer from EZNet.
And he said, and this was what was weird.
He said, hi.
So we're all out of four megabit.
We're just going to hook up to SDSL.
Okay.
Whoa.
What just happened here?
What happened to my four megabits?
It's working, right?
Long story short.
We're not quite sure what has happened.
But my line, as you remember, went down a couple weeks ago for about an entire week.
And then it came back magically.
But indeed, it turns out that I have now only a one megabit line.
I've been paying for four, but I have a one megabit line.
And now I'm going to stir up some shit with EZNet.
This just drives me nuts.
You know, you buy a business account.
You get all these big promises and service level agreements.
And it's all going to be a wonderful thing.
Takes months to get it hooked up.
And then all of a sudden, the old bait and switch, you know.
And oh, we're sorry, well, we can't provide you with four megabits anymore.
I don't know.
And then just try calling into one of these places.
You know, you have like 15 different phone numbers.
And it's all dropping to the same voice mail metrics of switches.
And, you know, usually I always wind up calling sales,
because they're the only people who ever answer the phone, right?
You never get the accounts department.
You never get the technical support department.
So now I've got a guy.
And I don't even know if he's technically in sales or not,
but he gave me his direct line.
He's really working on it.
But God damn, it makes me so angry.
You know.
Wow.
Just imagine five years ago, I was already thinking we could do this podcasting type stuff.
And I was thinking video at the time, man was I silly.
We still didn't even have the basic, you know, last mile requirement
figured out yet.
And then what's going to happen?
Pretty soon, cities everywhere will be completely wi-fi.
Will we even need these ISPs anymore?
Will just be one big giant ISP.
Will it be a part of your taxes?
You know, this is going to get interesting.
Very interesting.
I'm just to fed up with this.
I'm really fed up with it.
So of course I have two lines here at the cottage.
So I guess I'll get one of those.
And thank you by the way, everyone who sent me information about how to combine two different networks into a single internal network.
There's a couple of boxes out there that do it ranging from like a hundred to three hundred dollars in price range.
So I'll probably just get one of those and combine the two one megabits for now until they figure all this out.
And I'll probably need it for fail, fail over safety because, you know, when you get start going,
when you start stuff with them, then things start to get disconnected and reconnected.
And I'm in for hell again.
I can tell you.
I'm in for hell.
But maybe some of the hellishness will happen while I'm away because we made plans yesterday.
I'm going to step on the big, big red virgin bird tomorrow night, Wednesday night,
and fly off to New York, two meetings in New York, then over the weekend.
I'm going to go out to the west coast for two meetings on Monday and Tuesday, which means I think we'll be able to,
maybe schedule some kind of drink or get together or I don't know, somewhere out on the west coast.
We can all just kind of hang out everyone who wants to show up.
Maybe I should do an official podcast meetup.
Maybe that would be the way to do it.
So I'm a little, yeah, a little out of sorts today.
Right now it's 10 minutes past 12.
I still have my bathrobe on.
I know that's not necessarily the image you want to conjure up.
So I've got my bathrobe on and then I have my brown egg boots.
I don't know if you are familiar with the eggs.
UGG.
They're called eggs because they're ugly.
But they're made of, what does the deal with these eggs?
They made of like organically grown sheep or killed few mainly or whatever.
Or they used every single bit of the sheep.
Whatever.
Some sheep had to die for me to have these wonderful ugly yet extremely, extremely comfortable boots on.
And I have two pair, one for outside, one for inside.
That's how much I love them.
So I guess what they say in the mainstream media is true.
You know, we're just guys and gals in our pajamas.
Really?
Oh, like a lot of us.
Do you like it in common ring?
Well, get the fuck out because we don't think that shit.
They said we want some to get supporting bath, music, and some day we won.
The simians did a good podcast show.
Get the feeds as podcasts.
Don't say that they checked on you.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
So let's say, I think they have a comedy podcast.
And of course, as with all the daily source code shows, from the show notes,
you'll be able to find links to a promo's played in the show.
And if you have a promo, send it off to adamantcurry.com,
put in the subject line DSC for daily source code, DSC, space promo,
and then the name of your show.
So it'll get routed to the right spot in my email box.
And I'll be able to find it again.
Okay.
I'm using the cast blaster once again on the PC tablet.
And I figured out something which I thought,
why was pretty much assured it wouldn't work.
I wanted to play just a nice memory tune for you.
Something that'll put me in a good mood.
So I went over to the iTunes music store,
bought myself exactly what I wanted.
That experience is always wonderful.
It downloads.
But of course, it's only authorized to play on this computer in the authorized players,
which would be iTunes.
So I can't play it in the cast blaster,
the cast blaster fortunately does know how to record
from other applications while we're running.
Oh, man.
This just put the smile on my face already.
Steely Dan, really into the ears.
To get you going on your daily source code.
Good morning.
You're a relaxing summer.
You can see it fit and flat.
So you grab the pieces of something that you think is gonna land.
Well, you wouldn't even know a dime
and if you held it in your head.
The things you think are precious, I can understand.
Are you real in in the ears?
So in a way the time.
Are you gathering at the geese?
Have you had enough of mine?
Are you real in in the ears?
So in a way the time.
Are you gathering at the geese?
Have you had enough of mine?
You can tell me you're a genius since you were 17.
In all the time I've known you, I still don't know what you mean.
The weekend and the college didn't turn out like you planned.
The things that pass the knowledge I can understand.
Are you real in in the ears?
So in a way the time.
Are you gathering at the geese?
Have you had enough of mine?
Are you real in in the ears?
So in a way the time.
Are you gathering at the geese?
Have you had enough of mine?
Have you made enough of mine?
Do you have enough of mine?
Stealing Dan, Reelin in the years and a daily source code for April 26, 2005.
It's Tuesday.
I'm here at the Curry Cottage in Gilford in the UK.
Another great day, rain outside, not very nice.
So I must admit it'll be quite a nice little change to get out and get back to New York
and also onto the sunny left coast of the United States, even though the trip will be relatively
short.
Now, don't go email me saying, how do you do that?
Why are you playing licensed music?
What I tried to think of in these cases is this is a really old song.
You probably might be able to find this in the record store.
I talked over the intro, talked over the outro, bought it for 99 cents, only sharing
with my friends.
I'm not broadcasting anywhere.
I've made it unusable.
Clearly, we have to do something about that.
Just give me an option on iTunes.
Just an option says, buy a podcast license.
That will be really nice, or maybe the record company as well.
We're working all of that.
It's really nice, though, to hear a high quality digital music file, because when you
download from the iTunes music store, it's an AAC, it's not an MP3.
So different compression technique, it's a higher level of, or actually a lower level
of compression, I think.
So the file size is bigger, but the quality, man.
You forget so quickly.
That's one of the things that I've noticed, you know, whereas we've forgotten totally what
can be done with audio, and particularly with radio, which we're now rediscovering with
podcasting, we've also kind of forgotten what good quality is.
I've never been an audio file, I've never got into the gold connector as all that stuff,
but man, if it's sound is good, it really does, just open up your brain.
It's like breathing oxygen, pure oxygen, instead of just fresh air, you know what I mean?
Or the air around us, typically fresh air, it's so incredibly nice.
And yesterday I was talking about the blind, well, let's go out the blind community, I hate
that.
Anyway, but blind people, and how podcasting could do so much for them, media wise, man,
I've been delugeed by emails of organizations and all kinds of people who are interested
in helping, and it's just great, it really is.
And what's great about it is, anyone can get started with this, anybody can get a podcast
going, go to ipodder.org, there's many helpful places there that, you know, links and
stories and articles that help you get started, regardless of what kind of computer you
have.
The basics are an internet connection and a computer with at least a sound card or that can
either has a built-in microphone or you can plug a microphone into.
And then essentially you can get podcasting, and you can even podcast through a telephone,
there's some services out there that will allow you to do that.
Like openpodcast.org, if you're not necessarily looking for your own domain name, but
even what is it, risen.net has a phone interface, RIsZZN.net, Libsyn, is it Libsyn?
Yeah, Libsyn.com, man, there's all kinds of places.
So let's get it going, seriously, and when you have promos and stuff, send them to me, so
I can point people in the direction, you know, let them know what's going on.
Got a couple of the great promos today, well, maybe not the best of promos, but certainly
interesting podcasts, I'd like to point out to you.
So don't worry about writing stuff down and rewinding and trying to get the URLs.
All of those will of course be in the show notes for today's podcast.
Yes, I did my show notes a little bit differently.
I used the Inline Outliner of my weblog software to create the outline right in the
post itself.
We're still working on, I mean, obviously with the opml part is very important, it will
become important.
Somewhere down the line, we're going to figure out how to incorporate all that stuff.
So I do want to continue to make opml documents, but I do like rendering just an outline
rendering in the post itself, so that you really have your show notes attached to the same
item that is your podcast, so you have your enclosure, which is your MP3 file, you've
got the description, which talks about what's in the show, you've got your title, etc.
So I've been changing some stuff around.
Also, today's show will be coming from a different server and a different network all
together.
So we're stepping off at least temporarily to see how it works, stepping off of the dot mac infrastructure
which I've been using for many months now, quite with great results, except for the header
information, which has been breaking reception of many of the podcasts on different iPodders
like Doppler, for instance, which actually isn't Doppler's fault, it's correctly identifying
the incorrect information being sent from dot mac.
So hopefully this will have reached you and I would certainly appreciate any type of report
if stuff broke or if this broke, then you're not hearing me, right?
So you'll probably email me no matter what.
Just our name, people have been extraordinary story, thanksgiving day, I hope that it will
be.
If you wrote it in my committed suicide, there will be people like me who have been
a trouble with a dark fly.
Oh, I'm a raging alcoholic, the dancers are really good and bad.
I hate our boss, but I love seeing all the fly, shix.
The small world podcast, everyone's got a story to tell, what's yours?
This is the website at smallworldpodcast.com.
I gotta tell you, this is...
Whoops, this is an awesome, awesome podcast.
If you haven't heard WGBH's Morning Stories, which Tony Khan hosts and produced, it's very
much like that only, it's without just remove all the production part, right?
And it's just people who are being interviewed with variety different qualities of microphones
and setups and surroundings, which gives a very real-life feel to it, which of course it
is because these are real people.
Pretty little if any editing and people just tell these amazing stories about themselves
and it's enthralling, you just hear them like, oh my god, you know, wow, listen what
happened to this person.
Of course a lot of it is not necessarily great stories, but stories, man, that is still
that something that's in our DNA isn't, it's just storytelling and passing on information
embedded in stories and everyone loves a good story, particularly if it has a happy ending.
Of course you know, I'm an American guy, I'll say move, but in Japan, I'll say more.
Hi Adam, and are you listening to the Daily Source Code?
I'm Terrence Young, host of the Kobe Beef Show, a podcast out of Japan, about my life in
Japan, and also featuring a very wonderful Japanese language corner that I would like
you to listen to now.
It's the end of the time, let's Japanese!
Today's word is Bottakuri, Bottakuri, which means rip off.
For example, Sotava Bottakuri, that's a rip off.
So next time you want to rip someone off or someone is ripping you off, you can use the
word Bottakuri, Bottakuri.
That's was today's the over time episode.
Thank you very much!
Bottakuri, hey, easy now!
Enjoy that!
Bottakuri!
My podcast, Kobe Beef.
Bottakuri.
That's Kobe, that's beef, dot blot spot, dot com, thanks Adam, there you go, Bottakuri,
it's a great one.
I can't wait until if we really push this pod save music concept up the chain, it's
Sony Records.
I get to talk to the Japanese CEO and say, hey dude, your music is Bottakuri, you know?
Bottakuri!
Sent to me by CC Chapun from the Aksorn hash pod, cazz details follower, but check this
out it rocks the house!
yeah!
i moved on without me, maybe one day!
see things the same.
feel sorry I ever felt this way.
feel it sorry.
No one else to play, hey yeah
Time on my side, and after all the dreams
That no one understands for me
I'm feeling fine with this simple dream
And no one understands for me
I never saw it coming
I expect it, it's really somehow
Feelin' sorry, I never said I can
Time on my side, and after all the dreams
That no one understands for me
I'm feeling fine with this simple dream
And no one understands for me
Time on my side, and after all the dreams
That no one understands for me
I'm feeling fine with this simple dream
And no one understands for me
Whoa, just pick it in your ear
Oh man, I love that
No one understands, it's Birmingham from Florida
It's off the CD, life in the stars
And of course you can find a link to their album
You can actually buy it only five bucks
You can buy their CD right off the website
Oh man, you want to tell me that that isn't good
I really love it, thank you CC Chapman
Hopefully it'll be sending me some more
This is awesome, totally
And I guess if you email the guys
They'll happily give you permission
To play that track or other ones on your podcast as well
Not bad, not bad
This is Dan at an all-feet of the Florn.net podcast
Did you ever wonder what would happen
If a poet astronomer turned information security geek
Got his hands on Garageband and took advantage of unused bandwidth
Well, find out at the Florn.net podcast
It's my own little brain dump, poetry corner, coffee shop, soapbox and boombox
Caffeine is worshiped, snark is encouraged and BS is not tolerated
Stop by, listen to the Florn.net podcast at Florn.net slash podcasts
You're seeing you
Alright, so actually what I'd planned on having yesterday or today was
The next strategy cast with Ron Blumen myself
So now I'm not sure if we're going to do that today
This afternoon for air tomorrow or if we're going to do it while on the road
Well together, I'm going to bring my full gear
So I have everything that we need to record
Because it's getting very, very close
I know we've been stringing each other along for quite a while now
But we actually have most of our ducks lined in a row
And I'm ready to start talking about some of the stuff we're doing
Remember, we're mainly about listeners now to start off with
Certainly we need to get more people listening to podcasts
We have to make it easier, have to have more avenues of distribution
Have to get more word out there basically
So that's, that's what we're starting
And that's what we'll be talking about in the next couple of days
I promise
Okay, I'm going to keep it a little bit short today
Because I do have a lot to do
Again, I got like a two hour late start today
So plenty of stuff to take care of
Before the East Coast wakes up
Which is actually probably just about awakening as we speak
That's really, that's the only bummer
Even though I'm only five hours separated from New York
I do a lot, I have long days
All the Skype and conference calls which take place
Now around one PM to PM East Coast time
So that's eight nine o'clock here
And then you know, you're finally wind up
It's like, hey, it's the one AM again, damn
So the extra hours were welcome this morning
But man, I'm behind
Hey Adam, it's Dr. Joel, that's the creator
I'm producer of www.thritiscentral.com
Letting you in your listeners know that our new podcast
Called our Thritis Central News and News
Did you know that there were over 35 million people
Oh life suffering with arthritis to his huge need
For help for education information
Our program will cover news updates
With commentary and opinions
It'll be interviewing our Thritis patients
Speaking of medical experts about the latest treatments in research
So we invite our Thritis patients
And their family members and friends
To listen to our podcast at ourthritiscentral.com
Thanks a lot
All right, Doc
Okay, so check that out
There's a doctor doing a podcast
And he's actually selling exclusive
Kind of go to the website and I'll put the links in the show notes
He's selling exclusive content
For I think like $20
You can get a specific types of content
Which are also a specific podcast
So he has like a general podcast for free
He's got a real business
And I really believe in this
And what a wonderful topic
Something that so many people deal with
Personally, I've found that
Lots of people like marijuana
To take care of all the issues
For the hard practice
But and you know what?
I don't have any problems with arthritis
So I'd love to hear your views on that
Good doctor
That would be actually pretty cool
If you can send another promo
If you're happy to play
If you address some of that
Because it is all about pain management
I believe so
And that's it for the daily source code
A little bit shorter than normal
Just shy of half an hour
Of course we back tomorrow
With more pod safe music and mashups
And your promo
Adamacore.com
Where you can respond
If you send a promo
Just send a link to the MP3 file
And then put it to the subject
DSC promo
Follow by the name of your podcast
DailySourceCode.com
Where you can find the podcast feed
And the archives
And of course the latest podcast
And I said we're going to be on a new server for this show
So we'll see how well that works out
I'd love to hear feedback on that as well
And of course there's my weblog www.curry.com
You're welcome to
Drop by there anytime
And also leave comments on a variety of topics
All right
I'm going to get this thing up to the bird
Take care everybody
I will talk to you tomorrow
Bye bye
You