Delta Sierra Charity 2, 4, 9-Ear
I'm Korean
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need no sticky and crispy
I like to think I'm flying into the street
It is Thursday, September 29th, in the year of our Lord 2005
Well, day to the next day to the last coming year from Curricondo
In northern California, sunny San Francisco
I know it's not a kind of boring, but for those you just
Tooting into the daily stores code via Syria, satellite channel 103
Hey, it never rains in California
Well, maybe it does, not when I'm here
Oh, man
A show of all shows
Filled up with pot-safe music
It's able to find a couple of nice promos
And of course, we've got to talk about today being the first day
That the pot squad, which is an extensive lineup
Various on a day-to-day basis, we're basically being cymbal cast
Four hours a day on Syria, satellite radio
It's really weird, I'm doing the same show, but I'm still cognizant of this new audience and there, you know
So we welcome you, if you're wondering who I am, what the hell I'm doing on your satellite radio
I'm Adam Curry
I'm just the middle-aged white guy
The mild case of Tourette syndrome
And what's the show about?
Well, I'm much really, it's kind of like a jumping off point
It's a place for you to listen to stuff to then go discover your own podcast, dammit
The power of all the world is to us
And all seriousness, there is some really important stuff to talk about
Like, well, like some buddies in mind
Actually, this is a mini mix that a friend of mine did Ben Libre on to
I started off on the radio with that we were doing stuff
Man is early in 1982, I think, and he was, he remix
He was basically remix, remember those guys?
Remixers before they start to do mashups
Some kind of DJs
Well, someone found a mashup, a good old-banded
And I think you'll see here
Just while I love working with the guy
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, sweet dreams
Morty contenty, remix
On the daily source code, nice stuff
I've been
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sweet dreams are made of the answer
Who am I to disagree?
And travel the world and the seven seas
Everybody's looking for something
Some of them want to use you
Some of them want to get used by you
Some of them want to be used
Some of them want to fear you
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah you yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah,
What do you think?
What you don't think?
Sweet dreams and make you the champions
We'll be with you in my dreams
Typical pen
He always ends his mashups and mixes
I was from 2001
That's four years old
This is how far ahead of the times this guy is
As I said, I've worked with him since 82
He was doing the grand mix
If you're into the mixing, then you know about the DMC mixes
He did lots of those
He's on plenty of remixes that have gone on to become
Number one hits, let's see
Lovely day, Bill Widders, remix of that
To Varus
I know it sounds kind of...
If you haven't heard it, it sounds kind of
Flaky that there would be remixes
If heaven must be missing an angel
But it truly does kick ass
Oh, what a night
Four seasons
And he's produced a couple of his own albums
And it's...you know what?
It's interesting because he's from the Netherlands
As is DJ Tiesto
Tase as we know him
Do you know it does you?
Find Dutch name
It must be something
What is that? What am I hearing?
There's so much construction going on outside the condo
Right now in two years, this is going to be a great neighborhood
But right now, it's almost looking directly at the crane operator
And I'm on the 24th floor
Must be something in the water over there
In the Netherlands that's doing it for
You know, I should call Ben, I haven't spoken to him
God, man, probably a year or more
Maybe even I got to call him
Because he's the kind of guy that understands
That you need to give a little to get a little
So if he's working on some cool projects
I'm sure he'll give us, he'll
He'll, he'll pot, say, for five, some of his mixes
So that we can play him
Um, so there is some actual potsafe
Use it coming up
I just want to tell you about what we're doing on Sirius
Because that kicks off today
On channel 103, it's Sirius Stars
Which is the channel that
It's amazing how they brought together
Madge Weinstein, Don Andrew Adam Curry and
Cousin Brucey
So at 6 o'clock
As will be the case every week
Afternoon, it's Eastern Time
Three Pacific Daily Source Code will be on
And this is all kind of like a simultaneous
These are the shows that
Most of them come out as a podcast first
And then they go on Sirius
That's a timing issue
I'm actually up early here in San Francisco
To make sure that we have this show ready for
For Sirius today
So after the source code
We get Madge Weinstein
That of course is East Radio
Our angry bloated Jewish Lesbian from Chicago
Don Andrew followed by that
And there will be
Other types of shows just like these
That you're hearing throughout the week
I'll let you know what's going on
Attention Tech with Steve Gilmore
That's going to be a brand new podcast
I'm looking forward to hearing
I think he's teaming up with Mike Fizzard on that
Then we have DVD weekly Don Iran
And then later on the evening
We roll out to some pod safe music
Also Brian knows the Frank Truth
We've got Peter
It'll be rolling out digital flats
And tonight also Wichita
Everyone else has been listening to the podcast for
249 episodes
Definitely knows what the hell is going on
Stuff like this right for the best information
Concerning the fitness industry
Join Dave Depue and Tom Perkins on fitness business radio
For more information go to fitnessbusinessradio.com
And listen to fitness business radio
Hot show content that will make you squeeze the dog and burp your mother
This is Brian know your host
For the Frank Truth a weekly podcast
Celebrating the life and career of the
Entertainment of the 20th Century
Francis Albert Sinatra
Each week or thereabouts we cover session history
The latest about new releases and
Other Sinatra related happenings
And point you toward websites and other
Resources for the Sinatra fan
Throw in movie book and album reviews
From time to time and well
That's the show
You can find out more at franktruth.blogspot.com
On the web or subscribe through the iTunes music store
Join us won't you?
In the meantime Jen Donny
May you live to be a hundred
And may the last voice you hear be Franks
Jen Donny my brother
Cool new feature coming out
I think that releasing it today on the podcast
Music network music dot pod show dot com
This is where we we're building the new music industry
Taking place before you're very eyes
Thousands of tracks that podcasters can choose from to play
And they're reporting what they're playing
We've talked about this before
So we know what the top pod plays are and how many
What would it be called?
I mean you can't call them spins anymore
Because we're not really spinning CDs
Certainly not in most cases not vinyl
Hmm okay
So the top pod play MP3s that are being played
From the pod safe music network on
We have over like 2,000 podcasters now registered
And tons of other people who are not podcasters
But I interested in
Licensing this pod safe music for movies
And commercials and all kinds of amazing stuff
So we have this top pod play
And now we've expanded that i saw the beta
Hmm
Came in last night i saw this morning
So now we know the top pod play of all time
The top pod play of the month
To date the top pod play of the week
To date and the top pod play of the day
So this is now and now we're getting some information
It's really useful and there's a lot of stuff in there
I really love this feature because
It saves me out of a lot of time of going through
You know and sampling everything
I always listen to a couple of genres
See what's coming and look listen to the new submissions
But really knowing what someone else is playing
It helps a lot
And the cruise box still getting an amazing amount of play
And i keep reminding myself i got to keep on that stuff
Man
We're going to make hits
We don't have to do it right
Just like traditional radio played over and over
And over and over and over again
He'll make you feel
Can they be a fucking stop play
And i'll buy the record already
Okay
I heard it on the podcast
Rockin' fucking radio you wanted
You got it just downloaded a part
It on the podcast
No one's gonna stop you telling
KFC seats, pick it pick it
The revisions
Do you remember
Your first computer
That piece of shit was like a freaking roller-roader
Now we've got Wi-Fi
Downloading files fast
This meant to everyone
Save a down on my cast
It says to me
Now you see
Each and every nation
The radio is got to go
It's our imagination
Me that song
Seeing a loud mash it up
It makes it
You fucking wrote it
I can't fix it
Yes somebody heard it
Call
Now you can have it all
Thank you real son
I heard it on the podcast
Rockin' fucking radio you wanted
You got it
Just downloaded a part
It on the podcast
No one's gonna stop you telling
KFC seats, pick it pick it
The revisions on the podcast
Rockin' fucking radio
You wanted it
Got it
Just downloaded a part
It on the podcast
No one's gonna stop you telling
KFC seats, pick it pick it
The revisions on the podcast
Who's box
Tell the FCC to stick it
Kick it
Hurt it on a podcast
That's right
Revolution is on
I got to get a new version of that
So it's
I really can't wait to be back at the cottage
I'm going
I was supposed to be New York today
Actually but
The way things work out
And some stuff that has to happen
In Europe I'm flying directly
From San Francisco
To London tomorrow
On Virgin upper class
Yes, they're picking me up again
Love the limo service
Love what they're doing
So far I've had not really one bad experience
So I'm flying back directly
And I gotta tell you
I'm, besides seeing the girls
Obviously I'm really looking forward
To seeing Patricia and Christina
But I also want to get back to the studio
I got my, I'm missing the
The valve, the valve
The valve processor
And some people have complained about
The road set up
I think I have to tweak a little bit
Problem is I don't really have any reference speakers
With me, you know, you got to that one pair of speakers
That you listen to and you know what it sounds like
And you trust it so that's at home
The other home
And so I've got to, I've got to tweak the sound a bit
For what I'm on the road
Besides that being back
It's always cool because
You get to have that
Welcome home honey sex
Waiting, waiting for that
Thinkin' of it
So I'd said two days ago
Was it Monday, maybe thing Monday show
I said that I was a big fan of the distorted view show
Fan of that too
But what I meant to say was
The Pacific Coast Hellway
And that I'd listen to the show
And as we're subscribed to the podcast
And the host was right in on me
And so I mentioned that
And last night I came back after
After a fantastic dinner
By the way, some friends
Cooked a homemade meal for me
I was really cool
Shatobriol
And lots of mashed potatoes
And so I got back to the condo
I had the
I had iTunes open
So it had slurped stuff down
Even on the slow stolen Wi-Fi connection
I've got here
More about that later in the show
And there was brand new Pacific Coast Hellway
I could tell from the show notes
Or actually from the title of the
Not the show notes
The show notes are the same
But from the title of the podcast
That I was going to be in it
So I wanted to play that for you
Because
I thought it was just one guy
But it appears that he has a team
And that there is a lot of people
Actually work on this show
They did some good work
Check this out from Pacific Coast Hellway
Anyway, so get this
So Adam Curry
mentioned our show
On his podcast
On the Daily Source Code
This past Monday
So hold on, let me play this
Yeah, that was a great podcast
I was listening to
Over the weekend
Pacific Coast Hellway
This guy is good
He does a podcast on his way to work
Every single morning
And I guess he records pieces of it
And he must do some post editing
If not, he's got a great mobile set up
And he's funny man
He is
If I got a very Howard Stern
Ask Moment or Experience
I mean, I was
When I lived in New York
And I was commuting into this
Or a New Jersey
And commuting to the city
Every day
Always would listen to Stern
Even the
Even the best of repeats we'd listen to
And sometimes you get sick of it
And wouldn't listen to it
For a week or two
And then you'd invariably always come back
And I was such a big fan
I remember
Whenever Howard Stern
We're talking about me on the air
He would always say
I was a dick
And it hurt
Because it was such a fan of the show
And so I'm listening to this
Pacific Coast Hellway
Andrew Grummit
Developer for iPod Element
Turn me on to it
And
He played one show
Which was pretty funny
And so then I subscribed to the podcast
And I've been listening
And also
And he this guy say
Adam Curry, that big-haired fact
It was the same thing
He's like, oh man
I'm such a fan of the show
And well, to be honest
He's an equal opportunity
A fender
He definitely slams everybody
It's not for the
For the
We could heart
I guess that podcast
But I love it though
Because it is
It's the guys a great writer
And he's got bits on there
Check it out
Pacific Coast Hellway.com
Wow
So how fucking cool
Is that?
Wow
Adam Curry blowing sunshine
Up my skirt
And after I made him cry
So
I'm such a dick
You did
But you know
Now that you mentioned it
Adam
I do feel kind of bad
Calling you a big-haired
Fag
I mean, let's be honest
You don't have big air
So
So anyway
I was playing this clip of this Adam Curry clip
To my wife
And she was
She's listening to it
She's like
What's that noise
He's making there at the beginning
You know
There was this great podcast
I was listening
So I isolated
Yeah
There was
I put it through an EQ
Compressed it
We're in a whole thing through
Like a multiplex filter
So you can hear exactly
What Adam's doing
Yeah
There was this great podcast
I was listening to
I guess he really is a big fan
Fan
Adam
I said fan
Okay
And you know the funny thing
Was that
We listen to a show
We listen to a daily source code
And we were already
Reading a tribute
To Adam Curry
Even before we knew he was even listening
We hear today
To pay tribute
To a great man
Whether it was
As a big-haired Fag
MTV VJ
Or
As the big-haired Fag
Inventor of podcasting
Adam Curry
Has seen our nation
Through times of great change
Adam Curry
Who skillfully bridged the gap
Between MTV's mother Quinn
And MTV's Kennedy
Adam Curry
Who brought us the music of Paula Abdul
Vanilla Ice
And that guy who said
Wired Up
Today
Adam spends his twilight years
At his cottage in England
Steering out at the sea
A waiting the sweet embrace of death
And so
We salute you
Adam Curry
The greatest American
Who ever lived
Who's also a big-haired Fag
So Adam
Hey man
Glad to have your board dude
And if you really are fan
Dig the show
Hey, let's do some business, okay?
Oh crying
Oh man
It's the second time I've heard it
And it's just as good as the first time
So I went to my mic up there
Of course
Dude
You've done
We've got a deal
Absolutely
You're signed up
That was really real
I really
I really really enjoyed that
Oh man
Okay
Let me see
I've taken notes here on the blackberry
I've got to talk about today
Oh
I was given this most fabulous fabulous gift
It is a neon
And I'm talking about
Let me see
That's probably about
The neon's going to be almost
It's probably about three feet
Why is it almost about a yard
Wide
And at least a foot and a half high
And it's in blue
And
No green
And it's two words
It says the pod father
And the green
I think pod fathers
And kind of like a
Purpleish blueish color
And so that's
What is that?
The perfect gift for me or what?
So of course having the curry condo
Which is basically my bachelor
The bachelor pad
I never had
So I get all the benefits
Right
I get to have the
The godny neon here
In the condo
And it's not godny
It's fucking beautiful
I love it
You know guys understand that stuff
You know if you could choose
By the way
I mean a Budweiser neon
And something with your own name on it
How cool is that
I actually get a lot of the benefit
Of having a bachelor pad
I just don't have all the girlfriends
To clean it for me
Oh bummer
So here's the plan
And it actually has to be delivered to me
Because it's big
And you can't just
And it has no box
These things don't come in a box
They're custom made
Although they should come in a custom made box
So I can take it with me on my roadshow
For advertisers and marketers
Put down the MM50
Logitech speaker set
And the pod father neon
And we're good to go
Now so what I want to do is
And hopefully it's arriving today
I'm going to turn it around
And I'm going to point it out
Out towards the outside
Because I have these
Floor to ceiling windows
So it'll be on the 24th floor
I'll have this neon
That'll be like a beacon
A beacon of light
In the near the financial district of San Francisco
Now they turned off the Bank of America building
Someone's got to provide me the beacon of this area
So it might as well be me
Hello everybody
This is match winestein
Of yeast radio.com
Your favorite lesbian on the internet
I want you to listen to yeast radio
Because
Well because Adam called me about 10 minutes ago
Adam curry that is
And he said listen match
I need a promo from you stats
So I can play it on the serious radios
And I said what the hell are you talking about
I do have a day job
I got a goddamn girl band to manage
That's girls spelled g double rl
Called goddess ria chosen
Believe me these dikes are an easy
Anyway
I just finished dating a California kitchen pizza
And now I have to do this fucking promo
I don't know what the fuck to say
Listen to my goddamn show
It's fucking hilarious
Stupid bitch
He's radio.com
Match has been very angry lately
I'm kind of digging her angrieness
It feels really good
Radio.com
All right
This is a match up since me by art
72 actually today
From matchuptown.com
Funky cold ding dong
Mashed up by DJ Prince
Cold cold
And I'm looking for the action
But like never said
I can't get no satisfaction
I ask the guy I want his advice
And I want to go with dinner
This brother told me to stick it
On how to get boy chips
Put a little banana hay
Blast in the trouble
Come real quick
This better than any of our poor
Have a easy act
A couple of sims of this love
Postion and Shelby on your lap
He's all my gigs up to my soul
Where he began to beg
I didn't lick his bones
And looked at me in the wildly
One mile leg
He was distracted right
Before he was wedged by his feet
But now all the pooms run
That my house wasn't funky
Cold with dinner
Ding ding ding
So I took him to my crib
And everything would be well as planned
I wish he got a dress
It wasn't a big old mess
He's singing a love of the man
So I want him to walk back
I don't want him to walk back
But then I was surprised when he went up
He must be sure that he'd always feel a poor poor cold
But dinner
You know what I'm saying
You're good
Hey, no plans with a man
This is the 80s
And nobody's down with the lady
Remember tone load man
That was a revolution on MTV
Back in the day
He did that video
What the word was
He did it for 100 bucks
It must have cost more than 100 bucks
But it was a very very very low budget
That was number one with funky cold medina
Damn
Remember that
If
Oh
All of the mashups by the way
And I don't have a hit test today
I saw young palettes and sent one in
Just as I was starting to record
So I'll save that one for tomorrow
So I'll have a hit test number
Was it 62 already
So I've noticed that the iTunes links are showing up
In the show notes
I'm loving loving the wiki show notes
I'm not quite sure what happened
Or what we did different
Still not quite sure how it works
But the show notes are really really kicking
So basically I'm linking to
To the show notes from
From dailysourcecode.com
If you're just
Listening to this podcast for the first time
What the hell are show notes
So instead of me reading out
You were else to you
Where to go and find stuff
Like some of the promos that you hear
Or some of the pod safe music
Or the mashups
Anything based on the show
You can go to dailysourcecode.com
You can also go to curry.com
Both places work www.curry.com
Dailysourcecode.com
From there you'll find a link to the show notes
The show notes is interactive
That we're testing
The wiki show notes
Which is just a great name
Anyone who's name is wiki
I will hire on the spot
Can come and work for us right here at Pod Jo
I don't care what your skill set is
If your name is wiki
That's your real name
You're hired
Hi I'm wiki
I work for Pod Show
So it's a collaborative writing environment
And what I'm seeing now
Is that besides the fact that
People are going by the timecodes
Even the putting timecodes in
And probably my clue set it up
Is probably doing the first bit
Getting it started with the timecodes
Everything that's discussed on the show
Show's up in writing
With links
And so for instance
I'm sure the tonaloke
Funke called Medina
If it's on iTunes
Which it probably is
They'll be a link to it
You can buy it
So
It's pretty cool
And there's also a place to comment
Now I'm seeing that the comments
Are showing up as a part of the wiki
I really got a
I really got to get into this
Someone told me yesterday
That wordpress
Which is
It's a weblog software
When I'm moving to eventually
To do my show notes on
It has a wiki plugin
Or something like that
Boy this
Mike is shitty
It has a wiki plugin
Plugin
So that you can
I guess you can post your show notes
Or something and get it going
And then that can be edited
I got to check it out
You know who lives in this building
Matt and Mullenwegg
He's the guy who invented wordpress
I met him in the lobby
The other day
I'd met him originally at Nomdex
And Seattle
We did shoot that seems like ages ago
That was a 49 episode to go
Episode number 200
We did that on stage
The closing keynote
And so I met him there
And I was like
Cool software for sure
And we actually talked about
The multi-user software
There's some stuff that they had just
Taking out of beta into release
So he lives in the building
We've exchanged numbers
So I got to hook up with him again
So that we can
Yeah so that we can talk about
Stuff like that
Yiki stuff
And I will report back
As always
Let's say have
Oh yeah
Here's some disappointing news
So I'm all jacked up
About bio diesel
I've got
Where's it?
I'm getting rid of the Audi A8
In a couple of months
And looking to see what I'm going to buy
To replace it
I want to diesel
That I can throw vegetable oil in
Or my ultimate dream is get
Chris Rockwell from the daily download
To basically be my filling station
To poop in my tank and make it go
And it's quite apparent
You can use a lot of real raw oil
The materials to make your diesel engine fire up
Apparently in the United Kingdom
Where I was planning on having this car
You have to pay
Was it 27 pence?
27 pence?
It's like 50
Oh that's yeah
It's 55
U.S.
Dollar cents
Tax per liter
If you're using fucking vegetable oil
You have to...
What am I going to do?
I'm going to...
That's frustrating man
Well clearly they're way ahead of the game over there
The government's already figured out that
This is going to be a great alternative fuel
And they're already taxing it
I'm not quite sure
Someone asked to send me some more
But put it on the wiki please
Point to the information on
If I'm creating a couple of gallons
Worth of
Biodesally my garage
Which as you know
I'm really going to do
How do I pay the government
Do I just keep track of what I pumped into the car
And then send them off a check
Or how does that work?
Or do I...
Or do...
Maybe they have a official place where you can purchase
Biodesally
I don't know
Pretty interesting though
I...
I don't understand
I don't understand how you can tax somebody
For vegetable oil if you're going to cook with it
But then the minute you have another use for it
You know that's a rip-off man
That is a freaking rip-off
But I have to talk to the authorities about that
Dammit
Hi
And I'm Ryan
And we're from there
We learn cartoon characters
Can play the jaw harp
To be played the jaw harp
A dog could play a jaw harp
A cartoon dog
He got down with the jaw harp
You miss Dawn making fun of cartoon characters with disabilities
Did Charlie Brown have leukemia?
Dawn insults people she went to high school with
This one kid Jason I went to school with
You a smell like capy
And Dawn insults us all
You don't fucking idiot
History was made folks
Back to the jaw harp
Yeah
Chuck this out you guys
I'm so excited right now
Because in my hands
For the first time in my life
Is a jaw harp
Or some people call them Jew harps
Dawn plays the jaw harp for the very first time
Let's see if I could do it
Hold on, I'm so excited right now
Hold on
Ow my tooth
There's nerves in your teeth
I need a lesson
You got to do it closer to the mic
Okay, hold on
There you go
Let's sing a little bit
You're hearing history right now
Because you'll remember
You'll think back and go
I was there the first time
Dawn played that
I shared that moment
I was there the moment
Her tooth shattered
I still got it
Open your world man
And how can we forget Dawn's trip
To the YMCA
I could tell you about something amazing
What?
I went to step aerobics today
At the YMCA
That's not amazing
So
The instructor who hopefully
Doesn't ever listen to this
She had like this little line of pussy sweat
Really?
Around her pussy
No
There's a little bit of sweat line
And I was like
I'm so excited right now
I can't stop looking at that pussy sweat space
Her camel toe was sweating
Did you like point it out to your stepmates
So don't miss another episode of the Dawn and Drew Show
Or else Dawn might say
Are you fucking loser?
I'll show a dot com
Recommend listening with it
At least one foot firmly planted in reality
Well
What can I say?
Oaks
With a guy like this in charge
You can at least count your blessings
That the music is great
That's right
Here at the reaching for lucidity podcast
Which is located at reaching for lucidity.net
We offer only the best of pod safe
And independent artists
Here's my digital assistant faith
To tell you a little bit of what you can expect here
Monday
Rock
Tuesday
In the end of
Conative
Thursday
Rock
Friday
Hard rock
And metal
Sunday
Jazz
On Beyond
Classical
And New Age
That's right
You get all that
Plus
Humor
Great headlines
Gadgets galore
Fooders here are the dog segment
And trivia
All delivered
In a way that can only come from a big city
American guy that finds himself stuck in
Small town rural England
I'm Aben Crawford
Your host for the reaching for lucidity podcast
Which is located again
At reaching for lucidity.net
Come in
Kickback
And be entertained
Caution
Listening to the RFL podcast
Has been shown to be highly addictive
I did that Saturday night special podcast
From the condo
And I played a couple of non-pod safe tunes
And that bad boy I know
But I got an invitation from
Carin from Carin's theme song podcast
KTSP
And the rules, the laws are a little bit different
In the Netherlands
The their equivalent of Ask A BMI
The Buma Stemera
Have basically said you know what
Not only do we have a license for podcasters
But this is the way to do it
And it's interesting because they've basically put their foot down
And said alright
This is a performance just like radio
So pay up
And the record industry has been kind of silent about it
So what we're seeing now is a whole slew of podcasts
Originating over there
Where the podcasts are paying their license fee
Which is very low
I like that because these guys are definitely smart about it
You know this is long tail stuff
It's much better to get 50 bucks a year
Or 50 bucks a month or whatever
Let's say 50 bucks a year
I like that much better
From a million podcasters
Then it is to try and have them track the songs they played
And revenue based
Sliding scales
I'll never work it'll never scale
Literally so
Condon's podcast
Where she plays
But an hour's worth of songs that are all related
In a common theme
I think she doesn't have Friday
But usually I'm cognizant of it by Sunday
And I always look for it on Sunday
It's always there sitting in my
In my iTunes or if it's on the other computer my iPod or lemon
And it's just a great Sunday kind of vibe
And she really does a research on the songs
You know fill up an hour on one theme
You know and do that every single week
So she's invited me at any time
Said you know I said geez
I really love doing 80s
You know
80s music podcast
Just go through my iTunes basically and say here's another cool song
I don't want to do it every week
But I'd love doing it once or twice
So the theory here is that if I
If I make a podcast and give it to her
They'll then be released under her license in the Netherlands
And it'll be legal
So I'm going to talk to I'm going to talk to some people about it
But that would be just so freaking cool to do
And that not that I would do it every week
But I'd love doing
Probably get Patricia up that that might be the way to get Patricia back on the podcast
It will talk about you know
Good times
Like do old farts exactly
Quickly now
Yeah
Thank you very much everyone who sent an information about
EVDO the wireless broadband servers that is sweeping the nation
Looks like I'm going to get hooked up
I'll do it when I get back
But then that really does save me all the hassle of getting the cable guys in here
And I'll test it you know
If it sucks then
Then we'll know or if it doesn't
I mean I'm not expecting all that
I'm not expecting huge broadband speeds
But if it gives me 500 kilobit to it to to
Mega bit download speed
I'm good
No one is told me about the upload speed though
That is critical because when I'm shooting up
You know source code and other files up to servers
I do need some kind of throughput
So at least at least 250 kilobits
That's really not enough
I mean 500 would be perfect
But let's see what they got
If anyone has that post that on the wiki as well
On the wiki
Show notes
And
Oh yeah
I am super husband
I have hooked up Patricia and her sister Ivan
Next weekend
Not this coming weekend
The two of them go to Paris
They fly to Paris
They run day boo in Paris
And they're going to the fall fashion show
I don't know if you know anything about fashion
But it is really hard
To get any kind of
Entrance to these fashion shows
I mean
You think that it's hard to get in like the MPV awards
No no no no
Getting into the Chanel fall fashion line up
No that's really really hard
But I did it
So I got him tickets
And so that means that will definitely be a Saturday night special
Then because I'll be all alone
Well I'll be with Christina
But you know Christina
She's she's always on her own computer
Doing all her own stuff
She sent me a very cute email
The other day
I think she finally does miss me
It's hard for 15 year old to miss her dad
You know
That's so much going on in her life
Her social agenda is so incredibly full
I've rolled out some music from the pod safe music network
As we near the end of today's daily source code
This was amongst the top pod plays of the week
I played it before on the show
I just want to play it for you again
46 blisters the name of the band
This is in a long time
It's like fish you swim in
Took off your hat and turn your chin in
Time still still and say
Mark's place
We walked up with new hills
At times like this
And times like those
We felt the heat of all the years
I feel my head and spill
My tears in love
Time
In a long time
I feel the sea
I don't see you
I saw time round your feet once
Little seas that blink and shimmer
Throwing on more cold hearts in it
Don't walk and take your place
Little seas that blink and shimmer
In a long time, In a long time, In a long time, In a long time, In a long time, I don't see you.
I saw stars around the field, I saw the lights like wishes for me.
To go to a higher turn, A chillin' time still still to say.
The world's place we were dealing with, I always have time to say.
This is the most time I've ever seen.
I will see you.
Not pretty.
Like 46 Bliss.
In a long time, From the Podsafe Music Network, If you want to find out more about that band, song,
Any other Podsafe tunes, which means they can be played on podcast.
Go over to music.podshow.com.
The Podsafe Music Network.
As a listener, you can just roam around, see what other shows are playing, listen to the songs.
You can listen to it right online.
No special software needed.
If you're an artist, head over and get, you know, a couple of your songs up.
And you get a band page, and you can put up all your links to, you know, selling your music,
and your merchandise, and I think we're adding forums as well for the band pages,
so that you can go in there and post comments about it.
Podcasters as well.
Go in Register, which means anything you find on the Podsafe Music Network.
You can download, using your podcast.
As long as you report it back to the network, then it's all cool.
It's a very, very simple agreement.
Right, I got to get out of here.
So tomorrow, as I said, I'm flying back straight from SFO to Heathrow.
What was that like, 12 and a half, 13 hours?
So I'll have plenty of time to catch up on some podcast listening as well, working on some other stuff.
And that means that the show tomorrow show will be up, you know, really early.
I'll probably have, I'm going to, maybe I might even, I might even get a really, really early to do it.
We'll do it.
Why the frick am I up this early podcast?
And then I'm definitely going to chill over the weekend, hang out with the girls and Monday.
Of course, we'll be back with the, with the normal source code.
So that's it.
This was the first podcast that will simultaneously cast same day broadcast via satellite.
We're in space, baby.
And as well as on the, on the regular podcast feed daily source code.com is where you can find the feed to subscribe to the show.
You can search for it in iTunes.
That's a free download for Apple.
And we know as users from Mac and Windows users.
And of course, I bought a lemon, which lots of people really, really love and are very, very loyal to.
Adamaccurry.com.
I'll see you.
Bye-bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.