With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Delta Sierra Charlie 305 Tuesday December 27, 2005
Can't do a value with the evidence on a close case, high-class, high-class, high-class,
potential in a place against the clock.
You look like you could use a bricks to set as I lift my head, and I'm a looking from a danger.
Not sure how long I would talk for looking for the girl thought I saw her on the show, but when I looked together
I felt I had been mistaken looking in the wrong direction, I can question tape it close to the answer.
I can't a chance because when I hit the walls, I'm the back to send me up for the bowl of lunch.
I went somewhere to go.
I know I'd rather stay.
Mix it up, mix it up, stir it in a cup, turn it up, mix it up, mix it up, stir it in a cup, turn it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up
all just up with somewhere to go but I know I'd rather stay in, in search of a truth that lasts
Forever better stay at the end
What does it remind you of?
It's a couple of things in there that don't know if they get some Michael Frank's, I guess.
We should really check out the influences on all of the time, let's do that now.
Sound scientist, that's Phil, from the potsafe music network.
We want to find more out about sound scientist and hop on over to the show notes.
Let me go there right now, let me tell you who their influences are.
Because that's one of the things you're supposed to listen to your profile.
Hold on a second, let me see.
Let me go to my playlist.
Sorry, not only a little bit better prepared than this.
Oh, my goodness.
You know that this thing has been on the potsafe music network for a long time.
In fact, so long that it's like at page number 7 of my playlist.
Let me see if this is it.
Here we go.
Sound scientist.
Come on.
Why don't I?
There we go.
Click on the link.
I July 19th, 2005, my goodness.
That's when I added it.
I haven't played it since then.
Okay.
Influences, Queen, Stevie Wonder, Old Weasers, Chopin, and Radiohead.
If it's everybody, hope you had a great Christmas.
If you're celebrating Hanukkah, happy Hanukkah.
This is your daily source code, kind of a laid-back version today.
I have some things prepped and prepared and some stuff to talk about.
But I've kind of been keeping it loose.
Oh, man, it's so nice.
Just, you know, take three days off.
You know, it didn't do a show yesterday, which, of course, was in Europe.
It was the second day.
Well, it was everywhere.
It was the day after Christmas.
But in Europe, they usually celebrate two days of Christmas.
So you had the first day in the second day, both are holidays.
In the UK, they have something called Boxing Day, which I still don't really understand.
I'm not quite sure.
What, when you're supposed to give gifts, is that on the 25th and what do you do on Boxing Day?
One thing seems to be very similar between the, you know, Kingdom and the United States.
And that's the, a massive amount of shopping that I do on the day after Christmas.
Wow, all the newspapers are just full of it.
And we almost had a white Christmas.
Today it's snowed.
Some big, nice, white snowflakes.
So two days late, but we came very close.
So it's interesting because I've become kind of the weathermen of my, of my direct environment.
People are always asking me what the weather's going to be like.
And the reason why I realized actually I realized it last night when I said,
Oh, snow's coming tomorrow is because I'm usually right.
And why am I usually right?
And this is maybe this is not a big, oh, wow thing for people who are into weather.
And I know there's huge communities about weather on the internet.
I mean, weather and if you could really predict the weather accurately.
Oh my gosh, would you be the most powerful man in the universe or what?
The reason why my weather reports are pretty accurate is because I get my weather reports from aviation.
And the way it's done is through Maytars metro area.
What actually does Maytars town stand for?
That meteorological meteorological report for area.
I should know this shit. Well, then you have the tough, which is the terminal area forecast.
So basically, if you combine those two pieces of information and it's written in this amazing code that is actually a part of your,
and you know, part of your, your training as a pilot.
Let me see, I'll give you an example of some code for today, all right.
And I'm going to do it for London Heathrow.
Hold on a second.
You can look this stuff up almost anywhere on the internet.
So London Heathrow, I know, is EGLL.
That's the code.
And here we go.
Okay, so if I were to read the, the actual tap and Maytars, it would sound something like this.
270315Z space 270413 space 36010 KT space 9999 space FEW 014 space SCT 018 space PROB 40 space TMPO space O40.
I can just keep on going.
And there's more than there's minus SHSN space BKN 010 space PROB 30 space TEMPO.
So it's this incredible code, which if I were to translate it, let me see if I can do this for you.
I'm going to translate one of these lines of code.
This would be the long terminal area forecast for London.
So it's issued on the 27th at 1036 UTC.
Valid from 1800 UTC on the 27th at December until 12 noon UTC on the 28th.
Wind 10 degrees at 7 knots visibility 10 kilometers or more scattered clouds at 1800 feet.
So this is important stuff for pilot and really what I like about this weather is you're getting it from people who are in that real area.
Not just on the ground, but also reports from pilots in the sky.
So you do have a three-dimensional kind of view.
Temporarily from 1800 to 2100 visibility would be 5,000 meters light showers and snow broken cloud at 1,000 feet.
So there's a reason to maybe not go flying if you don't have an instrument rating.
We'll build the 30% temporarily between 1800 and 2000 visibility will be 2,500 meters.
So now we're really starting to close in showers and snow broken cloud at 700 feet.
So that's really where you're going to have some problems if you don't have instruments broken cloud at 1,500 feet.
And then the Omni is CB, which stands for Kamila Nimbus, which means badass thunder storm clouds.
Don't want to be in those clouds. So this is how I get my weather information.
So I can basically say, hey, you know, what it looks like showers, snow, it's going to be overcast.
And you know, I can give a probably about 30% that that'll happen.
And it's usually right because aviators depend so much on the weather.
And not just for bad weather, but you need to know where the wind's coming from.
What's, look, it's an element that you're dealing with is like, you know,
the road and weather conditions in the air. It's weather conditions.
So it really does work. And I'm, I hunted around a little bit to see if people are doing anything.
Really with weather forecasting based upon this information, which is accessible just about anyway.
As far as I know, it's completely freely available information worldwide.
And as long as you know what airports to look for, or you have a system that can look that up and get you the closest airport information,
you're going to be pretty good with your weather forecasting.
So anyway, we could start, I guess we could start a whole huge threat about weather here on the daily source code.
But I've gotten into it. I really have.
I actually saw someone wrote some pearl script that'll decode these codes.
It seems like a great programming project, by the way, if you're, you know, because the codes are all standardized.
Excuse me. Oh, my goodness.
It's a double shot of sincere, everybody.
Andrew Klein wrote me emails because I live in Brooklyn, New York and work in Jersey.
So needless to say, I've been driving people to work because of our transit strike.
Anyway, although the strike was over Friday morning, my wife still decided to go in early, so she could do some last minute,
Christmas shopping. I was okay with driving her, but needed to leave earlier the normal and warrant her of this.
Of course, the ensuing argument about my impatience got a little testy if not for the heater in the car,
the frostiness between us would have been unbearable.
That is, until you mentioned leaving late to go visit your mom and how living with two women,
you should figure it to have at least 30 minutes to be late when leaving with them.
We both started laughing and as the heater in the car had already kicked in, the last of the frostiness between us disappeared.
Thanks Adam for helping out with my marriage.
All a part of the public service that Delta shared a Charlie tries to offer you.
Got an email from my dad. He says he's okay. He has some new year's resolutions.
No smoking, no drinking, no more exercise.
And it was very nice of a couple of people who sent in and explained what a Tia is.
Dr. Katz who we've spoken to before chief of cardiac surgery in the Virginia Transplant Center.
Enrichment for genius art here by your parents' health problems.
If some information is to clarify what a Tia or transient ischemic attack is about.
Basically, a mini stroke usually occurs from a small clot or piece of cholesterol like debris traveling to,
and temporarily occluding a small blood vessel in the brain.
I'm going to scratch my head and then talk about that shit.
Fortunately, by definition, a Tia lasts only a very short period of time and then totally resolves.
Unfortunately, it is many times a predecessor of things to come.
And he sent me a link to the American Heart Association, AmericanHeart.org.
They have another one here.
William Pachal, not basically sent the same thing.
But the cool thing was, is that the way my dad sent the email,
and I told you that we don't really talk.
He said, oh, I happen to listen to DSC.
If you call it DSC, you don't just happen to listen to it.
It gives me a whole other perspective on the audience.
And Paul Nichols, bless his heart.
Good old podcast Paul.
He heard my call.
I wanted more cowbell, and I wanted some drum cadence.
And he sent me both in one nice little meat package. Thanks, buddy.
One, two, three, four.
Matthew Ebal.
Matthew Ebal. He's got a new CD coming out.
I'm really looking forward to it. It's called Bearing Coffee.
I know it's that it sounds great.
Very catchy, a lot of fun.
So I can't wait to hear the new one, Matthew, very cool.
Check out the website.
He's got this really cool, copy, folk rock going on.
Reminds me a lot of people like Jason Mirazz and how he day, who I adore, I think they're great.
I am really looking forward to that CD.
We're going to rip this podcast.
To this, the question, who is Matthew Ebal?
Now, live from the accident, hash headquarters in Metro West Boston.
Here's your host, CC Chapman.
Good Thursday, it is episode 133 of the financial aid podcast.
My name is Chris Panwalk, I'm a new Chris.
Daily.
Counting down the top ten podcasting tunes, being spun by podcasters.
podcasting, it's battle curry.
Almost live from the cottage at the 5th, safe music Tuesday.
Matthew Ebal on the daily source code.
She's a really solid, fun tune.
He has such a good voice, really does.
And what's great about Matthew is that he just had the urge to chase his dream.
One day, through everything the back is you haul, hooked it up to his car, grow from Washington state.
All in the national Tennessee.
Let's roll out some tunes.
This is, of course, you've probably heard this several times on the daily source code.
By now, you should know Matthew Ebal, right?
It was the time when nothing stood in between us.
Now there's a girl in the world so sharp, it'll make you bleed.
We don't talk, we just punch the clock and find each other in the same old rhythm that may be a little escape.
What we need.
We love and you work like a dog every morning.
The city's a pain like the latte's stain on your dress.
Hit in the bay and before you break down,
I don't cost the damn to leave this town.
But you don't know because we got to get out of this mess.
So let's drive away.
Let the sunlight chase us all day.
Now nothing gonna stay in a way.
Let's drive away.
Let the sunlight chase us all day.
Let the light chase us all day.
I'm sorry if I seemed fast but I gotta get going
Just gotta be more than the coffee shops in the barn
Baby, baby, it's still late
Baby, baby, it's just late
Baby, you take my hand, we'll get in the car
One, one, one, two, let's drive away
And some nice Jason's all day
Baby, that's all I got to say
Baby, it's right
We'll drive away
Baby, you take my hand, we'll get in the car
One, two, let's drive away
Matthew Ebel
I've said it before, I'll say again
Top down, driving around music from Matthew Ebel
Drive away on your daily source code for this Tuesday
Yeah, drive away has spent two weeks at number one
An amazing 13 weeks in the countdown
I'm telling you Matthew Ebel really knows how to promote himself
That match came in, I'm like, yeah, perfect, I'll play that
That's awesome, very, very cool, Matthew Ebel completely dedicated his life
to being an independent musician
And I wish him, of course, a great 2006
I don't mind quite sure about shows for the rest of the week
or actually rested the year
Because I'm kind of waiting for the weather to give us a nice day
The wind commander called me up just before Christmas
He said, dude, I've got two squared tires
This is from my night landing at Farrox
But he was pissed
And he's really just pissed, he's like, man, that's 200 euros dude
For your tires, don't do that
They did their job, of course, they did stop me
So he's like, okay, listen, the minute the weather clears
I'm coming out, we're doing a whole bunch of night landings
To Antwerp Airport, we can do it until 8 o'clock at night
And I'm going to come pick you up
So that's actually how I got to the whole weather thing
With the snow and everything last night
Because we said, we knew last night that it wasn't going to happen today
When it does happen though, which could easily be tomorrow
And I won't know until around 7 p.m. because that's when the new
Terminal area of forecast come out
And it has to be good weather here and in Belgium, obviously
That's where we do most of our training
And if possible in the middle of the day long
In the Netherlands, because I'd like to drop by and say
Happy holidays to cast Blaster Mike
I think my wonder
But I think he was sending his son off to stay with grandma or something
But I think he's having some kind of
Romantic week
Good buzzer's house
So anyways, so that could affect the shows for the next couple of days
If we do go, then I'll probably miss one day
Or I'll be late one day, something like that
We'll see what happens, new worries
Let me see what I have here
Oh yeah
Good buddy, comic strip blogger
Has his predictions for 2006
He has some really, really funny, funny predictions
The best one at number three
Adam Curry and his friend Rom Bloom will sell pod show ink for $400 million
To Yahoo, please
Why go and ruin a good thing?
I'm having too much fun, man
This is not built to sell
There's got to be a real reason
I don't see a selling anything to Yahoo
Man, oh man
I mean, yes, I'm pretty funny predictions on there
Check it out at what is it
Blogs.msmobiles.com
Yeah, I'm still presuming that mobile phone fan
Is the same guy as comic strip blogger
And I was kind of wacky
Who's Skyping me now?
Go away
What was he gonna say?
Something about comic strip blogger
Shit
Oh yeah, I received a Christmas card
From Jaysek
And I think that's
I don't know
So is this all three the same guys you have a mobile phone fan
You've got comic strip blogger
Then you've got Jaysek
And then you've got some guy who says he's Jaysek
But he isn't or at least CSB says he isn't
I don't know
But I got a Christmas card from which is
Very sweet in this concert
Oh shit
And disconcerting at the same time
How is this tape Marcus ID?
Oh shoot
I've been forgetting this for a long time
Marcus from the scenes scene
He does all those
All those cool
What do you call him?
All those cool little pod show IDs
And he asked me to cut him an ID
I'm so stupid
Hold on a second
Let me see
Marcus
Let me see if I can find his email
He wanted me to read some kind of line or form that he could then use
Um
Let me see
Trade
There you go
Trade me for rewind ID
Let me do this right now
I hope you don't mind
What doesn't even say
I guess I don't care if anything goes
Okay
Hey everybody
Adam Curry from the Daily Source Code
You're listening to the pod show music rewind
Well shit
That was easy
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do
Where are flink
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers
We're Earthlink
We believe your personal information should be just that personal
And we believe your internet should be a friend
Not a fo
We're Earthlink
Make this smart choice
Visit earthlink.net
And discover what our internet experts can do for you
Earthlink
We revolve around you
It's cool
And it's hip
It's a slip of the lamp
It's a word or a tip
My gosh
It's a hip
What's a hip
It's an expression of how you feel about something
It's you
Bursting with verbal exuberance
A total expression of audible opinions
And our hip cast
Is full of them
Yips from people just like you
What do you want to hear about
Formulate your thoughts
And call our hip lines
206-984-2-Yip
206-984-2-YIP
Or send your audio file to
Yipcast at gmail.com
Quick, you're a Yipin
Start to Yipin
At www.yipcast.com
It's time for our Metrosexual moment
And how many some music for that?
I got Jeff Smith sent me the Trinity stuff
And he did it perfectly now
I've got like eight minutes of day to day
Day to day
So I can talk over it and do the whole biodiesel Trinity thing
Which we're not going to do today
By the way
I'm saving that for another rainy snowy day
I've got a lot to talk about though
But we are going to do our Metrosexual moment
So I need a Metrosexual moment
Jingle
Let's talk about razors
We've been on the conversation thread here
Which razor is the best
Because we're guys
And we're kind of afraid to talk about that
Anywhere else
But in a synchronous mode
What is this?
James Dawsey
Or Dawsey said
Nevermind since say
I'm currently at Tesco
That's a supermarket here in the UK
Find myself paying for an M3 Power Razor
Before I knew what I was doing
Seriously
I did not realize I had put it in the basket
Shit works
Todd from Jersey on DSC303
Did you say someone is seeking a doopily?
Geez
Someone call Cousin Brucey quick
Okay
Also how come there's not been any discussion regarding electric shavers
Good question
As a tech head
I thought that you and your listeners would be all sorts of things
Electric
I'm a Devout Panasonic user
And it cruises quietly every morning in the shower
It gives a much better shave than I've experienced with the blade
And no worrying about slashing myself when I'm brainited in the morning
So okay, which model Panasonic
And so you're supposed to use that industry
I don't always shower in sync with my with my shaving needs
In fact, I'm a guy who definitely when I'm here at home at the cottage
I let that shit go
I really do have not gone anywhere
And until both Patricia and Christina just say look
We're not coming near you anymore
We don't want to kiss you
You're like a fricking porcupine
You can forget sex by the way
Or at least anything adventurous
So I'm easily like three to five days
If I feel like it won't manage that
Give you a shave
But I would like to know more about it
I'm willing to try all this stuff
I actually
As you recall from the last show
I asked Patricia she was on her way out to Sainsbury
To buy me the M3 Power Razor
What an interesting device
And someone at Gillette is laughing that fricking ass off
And in fact, maybe this is the whole reason why they acquired Duracell
Because basically now they've got one device
That has two renewable pieces
One being the blade
And please don't just put any mock three blade on it
It has to be one of those green ones
And it comes free package with a triple A Duracell battery
Which Gillette purchased Duracell
I don't know was it a year ago or two years ago
So those guys don't be fucking loving this
Anyway, so I tried it out
It's really weird
It's almost like flying by wire in an airplane
Because because of the vibration
And it really vibrates quite heavily
And you're pulling this across your face
It feels like you don't have the pressure control that you normally have
You know how you use your hand pressure
So yeah, just make it glide and some spots you may apply more pressure
And I don't know, I'm not too happy
I think that with any new shaving device you use
You probably have to get used to it in your
The way that it's working
So immediately I've got like bumps and razor burn
And I'm going to stick with it for another week or so
But I'm not really vibing yet on the M3
Again, it could just be because my face has to get used to it
And I don't really like the loss of pressure control
And I got this really long email from Robert Rottenberg
And he says, I'll just read some pieces from it
Most shaving problems arise from beard and skin
Having different levels of moisture
Good shaving technique can equalize them
And improve your results regardless of the blade
As long as the blade doesn't have a naked should do the job
He says he starts with a warm wet face
Now that's how I start all my days
In fact, I prefer to do this in the shower
To maximize the moisture
God, how metro sexual are we now?
Then I apply about a teaspoon of oil all over my wet beard
This is getting hot, baby
It can be baby oil light olive oil or that special shaving oil
With the aroma of peppermint the cosmetic company sell at
20 dollars an ounce
But the oil ensures that the blade will glide over the skin
Without pulling it, interesting
After the oil is worked in
I apply the first two layers
A ladders of shaving cream or gel
A brush is nice
And I use one when I can
But really any foaming cream or gel will do
The cream or gel saturates the beard
Holding the moisture to absorb
Then I shaved on my beard for my cheekbones
To my atoms, I'll pull in short strokes
Look, look, look, look, look
Removing as much of the shave cream as possible
I finish shaving my throat
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah
Anything else here?
It's interesting
So you think that it's all in the smoothness of the face
Good technique with any razor
It does go into
Oh man, he really
How much time do you spend
Bob Rottenberg from the Munchies podcast?
How much time do you spend shaving?
Which is another thing
You know, God damn sometimes it's like not convenient
Jim from Cleveland, Ohio
Adam, great show, listening almost a year now
I purchased one of those vibrating gelat razors a while back
I typically change my blade every couple of weeks
Anyway, I used this new razor that I got for a long time
At least a month, I think even longer
So eventually I replaced the blade
And it went back to my two week replacement rotation
So my theory here is that they give you a longer lasting blade
When you buy the razor to get you hooked
And then the replacement blades you dulled
You buy dull more quickly
Well, that's interesting
I think that they'll be pretty stupid
I would certainly consider that if I was gelat
But it'll be pretty easy to figure out
I think, is there a way to check the blades
And see if the one that comes prepaid
Maybe just do a comparison, see if the blade that you bought
Is even a little bit different
There's some kind of marking on it
The shows that it's different from the replacement blades
Who knows
And that concludes the Metrosexual moment
Hello Adam
Chris from Pennsylvania here
Wanted to give you some audio feedback regarding the comment
You made about the connection that podcasters have with their listeners
Wanted to confirm that you were dead on target
The connection that exists there is a very powerful one
Much more powerful than radio and TV have
And I'll use myself as an example
For instance, the advertising for San Seo on your show
Has convinced me to beg my family for a San Seo for Christmas
I can't wait to get one
And I can't get the freaking thing out of my head
Because you remind me of it all the time
On the flip side
I used one in a hotel last month
And immediately, guess what I thought of you
So the advertising works
And the connection there is very powerful
And there's no advertising that I can recall
Like that that comes from radio and TV
In fact, I never listen to radio anymore
And I don't watch commercials on TV because of TV
So the power is also in the medium
By nature, podcasting is a much more interactive medium
If you want anything
Find out anything on the show
You can just go to the show notes and purchase
Or find more information right away
With TV and radio, the advertisers are just hoping
That they leave an impression on you
So that who knows how much later
When they go to the grocery store or whatever
You remember their project product
Podcasting is a much more immediate
Much more instant gratification and much more
Impulsive medium
As well as a hundred times more targetive
There is much power in that
And I guarantee you that people will pay good money for it
If not for the so reason
That they will get better returns on their advertising investment
It's not a far cry from digital signage actually
Anyway, love your show has had a huge effect on my life
And I started my own family podcast as a result
Which isn't very good but I'm working on it
Anyway, thanks for the hard work inspiration
See you later
Yo Chris, thanks buddy
That's very nice of you
You didn't mention what the name of your podcast was
You should have plugged it
Let me know what it was
I couldn't have said that better myself
Obviously
And it does make
There's a lot of talk about advertising
And we talk about a lot here on source code as well
We have to change advertising
We really do
Otherwise we've totally failed in our mission
To overcome the man
No, overcome the man
It was holding us down
And I think that just because of
The nature of radio
It's not like anyone was really maliciously
There was any malicious intent on the
On the part of mainstream radio
But when you only have one frequency per station
There's a limited number of frequencies per market
And there's only so many markets you can be in
And you're limited by time
Because we're not limited by time
I guess we are
I mean if I were to make a 24 hour podcast
I can only do one every 24 hours
But that obviously
Well, no, that's not true
If I could split myself into
If I could host one and produce one
I could, I could do as many as I want
So, you know, it had to really come down to being
Slice and dice up into
I think but these days it's even 20 second segments
Is that it?
Is that what commercials are running for?
They're still doing 30s and 60s
Probably more 30s than anything
Or maybe 20s with a 10 second tag
Because you have to be able to account for
When you're selling stuff based upon time
That's what they're selling
Airtime
Airtime, advertising space
And there's only so much time in an hour
And there's even legal limits to that
So, when it comes to
What we're talking about here
And since say it was not a sponsor
I just happened to love the product
I've talked about it
With my passion
Same I do about products
That we do get paid for
Let's see like the eye dog or earthlink
Unfortunately we still have to
We're still working on the transition
So you hear a traditional 20 second or 30 second earthlink spot
But in actuality it would be very easy for me to tell you about earthlink
Because I've had an account with these guys for
I don't know
Seven years or something like that
I've always had an earthlink dial in account
It's like you can really trust these guys
Because they come from a good place
And that's the kind of commercial that I like doing
I really do
That's why you remember the Snapple commercials
That Howard Stern did
You know because he was doing him
And I guess he was paid by a result
Or they certainly weren't splicing it up by time
Because sometimes he just go on and on
And on with this commercial
So I think that's really what it is
You know it's it's integrated
And it works
The question is if I all of a sudden
Start getting paid by Senseo to do that
Or they would be sponsoring my burps
Which is a great way
We have limited resources
We don't have so much gas
Would you still think it's cool?
Let's see what we got
Almost 40 minutes
Christ
There's so much more I wanted to do
Okay
I'm going to skip over a couple of things
I'm actually moving them down in my outline
Here we go
I want to there's a couple of audio pieces
I want to share with you
J King says
Anna made a mashup if you're talking about mashups
And revving up Trinity
Hope you enjoy
I'm a sucker for a mashup any day
And I'm starting to figure this out
And I really what we're talking about here
Is
We're mashing up our own media
And you know we're
Mr. Pooch
Bitchigan moaning
Yeah, it's a podcast
Yeah, it's kind of like radio
But what is it really?
It's going to be figured out
Yeah, and you know what really is this stuff we're doing
What we're doing is
And
Listen to that puppy per
Come on, let's go look at the engine
Wait, I'll take my camera
Take some pictures of
We're taking each other
Shit, repurposing it and throwing
Throwing a back at each other
Looks like
It's definitely mashup
I think there's
Somewhere
There's a thing here
To open up the
Ah, there she goes
We're taking
Audio feedback from each other
Listen to that engine per
Huh?
It's kind of like a junkyard
It's bites and pieces
And
This is running like a charm
Just beautiful
Mainstream media
That you've been missed and mashed
And mangled
Listen to us
Listen to that engine
Podcast
You can hear the turbo
But it's really a mash
It's a mash of stuff
Listen to us
Ah, so sweet
Then I think that we're going to see
All kinds of mashups
We've got to pimp this bitch out
That's what we've got to do
It's going to be
It's going to be big
A cock-motion cock-do
I can feel it
I can't feel it
Cock-motion
But it's great
And cock-do
Cock-off-crap
How quickly we're able to organize
And create
Cock-motion
A mashup
There you go
Once again
You know what the hell was that
That was a complete mashup
We made entertainment
ourselves
This is really important stuff
That's happening here
Ah, I think that
When the enemies
That's going to be awesome
I'm excited about it
Hey, you can hear the turbo
All right, Jay
Thank you
It's certainly a mashup of some sort
We are putting our shit together
Mashup and spin it back at each other
Aren't we?
All right, to wind it up
Adam happy holidays
Says Rick Hood
And I'm a sucker for an email
Like this
Uh
The band my son is part of
Blue vagros
As put someone who songs up on the pod
Safe Music Network
I may be biased
But I really think they're quite something, especially for a high school band, as for the
primary song writer is amazing.
Here's Anne Bancroft's dad.
And I'm traveling.
She's a kid.
And all my dreams and superstitions,
I've been burning all the back of her.
It's a common little close with her.
Make sugar on my jacket sleeve.
Come on, this world feels better sweet.
This one is like to go back to you.
Oh, I love you.
And while it wasn't peace, all of this.
But you thank you, though.
She's a train wreck.
Crushing that place to the east.
She's always there.
She's always whistin' me up.
And I don't know why.
Because all of you, you told her I don't know why.
And I'll take my jacket sleeve again.
And all my dreams and superstitions
I've been burning all the back of her.
It's a common little close with her.
Make sugar on my jacket sleeve.
Come on, this world feels better sweet.
And while it wasn't peace, all of this.
Come on, this world smells good sweet.
Come on, this world feels better sweet.
I'm walking away, I'm walking away, I'm walking away, I'm walking away, I'm walking
out.
Blue vagrants from the pod save music network of music.podgeshow.com and bankrupt is dead.
Fine title for a high school band.
And before I forget, if you want to listen to a great rock and roll podcast, rock and
roll geek Michael Butler interviews Susie Quattro on the most recent episode of the
rock and roll geek show, at least the most recent one that I listened to was really
good.
Cool.
There's a lot of things I didn't know about her.
And in fact, there was quite bias until I had never heard her speak it interview and
it was very cool.
So that's it, 45 minutes on the nose, give her take half a minute, I'll be back tomorrow
the day after, you know, whenever I'm not flying and have some more cool stuff to talk
about, all the stuff that I skipped today.
Take care, everybody, and have a great day.
Pot show, breaking out of fat sack of the good stuff.