Fletcher's dribbling down the center core. Here we go. Hey, everybody
Welcome to a daily source code special edition from the curry condo in
South Beach
Or is this actually is this Miami Beach or South Beach? I'm not even going to tolerate that as a question
This would of course mean that it's
If you don't know the answer, you don't qualify okay residents and
So it's a special on the road edition
been here on vacation and
Ron and I thought it would be Ron Bloom my friend partner and co-founder out
Boku communications and do you hear that home all the sudden?
Yes, our neighbors maybe some of the colleges. Yeah, so we've actually got a pretty interesting set up
We're on the balcony here in the in the building Ron lives in this building and
We're renting an apartment for our 10 day stay. That sounds shitty
Where'd that come from all of a sudden?
You're much level here not another level here
And oh, they know how more sounds like you're a blackberry. Oh, move that away
No, no, wow. It's the coffee. We'll live through it. Yeah, actually these might so we've got a the task cam
Pocket studio five that we're using as a mic mixer and we're both wearing these headphone
Microphone deals the headset with a mic that come you know like the Jan Jackson microphone
Which actually makes us look more like to highly under qualified guys doing a
A play by play at a college basketball game. I must say I didn't enjoy your wardrobe now function
Half time and so we're sitting on the balcony
Overlooking let's see, that's the is that the Miami skyline
That's how Miami you're overlooking this game bay
And that sounds much better than the Miami skyline. I love the Miami skyline
Metropolitan Miami right you're listening to the airport flying over here because this week we're in the flight path
You know, they take off that they move it around. No, they don't move that around to please you
They move that around depending on the wind. No, that that's the other part. I mean noise control
You watch a no bank hard to the left. Oh, okay
I mean we call that noise abatement. Yeah, you do. We just like get the fuck out of my sky
Okay, Ron, so
There's a cup actually
It's as real treat to have you on the show
appreciate you making room on the couch. Yeah, okay
What's your you know, maybe we should set some stuff up first cool. So people know who you are they are they all know who I am
Do you want me to drag it out of you or yeah, that's the probability of something ring the pitch
So maybe we should okay, well, you're from Atlanta. That's where you were born born and bred. Okay, and you're how old?
Lenty
That's not 20
That's twice 20 plus okay, but your roots actually aren't necessarily business. No, no
Well, my roots are in entertainment
musician
a bag of bond
20 years on the road
And I'm gonna make it home tonight. You see you joke about it, but
You're well since we didn't establish your age, but you're old enough to have I did you actually play on some stocks records?
Yeah, I played a
A lot of R&B sessions in the 60s early 60s as a guitarist
And when you live in the south, you learn how to R&B pretty early so we we were a small group of musicians that ended up being in bands like
They came from the R&B world ended up being in bands like Leonard Skinner and Almond Brothers and the those sort of southern rock R&B inspired bands
Mm-hmm, and I played I became a session guy and a songwriter
Yeah, anything that we might have heard
Let's see now I was fortunate enough to be involved in one of the few songs in history. We are the world
Almost as interesting one of the few songs in history to be a top 10 record in two different
Generations same same song. Okay. I would know it. You would know it. Okay
It's like a hit testing how many bars and it's out. I'll tell you the the first line of the chorus
If I could fly
Is that a if I could fly
Is that bread?
Okay
It's not even water
But that's what I'm gonna be having it's a song called Into the Night and it's it was a hit song by a Benny Bernoude
Benny Mardonus any more down. Yeah, sure. We recorded that song. That was a huge hit number one. Yeah, I'm a one single yeah, and
Eight years later after all the drug money was used up with Benny for the next record
Was the advance for the second record you don't do drugs. I didn't ever have but he he did he did enough for both of us and
The second record didn't quite go anywhere but the first record had into the night which was a nice big hit and
Then about eight or nine years later after not speaking to him for a while he calls me up because they were running
In the band back together and some a disjocke and
Texas I think
Played it as an oldy but it had been been so long as since anyone heard it. They thought it was a newy right and they started requesting it. Yeah, sure
I know there was no record in the poly polygram
Didn't want to re-release it cuz they left on hard terms
So we went out and we re-recorded the single a sound alike of our own record really
Over just to own the master just to have a new master right and that master went up to top five
I don't think it made it to one but it like number three year number two. Yeah, cuz I was at MTV when it was getting a lot of play
Yeah, you go there you go
So I'm associated with a few of those in other records and bits and pieces and if you're watching late night
HBO or Showtime and you see some really bad B movies like a high school movies like you know more like Chuck Norris movie
Yeah, the bound to see some of my music hanging out
Now you didn't you do some business with Chuck Norris sure enough did we had a kung fu studio
Really, yeah, we had a recording studio well we called it audio post production
It's a very professional. We did post production for cannon films and Warner Brothers films out there in Los Angeles
Had a beautiful studio built into a villa and we ran that for about three years
During which time I made lots of lots of records and lots of lots of songs for film mostly be movies like mixing in action
Missing in action, yeah
Really you score for that not the score where lots of keys on yeah, and you know you see him for everything from
Disney movies like pre hysteria, you know children movies all the way up to
Movies of the other opposite ill-quare. There's not a lot of where your name is not rom-bloom, but then dover
He doesn't have a lot of dialogue
How a lot of dialogue and those but lots of room for sound the movie. I did the voice over for the
The voice dubbing got a fully wrecked penis or word from hustler magas. Yeah, I think I got a couple of those things too
for them on my
astounding hair raising or maybe it wasn't hair
Soundtracks
Okay, I was in Los Angeles
Yeah, man. I was in Los Angeles
And I was running the studio process and then I started thinking about this internet thing
Don't you skip the whole really important part when talk about Stephanie
Stephanie's simplest junior. Yeah, that one
Stephanie. That's an important part. Is it? Yeah, I think so
Okay, all right
So I won't delve into it. You just give me the highlight the executive summary
Executive summary like where do you meet her? I was like the first time Kavalo
Hello and far-knowly who managed
Prince
Asked me to remix some
Prince artist music and
I did that and put some the prints and
Myself have it the only two people in the United States that had this thing called a fair light
Which people do they call Sam?
Walk
Fairly was awesome man and
So
Disem stuff with friends or four prints and the same management company picked up Stephanie
Stephanie, Stephanie princess Stephanie of Monica. Yeah, yeah
That's a one of the managers over there call me and so hey, you know
I had already built a reputation for writing music for people who really couldn't sing
Kind of one of those myself were you behind me leaving you that guy?
That's right fair
Yeah, but between not being able to sing and not singing at all
Yeah
Yeah, you know people like
Jack Wagner. I'm a song for Jack Wagner
Excellent
I can sing pretty good, but it's not gonna be
Not gonna cover off the ball those type of people
So
The idea is to write a song that that person can handle so they ask me to write some songs for Stephanie
And she came over to studio. That's how I'm there
Okay
To be in the rest of the history to be continued one day. Yeah, okay
So
So then you start hearing about this internet thing so you were basically in LA you were
You're probably like just running around right trying to get some shit going on trying to get something happening
Well, I sold this studio right yeah, and I was with freelance producer just writing songs and working on tracks
And when I had worked on the fair light I started I had sent some files back and forth through the internet and
I started hearing about this thing called a browser
And I started screwing around with it. I'll you remember this old machine. I had the hardly worked in a dialogue dude
Where you had all the sounds for every single finder effect
Yeah, loser you're like so bad. I had a very swapping out files just to play this plug
Yeah, I was like into the sound thing. I did it. It's nothing
I'll never forget that. Yeah, okay, so
So you know man this got to be something to this I think I think this possible to
To reinvent music by bringing it on to this internet thing. So I'm checking around. I'm writing a
info Marshall and
Was that golf licks and not quite but it was of about credit repair which we all needed at that particular time
I grew and
And we needed a producer a camera man sound man in New York and we found this guy named Rick and Kilman
and Rick Kilman
And I were talking during the break of filming this awesome info Marshall
And he says you know I know this guy named Adam Curry who knows this internet thing
I said you mean long-haired
Video god Adam Curry
Now what did you really say
That dark I said is that dark a geek or that geek adore
Uh-huh, so Rick Kilman was the audio guy at MTV. He was also all he's a radio guy
He does all you know anything that has to do with sound and he does he's a piece of work
And so you know
I said well if somebody this is just out there as Rick Kilman says it Adam Curry's kind of cool
He also said he did Adam Curry was difficult
Really? So I said well if he's difficult
Yeah, I said if he's difficult and you know that's kind of guy I want to work with
I'm pretty difficult myself and so I cold called you that's right and you were kind of had one foot out the door at MTV or you were kind of
No, I think I was already you out just already out. Yeah, and I and I was sitting in an office with Brad Sirling. Yeah, and did I have
Do we have any other people there not yet just Brad right? Yeah, at Media America. We're sitting up there
With a half an ISD and line trying to
I share some internet a chair in a box. Yeah, literally a chair really that because when we had our meeting we had to pull in another box
I talked to you on the phone. I said hey man. I got this idea. I want to do this music thing on the internet
And I want to do it for the Grammy Awards because I knew the guy that ran the narrows the National Academy
Recording Arts and Sciences and I've done some music work around the Grammy. So I figured I would try to convince them to sponsor the idea
Bring in music online and you said cool
Yeah, you know, and then I came to New York the next day. That's right. I showed up with you like your black blue jeans your black
Adams and you're you know like black cowboy boots, you know way too hip for the fucking room black
Major black ass actually like attitude, but yeah, yeah, man. And then and that was a very enchanting because as many have said
After me
You've tell a story like Kenny you've been just a saxophone. I was I wove the web. You know, I didn't build a web. I just wove
So it's okay, so from my perspective that was like, oh, it's guys got something happening and
Did I didn't I agree to come out to LA the next day or two days later? We go back together. Yeah, we went to the next day. Yeah, all the way back to
I would know no plan on how to sell it. We went down to the narrows. They just moved into this new building and then right my green
And
Rob's sin. Oh, Rob's and I forgot I was gonna say what's his name right. Yeah, both George boys and
With the aquarium in the office. Yeah, he was real proud man. He had a beautiful office. We should go get that thing
He built a beautiful building and probably available. Yeah, you know, he he took the Grammys not many people listening probably know
I bet it Grammys was an inch away from exhibition. It was a death brand. No one wanted to fucking do anything with it
And he's got a little bit of craziness in his in his recent background, but man. He rebuilt that brand and
What we said to him was hey, you know
It's tired. You know in the Grammys is it's a tired brand for tired old people and if you want to get hit
You got to do something with the internet and he he said a very intelligent thing. I never forget what is the internet?
Yeah, this internet used to be go. What is that?
1994. I was like a October 94 right and we proceeded to explain what we thought it was and we came up with this idea that we called a cybercast
And that it not what the internet people think of it today
But for us it was a simultaneous. We were going to use television radio
And the internet see you see me. Yeah, and
Well, okay, I'm getting ahead of us. So we're more the story or later
Well, yeah, we'll do that later. Yeah, we'll just move forward the Grammys story. Yeah, so anyway
So long long story short. I said Ron
Was it before the Grammys or someone else had to well
Once you come on in take half the company and let's go let's go build this fucker
It was during the Grammys disc trade. Yeah, we kind of looked. I think we realized it
I think we realized we had a vibe in a way out of partnership and instinctively
At least for me, you know instinctively we just started splitting the work and getting some done and not bitching about it
Finding attracting smart people good people. Yeah, so then we'll just
Because there are lots of stories and we should certainly talk about some of them in podcasts in the future
Yeah, but then eventually we wound up taking our
Company
Public I mean that was actually I remember we had a conversation in the hallway and the conversation was okay here are choices
we can
Go take money from
John
And be his bitch, but in a good way yeah
In a good way
Or we have a maybe a once-in-one lifetime opportunity to take a company public
I think we both what's right there went
That's doing the public thing. That's going to be interesting, but that was 95 that was way before the bubble the first question we asked was what's public
Yeah, how does that work? Yeah, that was that work. Yeah, that was a really good ride. Yeah, that was I was most excellent
Well, you know considering what we've learned about people who think they have it down
I thought we handled ourselves pretty well
So we went through everything that a major a major corporation goes through without lying
Yeah, exactly and then you know we we built a business over a hundred million in revenue when we were selling that yeah, that was real money
Real money yeah, I mean a big payroll too
We do we have like four hundred and twenty five employees or something like almost five hundred
Crazy 60 million bucks a year payroll
Holy moly so
That that was merged into another public company. Yeah, and they're still around and they're still making my little money
It's always yeah, it's some of our original guys are back out on their own and lots of our original guys
They're all over the place. We see to the whole generation of misfits that really talented and there's still an alumni list that
Twenty-four all still post two once in a while, so yeah, and
And anyway, so we've been in touch often on for the past five six years
Yeah, we sold we sold it in 99 and we been on enough since then
And
Then what happened?
In the middle of that we tried a couple of ideas. I mean, I think that I think that both of us felt
That this idea of an individual being self-publishing or we we thought of it as self-casting
Was going to happen yeah, because you got into
Well, do you could you got into some interesting stuff with mesh networks and cable network?
I tried every possible form of technology. I could to convince any big company
That upstream was as important as downstream, you know
Yeah, close up all the time
And you had jambi and you were doing some really cool stuff and
You know, I came out and visited you in Holland. We almost did the jambi thing together and then you almost did capacity with me and we went back and forth and yeah
And then
And you know that it was just the drive to you go
Some place you know different and then you found it you found it you called me last year
One of those out of the blue calls that I learned to expect from you
That now other people have come to expect from us. Yeah, you know Lance is always like oh
There's Ron. Oh, there's that. Yeah, yeah, there's 30 years there
So yeah, it's a bridge. We hadn't burned yet. That's pretty good
You said hey you said they do it. I think I really have it this time. You know, and it was sound in your voice where
You know, I just said all right
He probably does it feels right even before I heard what it was and you said, you know
Look, it's very simple
File make your own stuff
Distribute it yourself. Yeah, and and and I said this is fantastic
You know and we immediately I think started doing some interesting things and at least talking about it
Which is the way we started the last big thing we did yeah, but for like months months
We talked for it. We really attracted for a long long time and you know
I think I think we made a commitment then to be to not overstep it on a commercial side and and let
The listener the potential audience tell us if they like the idea let the potential production audience
You know let us know if they if they dug doing it and
And to set it up, you know to use what we learned in our last adventure to our benefit this time
You know
so
You know, I subscribe to
Just millions of feeds and millions of podcasts. I'm listening to everything and everybody as much as I can
I have my life as one big podcast
And I came across this podcast just before we got on the plane to come down here or over here over and down here
From something called
dreadful snake radio
I like it already. Yeah, it's really cool and it's a creative bit which maybe we'll get tired of it halfway through
But it's worth listening to a little bit of it because it addresses some concerns that
The podcast community
You know, which means
I don't know what that means, but it's there's noise out there. You know, there's a lot of people want to know what's going on and there's like
Odio came out with something and then they didn't have something and now they have something really cool and and no one really understands what we're doing
That's good
I think is really great
That's the first step in doing something well exactly so he so we put together this
Podcast called money and podcasting a semi rant and he just asked some questions which you know
I think would be fun if we just listen to him just address it. Let's do it. It's it's a creative little thing
Come on, let me see dreadful snake radio. Yeah, I was so
So if you want to stop it just raise your hand y'all
Set funds on bread
Well, hi, this is dreadful snake radio guy and
Today's subject
It's about podcasting and I'm directing this
Conversation to anybody that's interested
But if you're if you're not a podcaster yourself
You may be going
I'm not sure if I know what this is all about
But give this a shot if you are into podcasting yourself and
Then I think this is really an important topic
So I'm gonna try to wax eloquent here. I've been mentally calling this a rant as I've sort of prepared some of the thoughts for it
You actually tell you why it is really sort of a poll-revere
Warning thing
I want to stake out
All around podcasting
Just as another line of thought because I see this podcasting as a movement that's at a crossroads
And I want to address some stuff that Adam Curry is bringing to the marketplace right now
See why I want to do here
Yeah
You got to listen to this. This is great. It's about this. He did some like bits. You'll like it. It's really funny
And it really has to do with the fact that this movement
may become a marketplace and this is not an anti-adom
That's a that's a good
The movement become a more marketplace thing. It's a matter of fact
Adam as you'll you'll hear when I do this is kind of a hero a mine
I think he's an incredible talent and has the potential to bring this in this movement if you will
To a place where it will be incredibly better than it will be today
But I'm a little worried
I'm a little worried. I'm a lot worried about some of the stuff I hear around it's me so bear with me here we go
Here's what I have in mind
Okay, this is not an anti-adom Curry statement. What this is is it's a plea
It's a plea for keeping
Populism popular and keeping access open
In podcasting. That's one of the things that's the coolest about podcasting is it's an absolutely open movement
I was involved in some early television when cable TV started coming out there was a movement called gorilla TV the Michael Shamburg
Did you ever hear of that? Yeah, I'm a gorilla TV man. What? It's like outgold scene
It was a lot of that stuff down south too with it. Really? That's a real time of return
Irundated in cable in his own way really
And the blue channel you know gorilla TV the blue channel and the york you know the blue channel
Yeah, that's what Robin bird and all that stuff. Yeah, is she still on well? I know Mr. Cameron man
Come on baby bang my box. We used to love watching that when we first moved to New York
That's sweet. We digress
We dude Howard Stern is gonna make a hundred million dollars a year
Let me just tell you something. Yeah, this is something you're gonna enjoy. Yeah, okay
250 mercer my old pad and yeah guess who had to be for me
No idea you just said our name dude
Robin bird had your pad 250 mercer
Did you meet her that's what I heard? I'm sure but there were some things on the wall that you heard about the bird heard about there was a wood
Little Robin bird all right back to this dude. Yeah, all right
Was the spearhead up I was involved in some of that stuff. I've just from time to time
I mean, I'm no revolutionary, you know, I'm a
Believe me, I'm not but I've been involved from time to time in these grassroots movements and I see what happens to them
The money comes in thing. I really think we're to cross roads and we got to make sure that we don't let the money aspect
Take this great possibility that's podcasting down the toilet of commercialism like it has on every other form of media that we've seen out there
Wow, he's flushed with excitement
But isn't that misguided? Well, yeah, I mean isn't this completely it's like
How can money control anything? Well
The only way that money controls is if there's a limit of resources to broadcast
If there's a limit of number of resources money can buy up the resources and control it
So the real thing that's going to choke off podcasting is going to be lack of enthusiasm from content
People if they don't do good stuff good enough stuff to attract attention then
It's going to be the victim of its own
Self out of the evolutionary chain right so but and and
Why do creative people not show up to the party? I mean they're they're here, but so what if that what would make that dry up?
Well, what that what happens is we have to simplify the process of letting people be creative
Look and let me try something else out on you
Okay, one to one communication through the phone. You know one to one audio
We've had 60 70 years to get every permutation of it you could possibly have
From from cell phones or regular phones to conference calls to calls with messaging and all these different things that are happening
Well huge industries
Have grown up around one to one communication, but now we have self publishing and there's no
Real industries around self publishing
Web logs
Is the first hint at an industry and an industry doesn't have to be commercial
Just has to have enough people to crank a wheel of progress, right?
So but that so it's an industry then web logs now isn't it? Yeah, it may not be a commercially successful one
But it's industrious and it's self perpetuating, right and and there's millions of people self publishing and millions of people listening
Reading there's not millions of people self publishing and billions of people listening
This is different
Is that again? There's millions of people self publishing right and there's millions of people reading
But the ratio of readers to self publishers is not of the typical ratio of a normal medium where you have a narrow amount of providers
And a large huge audience a large amount of consumers so what what needs to happen in
Podcasting at least in my arrogant opinion is that the that there needs to be an
Constantly open doorway for anyone to self publish
Filtering mechanism for them to find the level that they want to which they want to rise in their self publishing endeavors
And then all of those publishers need to support each other in a manner that drives the audience because some people want to listen
Some people want to speak and
Podcasting is an is in a method for one to speak to many and the many can be one to two or it can be one to two million
So this this industry where other than saying this commercial industry is is waiting for
People not to worry so much about whether there is money or isn't money and start talking about how we all band together
We're going to track listeners
You care about what being said
Because that's the that's the bottom line is if we could spend you and I could go raise a hundred million dollars
And we could get we could foster all kinds of podcasting make it free for everyone to do it in the end if no one wanted to listen then that's it
We'd have you know
What was it X football triple X football?
Whatever that was
Hundred million dollars of wasted effort of something that one was interested in we're part part of the beauty of podcasting is that
And this guy will get to it actually
Oh, hold that thought let's listen to it because he he
He actually asked the question that I would come up with next so let's go explore that topic in a couple places, okay?
Let me you like this format. I like to form that in
He start with a sound effect and asking you what you think it is here we go
No, this is the comedic bit. This is funny
So what is this sound?
Okay, what do you think that was that whistling wind sound? It was a whistling. There's two choices now answer a
That was the Microsoft evil empire blowing smoke up Adam Curry's butt by sending him a new machine that shows video of
Demembers of Doran Doran personally addressing Adam Curry
Backing him in and hypnotizing him into the evil empire of Redmond Washington
Or Doran Doran backwards is not rude in a rude it could be me and 4,000 other potters
Trying to blow smoke up his ass also trying to get a mention on his show
I know I've done it I sent him emails that he's ignored so what I'm trying to say is
I guess we're all pimping our stuff and I don't want to just say that Microsoft is doing it
I'm doing it to I'm I'm trying to get people to vote for me on pad podcast alley
I'm I'm pimping my show there's no doubt about it
But Microsoft is pimping our technology to add him and everybody like Adam that's a leader in this industry too
So there's a lot of that stuff going around and I only mentioned that because
It's going on and let's realize that a lot of the big corporate interests are realizing
Maybe this is something that's going to take off and people are worried about it people are interested in putting some money into it
Let's see what happens now
Let me specifically address a statement to Adam for a moment
Adam you are one of my heroes you are the
Does this will does a hot God that's my that's my thing for you the PG and then you are the pod god
And they're I just want to ask you to be careful
About where you take this movement we've got because it sounds like you want to take it from a movement
To an industry so let me examine that word couple of key questions question number one
Adam Curry can you actually take it somewhere and my answer is yes, I think you can and here's why
I consider Adam Curry a leader
Of what's going on in podcast
What's the definition of leadership?
You know, I do not work in business. I know what that means and I know that leadership can only be judged
If people follow that person then they're a leader now there's a lot of things that make a good leader a bad leader
A mediocre leader
But the bottom line is our people following will frankly many many of us are following Adam around
I want to know what makes a good and bad
Mastering means I've got a lot of great ideas about podcasting from Adam let me give you an example his whole concept of how podcasting is the new community radio
Oh, that's awesome. You know radio is a small community that's that's a small you know AM broadcast radio
But now with podcasting it's not a
You want to slow down listen to it later
This yet, but I'm recording it. It's a content community how I think about a good podcast is it's a content community and the boundaries of this little country is
The content and people that like it. It's not geographic. It can be anywhere in the world
It can be the wing commander and antwerp
It can be you and sorry
It can be me and the northeastern United States or whatever
So anyway, this is exciting stuff my point is Adam you are a leader
Many many of us are listening to you on a nearly daily basis and the we are interested in
We're taking the industry so be careful about what you say to us because we're kind of following here
He has a point there
Absolutely
He has a point oh in here. Okay. We're kind of following here. Okay question number two
Where are you going to go with this question? You've got to bring more dollars into this medium
That is content rich dollar poor medium today now. Let me explore that do you agree with that content rich dollar poor?
No
Okay, no
Is it content poor dollar rich? I
understand it. I understand it
I understand it, but I'm old enough to have seen
The birth of FM radio, you know the birth of independent record labels and and
There's a content and it's going to the beautiful thing about podcasting
The different from a lot of things out there is that it is at the content can find its own level
So I'm not sure content rich, you know, you can have a ton of content that's no good and you're never going to support
Holistic industry or revenue generating industry
What's great about podcasting is I believe that
That you're going to be able to have room for content to find its own level the long-tailed concept, right?
So a guy who is not that exciting but talks about something that a thousand people are in love with
And interested in they find an audience in podcasting right that can be commercial or non commercial
But if they do it right and we do our job, right that person be commercial or non-compare be a priest or a mechanic
Can can contribute to turning podcasting into a medium
Which it isn't yet
piggybacking on other things
But to be a true global medium it needs to have an audience
That that consolidates itself in admits that it is following the content, right?
So to be a medium
What's challenging about podcasting is we're inventing the technology we're redefining the content or what you and I would call format
And we're trying to to demonstrate it. It's a medium all at the same time usually usually it's a chicken or egg
HD TV
It's a technology that was it trying to find an audience before there was any content for yeah, we're doing those
My pacemaker
We're doing those the simultaneously yeah in real time and and and that's what's that's why it
In some ways it's foolish in other ways it's foolproof because if it's it's really simple if it's no good
It's gonna die. Yeah, if it's good. It's really
Almost unstoppable right but so the the next question of what the disguise can ask it to is do you need money to make podcasting good?
I mean, that's gonna be a fine line between you know getting some extra money in this thing to live on
Money that drives better content and so on to when you get a lot of money into a particular media time after time
We've seen that money corrupts it
Okay, there's a fine line between that well
We don't have any money in this medium yet we're waiting for Adam to tell us sort of about pod show and what might come into it and all that
And everything Adam tells us about community and everything I feel really good about it's just I sort of see that there could be some dark clouds out there
But when Adam goes out there and he sells the sentio coffee maker on his site. Oh
Insert commercial here. I put it back on by the way. I changed these years. Excuse me. Oh
Yeah, wait a minute coffee break. Hold on a second
Hmm
We actually could use a refill here
Where's my my daughter?
Another commercial break. We're sponsoring her podcast. Oh, wow. What was that? Do we just lose volume?
Are you there?
Check this out. What happened there? That was really weird. Hey, how's it? Did you hit? Did you? Did you? Did you? Did you? I didn't I didn't
Do I do something weird? Did you hit your microphone volume?
Oh, maybe I'm sitting on it. That's totally possible. Hold on. Oh, thank you. Yes
That did it. Hello, he's the uh, okay, let the ass ask me to this guy. He's coming. He's got some creative coming up. Yeah
You know, I'm fine, but it's got some good questions. He doesn't give a rest of that
I'm feeling fine about it or not, but I gotta tell you. I feel fine about that. He's very up front about what it is
Why he likes the product
Why his liking it is different than just selling it somewhere else. It makes a lot of sense to me. It really does
But what I worry about is occasionally I hear about well, there's other ways to do things advertising products
And I worry about you know somebody thinking out ahead of time not saying Adam would do this
But here we're gonna have a subliminal product placement strategy and then we'll get backing from a
Dodge Dakota and a Sancio and a someone so and I'll drop that into the conversation
What's this guy now? I mentioned something about a
What's he drive? Did he drive a Dodge? I think maybe I just wonder if I can
vagina and then I'll mention the car, but then we'll get the check to come in
Man, that is not the business model right there
vagina card check
That's Holland isn't
Adam or no one else is suggesting that but as this thing goes forward from a non-money media to one that has some money in it
We gotta find the right balance
We gotta find a way to make it viable for people that need the money they're doing podcasting
But it doesn't corrupt the medium itself
Question number three
I gotta take a deep breath here. In fact, I'm even gonna have a sip of water here and then question number three
This is where it starts to get very avian
Club love that was the water going down. Okay. Question number three Adam
You were choosing a group of potters if I can call them that to work with now what's great is
That we want to hear people with great content getting better and with better opportunities and promotion
So that the circle widens and the and the news gets out there
So far so good. Yeah, that would be great. We really are looking forward to that and I think that's where you're going
Okay, but let me tell you what with suck
What with suck is if podcasting becomes dominated by an elite group that has a louder megaphone
Then the rest of us so that the grass roots can't be hurt and I don't I mean
You know there's 4,000 of us now and I'm in there. That's cool
But there's gonna be 10,000 more behind me and I don't want to be the elite either
I want everybody to have a shot at building that content community that's out
To see where he's going. I absolutely do
But I ask him me
Yeah
You know our strategy. We should address this in many ways
He is absolutely online and incorrect and I have you know questions that I would ask is has commercialism killed the internet
What do you think?
No, it's only grown a bigger
Of course and and now we're discovering more
Look you can look at it sideways and say
You know podcasting is for people who communicate
Orally and the internet has been mostly for people who communicate with text
You know obviously not completely true, but there's a different way to look at it and and because
Our mission is to enable everyone to make a quality program
That is a good enough for a million listeners even if only one person is listening
So that's step one to make it take to provide the bandwidth the tools the utilities and the access
To millions of listeners to any individual at a cost that's equally almost almost free and totally affordable
We'll um we'll have include a hum like we have yeah that
Extra and what I learned and my record production days is if you can
Can't cover it up turn it up right?
Okay, what we're doing good with that that's not a hum that is a that is that they just think to air filter feature
So did you just say that this is gonna be free or not?
What did you just say? I think they'll be
First of all there's free and there's also freedom right so there'll be levels of free and levels of freedom
To the extent that you do not want to be that you first of all everyone should be able to make
Broadcast quality a podcast quality pod show quality podcast. There you go
That's what pod show is about is creating a quality of the product
So every single individual cost effective. They should be able to make a pod show quality podcast and when you make a kickass
Production of a podcast with with user friendly tools and you're really making a pod show and if you aspire to make a
Pod show quality podcast that should be within everybody's reach that's step one
Step two everybody who's interested even for split a nanosecond and and listening to pod
Has to be able to engage them quickly and effortlessly and get to what they're interested in or discover things
They didn't know they were interested in
I number two number three
For those who are interested in the monetary aspect of monetizing you know the aspect of monetizing
They're making making money making money. There should be a mechanism and it should be a fluid mechanism
One that's that enables a person with 10 listeners to make some money on the weekend
And one that enables a person with 10 million listeners to be able to make a life career out of it
And there's and there's that person will not the only thing that's louder in terms of a megaphone see
See the metaphor or the or the analogy falls flat because podcasting
It's not a megaphone business a megaphone is in implies broadcasting, you know
Podcasting means everybody has the same megaphone. At least if a pod show that's what I think we're trying to do
Get everybody the same megaphone give them everybody the stage
Try to find unique ways of filtering the contents of it can find this way to eager audiences
And a bizarre way it's what eBay or Amazon does when when they're at their best
You know when you're trying to find a when you're interested in just in cooking and you want an alternative recipe book
You can you won't find in your local bookstore
You go over to Amazon because pretty much someone is written a book that's only good for 10,000 people and there it is
That huge database and a great search and you believe in them
You and they're filtering it there and they're telling you that other people like this Tuscan cooking book and
Particularly people who like it who are on low fed diet
Like pod cast alley ratings
rate and and
And there's enthusiasm ratings, you know, this is all the rant about podcast alley ratings and
People voting a thousand times. Well, you know, there should be some some room for people who I love this so much
I call it a hundred times
That's how much I love it
It's probably shouldn't be room for people to go. I love this so much. I programmed a line of code to vote for me 10 million times
You know, there's a business there for somebody
But yeah, I think there's room first of all
How do you how do I like like me? I find out about podcast by listening to you by asking other podcasters
They're asking people what they listen to sure so on officially
I'm going to people I admire and I'm asking him we need to get that
We need to not assume that everybody who is a listener is a fanatic about podcasting
But maybe they just wandered by because they're interested in stunt something and if we don't grab those people
We don't just forget the business. We don't have a medium
We don't grab the casual listener and infatuate them like the dedicated listeners are we don't have a medium
Okay, so there's a lot of work. So yeah, there's work to be done on making
Lowering the barrier for anyone to produce. But we can do that. Yeah, well, yeah, totally
But then on the other side it's also really making it much much easier for you know for the audience
So the audience can find it so we don't go through all that how do I how do I find these things questions?
And that's what you know as a as a listener who's not a podcaster that that's what I send my message out to podcasters and to the
technologist which no one is talking about who are out there helping
You know
unsung heroes the technologists who enable this thing to happen unsung heroes people who manage
Directories that that their love is not the podcasting, but their love is listening to the podcasting and helping
Regular people find what's what they think is good in them. They're guides the guides and there's many many
constituents already in our hopeful medium that are already unsung and we haven't even gotten to the poor listener yet who is now got
4,000 things to you know we're acting like 4,000 is in a lot that's too much. Yeah, and you know so our mission is to figure out
How to let how to make it okay for one podcast to have 10 listeners one podcast to have 10,000 and one podcast to have 2 million
and all of those people live in the same universe and that's what I think we can do and the show will be the same quality
It's just it's just destined to find the different level when you say quality you're talking about the actual audio quality or you're talking about
What what does that mean? Good question. It should it it should have the same
production
Content quality so that you wouldn't turn something off just because it sounded bad
Like this like this and or it should have the
For those tools dude, yeah, quick. Maybe one of them is a hammer aimed at my head
It should have also
You know enough
rope for people to hang themselves or people to be incredibly creative right on and you know
As a musician it's what I saw happening in home recording you can make you know you know upstairs
I have a pro tools rig. Yeah, I cost me a million and a half dollars to build my last studio. I want to cost me
You know
$25,000 to build this when I could probably start over and do it for you know five grand. Yeah, and
It's it's nuts how how free it is and how great it is for musicians
So now we're talking about self publishing audio in a different way. So we we let people do it the next thing that we need is
most people who are making podcasts are self producing
And in music that works and doesn't work, right? So there's a good good analogy in music producers and artists are separate
And they bring out the best of each other reason. Yeah, and yeah, and you know these to say what makes a great producer and the answer was a great band
Yeah, and like Michael Jackson and Quincy Jones. Yeah, George Harrison. What did I say George Harrison for?
I don't know and George Martin and the Beatles and the Beatles. All right George Harrison was a beatle, wasn't he?
Yeah
Hey kids don't you want to be cool all the kids are drink and say oh, so you know
You could say no no commercial interruptions in podcasting everybody just pay
That's one way to do it. You could say no everybody gets it for free, but we have to write on the back a big brother
That's another way to do it. Why do people need to be paid?
If if you want to pause the stupid question, I think it's a good one
People don't some people will want to some people will want to quit their job
Some people have family some people will want to survive on their creative craft and be paid for why doesn't that work with weblogs?
Or why isn't it working with weblogs?
Well, I think that I think that web logs
You know, I've heard everything about weblogs and one of the most interesting thing that's we don't we don't break the news
We fix the news you know, and we triangulate
I think it's cool and everything, but I don't I don't know if that's
Exactly
What the essence of podcasting is podcasting is about non-trient and meet non-trient Galation. It's about
injecting personality
and giving something that someone to someone who that's interested in listening to it. You know, when MTV started
a great record executive lamented we just lost the last great thing you could do with your eyes closed
That that bringing videos to music meant you couldn't close your eyes listen to the lyrics and think of your own video
And I think podcasting
brings that back. It sure does and I'm not sure what what web logs
brings back. You know, and it's interesting because you know web blogs are email or whatever it's all basically the same thing
But it's I have to agree that web logs kind of started out as things like new sites and it's always going to be kind of like a
newsy-type medium. You're in general. I mean, of course, specifically that's absolutely not true
But and podcasting did kind of start off
Just as you know, no news to report because we all know it's delayed. We all know you're getting this late
There's like, you know, we found Osama bin Laden. I'm glad you're tuning in everybody and just getting this late break in news
So there's something different there that makes people communicate differently and you know, and a word
You know, it's hard to say, but if you find a great
author
that that is out there
contributing information and text and wanted to syndicate what they say
I think in the early days of newspaper, that's that's what happened and and
Maybe people would pay for that if someone wanted to charge for that
Now people think of it as how do I get the latest information about stuff?
You know, and you don't hear as much talk about the electric rap rapping
eloquently
How what great
content would great turn of word or phrase this person is you're hearing about well
Six people found out that he wasn't telling the truth and they posted his picture and that then that type of thing
I think in podcasting you go man that guy was funny or while he really knew his subject
Or can you believe this this couple that live out in the farmhouse? Okay, you know you you're not saying wow
Let's turn on the podcasting and find out if what you know what British said is really true
Right, yeah, this is yeah, you're right. It said that is a very different vibe in podcasting true
It's just just take a break from reality or find a different version of reality, and it's also appealing to a sense
The listening sense that we have there's been definitely by fucking flat top 40 crap radio
That's right
The whole line just want to play a little bit more this guy and we'll quit it
So which way is this going to go is a chosen group of people that are getting to get some money in this thing
Gonna make the circle wide and so it's better for all of us
He gets funny words about are we on a dominate by a leak group. I don't know
We don't know which way this thing is going to go yet, but let's keep an eye on
Okay, let me tell you when it comes to you know what I just talked about
It'll be great to have folks like Don and Drew who is the other podcast that I listen to constantly
That and frankly I got to tell you I get a real week spot for closet deadhead too
It would be great to have Don and Drew and a lot of other people have access to whatever
Makes better content and distribution for them man. I love to see that
But I tell you I
Just said two very important words there content and distribution now here's one guy's opinion
What the hell does Don and Drew need to get better content look what they do on a farm and was constant for God's sake
I mean what's what what else could you do?
Let's put Don and Drew on the space shuttle Don and Drew and outer space
You know, I mean waitless punani may have its possibilities
But Don and Drew's success is not in having a fancy set right with Dick Van Dyke walking on it and tripping over their couch
Don and Drew's success is about Don and Drew as
People reacting to each other and the world around them and we're all getting to feel comfortable about them as we get to know them
And I want my Don and Drew and I don't care if they're in outer space or not and it has to do with them as people
I'm getting comfortable with them like one generation did with Johnny Carson and another one is now with Conan and John Stewart
You know and I mean any screenwriter will tell you that the whole thing starts and ends with great characters
That's Don and Drew so
Between content and distribution. I don't think putting money in to help in them with content is necessarily going to do a damn a damn thing
Okay, Don and Drew man. They're like they're like
Cool as there's like Lucy and Ricky and hot as Paris and Nikki
Oh, there's Kenny G. It works again. It's calm. It's just coming out like a waterfall
So he's describing what what is he talking about okay? He's saying that he's trying to figure out why why podcast and needs money or why we need why we need money
Well, I want to make money or what we want to do and he's he's gonna split up because I say it's impossible
That it's for the content so it has to be the distribution. That's what he's gonna say well, you know
Here you go 4,000 podcasters
Let's say they have an average of 300 listeners
Okay, that's probably fair. Yeah, what is that?
100,000
And I just lost my math if all of them if all of them got together and decided to recommend
Shows that they like beside their own like like sort of like you do yeah, but in their own way
And all of them made it their mission to to bring not just their show, but other shows
Selfish selflessly out to the universe and we have a listener base of let's say half a million
Do a million people listening to podcast today two months we could have two million in two months
We could double that easy if the 4,000 podcasters were selflessly promoting themselves in other podcasters
Okay, there's a distribution for you. Yeah. All right. Here's another kind of distribution
God forbid somebody woke up tomorrow without asking for it
And had five podcasters on their iPod or their MP3 player other laptop waiting for which five
As a question to ask
Which five will that be different for everybody wouldn't it? Well, you know, let's let's talk about that
Let's let's say that you could wave a magic wand and go out to 10 million people
reasonably good target audience people that might like it and put and you had 4,000 podcasters to choose from
And you wanted to put five or three on their laptop or their PC or their
MP3 player that they would guarantee they would listen to and then from that they would make a decision
And whether they wanted to stay in the world of podcasting listen to more which one to a
Would you choose your own or would you somebody else? Well, yes, I would choose my own start off with
Because I'm a gateway
God of pod. I do a horror
Okay, so is there a right answer to this? I think that that many of the 4,000 podcasters might have to think maybe they're not on that list
That in order to
Get more people lined up to find they need to get 10 million people listening to find the 50,000
They're going to listen to you
Right, so you need
So you need something out there to draw people in you need to just strip is just you need to distribute
We don't have a medium that's where they're messing up with distribution you need to pick 5 or 10 great shows
And you need to get them out to 10 million people so they get hooked on the concept they know come and find the ones
They know right, that's okay. That's what I'll say so that should be the role of the pod squadty type things
It's not it's not for them to be the elite group
But what the rest of the podcasters should be doing is fucking making sure we have a pod squad
And aspiring to get that group distributed as leaders to create the market, you know to create create the medium
Okay, how many listeners do we need before we instead of how much money are we gonna make? How many listeners do we have?
We need to 100 million to be really significant. Yeah, to be significant. How many do we do? All right, so
What's our distribution goal?
And yeah, maybe it's a hundred million
so you and I know that there's ways
To get
millions of people to have a listen
Mm-hmm
And that's I think some one of the things we fear the most because we know how to do that. Yeah, and the question then becomes
Okay, here's your shot slugger
You're gonna put it right and
We better be selfless again and make sure that we're promoting the very best of our breed
In order to hook the rest of the listening world to come in and find the stuff that you need to them. Okay, that makes sense
Hey, we should start a company and do that
Man, oh man, what an idea now could they use better
Studio sound
Because it's a different part. I just been listening to the early shit
Let's do it
So um, but before I get there I just want to say that any effort to really do better content through adding money to it will be marginal at best
Now
Here's what we addressed that
Could happen and I want to give you a little he forgets that
I never mind
iPod play here and what I want to do now is take you to a little tour of what could be the dark side
And here we are as we enter Adam Curry's iPod plantation where the workers are sequestered
Shall we say over that thing barn building
This is Adam Curry and thanks for joining me on this tour of the iPod plantation
I have the chosen ones hard work on new content right in here
Let me just open up the barn door and you can hear what's going on
Or since they'll coffee I've got to get a creative idea
I made a sound seeing tour of let's go over to the real barn run
Yes, open up the door our secret door. Oh look what's inside
Everybody's party
All right, that's enough of that. What are we doing?
We should definitely wrap this up. So what are we doing?
Everybody will be able to make a world-class quantity podcast they will have the tools
They will have opportunity to make the audience this we will do. Are we going to build all that?
We and other people who will help us in building
We are really totally screwed.
We are going to bring we are going to try to bring together some really smart people
And really talented people smarter, more talented than us who are going to help us make this thing real
There's Patricia just as we are winding up
Man, I thought it was a vision
What is it?
If you come leaning into the microphone
A long one
A long podcast
It was good though
Yeah, but we talked about all kinds of things
I thought she wasn't talking about the podcast
Okay
Well thanks for having me
No thanks for being on the show this is good
And this is an extra long one so
People can
You drop out to my guest
No way
This is going to get analysed and exerted everywhere
Yeah
I don't apologize in advance
So when can we make some damn announcements?
Any moment now
As a matter of fact
I hate that answer
The clock is ticking
Well really really really really close
Being able to begin
I think the first thing we are going to try to do is just
Be a little more forthcoming about what we have in mind
Thank you
And we just want to make sure we can articulate it without
Even more bullshit than we sound now
So first thing we are going to do is kind of tell everybody what we are going to do something unusual
We are going to let everybody know what the strategy is
Exactly
Just lay it out
And then
Rather than saying that now we are not taking any steps towards it
Immediately afterwards we are going to start doing things
And making announcements
And I hope everybody who is interested will see that each one of those announcements
Is part of a strategy
Then you can tell us if you think we are crazy
And maybe we will change the strategy
But you didn't talk anything tonight about the two way
You know the interactive part of podcast English
No but what I would like to do is
Like maybe not this long this is just kind of like an introduction
But maybe we can talk you know
I think we should do this more often
You know we should do it
Maybe at least once a week
And just talk to what we are doing
And then people can follow along
And indeed give us some of that feedback
Yep
All right my friend
Dude what time is it?
What country are we in?
Oh kidding
It's podcasting
It could be any time any place my brother
That's right
Well we prove that once again
So it will only take me two hours to compress this
And upload it
Dude
Let's just talk about the connectivity here
We have to
Can we get DSL?
Absolutely
We have to
Because that's why some of your shit doesn't arrive
I mean you send a five or six megabyte file
It takes a fucking effort to upload
The last the last four megabytes on that
Important anyway
Is it?
It's just the front page
That's how many
All right
Interesting what your page
Just the only one you need
Okay
Is that true?
Yeah
No, but don't you have to
Put like a little thing on each page
Well I think it's important
Everyone out there just sign
We'll fill in the rest
Don't worry about it
Thank you
Yeah, trust us
Hey
Thanks everybody for listening
Stay subscribed
And we'll check in later
This week with another
Daily source code podcast
Thanks Ron
You got it, thank you
Bye