Daily source code, episode 189
Okay everyone, quiet everyone, simmer down, simmer down.
I just want to say thank you for all the hard work you've done.
We couldn't have done it without you.
Okay, quiet, static check, light, ready, sound, sound, boom man, ready.
Is that a mint position?
Ready? Okay, 10 seconds people.
Let's do this right.
Five, four, three, two, cue music, lights up.
Let's do this right now.
Ladies and gentlemen, for many years us and announcer,
it has been my privilege to introduce a number of very important people.
But never have I felt the pride that is glowing within me today
as I introduced the gracious and beloved star of our show.
Yes ladies and gentlemen, it gives me extreme pleasure
to present to you a man whose very benevolence has earned for him
the admiration, respect and everlasting love of millions.
And here he is!
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
Hey everybody, it is June 6th 2005.
Welcome to the source code.
And this show is created entirely on the cast blaster.
We're on data number 14 right now.
So things could go a little bit of rye.
Hold on, let me just lower the microphone a little bit
to make sure we don't overmodulate which seems to be the biggest problem
on the crap.
Okay, I think we're good to go.
Man, a lot of cool changes in the software.
Okay, so we've got automatic ducking on,
which means that the minute you hit the talk button,
the music starts to fade down a little bit.
Which now actually has a shortcut by hitting the space bar
it turns on or it turns off.
You see, so that's on, and that's on, and then it was off.
Okay, so we've got to figure out the ducking system here.
But at least it's working, and there's lots of cool features
which we'll talk about on today's source code.
Okay, so one of the first things I noticed
is that the headphone monitor is really soft, but man,
I gotta tell you, I've been talking to Mike,
who's the lead developer on cast blaster.
Just understanding the inner workings of windows
and the way it handles sound is, man,
that's a whole education by itself, that's pretty twisted.
No mash up today, although I do have a cool pod safe music track.
Which is from Iraq, so it's an Iraq pod safe music track.
I've got a couple things to talk about, and of course we've got
all the effects are loaded up.
I love the standard effects that come with,
this is just fantastic hold on a second.
Now, one I think is probably better is if I just raise up the level
there, let me just check for a second.
Okay, that's better, so I'll just leave it like that,
and then I can talk over it.
I don't think the auto duck works that well.
When you really want to bring the level up real quick,
like you just heard in the opening there,
when I do the power of pure intellect,
I want that to be highlighted,
it takes a little bit too long for the auto ducking to pop up there,
so I'll just leave it as it is.
Cool electronic effects though.
So I wonder if that was over modulated at all.
You know, I'll just turn the auto feature on.
There we go.
I'm going to keep this one relatively short,
because I'm not too sure of the quality.
The biggest problem being the sound card in the,
in the, what is this, a very tech tablet that I have.
Also, to make it completely fair,
what I've done is I'm using the headset
that I usually use for Skype on the tablet.
So it's not the normal processing that you have on the,
on the big microphone through the big setup.
So please don't go emailing me saying,
oh, it sounds like shit compared to other stuff,
because, you know, there's no way that this microphone
can sound as good as the, as the pure SM7 does.
But I actually had listened to a little test,
and it sounded pretty good.
Well, I want to lower the microphone just a little bit more,
just to make sure that we're absolutely not over modulating.
Okay, there we go.
Let me just go grab my paper.
That, of course, is really nice,
is that I can now walk around with this thing.
And, you know, I have the mic strapped to my head,
so I think going nowhere.
Here we go, sit down on the couch, perfect.
Okay, so today is Monday.
It's a dreary once again in the UK.
What can I say?
That's what you get.
It's supposed to be actually nicer
or the rest of this week,
but so far, no evidence of that.
Let me tell you a little bit about cast blaster.
This is, as I said,
I'll lower the mic just a little bit more.
This is beta number 14.
So we've had 14 versions to play with so far.
And we've got a lot of testers,
and a lot of people have been putting in their,
their beta reports,
and we've really gotten this most excellent features
and fixes and stuff is really rocking from what I can see.
We actually have a little menu bar now.
One that has says create,
which I'm looking at right now,
which is the interface that you've probably seen a screenshot of before.
Then we have described, this is interesting.
This is basically the ID3 tags,
and we now have a field for show notes.
Although, when I highlight the show notes,
field, the cursor does show up,
but I can't type anything in there.
So, must be something I'm doing wrong,
or maybe that's a bug somewhere,
so I'll have to look at that.
I've got a picture in there.
Now, publish is a relatively new tab.
Yeah, because we'll just call them tabs,
where you can give your podcast a file name,
and save it to disk,
and also upload to server,
which you configure under the configure tab,
and right there's an FTP server with a path,
the login password,
so it'll shoot it right up to the server,
and all I need to do then,
of course, is to create your RSS file,
and that will be the next step in the beta process,
but I think we're going to concentrate on this first.
It's kind of cool that you can do all the stuff on the flywall,
it's playing, by the way.
Let's see.
So yesterday, which was Sunday,
took the girls, Patricia and Christina,
who London's West End,
we had not been,
well, we've been to the West End,
but we've never been to a show in the West End,
and we went to see a classic,
Chitty Chitty Bang Bang,
which you may think,
at first hand, you might say,
well, that's, isn't that for kids?
Okay, just close the studio door here.
Studio door, the bedroom door,
converted to an office slash studio.
Yeah, of course it's for kids,
and of course it was a matinee show,
so there were lots of kids and adults there as well,
but as you'd expect from a typical kids play or a musical,
there was plenty of jokes in there for adults.
Interesting to see, was it Brian Connelly,
I think, played the lead role?
I mean, I have the official program here,
let me tell you, was that his name?
I think it was, he was really good,
great singer,
let me go cast,
cast in order of appearance,
no, we don't want in order of appearance.
Here it is,
yes, Brian Connelly,
correcticus pots,
Tony Adams, as Grand Poppots,
Joe Gibb, who was truly scrumptious,
she was great, beautiful voice,
and very interesting,
the child catcher is a guy named Alvin Stardust,
and Alvin Stardust in the 70s
was like a really,
which I say,
flamboyant kind of trippy pop singer,
who had a couple of hits,
actually he, he was critically acclaimed,
really, he's done a lot of,
a lot of TV work, a lot of other musical work,
and so now he is the child catcher,
and he was getting plenty of booze and hisses,
and yeah,
so maybe it's a kid's play,
but there's a really,
you know, actually there are a couple of great morals
to this, to the story,
and I'd have to say,
one embodies itself in,
you know what,
let me see,
maybe I can,
I was looking for this earlier on iTunes,
because the moral of the story to me
is embodying the song,
the roses,
what is it?
From the ashes of destruction,
rise the roses of success.
I'm just going to go to iTunes,
and see if I can find it in the iTunes music store.
Here's what happened earlier today
on a different computer,
on one of my max,
I wanted to get a hold of that song,
I wanted to buy it,
and it wouldn't allow me to purchase the song,
I'll just see the roses,
see if we can find it.
Because my credit card is still built
to the Netherlands,
shoot, see,
now I won't even show it.
And I guess because they don't have the rights,
or they haven't cleared the rights to that song yet,
you can't purchase it if you live in the Netherlands,
which is just so fucking crazy.
That's all right,
shitty bang bang.
And you also,
now you can't see what I did.
I checked it out on a fresh install of iTunes,
that didn't have me registered
through my account,
which is through a Netherlands build credit card.
So it did show me the song,
I couldn't purchase it by itself,
could only purchase it as the entire album.
So I wanted to purchase the entire album,
and then it said,
oh, we're sorry,
since your account is linked to
a credit card building through the Netherlands,
we can't sell it to you.
And now we're not going to show it to you anymore.
So that sucks because I wanted to,
at least play the little preview snippet.
But you've probably heard the song from the ashes of destruction,
rise the roses of success,
which to me was a great moral to that story.
Had a great time seeing it,
and can't wait to take the girls to see another show very soon.
We have great connections we've found out now.
You just hop on the train and go for it.
The 35 minutes you arrive at Waterloo Station.
You can hop on the tube,
or really just like a seven minute cab ride,
and it takes you right to any of the famous theaters there.
And it was a lot of fun.
We had a great time,
especially after having been away for so long.
It was really nice to just hang out
and do some fun stuff with the ladies.
Hold on a second.
Let me do a little.
See, I've got that auto ducking on.
It sounds a little bit soft.
I just don't have enough hands to control all the controls
and cast blaster, or really only have one mouse.
I wish I could have two mice to do that.
A couple of things I just wanted to chat about again.
I'm not going to make this too long in case the quality is just too crappy.
You're going to see it more as a kind of like a test
and an a source code mixed into one.
Sound seeing tours.com now has a manager.
Her name is Katya.
She is from Holland.
I worked with her on a number of things,
including our reality TV show.
And she just got back from a trip.
She went to...
What the hell is she going Malaysia?
I think she went to Malaysia.
And she is completely bitten by the sound seeing tour bug
and she recorded plenty of sound seeing tours there.
She was so excited about the prospects of it
that she asked if she could manage sound seeing tours.com
and of course I was happy to give that up.
So check it out.
It's the brand new sound seeing tours.com.
Katya is managing that.
And you want to subscribe if you want to hear all the
awesome sound seeing tours that are being produced out there.
And of course, if you subscribe to the podcast feed,
the RSS 2.0 feed, you'll receive those in your iPod
or whatever you're using to subscribe to these shows automatically.
It's very, very cool and look for some developments
as we move along with that.
I received a couple of emails from
Exit50.com.
It was that.
It was names completely, completely looted me.
Not have to go back and look at my Gmail.
Actually, I will.
I want a second.
Let's do that.
See now I can do all this stuff off from one screen.
That is kind of cool.
Let's see, exit 50.
Now Gmail, you know it's great search.
Andre there you go.
Andrew coffee.
That's right.
And if you go to exit 50.com, you'll see right there
that he is promoting live from Iraq the 425th,
which is, I guess, the Infantry Division.
He interviewed them because they have put together
an album of music that was actually recorded in Iraq.
The lyrics are written in Iraq and it really,
yeah, it's pretty heavy stuff.
The whole story is there on the exit 50.com website.
And they have their own website, which is www.425.com.
Let's see if there's any info I can read.
It has made a couple.
Okay, so I'm seeing here fresh off the press live from Iraq.
Makes the front page of the killing daily Harold.
Okay.
Well, I think they should get a little more,
a little more press than that.
You can actually buy the album.
It is shipping now.
And I was fortunate enough to receive a track,
which I want to share with you now.
It's pretty much a wrap album.
But again, created in Iraq by the 425th Infantry Division.
And let me just check and see if that's Infantry Division.
I don't really have the website as cool,
but it doesn't have like an about.
Let me see.
Let's see what the article says in the Colleen Daily Harold.
That'll be interesting.
Fort Hood troops tell a soldier story.
Well, waging a verbal war in the first wrap album is the headline.
Title is live from Iraq.
Let's go right to it.
And let's play the fourth track off of that CD,
which you can also purchase at CDBaby.com.
This is titled Holding My Breath.
And I can feel myself dying.
To norm it, I might as it's in my lungs.
For maybe I'm tired.
Maybe it's time for me to breathe in.
And I can never let you see.
And it made me an empire.
No matter how soon I breath I can.
Because I let it show.
So let's know what times help me.
I really get.
And I'm trying to be strong.
You're both the lesson.
You hold on for the focus.
And I held on.
And I hold my breath for the focus.
It's too much on my show.
It's here.
And I just can't hope it.
No one does smile to corner.
And I'm standing so close to them.
It's the closest show to my most.
But it's me calling my focus.
And we have a new mind like humans,
that I have no control.
And we need to come over here.
No matter how soon I breath I can.
And I can't be sure of it.
And I can never let you see.
And it made me an empire.
So let's see.
So let's have.
Now let's.
So let's see.
And let's see.
Let's see.
stuff. So I'm liking this. The cast blaster is, it's work and it's not exactly the type of
sound that I'd like, but of course this is the basic setup that anyone should be able to use
with a computer and with a headphone and a microphone jack and at least a headset or you could
use a separate microphone. You could probably use a USB microphone. Actually I don't even know if you
could use a USB microphone. That's something I don't have to write that down. Make sure we test that out.
And it's really completely mobile on the fly. It has all your stuff in there so I'm really
digging it. This is cool. The two other things I need to mention, the podcast specification
working group, PSWG, who you can find at pswg.blogspot.com, seem to have come to consensus on
one click subscriptions. And Andrew Grummet, who was one of the iPod or lemon developers,
had an announcement about that on his weblog Grummet.net. Of course all of this will be in the
in the show notes if today's podcast at dailysourcecode.com as well as at www.curry.com.
I'm not quite sure how it works. In fact, it's very confusing to me. All I care about is, hey,
it appears to be working or they have some consensus on how they want to do it.
And there seem to be some interim steps. So if you're not a technologist, you should be able to
set this up and make it work. But it's funny because it includes a version of the atom ATOM,
atom specification. And I guess it, it'll download a little thing to your desktop and then it will
automatically subscribe you to whatever iPod or aggregator you're using that understands this.
So it seems like there's like there's a lot of work involved to get it up and rolling, but it doesn't
matter because of, you know, I'm just looking at their website now, how many different aggregator
and iPod or developers have joined the pswg, cpodraiser, audio blog.com, podcast 411, portlet dev,
castfire, podster.de, libson. So it looks like everybody's in there. So that's good.
If everyone's in there, everyone's going to support this and not know fantastic. I did read on the
iPod or developers list now that there seem to be some confusion about, you know, the consensus on this,
whatever, you know, the minute it's working, you know, show me, help me and you know, I'll be happy to
put any kind of links or anything on my website to get people comfortable with the idea if we actually
have a solution, I would love it. I don't quite understand how it works, but then again, I'm just
the disjockey, right? What else did I want to talk about? I want to talk about Google's site map,
another great technical development that I understand very little about. Apparently you can set up your
you can set up a file. Boy, let me see if I get this right. You can take your weblog and you can create a
file, an XML file, which seems kind of strange because I think I'm already creating an XML file,
namely an RSS file, but they want a new type of XML file that Google can then index, you can tell Google,
okay, here's the XML version of my site, the more I think about it, the crazier it sounds,
that it's not just an RSS file, which already is created by every weblog in the world almost and
is automatic. So I guess now we have to have new functionality baked into our weblogging software
to create this new Google site map XML file. Whenever that changes, then instead of traversing
through your entire site, Google will read just that one file, I guess pick up any differences and
we'll know what to index, which is a fantastic, it makes so much sense. I mean, it really does.
But of course, I have no idea how to make this file. Yeah, there's all kinds of
unix programs and sources available to do that. I was thinking, would it be interesting if you could
create like a converter that would convert either your RSS feed to this new site map file,
or maybe even better an OPML file that you could then convert to this site map file because
that would make directories indexable as well, almost immediately, and wouldn't be cool to have
places like podcastali and iPotter.org and other OPML based directories automatically indexed by Google
and those reflections, those changes reflected the minute that they're changed and that Google
would know about them and would be searchable. I think they'll be fantastic. So, call out to all
the developers out there to see if they can hook us up with that. 23, 24 minutes into the show right now.
I've been waiting for it. It was sitting in my email. I just overlooked that I guess, but what
do you want? With four and a half thousand unread mails, time once again for the hit test.
Three intros and three answers and this is intro number one.
Okay, that's one of my favorites. I know it very well. That is Kaylee by Meridian.
And this is number two.
Okay, and it's that Skype call there. That's Prince. I would die for you.
And the final one for today. This is number three.
Uh, two. The heat of the night? No. I want somebody.
Time's up and these are the answers. This is answer number one.
And that's number one. It's Meridian with Kaylee. Yeah, got it.
I should give myself a point for that.
Answer number one, Kaylee. And this is answer number two.
It's Prince and the Revolution. The song is titled, I would die for you.
Oh, yeah, another point.
Prince answer number two.
And this is the third and final answer for today's hit test.
Number 40 by the way, so it's more than 120. I know the song.
In your hit test, Adam. That's a survivor. The burning heart of course.
A little boy.
The third and final answer for today. Burning hearts that was that was survivor.
Okay, that's it for today. I hope you enjoyed this one. Of course, feedback is welcome
to hittest.gmail.com and you can find information about this hittest.
And also the separate hittest podcast on www.yompolet.nl that's Jay and P-O-L-E-T.nl and also.com.
Well, thank you for listening. See you next time. Bye-bye.
Okay, young. Thank you very much. Like to like it a lot as always.
And sucked just a little bit as usual. Okay, that's it for today's source code. Thank you for listening.
I've got to crank this up a bit. That's the only thing I really need to have it just as I need
more volume on the headphones when I'm doing this. I can just barely hear the mix, which is
difficult for the way I like to produce the show. But it seems to work. Okay, it shouldn't be too long
before we have the cast blast or website up and we can go to a broader beta. Hopefully this show
turned out okay. If there aren't too many crappy bits in it, besides the actual content of the show,
with as it pertains to the technical production, then I'll just upload it as today's source code
189. As always, you can find the latest show, the archives and the podcast feed at dailysourcecode.com.
Feedback always welcome adamaccurry.com. If you want to send in a promo, which I didn't play any of
today, actually, the email address to do that is submit at podshow.com. If you have podsafe music that
you want to put in for, for payment, for payment. That's podsafe podshow.com. And should you have a
mashup somewhere nearby mashup at podshow.com really appreciate anything you send in. And that'll
do it for me for today. Thank you very much for staying subscribed. I'll be back tomorrow as we
have the weekend full gear with all the tapping in podcast land. Take care, everybody. Bye-bye.