Delta Sierra Charlie 2-84
$60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need lost digging crazy.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding, it's Adam Curry.
And hello everybody, good morning coming to you from Curry Cottage and Gilfer.
And the United Kingdom, it is your daily source code.
I still feel like crap, just why I think this particular song
to kind of get me through the start of the show.
I'm just gently pissed about how I'm feeling.
Health is everything my friends.
Starting off your Tuesday source code.
This is available from San Francisco's griddle.
I've been looking at you now to come again.
We only want to know in this place.
We want you out.
We just see all your friends.
Let me hope that I'll be able to meet you again.
Let's see all the food on your back.
Cause it's you, come.
I've changed that into a picture.
I'm available.
I'll be there to a picture.
You know this.
Where you waiting for someone to talk to you.
Those who might be high on their masks of cool.
You won't just zip as me.
Too bad for all.
I'm swimming on the floor.
Sorry, but cause it's you, come.
I've changed that into a picture.
You know what is the spell to throw.
But what's the main last thing?
You gotta keep coming back to me.
I'm available.
I'll be there to a picture.
Tell me what's there.
Things that you found all of me.
There's something that you found me too.
Tell me what's there.
Things that you found all of me.
Kicking off your daily source code.
It's critical.
And available.
I heard that song yesterday on a new podcast.
The ultimate podcast.
The ultimate mix, ultimate mix, ultimate mix, weblog and podcast.
And the point of that podcast is to play.
The ultimate from the podcast is music now.
Totally dig into vibe there.
As you can tell, I'm still pretty stuffed up.
I didn't have a very good night's sleep.
This morning woke up around 730 to take Christina to school.
As I really enjoyed doing this morning was not an enjoyable experience.
I think maybe I should talk about that first and get off my mind.
There's things with 15 year olds.
This is parents.
I know we got mommy casters and daddy casters.
Everyone's listening up.
What a dilemma this is.
With a 15 year old.
A lot of borrowing goes on in a house.
A lot of borrowing.
Luckily none of my stuff.
It's make up.
It's eyebrow pencils.
And it's tweezers.
And shampoo.
And God knows what.
It usually doesn't affect me.
But Patricia will usually bitch about it and go retrieve it.
And it's I think that what's been building a little bit here is a bit of lack of respect for other people's stuff.
Maybe just stuff in general.
Christina is very good at losing her house.
She's good at losing herself.
She's good at losing a lot of stuff.
And then there's the 50 pounds that Patricia gave her last week at school money.
You know, you're supposed to give it to the school, so the school can do extra stuff.
And she put it in the envelope.
And then, you know, that wound up in the trash by accident.
She retrieved it from the trash.
It was literally in the, this is all last week when it wasn't here.
It was in the garage where it ready for trash pick up day.
And the this morning Patricia inquired again.
Christina said, oh, oh, no, I haven't haven't given that yet.
Well, where is it?
I can't find it.
Or it's a particularly early in the morning that that made for a very grumpy start of the day.
And I'm just trying to help my teenager understand that, you know, if it's 50 pounds, 5 pounds, 50 pence, 5 pence, or 5 million, it doesn't matter.
You know, you have to have respect for what stuff is and who it's intended for.
And I'm having a parental moment here.
So, you know, and then, I don't know, well, that we'll talk about it.
Maybe she'll actually find it, but she just seems so easy about it all.
And I want to understand that it isn't all that easy.
And part of that part of that comes a consistency between what mom says and what dad says.
And I think this is stuff that everyone deals with all the time.
And it's not the end of the world because we're all reasonably healthy.
But man, I just really put me in a fucking bad mood.
And we'll have lots of interesting moods to listen to today during the source code.
Because we've got feedback in all shapes, sizes and forms.
Some about some stuff I messed up on.
And some just about, well, general topics, like I'd recommend.
Hi, Adam, this is Chris from the financial aid podcast with some feedback about the earthling sponsorship.
The first thing is that the sponsorship, the ad on DSC282 did nothing for me because it was so commercially.
It felt like it was spliced right on a magic one of 6.7 and into the DSC.
And I'm so trained by mainstream media.
So ignore all the ads that I literally did not hear it.
I had to go back to the show and listen to it again.
And it still didn't make much of an impression.
The thing about podcasting, that's so cool about podcasting.
Because we have so much more freedom than mainstream media.
We don't have to resort to 30 second genitals.
We don't have to listen to music hits that are exactly 305.
We have all the freedom.
So it would be great to hear some more lengthy ads or some sponsorships that really connect.
I used to be an earthling member until my cable company came out with a gigantic 7 megabit pipe that lets me download the DSC in 30 seconds.
But when it wasn't earthling member, the things I liked most, when I dialed in, I didn't get it busy signal.
I got reliable connections. I got fast bandwidth.
And they don't filter their use networks.
So if you were interested in downloading binaries and the binaries and use groups, they didn't screen that.
They didn't filter that. They didn't censor you.
You know, earthling, the technical support was reasonably good.
But really, the access to bandwidth and stuff was so important for me that it really made a difference.
And that's why I wasn't earthling member until my cable company came out with, you know, the gigantic fire hose of internet connection.
Incidentally, earthling wants my business back.
They need to offer the same kind of access at a competitive price.
And hey, I'll be more than happy to jump right back on board with them.
Just some feedback from Chris from the Financial Aid podcast.
Check it out at financialadpodcast.com.
And I'll see you around. Have a great day, Adam.
Yeah, Chris, thank you very much.
And that's a great endorsement, actually.
I completely agree with what you were saying about earthling.
And I also agree with what you said about hearing the ad.
And that basically either came from them or from their ad agency.
And I felt the contrast was so large between that one and the AOL music ad that's been running on the network,
which we had griddlekakes.com produced actually for us.
And what I like about it is it doesn't, you know, the AOL music promo, I think, is much more effective.
And in fact, it sounds like a promo, which is why I like it so much.
So I'm going to suggest, and I know that not all of us who listen to the show,
diligently every day from this pod show cubicle will work with me on getting some new creative in for earthling.
Because I agree, it sounded like something different.
It didn't feel right, didn't fit right.
So it made me cut up what you just said and use that.
And that's a great testimony.
I totally agree.
And I understand the seven megabits if they offer that that you gladly take them back.
I'm not too sure about a, about bandwidth anymore.
You know, I pay through the nose for four megabits on a dedicated line because that's all I could get.
But sometimes I wonder if it's, you know, the upstream is never been, you know, the 500k that they said it would be.
It's a 350 at best, usually more on 2 to 300.
And I've heard varying results on cable systems.
I have a Comcast in at the condo in San Francisco.
That seems to be working okay, but the upstream there is even worse.
Okay.
I wish this was an audio feedback, but it's, it was so good.
I want to read it to you.
Brian Polensky says, an award should go to the Virgin Airlines gate attendant in Sydney.
Some months ago for being customer focused while making her point.
When confronted with a passenger who probably deserved to fly in cattle cargo.
So here's the scene.
A crowded version flight was canceled after version 767 has been with drawn from service.
A single attendant was rebooking a long line of inconvenience traveler.
Suddenly an angry passenger pushed his way to the desk.
He slapped his ticket down the counter and said, I have to be on this flight and it has to be first class.
Which I don't even have, of course.
The attendant replied, I'm sorry, sir.
I'll be happy to help you, but I've got to help these people first.
And I'm sure we'll be able to work something out.
The passenger was unimpressed.
I'm sure it was an American, so I'll do him in American voice.
He asked loudly, so the passengers are present who can hear.
Do you have any idea who I am?
Without hesitating, the attendant smiled grabbed her PA microphone and said,
May I have your attention, please?
Wait, let me do this.
There we go.
May I have your attention, please?
We have a passenger here at Gate 14 who does not know who he is.
If anyone can help him, find his identity, please come to Gate 14.
That worked out pretty good.
With the folks behind him in line laughing hysterically,
the man glared at the virgin attendant,
gritted his teeth and said, fuck you!
Without flinching, she smiled and said,
I'm sorry, sir, but you'll have to get in line for that as well.
Oh, hi, Mr. Nice guy.
Ooh, some fun on Mr. Nice guy shows one ninety five and six with me,
marve, as I talk with Dr. Alan Ray.
I got this itching problem.
No, no, he's a comedy writer who's written for J. Leno,
Dick Cavitt, the capital steps, and he's a PhD professor of broad casting.
Still wise, there's not a lot to teach anymore.
You know, it's been a lot of time on equipment.
That's great, so it frees you up to talk about issues,
talk about ethics.
What do you make of podcasting?
Make you think and make you smile.
The Mr. Nice guy show, mr. Nice guy dot O R G.
Hello, this is Keith Richards at the Rowling Stones.
Whenever I'm in the neighborhood,
I stop in the Murphy's saloon for a big Guinness doubt.
They had a best pose around.
Right.
Hey, what's up, Adam and all you daily source code listeners.
My name is Zach Winnick and I have a new podcast called
Sounds with Einstein.
Ooh.
Some say oh.
Anyway, so basically what I do on the sounds with Einstein is
talk about life in Las Vegas.
Yes, Las Vegas Nevada and Las Vegas, New Mexico because
Las Vegas, Mexico would be pretty boring doing you think.
Anyway, so I've talked about life in general.
I work at one of the major casinos here.
You have to listen to the show to find out which one.
But basically, I just ran to about my job,
living life out here, especially all the stupid people that drive.
The stupid weather that we have, especially when it snows
in January.
What is that?
It doesn't snow in the desert or when it's 120 degrees
and at two o'clock in the morning.
But then I also play some great blues and jazz music
that you can find on the Podsafe Music Network.
So anyway, check us out.
Sound with Einstein.com and thanks for listening.
Hock, Captain Curry, do not be afraid.
We bring tidings of great joy.
My buddy Jeremy and I have been sent to you
from the city of Melbourne, Australia
to bring you the news that your cries have been heard from afar.
That's right, Adam.
We know how hard the past few months have been since the passing
of e-fakeful G4 Titanium Powerbook
and the devastation that this is caused throughout Curry Cottage.
Oh, yes.
We are sure that there were periods of sadness
and at times anger.
When you look to the heavens and cry.
Why?
Questions no doubt formed in your mind.
As to why bad things happen to go power books.
Will the old faithful happy?
Remember you when you meet again in heaven?
Hmm.
Oh, poignant.
It's somewhat ridiculous questions.
But all deserve answers.
Do we have them?
No way.
But I'll show the god find a podcast
and certainly point you to the people who might.
The god find a podcast stems from its system podcast,
but pod finder and is the sole map to Christian content
on the digital airwaves.
Each week we feature some of the latest and most powerful Christian podcast
that deal with the real issues of the 21st century.
You and all your listeners can check us out by searching for god finder, one word
in the iTunes directory or going to www.godfindepodcast.com
God finder.
Where the search for truth begins.
Guys, more echo, please.
I go in more cowbell.
That'll help.
So I got burned via audio comment the other day about not having followed up on the MM50
Logitech MM50 speaker contest.
Apparently we had a contest going.
So now I've gone back in the Gmail and a couple of people have now written in with thoughts
for renaming the product.
This is a great way to advertise.
Hey, come and rename the product.
And I see that one of my programs here is basically freezing, which won't help me very much.
So I can read the first three until my outline unfreezes.
Let's see, this is from Michael T. Garlic, garlic.
It says, how about mighty minis?
MM50s.
Yeah, I did that mighty minis.
That sounds pretty good.
Do we have Eric Fisher?
I say call the MM50 the headrest entertainer or the head entertainment center.
The slogan goes something like this.
It's like TV for your headrest.
Okay.
Don't quit the day job.
On demand entertainment.
When you're on the go.
All right, Eric.
Thank you.
Let me see.
Oh, man.
This fucking thing is.
Why is it bogging out here?
Okay.
Douglas Yoda says, how about the Logitech earwig, the Logitech beat buddy?
I like the beat buddy.
I need some now.
The Logitech speaker power, 2000.
Or wait.
The Logitech port iPoddy.
Port iPoddy.
I like that one.
That's good.
Port Dash iPoddy.
Very good.
Paul Sullivan says looks sort of like a boom box.
I'd call it the iPoddy.
I think so far, the port iPoddy is pretty damn good.
And we got some audio feedback about the topic as well.
At least.
There we go.
It's Nick.
I was just listening to Delta Sierra Charlie 283.
I thought it'd help you out rebranding the Logitech MM50.
I think it should be called the Portable Bump.
You could take here.
Anywhere you please.
Okay.
Portable Bump.
I'm still liking the Porto Party.
That's working the best for me.
Here's a different piece of feedback about the MM50.
Hi, Adam.
This is Melinda Mason from the My Maryland podcast.
I have a quick question for you about the MM50 iPod speakers.
I'm putting it tentatively on my wishlist for Santa.
But I wanted to check on the compatibility between it and the new video iPod.
I just got myself my iPod.
And I love it.
I upgraded actually from a black and white generation fourth generation iPod.
So just to have a color.
Wow, it's pretty cool.
And the video is just an absolute bonus.
Of course, I've got it filled with Maryland and Earl Clips.
But, you know, that's just me, I guess.
So my question is, since you have both of these items.
Are these speakers going to scratch my new baby up?
I'm trying to take really good care of her.
So I'd like to know how the fit is in the dock portion.
You know, where you plug the iPod in.
Do you have to really squeeze it in there to get it to fit?
Or does it?
Do I need any kind of an adapter to make it work with the speakers?
If you could address those issues for me, I would really appreciate it.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
Well, Linda Mason from the My Maryland podcast.
Big fan of the show.
I'll be fan of her show that is.
You know, first of all, your iPod is going to get scratched.
It's crap.
I have the black video iPod.
You know, I'd used the three times maybe.
And it was scratched all over the face.
So just, you know, get over it.
It's going to get scratched.
I have successfully put it into the MM50.
Now what they've done is they have a
slot that will fit any generation iPod.
And they give you adapters, which are pieces of plastic that slide into the slot.
So that your iPod will fit snugly.
Honestly, what I'd like to get.
I'd like to get an opinion from Logitech first to find out about the compatibility with the new video iPod.
Before I recommend anything to you, Melinda.
So I'll get that to you tomorrow as well.
I know exactly who's listening, who's going to take care of that.
And thank you.
Okay.
I can't.
Kim sent this in.
I love your show.
Listen every day.
Decided to tune in with Pacific Coast Hellway.
Played your sound by it.
Cool.
I love it when I get traffic from someone else.
Now I'm hooked.
I listen to four to 12 hours a day while installing satellites for the dish network.
I know you didn't want people to send you MP3 files with email, but I couldn't figure out how to do it properly.
Blow it.
Okay.
Listen to this clip.
Tell me what you think.
I'm wondering for votes to non podcast listeners is definitely a breach of etiquette.
I'm interested in your response.
And what she sent me is indeed one of the top podcasts as listed on podcast alley.
It's a free talk live, which has been a radio show since I think 2002.
And they've always made their archives available online.
And this is what they're doing on the air.
And you can join us online free talk live dot com.
We give you everything for free on our website at free talk live dot com.
And if you appreciate that, you want to show your appreciation.
We have to do as vote for us.
It's a once a month kind of thing.
You just go to vote dot free talk live dot com.
Take your straight to where you need to be at podcast alley because we're home.
Hold on.
The first of all, that's really smart.
They've done a really cool thing.
They've given you a direct URL to type in.
So that you go immediately to the voting section for their podcast on podcast alley.
That's just really smart marketing and a great idea.
So that right off.
And by the way, that's a, let me just write that down.
We should be able to offer any podcast or that wouldn't that be cool.
Okay.
Let's remember this, that any podcast should be able to have like, you know, vote
dsc dot podcast alley dot com.
Wouldn't that be cool if we could do that?
And that would be your link.
God.
It would be nice.
And much easier to remember than go to podcast alley and vote for our show.
So first of all, they're just smart.
Let's continue here for a second.
We're radio show first and foremost, but then once the shows over,
we shop up, shop up the show and put it online as a podcast.
As a result of your votes, we're the number three podcast in the world.
That's out of about 10,000 different podcasts.
And admittedly, we're relatively new show.
And this is a great way for us to get listeners.
We have thousands of listeners from podcast in the podcast arena.
But you don't have to be a podcast listener to go vote for the show.
Well, voting for the show brings us more listeners because of being number three or
possibly two or number one.
Right.
So there's a number of things that work.
I think people who have figured it out really understand how this works.
So first of all, they have a great way to get to the voting page.
Second of all, they probably have a reasonably large audience on the radio.
I'm not sure how big it is.
I'm not sure what this program is broadcast and what the potential listening audience is.
But also things that are in the top 10 to get listened to and, you know,
it's perpetual motion almost.
It's the same with iTunes and they basically, they're top 100 is comprised of new
subscriptions through the iTunes music store to a podcast in a certain period.
I think it's 24 hours.
So if something is featured is also going to automatically go up in the top 100.
If it's in the top 100, people find it.
There's more new subscriptions and it just keeps on propelling them up,
which I think is actually a pretty damn good way of looking at the top 100.
But what is it the top 100 of?
You rarely see the daily source code there.
You rarely, I don't think you see daily source code in the top 10 on podcast
down there anymore either.
And, you know, so you have a kind of like a base and then actually once a while,
I'll go on a campaign, I'll promote my own show.
I do it on the pod finder.
I'll put a mention at the end of the show that people continue to the daily source code.
These are things.
I don't think there is any fair way or non fair way, you know, come on.
If you want to get listeners, then every way counts.
Another fantastic thing I've seen is putting a dash in a space before your,
before the name of your podcast and your RSS feed.
That way it shows up at the top of iTunes.
I've seen a couple of podcasts to do that.
Now, please don't all go doing it because,
I'll shoot up, give it in a way.
No, have an eye.
Screw it.
All right, next topic.
This is about the Christmas song.
The pod safe music Christmas extravaganza choir.
I don't have to explain it to you because I have a piece of Kevin Reeves podcast,
which I caught just yesterday, and I'm going to kind of skip through,
but I want him to do the explanation of what we're trying to achieve here.
Kind of the history of what happened.
This is from his, from his most recent podcast.
Hey, kids, welcome to a special edition of Studioography.
My name is Kevin Reeves.
And today, what we're going to do is we're currently working on,
if every day we're Christmas, which is the pod safe Christmas tune
that everybody's kind of joining in on and putting their two cents in.
But for those of you who are not current residents of the podosphere
and aren't really aware of what's going on, let me explain.
A couple weeks ago, Adam Curry from the Daily Source Code
had put out this challenge to all everybody.
He said, I am looking for a quintessential Christmas song
that we can play the hell out of.
You know, like, you turn on the pop radio and everybody's playing,
you know, simply having a lot of Christmas time.
You know, that is the quintessential pop Christmas song.
You know, along with, you know, white Christmas and all that.
But, you know, Adam was looking for the quintessential pod safe Christmas tune
that could be kind of the holiday hit.
In response, a friend of mine by the name of Slaw,
posted this tune that he had co-written with a friend of his about a year ago.
Now, I met Slaw in New York about, that was about, oh,
and actually it's been two years now because I met Slaw in New York
Christmas of O3 while I was on Martha's Vineyard at Music School.
We took a trip to New York and I took a day and went to his studio and hung out.
And he said, hey, I just finished this tune, you want to check it out.
And it was, if every day, we're Christmas.
He had just kind of demoed it and stuff like that.
So he had this tune and he uploaded it to the pod safe music network.
And Adam Curry just completely went nuts over it.
And he said, all right, well, why can't we do like a band-aid kind of deal?
We are the world kind of thing.
And get all the pod safe artists to join in and do this big, huge,
anthem Christmas chorus kind of thing.
And then we'll have the top pod safe artists.
The brother loves and the bitties and, you know, the 46 blisters and the,
you know, all the, all the top people sing all the choruses.
You know, are sing the verses and have solo parts.
And so there we are.
Slaw is now completely engrossed in this project.
And he sent me the tracks and said, hey, why don't you get started on this?
Do the, you know, do the choruses.
And so that's what we're going to do today.
I'm currently standing in the vocal booth and in front of my other keyboard here that controls
Pro Tools.
So this is where it gets really cool.
He actually walks us through the process of him recording parts of the chorus.
And what's happened is Slaw has made all these tracks available.
You know, the different pieces of the harmony for the chorus.
And he's basically put a whole kit together.
And anyone who wants to join can go to music.podshow.com.
And there's a link there and from there you can get the information about how to
participate in the song.
And I'm really excited because Slaw was invited Patricia to do some of the, you know,
to do a solo piece.
So that means that I get to engineer it.
And I'm really excited about that.
And I think by December 1st, that's kind of the deadline is when we want to have this thing out.
Which, of course, is a little bit late for a hold on.
Listen to just a bit here of how it does all this stuff.
All right, so have that instrumental.
And then I've got to let me fast forward a bit.
Hold on a second.
All right.
So I've unsulled it.
And now this is really cool.
And he has some kind of feedback on the buttons that he's trying to do it.
Okay.
Listen to him.
He's going to sing a piece now.
And he can go.
Apparently you have to say shit a lot when you're doing this work.
This and make it work.
But here we go.
Check it out.
Oh shit.
Okay.
We would never.
Let's see how well I did.
All right.
Let's just listen to this one piece.
Let's solo.
It's so cool because I learned so much about doing it.
Just through listening to his podcast.
Here's the click track.
And now you're just hearing this.
Oh, I see why that's not working on it.
He's got to put his vocals in.
And auto input.
Here's the feedback on his computer.
It's really cool.
Here we come.
That is absolutely shite.
So check that out.
It's with a lot of a link to it in the show notes.
Very, very, very, very, very cool.
And I can't wait to participate.
And by engineering Patricia on this.
I'm really excited about this whole project.
Hey Adam.
This is Sarah Fisher from Marion, Indiana.
I'm a blogger and podcaster.
And I could not help but see the ad or the blurb over at podshow.
The biggest promotion and podcasting is about to hit you right.
Between the years, ambition will you be ready.
Well, I just got to say Adam.
Heck, yes, I am ready.
To not wait to hear what this is about.
Just got to say very excited.
Can't wait.
Of all the things.
I mean, a friend of mine and I were working on our podcast right now.
We haven't started yet.
But we've recorded some material.
We're getting our mic set up to the best sound quality.
Getting our beds and our pot safe music ready.
And writing our material and seeing where we can improvise upon that.
But the place where we really need to help is just the promotion of our podcast.
The network for it to sail upon.
So anyway, just wanted to draw a line and say we are very excited.
Can't wait to see what comes out because we'd love to get in on that.
So hey, if you've been made a testing or anything or whatever.
Hey, just let me know.
I am all about it.
So Dr. later, thanks for the shows.
See ya.
And for any listeners out there, my blog is Eric Wrights.
That's Eric with a K.
Wrights.
Block spot.com.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Well, good news.
The audition will be for every podcast or anybody.
With you have a podcast or not.
And we're going to start unfolding details of that.
Just keep watching podshow.com.
You can subscribe to the RSS feed and podshow news.
Because that's where it'll be posted as well.
So you can get it automatically in your newsletter, your aggregator.
Before we open it up to everybody, we'll be starting with what we're internally calling the Super 30.
It's a long story.
What these people will be invited to come into the audition,
into the network.
And we want a very personal relationship with them before we get started.
Because when we really open the gates for everyone to participate.
And this, by the way, is all related to our internal codename Q.Y.D.J.
That's the name of the promotion Q.Y.D.J.
Which means quit your day job.
So yeah, the marketing, of course, all a part of the services we're going to provide at the podshow podcast delivery network.
The advertising, helping you grow an audience, helping you bring in listeners.
You helping us bring in listeners, making money.
All of that will be a part of what we're going to be offering to everybody.
But also, and that's really what's going to be cool this audition.
Where everybody can enter.
And some of you will be able to literally quit your day job.
And if people are still subscribed to your old feed, they don't receive updates anymore.
I think we need to solve this problem, because this is something that can happen to a lot of podcasters at some point.
How can we relocate an RSS feed without losing listeners?
Now, I'm not an expert, but here's my idea.
Why not integrate a special tag in the RSS feed protocol that points to either a backup location of the RSS feed,
useful if, for instance, the main server on which your RSS feed is located goes down,
or with the future new location of the RSS feed, and perhaps even also the date when the relocation will happen.
If there were a tag like that, we could ask the various podcasters, like Jews, iPodracks, iTunes, etc.
To scan for that tag, and if they find it, make a change in the subscription data for that particular podcast.
Say for instance, that I want to change the URL of the feed of my daily breakfast show to another server by Friday.
I could mention the new location of the RSS feed plus the date of the change in my current feed,
and when I launch iTunes on Friday, it will know that from that moment on, it will have to grab the RSS feed from the new location.
iTunes introduce some custom tags in the RSS feed sometime ago, so why not get together as podcasters,
and launch general requests to all the makers of podcasters out there to integrate a tag like that?
So these are just my two cents, I'm curious to know your thoughts about this, and by the way, get well soon.
I think our road rig always there, friend and need.
I love that music.
Okay, well, unfortunately, I think we need some divine intervention to make that happen, father road rig.
And of course, if anyone can call that upon us, it would be you, I'm hoping.
I think what we're going to do in the meantime on the second is this someone calling, please say no.
I don't know what that is.
All right, hold on, let me just check my calendar because that was some kind of calendar alert.
What am I missing?
Okay, nothing, it's exactly what I thought.
So we need some divine intervention for RSS to be extended that globally.
I think that for what it's worth, iTunes actually has solved this if your feed changes because they're basically acting as a buffer in between the iTunes music store.
There is a tag you can set in there that will change the feed so that it'll update an iTunes.
I think that's the only way to go, and it would be great.
I'm sure the juice receiver has something like that already.
It may detect a redirect feed.
Maybe the thing to do is to create a small little directory of the different ways that all of the receivers handle this.
And if you have built an iPod or pod catcher podcaster receiver.
Please consider probably using the redirect method.
So it'll recognize a feed that has a redirect tag in it so that it'll automatically change the subscription internally.
I think we should probably get the juice guys to look at this if they haven't done it already.
So please let me know and I'll make note of it because that's really the way to go.
And of course the ultimate way is to have no feed lock in.
That's why yeah, you may be lucky quote lucky if you're doing this with feed burner,
but a feed burner goes down or something happens there or you disagree with what they do next.
I mean anything like that could happen.
Then you'll be stuck with feed burner.
The other way to do this is through DNS because DNS works universally across the network across services.
And when the pod show podcast delivery network launches will be offering a fantastic DNS service along with that so that you can basically set up,
you know, your podcast dot com slash the name of your feed dot XML or whatever we want it to be.
And you will own your DNS registration so you can move it anywhere you want at any time.
And we've teamed up with an excellent partner for that.
Oh man, I'm telling you guys too much.
Coming.
Oh yeah.
Coming to you from their bedroom.
I mean their office.
Welcome to the Pete and Renee show.
Hi, I'm Pete.
And I'm Renee.
Our show is mainly about our lives here at the Jersey Shore.
That's right.
We talk about family, friends, relationships, sex.
We also have a happy hour where we talk about drinks.
And sex.
And we may also talk about other people from time to time.
And as you can tell, he's the only one.
And sex.
Oh, right.
So come by and check us out at.
Pete and Renee dot com.
You won't be sorry.
Why did you say it three times?
So people won't forget.
Everyone want to go to an adult bookstore.
But we're afraid to come with us on one of our episodes.
Or find out if Renee spins your swallows.
Peter, is there anything sacred with us?
Of course, honey.
It's just us and our fans.
Oh, okay.
I can handle that.
So come by and check us out.
The Pete and Renee show.
If you're an information technology professional,
that typically finds themselves behind in the technology magazine and journal reading,
then check out technewsradio.com
for two potentially helpful podcasts.
The first is tech rack tarots,
which comes out every two weeks and reviews latest in mainstream technology references
for news and resources from an enterprise system architecture perspective.
The second is techtivots daily,
which brings you short,
under four minutes technology pointers from new software
to hot gadgets to conference notifications to productivity tips and tricks.
So check out technewsradio.com for transparent technology podcast reporting
where agendas are checked at the door and information flows with focus.
You can also contact us directly at technewsradio at gmail.com
for leave audio comments by calling 206-337-15333.
Technewsradio.com is a proud member of techpodcast.com
and friends in tech.com
Hello.
Hi, Mr. Nice Guy.
Ooh, some fun on Mr. Nice Guy shows 195 and six with me,
Marve, as I talk with Dr. Allen Rafe.
I got this itching problem.
No, no, he's a comedy writer who's written for Jay Leno
Dick Cavatt, the capital steps,
and he's a PhD professor of broadcasting.
He's still wise, there's not a lot to teach anymore,
but you don't spend a lot of time on equipment.
That's great.
So the free you have to talk about issues,
not with ethics.
What do you make of podcasting?
Make you think and make you smile.
The Mr. Nice Guy show.
M-R-N-I-S-G-I-D-O-R-G.
The ready.
For those of you who've ever looked at my web log,
at curie.com www.curie.com.
We have a person who comments very often.
Just about every single day, it comes in spurts.
It's the comic strip blogger.
And he writes the most obscene, outrageous stuff.
And you know, a lot of people really despise him.
I have to be very honest.
I like it.
I like it when he comes in with his comments,
because it stirs up stuff and people start posting.
And I like it when people are fighting with words
back and forth.
It's interesting to see.
Because it's comic strip blogger.
He's nuts.
He doesn't give a shit about anybody says.
And apparently, he's been the subject
of many a controversy on the internet.
And he finally sent in an audio column.
He may have actually sent one before.
I don't know if I ever played it.
But he sent one in that I'd like to share with you today.
Hello.
Here is comics strip blogger.
No, no.
Or so, as my wife owns a fan.
I would like to wish you, okay.
Well, soon.
And by the way, I would like to remind you,
and ask you kind of,
we should get on top of.
Could you please ask,
management of series three mail here,
to enable streaming of
portfolio over internet.
Forced to subscribe.
So this is one of the main things he keeps yelling
that me about.
He's, he subscribes to series to listen to it through the website.
So he doesn't even have a receiver,
because he lives, I think, in Germany.
He'll go on to tell us that in the rest of his comment.
But he's been asking me to get the serious guys
to stream the channel.
And the problem is, and of course,
have asked them comic strip blogger.
Of course I have.
The problem is they can only stream the whole channel or nothing.
And they can't stream the whole channel because
there's a lot of,
differences in the way they adhere to the digital
Millennium Copyright Act for their,
a full-time music channels and their talk channels.
And there's some legal reason why they can't do that.
But they've heard you request again,
then here on the show.
I don't remember that.
And also I'd say it's cyber.
I had a, for a turn on subscription.
And obviously, I can listen to the satellite radio
series over satellite.
I can listen to it over internet online
because I'm not in the same.
I, I, in Germany.
I ask you very, very kind.
I would show you the top of me.
Please talk to that.
And the range for Atlanta.
And of course I will show you very well.
I'm listening to your pop-up regularly.
And get well soon, man.
Hello.
Is the most important thing in my life?
Ah, how sweet he is, our comic strip blogger.
Dude, so I've already asked, okay, I can't help you.
That's some, it's some legal issue they have.
The comic strip blogger, comic strip blogger.com,
is a great artist though.
He does these fantastic,
like three pain cartoons of daily events in technology,
blogger sphere, the potter sphere, if you will.
And it's really something to check out.
And he should do more of that.
And he should actually, he should focus,
completely on that.
I think that would be the best.
Yeah, I'm casting with Adam.
Hey Adam, who are you ready to be stumps?
Oh, I wish they used that.
Fantastic.
With young projects.
Hey Adam, I really miss doing the hit test for the daily source code.
I hear you.
But I understand why it's not possible anymore.
Maybe something will change in future regulations regarding copyrighted stuff.
And something will be possible.
I just wanted to let you know that I created the next hit test podcast that is featuring a hit test.
So it's available at youngpolets.com
and through the RSS used for the hit test.
So that's all.
I enjoyed it a lot creating the hit test.
I know you enjoyed them as well.
Maybe until next time.
See you later.
Bye-bye.
Get a test at gmail.com
info.
youngpolets.com
and the OLDT.com
Oh, young.
I miss you, man.
I miss the hit test.
But, you know, since we went purely pod safe.
Just can't do it anymore.
So that was young's call.
You can go check out the last hit test podcast at youngpolet.com
and he's working on something else.
And I hear he's working on it with another well-known podcaster.
Looking forward to what he's going to produce because young is a great producer.
And I don't think he should limit himself at all to pod safe music.
Okay, just briefly, since I do have to get out of here pretty soon.
I have now learned that both the Gemma, the GEMA in Germany,
and the Seicam in France, this SACM, both of them say.
And these are the ASCAP BMI equivalent say that when you sign the contract with them,
you have signed over the performance rights to them.
And indeed, according to their rules and regulations,
you then can no longer play that music pod safe.
And I think that is an absolute outrage.
We have confirmation from ASCAP BMI that it doesn't work that way in the States.
But to have that happening in now three countries, including the Netherlands,
is a travesty.
We've got to keep our eye on this and change that because that makes no sense.
Last pod safe song for the day is the candy but you're...
Man in Paris in 94.
Oh, was it 95?
She was best studying abroad.
He was on tour, playing in another dime.
They potted hard and they potted wings.
A little north of the sand.
He dreamed about her in so many ways.
She dreamed about her in French.
Well, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's his mother's son, not like anyone.
He just needs time to heal.
They met him in New York a few months later.
He was still living alone.
Hugging the ball and masturbating.
Never answered his phone.
The first date was a movie together.
Outside it Brian Pock.
It was spirit of St. Louis just went on forever.
So they drank wine until they saw stars.
Well, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's his mother's son, not like anyone.
It just needs time to heal.
They finally hooked up for the first time.
The night before the Fourth of July.
He felt so awkward saying goodbye to the girl who just changed his life.
Now my friend, they are in separate ball.
She even gets that boy to go to the gym.
Now if you don't think that's love, you must be cynical.
Oh, make a man, you're just dreaming in French.
Yeah, because she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's his mother's son, not like anyone.
It just needs time to heal.
Oh, she knows what to do with my call.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's his mother's son, not like anyone.
It just needs time to heal.
Yeah, he's the one.
He's his mother's son, not like anyone.
It just needs time to heal.
Well, that's right.
He just needs time to heal.
What to do with my call, Candy Butchers?
You can find three of their tracks at the Ponce Music Network at music.ponshow.com.
That's it for the Daily Source Code for today.
Check it out.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.