Daily source code, two, two, two, two,
two thousand five transmitters.
We don't need no stinkin' transmitters.
Get ready for the generation of rockin' roll.
Fantastic! It's Adam Curry.
And it is Wednesday, officially,
it's the second of February.
The power of New York, New York, New York.
Of course, yes, they are. I thought it was Wednesday, right?
Hey, everybody, how you doing? Welcome to the hum day edition
of the Daily Source Code.
So, coming to you from the Curry Cottage, I'm alone once again.
No camera crews, no journalists, no damn, no nothing.
Just you and me, I pod listener.
It's your source code.
The power of New York, New York, New York, New York.
It's the second of February, 2005,
on the show today, some pod safe music.
Update of the Blue Man group.
Got some promos, including some of some pod safe music.
Talk about some technical things.
Like pod cast production consoles.
An idea for a reality television show you can steal from me.
Oh, and we have some trivia, yeah, that's right.
I missed it yesterday somehow, but Young Plet got a new trivia test
in there, so stay tuned for that.
All that and more, in the next 40 minutes on your Daily Source Code.
The power of New York, New York, New York, New York, New York.
Got a second, just take a stick here at the coffee.
Hmm.
Actually, it wasn't completely prepared as I wanted to be.
Normally, I got my smoke here as well, but on the second, I made it.
I could just grab that for a moment, don't go away.
Actually, you can come up with me now.
Carry the mic.
You know what?
I needed a pair of wireless headphones.
That's the last step of the podcast equipment that I'm looking for.
And he's a pair of wireless headphones.
We're going to pair those send hisers.
Although, I think they're on IR and not on just a regular radio frequency
because I've got the wireless mics.
Actually, this is not the wireless mic.
It's my sure mic, but I've got a really long cable.
So I can walk all over the place, but then I can't hear the music.
I can't hear the mix or I actually need like a.
Well, maybe I just make my, my, my power book portable.
Maybe I had some kind of straps like later hosin.
Suspenders.
So I go walk around with it.
So I'll have the microphone and the headphones with me at all times.
Hey, it could happen.
So for the past, what is it now?
Is it almost two weeks that we've been playing different versions of you don't own me?
Let me see what we've had so far.
We've had the bitties, of course, list of these bitties.
We've had Leslie Gore.
We've had Rasputin out.
Yesterday, we had a shoot.
What was the name of that?
I should get yesterday's show notes up here.
Hold on a second.
I haven't had them close by.
It's 120 in the afternoon, by the way.
Just so you know, it doesn't really matter because you may be listening to this in the morning.
You may be listening to this in the afternoon or in the evening.
Let me see.
I don't know.
Oh, here it is.
You don't owe me.
Yes, there was by.
Oh, clouds, no me.
That's right.
And Michael Butler.
We all know and love him from the Rock and World Geek Show.
It sent me, and actually it's kind of cool because it's cool when you see a familiar name
show up in the in the Gmail account that I'm using for MP3 files.
It's MP3 feedback at gmail.com.
Michael Butler from the Rock and World Geek Show sent me a Joan jet in the black hearts version, which is kick ass.
You don't owe me on the source code.
You don't owe me.
I'm not just one of your many toys.
Don't say I can't go with other goals.
And go tell me what you want.
Don't tell me what you say.
And please, what I don't want with you.
Don't want me on this way.
You don't owe me.
Don't try to change me in any way.
Don't tell me damn cause I'll never stay.
I don't tell you what you say.
I don't tell you what you want.
Don't tell me what you want.
Just say you can't go with other goals.
And go tell me what you want.
Don't tell me what you want.
Don't want me on this way.
I don't tell you what you want.
Don't tell me what you want.
I remember the big San Francisco earthquake earthquake.
Right here at that birds singing outside.
See what God is playing outside.
That's very day when the earthquake took place.
Patricia was actually doing some backing vocals on Johnny's album.
Was that an emergency moment on the wall here?
Or was it up your alley?
That's right.
Which wasn't an huge success,
thing. Well, that's relative, right? I have a platinum album on the wall for a million
sold. I guess it was pretty good. But so Steve said that you know everything's going great
with him and it was fun to talk to Steve because as we found out he is actually doing some
consulting now for a serious satellite radio and so of course I got to dig in and ask him
some questions. Some of which I can't talk about because I promised I wouldn't because you know
hey he has some kind of confidentiality confidentiality going on there. But I can't tell you
have you talked to Stern because he certainly went back in the day when I was at MTV he would
talk to Howard Stern a frequently. He says yeah I want him two times but he mainly talks with Gary
Delabate. Better known as it. Baba Bowie. And I said oh man we need to get Stern in on this podcast
and he said now he'll never do it because he just won't give it away for free. I think the words
were he's a commercial fucker. I can't blame him I guess. But something interesting Steve
did tell me because we were talking about well first I said hey dude did you put that deal together
with Nina Blackwood Allen Hunter and Mark Goodman on like the 70s and 80s. Now the 80s channel
on serious and he said no actually that that deal had already been put to bed before he got there
but I said yeah so what are their channels or are expected he says well no channels because
basically we're out of bandwidth. I was like whoa that's interesting. In fact it's gotten so here's
how it works the government has apparently allocated by the FCC then has allocated x amount of
spectrum there's that word which means you know frequencies in the air that you can't see touch
taste or feel or hear for that reason not without a receiver and they yeah that's like bandwidth
it's like you know so you have x number of megabits per second to use in fact I think it is
measured in megabits per second satellite bandwidth. Excuse me and they filled it up so they
had really they don't have any more channels left in fact to make more room the all talk channels
are now being broadcast in mono so even though it's really cool and they have quite a future ahead
of them it's interesting because they can't really add more channels whereas in podcasting hey
we don't need those stinking trans meters. So that's good to talk this Steve and look forward to
hooking up with him in New York hopefully I'll see him because I'm trying to get to New York around
the 16th or at least for the for the Bitties cast launch on the 16th in in Wave I Yorker and
oh yeah one other thing Steve said he was doing or he had he had done some some work at Virgin
Records and of course then then you say oh so what talent were you working with he said oh
Courtney love I said oh dude that's a podcast he said you bitch yeah so he's gonna tell us all about
the nightmares he had with Courtney love if I get a hold of him in New York in the next couple of
played the blue man group a couple days for you with that awesome version of I feel love
got an email about that from Sebastian Adam greetings for Germany let me tell you about the podcast
but wow what do you say here um okay it was on the 31st right you played a track from the blue man group
with vocals from Venus hum that track is actually from the complex rock tour live
it's a DVD he provides a URL so you can get that link from the show notes for today an awesome DVD
music on it is awesome it's not the normal show or the program that you see in Las Vegas but
it's a special rock tour which the blue man group did and it apparently well the theater program kicks
ass but he says that the DVD is something you have to see the the rock show was perhaps even a
little bit better so I guess we still need to go to Vegas and check that out because man that has that
track kick but that's where I belong hold on let me hear that okay okay
tape for all that and only all high where we go all the world why well oh dude start over making
sure the net never gets predictable it's a modify it was a sound you tried out the new
MSN search pretty interesting something really irritating that I found about the MSN search is
when you when you live in a like in any country it basically searches under your country first
which because Dave Warner said that he was the number one Dave on on the new search and had the
number one RSS result and I and I clicked on the links that he provided and I got whole different
results like whoa but then I noticed that no matter what I did I tried forcing the dot com you know
as search dot MSN dot com and it kept going to dot code dot UK and yeah you can change it to
the location to be the United States but I really want to be able to search the whole internet or
all the internet as our president would say and I finally got a tip from Simon Simon's bait
spiked something like that Simon who gave me the URL which you need to use it's well it's in the
show notes search dot MSN dot com then it's like slash question mark no reader it equals one
you just have to copy that from the show notes but essentially what it does is it lets you search
the whole internet at the same time it sets your cookie so the next time you go to search dot
MSN dot com it won't just redirect you to your own country version so that's something that I
consider a bug really I mean why what I only I like the idea that you can say search locally
because that is a button on the MSN search page but the default search should be the entire
internet I mean there's there's absolutely no reason why I should whether default should go to the
country that you're in so that's a solid guess hey I'm just a quick dot here I know
one of your shows you were talking about having mp3 devices kind of like Linux on the iPod
just have it display your show notes and one of the things I just wanted to make a comment what some
newer mp3 players out of the box automatically support the displaying of song lyrics and those are
just notes encoded with a timestamp and well it's not exactly the kind of thing you're looking for
it might be a good first step to putting show notes that synchronize with the mp3 playback at a certain
time you can have the show notes appear on the display of the mp3 device and I'll include a copy
of that so you can see what the format of that is like but it's just an interesting side development
just something I noticed some of the new portable mp3 players that are coming out in the market
take care love the show yeah dude thank you very much I think this is actually really exciting I
for the past couple of weeks I don't know if anyone noticed that at all but if you look at the
daily source code file if you look at the ID3 tags I have been pasting the show notes into the
lyrics field so of course that's not doing anything because apparently there's some special type
of encoding that you need to use for the lyrics file but if I understand this correctly then there are
some mp3 players that understand this particular file format and I don't know if it has to be
encoded in the ID3 tags or if it's a separate file that needs to be picked up but apparently there's
some kind of synchronizing that you can do so that if you say okay I want this particular lyric
to show up at this particular time code that it will show up in the display of the mp3 player so
this could be really interesting the email that that he sent me was so long I didn't post that
into the show notes I'm looking for links looking looking for pointers looking for people who are
experimenting with this because it's could be extremely cool and the question of course is does
this work with the iPod does it work with the iRiver I mean I know nothing about this this is
pretty new to me so let's work on this and see if we can figure out what what these lyrics are
if we can use lyrics or use show notes in lieu of lyrics in our podcast very cool appreciate the
feedback promise that update you on my progress with windows as I of course installed that for
Christina downstairs so yesterday and by the way I love the fact that that I've installed windows
for her because I'm pretty much the and I'm sure most people know this is like you know if if you
know anything about computers and the increments then you pretty much become the default go to
guy for your friends and family and whenever the computer's not working you know which can range from
it's not plugged into something very complex you get the call right and sometimes it's sometimes
it's like trying to help the flight attendant land the 747 from the control tower especially if
you're helping people troubleshoot over the phone and I told Christina I said look the support I
give you on fixing your computer issues is going to be less because I don't know very much about
windows and quite honestly a lot of windows shit is mystery to me so she had a problem she has a
vanilla site the land of the young and the hopeless dot com which is her good Charlotte
vanilla site and vanilla site of course is it's a great weblog tool only it does want to see
the refer coming from your browser and I've seen this error before and I thought it was usually
something that had to be fixed inside vanilla itself when it says who couldn't find a refer or
couldn't match the refer whatever it is so we can't post or we can't edit this particular page
that you requested so I'm like oh man it's of course she comes to me and she says oh it's not working
can't update and so the first thing I say is well it's windows so you know there you go I don't know
if I can help you but it's pretty proud of myself because I figured it out first I copied and pasted
the actual error message into Google I should try pasting it into MSN search actually see what comes
up there and of course it turns out or one of the one of the results that I got was from a
usual and hosted site that says well basically your browser is not passing off the refer information
and it had a link down there to something called norton internet security which I had seen
automatically installed when I when I installed the whole computer for her and indeed there is a
security setting it's very down pretty deep it was very confusing to find but there's a browser
security setting which doesn't really tell you what it does or doesn't send but apparently it's
not going to be sending the refer so I unselected that and lo and behold it started working so
well very cool I got to tell you man windows it's still a deep fucking hole
I had on my name's christian stout and I just want to leave you a comment on your
two most recent podcasts good to hear that you moved over to the windows world it's nice to
see a hardcore Mac fan enjoy the the the thrills of windows of course yes indeed christian thrilling
it is we all know that the Mac was built on better architecture really we want to tell people
that will be about the hard drive you might want to actually go into system tools oh this is a
me talking about the the windows hard drive making such a freaking ride to start programs accessories
and bring up the disc defragment her and run that it might quiet it down a little bit
also I'd go to windows update dot microsoft dot com yeah i did that do the update if you haven't
now it it it it came through automatically you know get these pop up saying you have to download
18 megabytes of stuff to update so make sure you turn on your automatic update yeah it's a
you know I didn't hear about the section of your podcast where it was skipping but I do I did catch
the comment about from the person about running off the dual hard drives okay just to make clear
now this is going back to the Mac where I was having problems playing back huge AIFF files
and recording a new one at the same time on the same disc suggestion came in to record the podcast
on an external drive for instance fire wire and use everything else off of the internal drive
that could work um you probably don't have to if you've got a powerful enough system but you need
to consider how hard drives work and that when you're reading a file it's in one location when
you're writing it it's in another location even though drive spin fast and access time is pretty fast
nowadays you're still having to look at how big your files were and you're probably moving
working that little hard drive you know head really hard bouncing all over the places it's trying
to do two things it wants right you probably you could maybe fix some things by increasing your ram
I'm not sure what your broadcasting off of but it would not hurt to double that if it's only
like a gaker so that would definitely give you more available ram to pull in files as well as store
your files before you even write them. Additionally you could probably go into the program you're
using and bump up the ram that it uses so I'll try that or you could just I don't think
that actually works can you do that on OS OS X now on OS 10 sorry is that possible keep the files
smaller and not try to read and by the way I like saying OS X lots of people send me comments and
say it's OS 10 not OS X OS 9 was the operating system before but it's OS X it's easier it's nicer
sexier OS X and a 600 meg file lastly in the mind the magazines I was reading I get a bunch
every week you know information overload sucks anyways it's called TV technology this is the February
second issue in 2005 and on page 28 of Frank Beach and talks about podcasting and you know you're
in the news everywhere and I didn't know if you knew about this one but there might be some of your
listeners that read this magazine and if they don't they might want to pick it up it talks about
everything we've called heard about as well as the video feature possible of this and who knows
where else casting might go anyway I enjoy your podcast and just want to let you know now that you are
in the windows world I definitely asked that you give my podcast to listen it's something I added to
a website I've been running for a little bit that deals with the home network hopefully one day soon
I'll get my Mac many and I'll be able to start supporting Macs but it talks about everything
that's going to deal with your home network and environment and how to keep yourself secure
manage it etc it's called home network help dot info all right and I would really like you to
give it a listen and give me some of your great feedback I will do thank you very much Chris and
appreciate the technical info there I understood just about every single bit of it a little bit
of confusion there because I'm still recording the podcast on the on the Mac side but I'm
exploring windows exploring when you hear me talk about buying a windows laptop that's when you
really got to get worried oh yes hello Adam Curry hello and the listeners of the daily source
code hello this is Michael Randall here from Cambridge podcast Cambridge podcast dot log spot dot
com you know it was only last week I was sitting in the drawing room and wondering is there a
way to help music in this university town this historic little aisle of ours and I think there is
I think there is now with the Cambridge podcast our aim is to play the best and independent music
that hasn't been heard before that hasn't been given a chance to be played and I think we've done
and if you want to support us why not come on down hey haha yes I thought say at Cambridge podcast
dot log spot dot com but not always this is eccentric most of the time we just play some
darn good tunes and I hope you enjoy the show and at Cambridge podcast I don't miss a little
shoot thank you very much so this is the podcast that is doing a podcast about local bands
local to the school in this case Cambridge University and in their show notes they provide not only
links to the songs but also where the bands are performing in the neighborhood so it's a very
geographic community based type of podcast and send me a couple samples this is one of my
liked bad well ash it's take as heard on the Cambridge podcast and today on the daily source code
the last time that I can switch my mind to you always put a scene of my high you
the bottom of my brain it is burning from what am I just know the trees this year my
I run a lot that I must not see and I just want to take take it home I want to drag it home
and when was that time I tell you and when was the last time that I can I touch my
mind for you always but I can't see enough behind you
but once you're my brain it is burning from what am I just know what am I just not
I wish you for this time but I just don't wish for me and I just want to take take take it home
bad well ash take on your daily source code once again that came from the
Cambridge podcast let me see oh yeah he's what I want to talk about audio hijack pro if you're
a Mac user and you're in the podcast that you've probably noticed me talking about this before
this is the program that I actually use to record my podcast and I think we've talked about
the setup a couple times before what the way I'm using audio hijack pro by the way is not exactly
the way the makers of the program intended it and I've been you know trying to get some attention
for a long time actually had an email conversation a couple months ago with one of the guys
from audio hijack pro it's only four guys I think and I saw blog post yesterday which I pointed
to from curry dot com where Quentin one of the founders says hey you know what do we need to do
to make this software better for podcasts and just looking at you know what they really intend
they're software to do I can kind of understand what the confusion is coming from because what
their marketing audio hijack pro mainly for is that you can record audio from any application which is
of course where the name comes from audio hijack pro and you can also set them up on timers
so you could basically say please start up my real player and fire up a URL which could be an
NPR program if you will and record that either you know this day or every every time weekdays
and you can set all these recording schedules up is pretty sophisticated and of course that is very
much like an iPodder only it's a functionality of an iPodder but not really doing it the same way
nor is it actually grabbing MP3 files oh not just got a Skype request from Michael Butler of course
approve you dude you crazy there you go you know so but that would be like kind of like an iPodder
for existing existing radio streams or if there's some other application you wanted to hijack the
audio from at a set time the way I've been using it is is almost backwards what I've been doing is
I've been hijacking my audio input and running that through all their great filters and plug-in
et cetera and adding to that just basic you know sound out from from my Mac there's a couple of
reasons and it's it's actually two technical to go into in a verbal explanation I think a couple
of reasons why it's not really easy to use and a couple why it is very easy to use but I man I'm
really looking forward to a dialogue with these guys and I don't know maybe we have to just draw
diagrams and stuff to explain what we need but essentially they've got all the bits in there you know
what records that does your ID three tags you can plug in audio the only thing that's a problem
is well actually I'm using it backwards let me let me try and explain so typically let's say you play
everything like your sweepers and your jingles and if you play any other audio except a microphone
then you let's say I use quick time to play that so you would hijack quick time right and then
this is voiceover plug-in which actually lets you add and add in a microphone that's why it's
called voiceover and it can even do what they call auto ducking so if you start to talk it'll
bring down the music automatically if you stop talking to bring it up again automatically
I've tried this several times and it really works very well except it doesn't work
and the program will not hijack audio if there's not an actual audio stream coming out of
the application you've hijacked so let me try and explain so if I'm hijacking quick time it will
it will only actually record if there's audio coming out of quick time I've tried this before and the
solution that came up with was to have like a really long track running on a loop that had just a
little bit of noise barely audible but just enough to kick audio hijack pro into record mode
so actually that work pretty well but you know if actually every single time the loop would restart
then the recording would just stop for like a miller second and it would throw off the latency
and it'd become really complicated oh it's actually a phone call I gotta take tell you what
hold on a sec how much do you hate that huh sorry that was the bank I just got yeah you
don't want to hear my conversation well you do want to hear my kind of conversation with the bank
probably but you're not gunna okay that's just the way it is uh let's see we're back at audio hijack
pro I don't know where the where the hell I was I guess I kind of explained it but anyway
I think there's a big disconnect between what the podcasters are looking for at least the
ones that are using a Macintosh and what audio hijack pro is doing because they are almost an
iPod or client as I explained where really we want to use their stuff as a production console so
I'm going to keep working on that and it's just a we need a better way to describe it and I don't know
if I can do that in in written words and maybe someone can help out let's see if we can get together
with these guys quite and certainly seems to to be interested in getting stuff going and I love
this company I love their products so let's see if we can work something out just a quick thing I
want to mention I noticed this the other day I'm a I'm a horrible typist and I wonder I know
in the states usually typing lessons are a part of grade school I don't know if it's extra
curricular activity or and what have you but I never had typing lessons I'd just kind of taught
myself then I type with I don't know one just maybe five fingers four and a half fingers something
like that but I have to look at the keyboard so I'm I guess I'm not I can't blind type and I was
wondering if anyone else you know has this and if there's a way to transition off of looking
I mean I can do it if I type I pretty much know where all the keys are and I do pretty well I still
have to glance down but you know I am just not a blind typist and if you have any is there of course
that you know that can unlearn all these horrible you know typing methods that I have which of course
are you know the shit it's no good let's see if if we can if we can improve that and let me
know what kind of type you are you like a hunt and you know peck and peck and hit type of person
or are you a complete blind typist you know I don't necessarily want to go through some computer
program that's going to take me back to square one is there a shortcut to get from pecking
at the keyboard but using you know really being able to to go pretty quickly it's just that I
can't look at the screen at the same time anyway you get the idea so let me know what you find
out okay
huh I'm y'all pull it here with yet another hit test it's good time so I could not reach
just making another one for you know it works your tracks lined up for you and here is number one
there we go oh human league don't you want me easy one
don't tell me gonna make it too easy for me now you got to be a challenge buddy
yeah and this is number two
the tears for fears everybody wants to rule the world
ah come on I love the processing on this by the way it sounds so hard
well done to your
all right number three number three
uh I love your smile um shenis shenis
cherries shenis I think it's shenis
yeah as I love your smile I like your smile I love your smile
all right number four
I made this test a little bit easier for you to
oh there is no number four
get some of them right
okay and just this was number one
okay don't you want me yeah human league
we got one right
and this was number two
tears for fears everybody wants to rule the world
by the way another favorite of tears for fears is shout
that's the song you got to play in the car when you're sleeping
shout shout let it all out
and number three
and the final one you're not allowed to have this one
wrong you really had to have it right
or really listen to what I mean
for yourself to see one hundred I'm out of
theory from MTV in the middle of thirty minutes of continuous
commercial free music some time before six o'clock today
I'll let you take a stab at guessing the identity of secret
standards number my car New York's best in music first now from a young lady who made
her first record age twelve show but over now we do like that
her name shenese I love your smile the song and it's on W
H T Z
oh man that's cool
where the hell did you get that
awesome
I'm sorry about the poor Sean quality but I just couldn't
reach his to let Adam from the fast give the right answer
I hope you don't mind
okay that's it
see you next time all the hit test
love it
love the hit test
oh man that was crazy that was an air check from Z100 I guess that was uh
was that eighty nine nine no it must have been later than that
this is Z100 secret Santa oh my god
there I was pushing line of cards
reading it just hitting the button really easy
cool very very cool thank you you and I love your hit test and I think
actually um did I miss one yesterday or did I play it
or let me see I have a hit test number two I thought I played this one maybe I
didn't let's if if I played this one well let's see what it is let me
let me just
one girl in casting with Adam
hey Adam this is a young boy with this week's hit test again three
tracks next to the first one
oh I guess no that we did do that one that was Tom Jones right okay we did do that one
all right anyway young love them love them to death man keep
them coming for sure last night I was watching uh celebrity
fit club here in the UK which is a weight loss reality show
it's really quite good actually um uh it's just one of those shows that's kind of
addictive to watch and you know they go through uh exercise and eating but
also um there's some psychological aspects to it and there's some
regression uh hypnotic therapy whatever and I was
watching it last night and I said the Patricia said you know what's coming next
what is unavoidable uh it's going to be the celebrity stop smoking show
and I think it actually would be a very good reality based show I mean we say
reality but of course television has no right anymore to the use of word
reality um but I think it would be cool imagine having you know a couple of
celebs and you follow them around and you know of course you want to try and
catch them sneak into smoke and you got to have all kinds of test built in you know
where I also get a pop quiz and we have to smell your breath and
I don't know if there's other ways to check if someone's been smoking you know
nicotine check basically but that could be really cool just to watch how people
go fucking crazy when they can't smoke so it's a free idea go ahead use it
abuse it it's about to happen and besides uh it probably being something
a lot of people would watch um uh you could probably get it subsidized by the
government uh just a thought finally for today's source code is we're just a little bit
over a 40 40 minute mark I'm gonna play one more song for you um I was introduced to
a group called Clare Fader and the Vaude villains by uh Leon from the from the
the city's bitties um and I've been listening to a couple of their tunes of course the site
is listed in the uh in the show notes for today's podcast uh but hadn't really done anything
with a yet cause I was still kind of you know trying to figure out which track I want to play
and and uh it's a very uh interesting type of music and then yesterday I got an email
from Mary Kay Elkins uh I'm gonna read a little bit of this because it it really caught my eye and you
know and this and this really worked uh hi out of my girlfriend Leon Westover turned me on
your podcast my friend and former co-worker Adam Howell spoke over the cube to me back in
November about podcast blah blah blah blah where was it where was the good part um how shoot
she plays okay so she plays the cello in what she calls the new generation cabaret band called
Clare Fader and the Vaude villains if you like the idea of music which includes girl on cello action
I'll repeat that if you like the idea of music which includes girl on cello action you love us
oh my goodness yes I do like girl on cello action did I say that recently that um
that girls playing cellos are basically hot and I think I got turned on to this first one
what's your name from CNN she used to be on a CBS oh shoot now I was gonna room I thought I
didn't have to write it down Paul is on that's it actually I have an autograph picture of Paul is on she
once said no I was on uh I was on her show at one point she interviewed me when I was at MTV
and and she plays cello and I told her I said oh Paul I gotta let you know that
girl's who played cello really sexy it really turns me on and she signed this picture which of
course I can't find anywhere just some like you know some half sexy note there saying oh yeah I'll
play cello for you anytime bad boy and so Mary Kay Mary Kay Alkins sent off a couple of different
clips from her from Clare Fader and the Vaude villains see uh and actually she's listed a couple of
I don't know I should take this out of the show notes I don't know if I can actually put these
URLs in there or I'll have to ask if I can I don't I don't know if I can list all of these but
anyway she sent me links to a couple of different ones and like with comments like listen to me
shred my solo on the Isle of Summer with the symphony so anyway I did get into this totally dig
a lot of the tunes that you guys are making love the girl on cello action and chose the
Martha Stewart rock and roll version of a song that did well just Martha Stewart rock and roll it's uh it's
called Betty Crocker's bail listen to the lyrics you'll get it but also please pay attention to that
girl on cello action
Mrs. Betty Crocker is going to jail but chocolate brownie cake mix is looking mighty
got a lace of the city are having a babysitter crazy necessary though for Betty Crocker's bail
I'll go says cooked and a fish is fried
cover and got burned by the fire side
a jam on set and a buzz on rise
take a dive in nuts from telling little I'd lies little I'd lies little I'd lies
darling with red ribbons to make sweet elevise she's been making gravy out of store box time
got the butcher's wife and I stayed I shot all Mrs. Betty Crocker where is the head
for making grease in the gingerbread your neighbor said that you've been stealing things
so you're tied her up with your rape friends strange I'll miss a Betty Crocker
what you're going to do
girl band has been telling on you what you're going to do what you're going to do make a
big ol' badge of jail birds do
Mrs. Betty Crocker is out of jail and boy oh boy
has she a tale to tell well not you won't be coming she don't give a damn
oh she's going to run away with the gingerbread man
well hot girl on chillow action coming to you thanks to Claire Fader in the
vault villains and Betty Crocker's bail and that's it for the source code for today
it's Wednesday the second February 2005
has always thanks for all feedback give me give me if you got any freeze to send
which could be promos pots if tunes comment whatever it's MP3 feedback at gmail.com
my regular email address adam of curry.com and of course the daily source code.com for the current episode
all the archives and for the podcast feed. www.curry.com is the weblog
I guess it's time to end the show because my computer's freaking out all right everybody I'll
see you tomorrow for the Thursday this is the daily source code take care bye bye