Delta Sierra Charlie 2-7-5
Please save me from people who've been told what to like and then like it.
In my opinion, if you're over six years of age and you're still getting your music from the radio,
something is desperately wrong with you.
I can only hope that somehow MP3 players and file sharing will destroy FM radio
the way they're destroying record companies.
Then, even though the air will probably never be safe to breathe again,
maybe it will be safer to listen to.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Good afternoon everybody, coming to you from Brussels.
That's right.
An undisclosed hotel in Brussels in Belgium.
This is the daily source code for Monday, November 7th, 2005.
As you can tell, I do not have the Yamaha Mega Workstation with me.
I just had to throw some stuff together.
I basically pulled out whatever it's fitting a small suitcase for my two-day quick travel
to visit the European Parliament and a couple members of Parliament.
About some serious issues, some things that took place Friday and over the weekend
that we got to talk about.
And what better than this is kind of like pulp fiction like music from a brain bucket.
Which I found on the pod save music network.
This is a buy-out something.
Anyway, wow, where to start?
I think the best place to start for today is kind of a spin it back to Friday.
Now, sometimes there is just no coincidence in life.
But for the past couple of weeks, actually for the past year or so,
we've been talking about music rights and how performance rights work versus mechanical rights
versus publishing rights and how we can use license music in podcasts.
And I think we pretty much determined that it wasn't going to work on a short term.
And now some events took place this past Friday and a little bit over the weekend
that made me realize that it's definitely not going to happen.
But it gets a little bit worse than just that.
Okay.
So having grown up in the Netherlands moved there when I was seven.
And of course, there was like a 15-year period when Patricia and I went back to the states.
But we've been back.
We were back just at the end of 1999 and stayed there until a year ago.
We moved here, but we moved to the cottage in the UK.
So I'm a very familiar with it's a small country, right?
Oh, man.
I did it.
I did a valley wood.
I said, right.
After my myself to find myself for that.
It's a very small country.
And Patricia and I were both very well known there.
And there's just a lot of activity around us.
So people are very aware usually what we're doing in podcasting of course is no different.
Since it was basically developed partially in the Netherlands.
I was writing the iPodder script during the decompression hour of my morning radio show
for Veronica Radio, which I did for a year in the Netherlands.
I would drive from the castle up and back every day.
You probably remember some of that if you've been listening for a while.
And of course it was further developed at the cottage in Belgium.
So podcasting, although it really caught on first in the states and probably about six months ago
the Dutch press caught up and started to talk about it a little bit more.
The conversation about playing licensed music on podcast took a very interesting turn.
Probably about that must have been about six months ago.
When the Dutch version of Ask Have Be Am I, who of course affiliated the Buma Stemera,
said that podcasters, non-commercial podcasters could obtain a 35 euro month license
and play whatever they wanted on their podcast.
At least that was the way it was construed.
I never quite read it that way.
I thought it's still meant that you had to have permission from the owner of the masters themselves
to play it on a podcast.
Hold on, I'm just having a sip of, unfortunately, my favorite coffee.
And one of those coffee makers in the corner hall.
I missed the froth.
So unbelievably, last Friday the message is started to come in that the Dutch version of the RIA, which is the NVPI,
decided that they were not going to go along with us.
Didn't like the idea there was going to be no test.
The only way they will work with people and license music with podcasts is if podcasters
DRM their podcast, which of course, I mean, what a can of worms that is we can't even get
iTunes songs on different devices.
So I think that's the last place we want to go.
But they're very adamant about it.
Now, you have to know something else about the Netherlands and how it works there.
Hold on a second.
Let me just stop this.
Bring buckets almost over and I don't want to go to the next song just yet.
Something else you need to know about.
Oh, boy, I have a little too much reverb there.
Oh, well, it's the multi-effects box that I brought along.
I don't want to mess with it.
I got to get this story to you.
So something you need to know about broadcasting in the Netherlands.
And in many other countries around the world, unlike the United States.
I think even in the UK, you purchase a license for, let's just keep with the radio for a moment here.
And let's keep it with the Netherlands because this is where the issues are coming from.
You purchase a license to use the frequency.
And you purchase that.
Actually, it's done in an auction.
Every, I think it's, they've done two auctions now.
This is the second auction in 10 years.
I think that's what it was.
But most of the time these frequencies are auctioned off.
Just like cell phone frequencies are auctioned off.
And they're auctioned off to the highest, usually to the highest bidder.
And some radio stations are paying up to 10 million euros.
So call that, what is that?
That's probably like 11 or 12 million dollars.
Like 11 million dollars a year.
Just for the privilege of using the frequency.
You don't actually get a transmitter or an antenna or even two-tain cans in a string for that price.
And of course, depending on your coverage, depending on the actual frequency,
if the middle of the band is sometimes more,
it can be more useful than the side bands.
You know, there's all these different parameters that play along.
And so, you know, the smaller stations are playing,
still paying up to a million, I think,
anywhere from half to a million euros a year.
Just to use it.
Now, what is the USP, the unique selling proposition of these broadcasters?
Well, 90% of all broadcasts, radio broadcasts,
and the Netherlands are music-based.
There is an all-new station and they have it segregated.
In fact, they've done it so trickily.
So it's very intricate, actually.
You can purchase a cheaper license,
but then you may not be able to play songs from the 90s and today.
You can only play 50s and 60s and 70s or 70s, 80s and 90s.
And then there's how much talk versus music and how much news you have to bring.
And so there's all these stipulations.
It's a very, very messed up system.
It's not really a free way of operating.
And it doesn't really give for good competition,
because you're competing, you know, well, forget about it.
So the main point is that there is a fee that has to be paid.
And so the USP is being able to play licensed music.
So there's not just an issue with the record companies in the Netherlands.
And again, this is something that is very common amongst other European countries,
other countries in the world.
There's, so there's a big disconnect between what we're doing on podcasting.
And what's happening in the music business and what's happening in broadcasting.
But it must be very clear that it behooves both, obviously, the record companies,
because they do not believe in the power of promotion of a podcast.
They think that because we're playing or if someone played licensed music on a podcast,
that it would actually, would detract from record sales.
Now, you all know that I believe very different from that.
Now, the, the broadcasters, they only have that music,
that licensed music as their USP.
In fact, the backlog is in many, many instances, very, very important.
So think about, you know, the kind of music that I use in backtracks,
or that is, that I play, that is used in, and produced in backtracks.
And the, the hit test that young poet does.
And that's a lot of backlog.
So basically, I got a phone call.
Well, actually, it wasn't just a phone call, but it was more, more than one means of communication.
From more than one representative, or people who I deemed to be representative,
of both the music business and broadcasting in the Netherlands.
And I was told, maybe I should say, well, threatened wouldn't be the right word.
But I think, promised probably would be a better word, that these organizations,
the broadcasters, particularly the commercial broadcasters, who are very,
very sue happy in the Netherlands.
They sue each other all the time.
They sue the government over their licenses.
You know, if someone plays a song from the wrong era that doesn't belong to their license,
they go out and sue that station.
And they go through the government again.
And it's just a very, and believe me, you do not want to be in the Dutch legal system.
Certainly not on the, on the being sued side.
It's not fun.
Very lengthy.
And they have no, it's a professional judge system.
They have no jury.
So eventually some guy or gal is going to decide your fate.
Not a jury of your peers.
So the promise that was made is that they're going to come after podcasters.
And they're going to shut them down.
Now, what was implied, but what wasn't said implicitly, was that they were going to shut podcasting down.
Many of you may have wondered how come there are several episodes of daily source,
that you can't find in the archives.
So maybe it's time for me to tell you why throughout the past year,
I had received notices from certain organizations.
Again, these would be a Dutch, local Dutch chapters of international organizations
that would say, hey, you have licensed music sitting on your server.
Here's the file.
And they typically would point to a daily source code.
Now, of course, a year back, I was certainly playing licensed music.
And I would just remove it and I didn't make a big deal out of it,
because I just wanted to keep podcasting rolling on.
The last thing we need is the RIA and Ask Cap or BMI or Harry Fox,
or the NVPI or Sainat or C-SAC or PRM, all this PRS,
PMS, we do not want these guys descending on us and just making trouble,
because we're doing so well.
And we do have an alternative, of course, which is pod save music.
So here's what I did.
And I did not take this quote, Promise, lightly at all.
And I even went, so this is the severity of what it meant to me.
I actually removed every single MP3.
I could find anywhere on a hard drive in my house.
So anything that was not, I probably even threw away a couple of songs
licensed through iTunes and music store.
But I just took everything out, got it off my hard drives.
You know, I archived it and the disk is safe.
We're, you know, no one will find that.
So that won't be a violation, but I just took everything off.
And in fact, I've been enjoying pod save music all weekend.
Excuse me.
Cheap ass coffee and Brussels hotel room.
Oh.
But I'm not taking this, this lightly.
And I happen to know a couple of people in the European Parliament.
Because what happens is, if the Dutch organizations go after this,
and it's very easy to get, to get lost past in the Netherlands,
the way the structure is.
And, you know, just the way the old boys network functions.
That this could become a European directive before you know it.
It could just happen overnight.
So I want to see, you know, what, what can be done,
what kind of rights there are.
But one thing I do know for sure, it's over.
There's no, I'm not going to be playing anymore licensed music.
If it's not registered through the pod safe music network,
which is a very clear agreement.
Once the podcaster signs up, once the artist signs up,
then, you know, you can feel reasonably safe
that anything you're playing there is going to work
and is going to be deemed pod safe.
So even though I, and it really hurts, man,
because no more mashups, it just, I can't do it.
Because how much fun would it be for a couple of bullshit organizations
to come after me and make a huge example out of me?
I think it would be way too much fun for those guys.
So I don't want to give them that pleasure.
I'm going 100% pod safe from this moment on.
And we'll keep you abreast of what's what I find out here in Brussels.
I think I pretty sure, I know what I'm going to hear.
I just want to see how fast it could spread.
What, how fast the directive can be put in place.
Because we do have some transitioning to make.
And I think everyone should be really aware of what's coming down.
And it, you know, it makes a lot of sense.
And thinking about what could happen.
And I think that we're just on the edge of that place.
So pod safe from now on, my friends, 100%.
And I couldn't think of a better song to kick off my proud to be pod safe
edition of the Delta Sierra Charlie than monk.
The pod people.
And I think we're really free.
But maybe we're not doing it.
We're going to sing up the beat.
To be in the right to me.
If everything I need, better than the old dead frequency.
From underground, hold down the sound.
Come set the fire, burn the old dial.
A China's now.
You are never alone.
All I know is a drum, can't stand the throttle.
All I know is a drum.
You've been part of the bomb.
I'm looking like people taking it away from us
In visions coming closer
I'm looking like people taking it away
We're in control
Everywhere you go
Once we start to blow your in the middle
Like the blue sea and show
You can't stop the blue
Suck away the green
Break down the beach
The parade for free
Kill the radio crew
You are never known
All I know is a grown
Can't stand a daughter
Of all the anxiety
And you have wasted
You've been born in the mind
Same with all you men show
You can't stop the blue sea
And you have wasted
I'm looking like people taking it away from us
In visions coming closer
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, chis-mm, good, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, às-rr, yeah!, yeah. yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
You better believe it. You can come after us, but we're here to make you irrelevant. That's right
So speak of the devil RIA makes a land grab. This is sent to me by
A non-E mouse and that makes sense that someone sent it to me anonymously
Let me just share this with you. Hey Adam, I might be interested in this although it's not directly related to podcasting
It might be indicative as to the state of the mind the RIA is currently operating under
So this is the American counterpart of the of the Dutch guys who made that a little promise to me
So he sends a link here it is
They've asked all webcasters so this falls under the
Man bad Russell's coffee
This falls under the I guess the digital millennium copyright act
Usually webcasters do but anyway
They have asked all webcasters to agree to paying
More than one third of their revenue or two point three times with their currently play a
Paying for playing RIA controlled music online
As you mentioned previously, I work for a small media
As mentioned previously, I work for a small media conglomerate and I can tell you we don't make hardly anything
Off of streaming online
The insider to the negotiations that I've spoken with seem to think that basically the RIA is running scared
Yeah, no shit. They're argument asking for these exorbitant rates is that anybody can now find any song they want online at any given moment
And can use something like audio hijack pro to get a CD quality copy of any song they want
Oh, man, these guys do not understand it. They're for an order to make up for the lost revenue in CD sales
They need to jack up the prices to the middle man
So then he goes on to say that obviously
This elbows out the middle man. So what does this mean for podcasts or thing? It means mostly that it seems quite unlike you
There'll be any reasonably priced license for including RIA protect it song at any time in the foreseeable future. Yeah, no shit
So there you go. It's happening in the states now to with the RIA so
And now we got to be really careful because
Don't try to do things under fair use just if you if you when in doubt
Kick it out. That's what I say
If you're using some kind of you know a bit from a CD that you used for an opener or for a tune for your show
Get rid of it. You don't want to run any risk. You can find lots of stuff on the pod safe music network
Wow, this is gonna be pretty interesting. So I'm kind of you know, I mean a new year
I'm in flux man because one on one hand. I'm like
God this is so stupid. I can't believe it. Why don't they understand that this is not the way to go about it
On the other hand. I'm like screw that the pod people are here, baby
This week on the squad cast
He's taken double the fucking dosage a bite get it. Well, that's because the last bottle that I had it was is said to take a table spoon
So and what did this say? Well, I didn't read the directs that I assume this was the same and then I looked you know
Then I've all of a sudden. I'm like, oh, it's probably the same and
Fucking balloon head
What is on the bottle?
So if you on two million dollar if you take the cash pay out which I always did you walk home with seven hundred and seventy thousand
Oh, he's dead how many times you went? Yeah, yeah
What's that you said that you always did as if you won repeatedly on the lottery. Oh, no
That's the hang on her
He can his ugly hand
Anthony. Yeah, what did a noise shit out of you Brian ice cream really loud?
Yeah
I was only kidding, but there you go
I guess
Squad cast a Gmail dot com squad cast squad cast dot com yeah, I'm Mrs. B here. I was just listening to daily source code number 272
and you were talking today about
Football fans in Europe having podcasts and that there's not much of a voice of the fan out there
Well, that applies to American football too, but guess what? I do have American football podcast and it's a Patriots podcast
And I've been going out at since some training camp this summer. I attended training camp every day
And I've been I did something towards and I'm continuing on through the season so
If any of you listeners want to check out Mrs. B's Patriot World podcast
Here's just a sample
Oh
I miss his view of Mrs. B's Patriot World Patriots 2003 fan of the year people that know me know I'm just a passionate about my past
In fact, I attend training camp every day in the summer that's every session and then I come home in podcast
And these are some of the kinds of things you'll hear here
I don't know it's got all bits taken. I'll have first lap the odds in the league all the whole offense taken
I'll have and the crowds of people out in the little that they know that they're in trouble
It's a fault in the wounds I guess
It's tailgate to your bed
You come to the right place. We at the raises edge tailgate know how to do it right
All fans are always welcome to join us whether we're a Patriots fan or an opposing team's fan
But if you want to join in the fun without really being there
This into the podcast
I'm a foreign my hypnotic shots your raises edge tailgate to additionally those a shot of hypnotic
The big willy so the big willy has an other big game many of us have whiskey backers
We also support big willy as we support all of our pages and of course
There's always the game
So please subscribe to Mrs. B's Patriot World podcast and like the three-time world champion in England Patriots
It's a sure winner
Thanks, so what do you think you can find me at www.patiateworld.com and I go to our waggames as well
I've been to a couple already this year I'm heading out to Miami
Next week while all of you guys will be at the portable media expo. I would have left to go there too
I already had these plans and
So I think it also falls under that category of regional
Podcasts too. You talked about that a couple days back and how does the niche for certain
Certain podcasts and certain regions and although
The Patriots are the New England Patriots Patriot Nation extends far beyond the borders of New England
There's Patriot fans all over the world. So if any of the listeners out there I want to jump on and and live
Vicariously through the season ticket hold as eyes ears and taste buds
Jump on over to Mrs. B's Patriot World podcast. Go
Hi, this is Allison Sheridan with the New Silicast podcast hosted at podfeet.com
I wanted to tell you about my podcast. It's a technology geek podcast with a slight Macintosh bias
I just love technology. I love to talk about it. I love to to read about it. I love to play with it
I love to do anything to find new tools that are gonna solve problems that we all have
I like to teach other people how to use tools. I just love technology
It's what I play with all day at work and all day at home
Just really really get a big kick out of it. So I thought if I was having that much fun with it
Why not do a podcast and get other people excited about it too?
I like freeware and shareware best of all. That's my favorite thing in the world anybody can send me a link and say here
Try this and all load it. It's kind of like hey Mikey. He'll try anything. I'll try any piece of software
You send me just to see what it does. I don't care what it does my operating system. Let's just find out do some experimentation
I've got listeners from 24 countries already and so I'm hoping that I'm inspiring people enjoy technology as much as I do
Why don't you head over to podfeed.com and check out the no-silicate podcast. Yeah, right home. I love playing with playing with it too as much as I can
So my new setup clearly does not block Skype from ringing through
That was kind of interesting Skype went off then I rejected it and then two seconds later
My cell phone rang because I forgot that I have Skype forward into my cell phone
My goodness so that's just stay off for now now. All righty that was kind of that the
That pat New England Patriots podcast man that promo was long
Hey, let's try to keep promos under 10 minutes if we can
Oh wow so a little depressing here the weather is really crap in in Brussels
And by the way the parliament moves back and forth between Brussels and Luxembourg so the idea is is to go to Luxembourg tomorrow because there's a
Basically the people that I want to talk to are split up
But I'm I'm pretty sure I know what I'm gonna hear and by the way this is not like it's like it's a
A huge punishment for me to do this because you know that when you make those little hops in inside Europe
You don't really get on an easy jet if you have
The Charlie 182 Romeo Gulf you know what I'm saying
Hey, here's a premiere for you. This is a brand new from Josh Cruz
You know from cruise box listen to mash it up
I've got it in love to feel a good connection
I gotta get down and miss it
Get it up m mix it into mash it up get on down
Get it up m mix it in my shit up get on down
Get it up m ced in my shit up get on down
Hey!
Who can I?
Do you wanna get mad?
Enough to make the phone listen
on a podcast and makes you wanna move?
I'm hurting you down, skinny white boy
Four and one and a job, oh please a trick I chose
It makes you wanna move
Get it out, mix it in, mash it up, get on down
What do you see? You can't always believe
But you gotta have faith, and you know that ain't free
I'm on the foot, it's got a huge house
Why not buy a song?
I'm just gonna die, you can sing it alone
But you see, you can't always believe
But you gotta have faith, and you know that ain't free
I'm on the foot, it's got a huge house
Why not buy a song?
I'm on my foot, it's wrapped up in the cord
Josh Cruz, mash it up, it's the title that one
I said premiere, it's a premiere on the daily source code
That's for sure, maybe CCC Chapman played it, that wouldn't surprise me
I haven't listened to the latest pod show music rewind
Which I think it's number eight came out, no maybe seven, seven or eight
Oh man, if you haven't heard that definitely go to music.podshow.com
There's a link to it right there on the homepage these days
So still working on that Christmas song, a slow is communicating with the
Ronald Treiber in the Netherlands and they're working on coordinating
Getting some artists, I guess, actually into a studio in New York
Some of the New York guys and gals
And hopefully they're gonna have other stuff sent through the net
That was kind of the whole point of the experiment
To see if we could get a whole bunch of pod music artists sending in their submissions
And basically syncing them up, I have no idea how that's gonna work
Technically, but looks like one big pro tools project to me
And CCC Chapman is now kind of coordinating that
So I'm so happy that all I had to do is just hand off the idea
I don't actually have to do anything
But the minute there's something I can listen to guys
Maybe you got some session tracks or something, please send it off to the source code
So I can let everybody enjoy it
And of course, I got a whole bunch of comments about me talking about Christmas
In many aspects
Hi Adam, this is Brent from mac and rollpodcast.com
What's the fucking deal of playing Christmas music the first week of November
You're getting as bad as Walmart and Target
What next Christmas tree websites
And correct me if I'm wrong, but I don't think I've ever heard a death metal band
When the pot safe music network on the daily source code
Like you think death metal artists don't have feelings too
I think they'd go over great on your Christmas song collaboration
So don't forget the death metal artists
Keep talking to Adam
Hi Adam, it's Glenia from the Zedesh pot cost
Down here in Cape Town, South Africa
Or as you yanks are called at the Zesesh
Well it's early November
But you know has you know time flies and we're heading towards Christmas time
And one thing that really piss me off the most
is when I turn on the TV and I look at foreign media
The phrases like happy Christmas, merry Christmas
Have a great new year
Or whatever, you know people use to express
You know good wishes and good wealth of Christmas
Or it's been replaced by two words
One phrase, happy holidays
I think this is a lot of politically correct bullshit
That we have to endure during this time of year
Where we all come together and we all close and family
And all those good things that form part of the Christmas spirit
I would like to ask all pot-casters
Are there please refrain from using happy holidays
Please express yourself the way you should be expressing yourself during this time of year
So if you're in a religion that celebrates Christmas
Same merry Christmas on a happy new year
And I hope you have a great 2006
If you're Jewish, well happy on a cold
And if you're anything else that celebrates this time of year
And a different way, express yourself
Come on guys, stop letting the foreign media
And all the politically correct bullshit
Interfere in your Christmas time
And secondly, I thought I'd plug my own show
You can listen to the Zerez Show podcast
Probably one of a handful of podcasts coming from Cape Town, South Africa
Well yeah, we talk about all things South African
It may be news interviews
Sensing tours and of course we try our best to play the very best in South African music
Oh, and another thing
We've also been making some bolt-on
Which is the South African delicacy
A spiced dry meat
And no, it is not like that horseshoe
You guys call beef jerky up there in the US
So come on subscribe to the Zerez Show
Search for the Zerez Show in iTunes
Or subscribe via the website
www.Zedeshow.Zeday.net
And of course don't forget
Zed in South Africa is pronounced as Z in the US
Well until then, thanks Adam
Bye bye
Thanks Glenn
Now you make a good point there
Patricia now we're just talking about that
About right now how beautiful a Guilford is
And it's a holiday spirit
I think the I think what we should do
As responsible podcasts
I'm going to make it my business to find out
And usually I do actually
Find out what the exact dates of some other holidays are
So I can say happy Hanukkah
And what else there must be other things you say at Hanukkah
I know that
Around young Kippur Jewish New Year
You say Shrenatova
And then of course there's Kwanza
So maybe we just
And how can we don't have
Shopping season for Kwanza
And for Hanukkah and for Ramadan
And what else you might have
You know I think it's a commercial opportunity
There's not a
Maybe we should start with Ramadan
I'm telling you that's like a month worth of partying
Ah
Oh well
Yeah I kind of agree with that
Political politically correct
Happy holidays
Oh please
Please
And of course that means that we should also have a
A pod safe
Happy Hanukkah song and happy Kwanza song
I'm all for it
Send it in just send it into me
And I did a request
Last week for some creative ideas about
New types of advertising
And I received a couple of entries
I want to play 140 right now
Which I like very much
Although it wasn't really a new way of advertising
But it was actually it was kind of
It was very creative
And it's not 30 seconds jammed into your face
Here listen to this with me
I think you'll enjoy it
Hi Adam
It's Ron from Griddlekakes Radio
Where we explore the last art of
Audio Storytelling
Check us out at griddlekakes.com
Just like you
I'm a big
So we decided to take you up on your quest
For an eye dot commercial
And delivered it to you
Griddlekakes style
Take a listen
Here you go sweetheart
Happy birthday
Hmm
The box is bigger than I thought
Oh, what's this?
It's a puppy silly
Isn't that what you wanted?
Well dad
I wanted an eye dog
I know but isn't a puppy much better than an eye dog
Can he make his head light up?
Well no
If I plug him in on my eye pot
Will he play music?
No sweetheart
Can he dance to my music?
Maybe in time
I just thought
I'm just think about all the things
We won't have to do with an eye dog
We won't have to feed him
We won't have to clean up after him
We won't have to get him
Since the dawn of time
Dogs have held the title man's best friend
But not anymore
As children around the world
Choosing a cute little pooch with a pinched from music
Called Eye Dogs
And we'll never have to take ticks off of him
Oh look honey
He's trying to moonwalk
Oh hum
Boring
Um
Dad
What's he doing now?
I don't know
I think he's trying to plug himself into the stereo
No
And Eye Dogs run on batteries
And I can carry him in his eye doggy bag
And I can take him with me
And I can dress him up in this cute little sweater
Called a chill set
And he's allowed to stay in home
Come here boys
Are you alright?
Eye dog
Man's new best friend
Okay
I don't know if we could ever use it more than once
I might try and see if I can get away with it
But I like it very much
Very, very cool
Um
You know what?
Tell me your address
And I'll send you an eye dog
If I'm sure we have one lane right
If not we'll just grab the one that belongs to
Chris McIntyre from podcast alley
We'll steal his eye dog
Alrighty
How wild this is so weird
The sound is completely different
I think I might have a
I see this is my old soundcraft mixing board
It has the
Let me just tell you what I have set up
Because I've been doing a little bit of experimentation
With mobile setup
I brought out the...
So I have to say that for short trips
Schlepping along the Yamaha digital
Workstation, the 16
Alfa whiskey, whatever it is
It's just way too much
Of course, what I really need
Is any of the great Mike Priam
Something that makes the microphone sound good
Like having a little bit of reverb
I think I have too much
But I just have to live with it
And a compressor
And I have from my previous setup
I have this, what does this say?
Let me see
What kind of unit?
It's a cheap ass one
It's the TC electronic
Does it have a name on it?
I can't even read him
So freaking blind
The dual
Engine processor
The M300
Okay
So I've basically routed
The signal out of the new power book
Into a channel there
I have the mic just plugged in up on top
And it all runs through the same reverb
And processor
Sounds okay I guess
It's better than the live mic
Oh by the way, I can also put the live mic on it
So once I get the sound a little bit better
And I'll have to work on that
And tweak it
This will be a great mobile setup
Because it's a much more compact
Than the Yamaha
Man
I'm also sitting on the ground
I have all the equipment
Strow now
You know I like to stand
When I'm working
And I don't get as much gastronol interruptions
So I have my back leans
The lean the lean against the bed
Here on the carpet
Which kind of grosses me out
The carpet of the hotel room
Who knows what
Euro Parliamentarian
Been walking around here with a wet damp feet
From the shower
Ooh
Freaky man
Just freak out of him
This is Thomas from Germany
Hey Thomas
I'm a regular listener since about two months
I'm really enjoying what you do
In fact, your show is just about the only podcast
I have the time to listen to on a regular basis
It seems to cover a lot of what I've interested in
Music, political aspects of the music business
Geeky stuff
Apple porn
You know, you've talked about German reggae music
And one or two of the last shows
Reggae, especially German reggae, is extremely popular over here
I'm sure you must have heard about seed
A band from Berlin
They have a huge hit at the moment called Aufstein
I think there are also popular in Jamaica
Which goes to show that music really is a universal
Border crossing phenomenon
It's also refreshing to see you know
The young folk listening to some proper music for a change
I know
That music is not part-save
But I think you're not wanting to miss this really, really cool
But pumping kick ass reggae
Which, by the way, also has some very cool lyrics
You might even understand most of it
Since they're singing in German as well as English
Don't miss him
Okay Adam, that's all from me
Keep up the good work
I wish you all the best
Bye
Dude, Thomas, thanks
But there's just no way, man
I cannot play it
It's not pod-save as you already pointed out
I played it, so that was an illegal transfer
I played it, I listened to it
I liked it very much
Seed with Triple E
And I immediately deleted it
Because
No more risk
Proud to be pod-save here on Delta Sierra Charlie
This one's just been haunting me
As I listened to it on my iTunes
Bob Gentry's upside down
I've been talking in my past sleep
When I'm waking
Well, my tongue is tight
I've been thinking I should leave
Instead of waiting for her when the time is right
I've backed the bags under my eyes
Well, I've seen enough to know what it's like
It's turning me upside down
Tell me what I've done wrong now
All I can do is try it
When everything's breaking me down
Looking at the end side out
Well, those rules got changed somehow
Maybe it's suicide
To stay here and just sit around
I was able to hide every bruise on my body
Till now
I've been walking in my head
Sleep
When I'm waking up
Well, my legs are tight
I've been thinking I should leave
For the window of it's a marathon
I've been dreaming I could fly it
Well, I'm free enough
But I'm still way down
Just turning me upside down
Tell me what I've done wrong now
All I can do is try it
When everything's breaking me down
Looking at the end side out
Well, those rules got changed somehow
Maybe it's suicide
To stay here and just sit around
I was able to hide every bruise on my body
Till now
I've been afraid to just walk out
Ain't nowhere to stop me now
Just turning me upside down
Tell me what I've done wrong now
All I can do is try it
When everything's breaking me down
Looking at the end side out
Well, those rules got changed somehow
Maybe it's suicide
To stay here and just sit around
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now
All I can do is try it
When everything's breaking me down
Tell me what I've done wrong now
All I can do is try it
When all rules got changed somehow
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now
All I can do is try it
Oh man, I love that song
Despite the skipping
The audio hijacked pro and mega Sega produced
Well worth the price of admission
Pot say find that a music.podshow.com
Bob Gentry upside down
As the final sounds for today's daily source code
Which means we'll be back with you tomorrow
It'll be from Luxembourg
And I'll have hopefully have some more to report
And we're still proud to be
Pot say
Another Pot show podcast
Stick it in your ear
Thanks for watching