Delta's Yeracharly 2-2-9er.
You're DJ.
I you don't make fun of you!
Your DJ has only just begun.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky drinks.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Fantastic.
It is Friday.
It's August 26, 2005.
Hello everybody.
How you doing?
Today is your daily source code.
We did another full week.
I'll show you every single day.
Well, let me just call the newspapers.
Let them know that that's happened.
Another beautiful day.
For a change here outside the Curry Cottage.
And killed for the United Kingdom.
The sun is shining.
It's about 75 degrees.
And visibility.
Visibility is more than 10 miles.
So it's a beautiful day for flying, which I won't be doing.
Because we got plenty of stuff to do today.
Time now is 145.
And I'm behind.
Oh, by the way, it's no longer the podcast complex.
I was sent an email that with a much better name.
The curry console.
That's what it is.
And yes, indeed.
It doesn't fit in with the furniture.
And that doesn't.
Maybe we need to put some wood and twirly bits on.
So it can go with the Louis Couture's desk.
So nice to see though.
Everyone's amazed at Patricia.
Let me have this thing up in the office.
Well, of course.
This is how I make a living.
But yeah, it won't be too long before.
She either wants to repaint it or wants to put curly wood bits on it.
Maybe we should go find some of those curly wood bits.
For example, I'm pretty important for action.
She's going to take it.
I have not even taken my shower yet.
I'm standing here in my house coat with my eggs on.
You know, I should take a picture of this.
Today, I am in the perfect outfit for podcasting.
This is our office.
And also my hair is perfect for podcasting today.
Because you can't see it.
It's kicking off with a great Friday mashup DJ Errorman.
I bring you scissors sisters.
The Beatles, George Michael, and Arita Franklin in no one takes your freedom.
Mashed up on the source code.
When you grow up, leave like a good boy out of.
In your mama, days are shining for a better son.
Something different.
Oh, the girls are seeing the like you.
Because your handsome, like to talk in the pool out of fun.
But now your girl is going to miss an end.
How's it got in them deep in?
The folks are wondering about the wedding.
They won't listen to a word you said.
We're going to take your mama out on that year.
We're showing what it's all about.
We're going to jack the phone.
Some cheap champagne.
We're letting the good times all roll out.
And if the music ain't good, well it's just too bad.
We're going to sing a low, no matter what.
Because it doesn't mind if the new world is.
It's a different man to make a good.
Your day breaks.
Your mind makes.
You find that all I want is a kind of thing wrong.
When she no longer needs you.
She wakes up.
She makes up.
She takes a time and doesn't feel she has to know.
She no longer needs you.
And then her eyes, you see nothing.
No sight of love beyond tears.
Cry for no one.
I love that you would have lasted years.
You will.
Hey, I'm a man.
I will.
Do it.
Then make a good.
It's a happy thing.
It can stay.
If it's a calm.
Gosh.
Maybe you're a poor man.
You want her.
You need her.
And yet you don't believe her.
When she says her beloved dead.
No thing to need you.
And then her eyes, you see nothing.
I love beyond the tears, cry for no one
I love that shirt of last years
I'm always down
I can't stand it, I'm always down
I'm always down, I'm always down
I'm always down
I can't stand it, I'm always down
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you know, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, José that, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah Yeah,
I don't know what he's on because he didn't know where I was doing it but he better start
to share it, but it also matches no one takes your freedom, it's his assistant's Beatles,
George Michael and Rita Franklin.
On the daily source code for Friday, August 26th, 2005, thank you all so much for commenting
on the Curry console.
For those of you who are wondering if that was a CB radio that I have set up in the
booth here, no, that's not a CB.
Although I used to be a huge CB radio fanatic, I mean big time I was on the single side
band.
I was sniping diodes to create an extra 120 channels, I had the halfway of GPA and Tana, I had
all of that stuff.
No, that's the TLA 5052 stereo valve processor, which is basically key to a part of the
sound, which also a lot of you commented on, yeah, it's got, I've got the big gehonus sound
now, which I think I posted that on my weblog, you can see where PW Fenton was comparing
oscilloscope readouts of my voice versus his voice, saying, you know, the same, making
the same noise, and really what does it all, it's all electronics, I don't really sound
like this in real life, you come up to me, you'd be like, who's this curly boy talking?
By the way, I've had some email back and forth with the adub from mashuptown.com, about
legal ways to distribute mashups and also get the mashup artists themselves paid for
their work, as well as the artists whose music is used, and he has some pretty novel
ideas, certainly for a distribution of it, and I guess the real question that we have
then is how much you're willing to pay for a great mashup that you could own and play
in perpetuity, play for your friends, the problem still is, you know, how do we get this
to be legal on podcast, you know, that's the part that I'd, that I'd really really like
to figure out, at the end of the day, if we can, I mean, anything you play is going to
be subject, I guess, to ask at BMI rules, now that's not all that hard to, to get those
payments going, but still it comes down to the record companies, they're going to want
their piece, and if you use 15 different pieces of a, of a 15 different song snippets
in a mashup, you're going to run into a huge administrative task, but there are some
other ways, and we could, we could actually do a mashup show as long as we had it protected.
So I'm, I'm just think about a whole bunch of different ways and different things that
I love having MP3s just out there and anyone being able to download the show and listen
to it, but when it comes to copyright and material, we're going to have to figure some
stuff out pretty soon, because this is just way too much fun, you know, someone's going
to spoil this mashup fun soon enough.
I need a bar stool for this complex, yes, and I, you know, I love standing up while
working while doing, you know, emailing or talking on Skype, I just like standing a lot.
Unless they was the first full day with the laptop on the console, on the curry console,
had to got the Skype machine up on the top, and there, my feeders, I think I have, I
need a place to sit once in a while, so I'm going to be on the lookout for a bar stool
very soon.
Lift the Gmail bag, got any mail from Joe Carpenter, he's the guy from a guy a girl
and the bottle podcast, which is tagged as an innovative wine podcast from in and around Silicon
Valley.
And I'll put a link to that in the show notes, of course, but he wrote me an interesting
email.
As his congratulations on the founding of your newest venture, I wanted to say how appropriate
you brought this to Silicon Valley as Charles Harold was the first abroad cast from San
Jose to the world in 1912, I'm going to cite a little bit of this, I think some of
this came from Wikipedia.
Charles Harold pioneering radio was the first person to transmit radio programs of music
and news to a listening audience, beginning in 1909, three years before Congress's radio
act of 1912, which is largely still in effect, by the way, Harold broadcasts from his
college of engineering and wireless, located in the guard, he believed that the college
of engineering and wireless in 1909, I was located in the garden city bank building at
first and San Fernando, I think that's not too far from from the condo.
His wife's civil was the first female disjocke in the country, together they initiated
commercial radio advertising, a tireless experimenter, Charles Harold developed more than
50 radio related inventions and there's a Wikipedia entry and I'm going to put all that
in the show, no, it's fascinating stuff, this is how radio got started and I didn't
know that, I didn't know it started in San Jose and of course, it started off with
the Don and Drew of the Day or the guy in the girl on the bottle of the day or the
Keith in the girl of the day, it seems like having a guy in the girl on the radio in
that type of format really works, so there you go, once again we're reinventing a lot
that's already been done.
Hey everybody, this is Jay from the Death Podcast, if you're among the millions of Americans
wish they had more money and less debt, you need to listen to the Death Podcasts now,
we talk about consumer finance, how to do battle with debt collectors, correcting your credit
report, the ins and outs personal bankruptcy and other debt relief options and more, subscribe
by going to deathpodcast.blogspot.com or paste this feed into your iTunes or podcast or feeds.feedburner.com
forward slash death podcast.
When you listen to the death podcast, you can nod your head and tap your toes.
Nobody needs to know you're getting the latest information on how to make your financial
future better and stronger.
We've in place some great pod safe music because who says getting information has to be
dry and boring.
The death podcast, in your ears or on your computer, there's never been a better way
to get the information you need to make your financial world a better place.
Pod Joe, content that will make you walk the job and kiss your mother.
My name is X246Y7 from the Planet, Don'topia and when I'm in your rather primitive solar
system, I go to paranormalpodcast.com and set my podcast aggregator to paranormal podcast
with Jim Harald.
Finally, a show about me.
Well, sort of.
At paranormal podcast, we interview authors and experts from around the world about everything
from UFOs and ghosts to the existence of life after death.
Our crop circles real is their scientific explanations for the Burmuda Triangle phenomenon.
Learn this and so much more on the paranormal podcast.
Now we take our subject matter seriously, but we have fun too, even skeptics are welcome.
So please subscribe.
It's free.
You can find us at podcast alley.
The iTunes music store or at paranormalpodcast.com.
Take a listen.
Open your mind.
So I've been playing around with all kinds of online applications.
I used Gmail pretty much exclusively right now for anything and everything.
They're all of my document management because that search feature is just so incredibly
handy.
And even if you just think, oh man, I've got to send so and so an email, a memory sent
something in and you just do a search for that person's name and the email pops up within
seconds, which is wonderful.
Now I'm getting a whole bunch of these Eid Google Talk requests and I don't know.
First of all, this is Windows only, which is a bummer because I do like cross-platform
application.
So of course, web stuff works the best and this is a Windows only app as far as I understand.
And it's supposed to sit in the middle of a whole bunch of stuff, but my community where
I use my instant messaging is through Skype.
I'm not an MSN guy, not an Am guy, although I have looked at Am recently, they have a lot
of really amazing, amazing features in this, the new version is very, very out there.
I think that's also at this point Windows only.
It still is the predominant operating system.
But these Google Talk requests, where I like what they did with Gmail, they're incredibly
lame.
I'll see if I can bring one up here because and I hate it when this happens is when they
send out an email to you automatically that has a quasi personal message in it, let me
just grab one.
I have a thousand at least and from people I know and respect actually, I just do a search
so I'll do Google Talk, that says what I love about Gmail, it's going to search my mail
and bring something up within seconds.
There we go.
So here you go.
CCC Chapman has invited you to try Google Talk and that says, I've been using Google
Talk and thought you might like to try it out.
We can use it to call each other for free over the internet.
Here's an invitation to download Google Talk, give it a try.
That is where the Gmail invites were great saying, so and so was sent to an invitation
to join Gmail.
This is lame.
This turned me off immediately, it's like, come on, first of all, I know CCC doesn't
talk like that.
Second of all, I'm going to go to the next one in the list from Noah Centanero.
I've been using Google Talk and thought you might like to try it out.
Yeah, so that's stupid, you know, Google is good as you are at some of this stuff.
This one, you really, really missed the mark.
And I'm just not quite sure how it's going to integrate into my life.
I'm afraid to get on it because once you hop on it, then people think you're available
through that and if you go away, then you start to lose messages.
Anyway, just thought that was interesting.
Google, you know, went that direction with their messaging, with their secret invite system.
It was good up until this.
And just to prove how much email really sucks, I've been waiting ever since we got
back from vacation for a new hit test from Beyond Palette.
And we've exchanged a couple emails, he's working on some stuff, he's been offered some
interesting opportunity.
So, you know, we always have a little sidebar conversation going on.
You know, I didn't feel like I could say, hey, young, you know, he's going to send me another
hit test because he just doesn't want to ever recann, he's got a busy life.
And then yesterday he sent me an email last evening saying, you don't like the hit test anymore.
So we're talking about it.
It turns out I've had one in my inbox for, well, ever since we started our vacation.
So so much for the great system.
But of course, I was able to pull it out really quickly and, well, why don't we play
along?
Oh, yes.
Hey, Adam.
Hey, you're on the road again.
And now you're on a vacation.
Okay, so that's yarn thinking that we were still on vacation.
So apologize.
Let's continue with hit test 51.
Um, I also hear you're not feeling too well.
So let's hope.
I can brighten up your day with a bit of good music.
So if you're ready, we're going to start to hit test.
This is number one.
My day, yeah.
Was it full force?
No, um, ready for the world.
Oh, Sheila.
And this is number two.
Please, John.
It's almost insulting my intelligence.
Philip Bailey and Phil Collins easy lover.
And the final one is always number three.
That's all back to my youth.
Earthwomen's fire, fantasy.
This is a good song, John.
And time's up.
And here we go with the answers to hit test number 51.
This is the answer number one.
It's ready for the world.
This is Oh Sheila.
That was the jam back in the day.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Ready for the world.
And this is answer number two.
Philip Bailey and Phil Collins.
This is easy lover.
Now take me back to my final answer for today's hit test.
It's song also.
I feel like Bailey.
Great song this.
Philip Bailey and Phil Collins easy lover.
Now take me back to my final answer for today's hit test.
It's song also.
I feel like Bailey has lead singer of Earthwomen of fire.
This is fantasy.
Down.
Come to see me.
Earthwena fire.
And fantasy has answered number three.
Well, that's it for hit test number 51.
I hope you're feeling better.
Well, I don't know when you're going to play this hit test.
I hope I'm not wrong.
And well, hopefully you're already feeling better.
Okay.
It's always two addresses.
Hit test the Gmail.com for feedback.
And young polette.com.
J and P-O-L-E-T.com.
For info about the hit test and the hit test podcast.
That hasn't been there for a long time.
But hopefully I'll be able to make one soon.
Well, thank you for listening.
Until next time.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
Young polette with the everlasting hit test.
Good to have one back.
That was easy.
I liked it though.
You know, after I'm done with the show today, I'm going to head over to iTunes.
I'm going to download fantasy by Earthwena fire.
Actually, I'm going to download, I'm going to download all three of those songs.
Those are great.
I haven't heard those in so long.
I remember fantasy Earthwena fire.
That's when I was like 15 years old.
And then hop on the back of Buddy's motorcycle.
We go down to the next town over.
I was living in Holland south of Amsterdam.
And we actually went to the fantasy disco tech.
You know, and in Holland it was drinking is no big deal.
So therefore it's also no big deal.
But you know, I remember having one gilder beers at the fantasy disco tech in At Horn.
When that was like the number one hit.
Oh man, what was in those days?
We had reunited, peaches and herb.
Captain Teniel.
Do that to me one more time.
I wonder.
How many of you have actually purchased a track off of iTunes after you've heard it on the hit test?
If you do that, would you please let me know?
Because I think that, you know, things like this items and bits like this in podcast are fantastic
way to promote back catalog.
And I'm sure that people, I've heard many times from mashups that someone will say,
Oh, you know, I love that mashups so much when I'm bought the original.
So if you ever go and get anything off of iTunes after hearing something in the hit test,
let us know at curie.com.
Another email here from Darren Helprin.
I just started listening to podcasting since iTunes 4.9 introduced them to it.
Has a comment about what I was saying about oil.
Peak oil actually.
And this is a pretty long comment.
But in essence, I'll just give, well, I will give it the answer.
As soon as you know, oil is a finite resource.
That is, there's a fixed amount in the earth minus that which we've already used up.
There are three things of importance.
One, how much is the total amount of extractable oil?
And the planet, how much of that have we used since we first discovered oil?
And therefore, how much of it is left to extract?
Two, how many barrels and total worldwide can we produce per day?
And three, what is the demand in barrels per day worldwide?
And then he goes into a whole bunch of background about China,
who, of course, are consuming more oil than I think anyone,
or than ever, at least, they have an incredible rapid rate of usage,
ascending rate of usage.
And essentially, the whole point is, is that this is supply and demand.
And here we go.
China has bought something like 80% of the world's steel production of the past three years,
and a rapidly trying to negotiate deals with low-peck countries to acquire oil.
The USA2 is trying to acquire as much oil as it possibly can.
This is because it's running out.
You can expect to see the price of oil escalate much higher than $70 per barrel.
It may hit $100 before we know it.
This may sound like a lot of doom and gloom,
but I invite you to read many articles that are available at from the wilderness.com,
and I'll put that in the show notes.
Because I've read about this, this theory of peak oil,
and how soon we're going to run out.
And I have to say, I do subscribe to some of the theories in it.
And if you just look at supply and demand and assume that that's based on free open markets,
like the Chicago Exchange and wherever else oil is traded,
that indeed we've got some problems brewing here.
So what are we going to do about that?
I personally, I for one, I am totally into bio diesel.
I've talked about that before, I believe, on the show.
I think my next car is going to be a diesel just in case,
because you can basically take a crap in the tank and a diesel engine will run.
But below Adam and all the DSC listeners,
this is Rob Cossill with a new artist's podcast,
come an answer from Indianapolis, Indiana.
I'm going to be featuring new music from all over the world in various genres.
And a couple of shows out right now.
It'll be doing at least three or four months.
So come subscribe to RobCossill.com.
That's ROB, C-O-S-T-E-L-O-W dot com.
Just click the XML link on the site and I'll see you online.
Thanks.
Potchow.com makes no claims regarding the quality of its potchowers
or the sanity of its producers.
Listen at your own risk.
Another one from Brian Deamer.
Welcome to the show we're glad you're with us here.
I'm Brian Deamer.
I am Peter Reos.
Excellent.
Fire Superman.
That colossus.
The Phantom.
We got a geek of the day.
We can be sexy bitches too.
Lightning fanboy.
How did you first get in the comments?
This is Comic GeeksB.
ComicGeeksB.com.
It's just so entertaining.
Let's get to the daily source code.
If you didn't know that, like you were scanning some radio dial and bumped into it.
Got a lot of feedback on the teenager comments.
Feedback from people who have teenagers.
Feedback from people who have kids who will one day be teenagers.
And no feedback from teenagers actually.
But thank you very much.
I think that we should do some more with that.
There's a huge community.
That is kind of everywhere.
And it's the community of parents.
That's what I like about the mommy cast.
And I was the name of that.
I got it.
Oh, man.
I really got to get that show.
I got to get a piece of that show for you.
Hold on.
Let me just look up my podcast outline here.
This is 101 uses for baby wipes.
That's what it is.
I've got to get.
I hope those guys will send me a promo.
We talked about it yesterday.
Please make promos.
And then promos in.
It is by far the best way to promote your show.
I think you can also put promos now on podcast.
I'll leave.
We're going to have that capability for promos to be automatically inserted on the indie
Potter.org.
And of course, promos.
You know, I love playing promos.
And it's easy.
You know, because you can really focus all of the attention of what you're trying to or what
you do in your regular show or podcast or program whatever you want to call it.
You can really focus that and get your message across in condensed form.
And it's a great way for exchanging promos is easy.
Although it does fill up my Gmail.
I just went back and had to delete a couple different emails with the attachments.
You know, it's just not true.
Google can't keep up with me.
You know, this infinity plus one.
I see what they're doing.
You know, whenever you get in within like 10 megabytes of your quota,
then you start to get more.
But that goes with like one or two megs a day.
And interestingly enough, your quota gets set to 100% even though you still may have five megs left.
So then you can't effectively send email have to go in and delete something.
And lots of people said, well, why don't you just open up another Gmail account and forward the email from that.
I'll tell you why I don't want to do that.
The main reason is I want to keep, you know, just that search function, all in one place is fantastic.
That's the whole concept of Gmail.
But also it uses JavaScript and I guess it's Ajax maybe.
That's, is that with the new HTML programming language that everyone, you know, that flicker uses and all these other great sites that have incredible functionality right in the browser.
I think that Gmail uses that for.
How was that?
Okay, in 15 minutes, I have to call my banker from almost to give her an update.
What was I saying? Oh, it uses, so Ajax or JavaScript or whatever it is.
To remember the email addresses that you've typed in or people you've sent an email to or responded to.
And that is that really makes that interface fly.
You know, not having to click on anything to figure out what someone's email address is,
but just start typing in a piece of a name and then it works and I love that so much.
I don't know how I got to the Gmail thing again.
One last bit of feedback here from Peter.
Yes, I was talking about how if you look at the GPS track that I flew when we went to Rotterdam.
You see when the plane was actually parked.
The GPS registered it as if we were running across the tarmac and running through the building.
It looked like we were really going berserk.
And as I thought, this is, well, what I said is I thought it was probably because of the overcast skies that the GPS couldn't get a handle.
Couldn't get a good fix.
Peter has a different explanation.
Because most folks don't know it, but the GPS system is accurate to within a few inches.
That's why those smart bombs work.
Okay, here's the part they don't know.
The US government, of course, doesn't want to share that technology with someone who might want to use it.
Against the US.
So they build in a certain amount of pseudo random inaccuracy that they alone know how to decode and defeat.
Manufacturers of GPS of consumer GPS units have become quite skilled at looking at a whole bunch of satellites at once and sort of averaging the built in errors out.
Hence we enjoy accuracy to within around 50 feet or so.
But in reality, three satellites could actually get you accuracy measurable to within inches.
So every time you hear about a new advancement in consumer GPS units,
it's an advancement in defeating the US government's built in on purpose errors.
If they turn their scrambles off, our GPS units would probably work better than theirs.
Interesting.
I had heard this.
And you know, there is a way in aviation GPS.
I know what they do in the states.
I don't know if they, and I think the UK as well, you can synchronize to a radio station that is sending out a signal.
Some kind of pilot tone, and you can use that to get accurate results on the GPS.
Again, I'm not sure how accurate those results are, but it does make sense.
And I have heard this story before about messing up the GPS signal on purpose.
So I guess that the Bluetooth GPS that I have basically, you know, just does a reasonably good job if you're moving.
But if you're stationary, then it starts to have problems.
And it's particularly with an overcast sky.
It has problems trying to really figure out where you are.
So that does sound like a very feasible answer.
Damn, what are we at?
Not 30 minutes?
You know, 33 minutes.
We should wrap this up.
I was listening as usual every morning.
I go through my email, and I usually pass by the podcast music network to check out what the top pod plays are.
You know, what people are listening to, what other shows are playing.
And we're coming up with more functionality.
By the way, the store will be opening very soon.
And also, we're going to have forums.
So you can comment on on the artist's pages or on the podcast or pages.
So we can get some some real good feedback flowing through the site.
And I was playing this next song by Grittle, which is one of the top plays.
And Patricia walked in and she said,
God damn, I quote,
God damn, this is good, she said.
I think you're like a two.
It's a little bit of Beatles influence there.
I saw you sleeping in your house.
And I can't think of nothing worse.
And I saw you sleeping in your house.
and I can't think of nothing worse.
And I can't think of nothing worse.
But I can't think of nothing worse.
and I can't think of nothing worse.
You are the fairest of the mall, griddle, I'm reading it and had it all in there.
I think Patricia is absolutely right.
She said, is that a new band that said, no, baby, this is what we call pot-safe music.
Haven't you heard about it?
All the kids are doing it.
It's really cool.
You should check it out.
She's surfing over already.
And that is it for today's Daily Source Code.
Going into a weekend where I'll be plenty busy.
We've got lots of pot-show stuff going on, I remember I'm on the dual-life cycle right now.
We start a whole new day around 4 in the afternoon.
So I'm not complaining about it.
If I haven't mentioned this before, let me say it again, I love doing this stuff.
This is this the dream or what?
Hang out, get up, don't even shave, just crawl behind the console, do a little show, always want
to work with computers and combine it all the way.
And finally got my wish, so dig in it.
Hey, send me your promo.
So I can play them on the show, we can get them on the serious satellite radio, and soon
we can also start promoting those on the podshow.com homepage, submit at podshow.com for all
your promos.
And feedback, of course, is always welcome out of Maccurry.com.
Please do not attach an MP3, stick it up on a server somewhere.
Give it a real name, put some real MP3 tags in there, so that it works in my player,
and I know what the hell is going on, I don't have a grip notes everywhere, and also
is really handy for moving it through our system, our promotions engine, if you will.
www.curry.com is my weblog, for comments.
Of course, daily source code.com for the podcast feed, I'll be back on Monday, unless
Patricia and I do something over the weekend, it's Christina's birthday on Saturday, she
turns 15, so we'll be having a party, talk to you on everybody, bye-bye.