Delta Shira Charley
2 8 9
We here at Legal Legal Television
Bring you exclusive live coverage
of the man versus Adam Curry trial.
We take you now to the courtroom.
Hey Lars, for the Apple Church,
on a handgun.
This is federal court case
1 0 0 0 0 9
And the charge is against the defendant.
Adam Curry is lack of respect for music establishment.
All those Mr. Clay, please.
Your honor, my name is envy,
and I am defending Mr. Curry.
He plays guilty to being correct in his opinion
of the music established
and not guilty for expressing those feelings.
You're honor, we find Mr. Curry to be a disruptive force
to the well-established music industry
and as the charges read,
very disrespectful indeed.
We find Mr. Curry to be a disruptive force
to the well-established music industry
and as the charges read,
very disrespectful indeed.
We'd play for the court the following evidence.
The issue of copyrights that you sign over to them
or assign them,
and we heard about the Dutch Buma Stemera.
We heard about the German Gema,
and now you're not going to believe this.
This is exactly what I was,
I joked about this happening.
I've choked about it.
Okay, so essentially what is happening here
with the European rights organizations
and so far we know it's the same.
Also, it's for the Dutch, the Germans, and the French.
When you sign up with their version of Ask Had BMI,
you are not allowed to give away any other rights to anyone.
So you cannot say to a podcaster,
hey, go ahead, take my stuff
and go and play it for free.
That will be a breach of your contract
with that rights organization.
It's like it's a conundrum, I guess.
So I feel that we need to address this issue.
I'm not quite sure.
Is there one central organization?
I didn't find it.
I didn't find that it works across all of these rights organizations.
But this is wrong.
I mean, if it's your property,
then you should be able to change that license
however you want.
I think it is a constitutional right
of these organizations to be the only one to collect
or not collect, I guess.
On artists' copyright royalties.
It's not just what it is.
And with that, you're on a...
the prosecution rests.
Well, what does the defense have to say to that?
Your honor?
The fact of the matter is...
the truth hurts.
In addition, the words spoken by Mr. Curry simply reflect
the feelings of thousands of podcasters
and millions of listeners across the planet.
I, your honor, and both a podcaster
and a listener of podcasters.
I serve producer podcasters
and in bedtime stories my kids love
and begin listening to podcasters
and then producing my podcasters
do in part to the hard work by the podfather
Adam Curry.
I for one agree with Mr. Curry
and believe thousands and thousands of people
feel the same way.
Whatever, that number is growing every day, your honor.
The ground swell has just begun.
The tipping point is near.
Your honor, do you want to always be known as the judge
that failed to support podcasting?
I do not think so.
Your honor, I employ you to listen to my podcasters
bedtime stories my kids love in items.
And your honor, in closing,
I am speaking for Mr. Curry
and thousands of podcasters across the world.
Get off our back.
We are not going away.
And with that, your honor, the defense rests.
I am overwhelmed by the compelling evidence
presented.
Mr. Curry is obviously disrespectful
to the established music industry.
Whatever, in light of the growing audience
and the obvious following of Adam Curry's opinions
indicated by the swelling number of podcasters,
both listeners and producers,
I find Mr. Curry, my guilty.
60 million dollars worth of airplane
strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
I'm just kidding.
And it's Wednesday.
Hello, everybody.
Finally, after weeks of bitching,
we've got one.
A Hanukkah holiday pod save music track.
Good morning.
Hanukkah, I know it's going to be all right.
Everyone's together tonight.
Feeling good, it's Hanukkah.
Two candles left.
The holidays just begun.
We're in for lots of fun.
The time has come, it's Hanukkah.
Sun and sun.
Your home is fast as it can.
Put the oil into the ground.
It's a common joy.
Why do you call?
As we are not good friends.
It's true.
Rock up here.
For the wind from our town.
It's nice to have them around.
Even though he's weird, it's Hanukkah.
Sailors cool.
But Hanukkah hares the man.
So come and join our long good plan.
We'll save you and play this Hanukkah.
Sun and sun.
Your home is fast as it can.
Put the oil into the ground.
It's a common joy.
Rock up here.
Sun and sun.
Your home is fast as it can.
Put the oil into the ground.
It's a common joy.
Rock up here.
Sun and sun.
All right.
Enough people sent me that one.
Thank you very much from the pod save music network.
The very first holiday Hanukkah song.
I'm sure we're more to follow.
We missed Ramadan, but maybe next year we'll catch up on that.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
Welcome to the daily source code.
I'm back in the studio at the Curry Cottage in Gilford, United Kingdom.
Here for another week or so before I head off to San Francisco.
One more time before Christmas.
For a number of things.
Man, man, man, man, man.
It's been so busy last night.
I had a really, a lot of seconds.
Let me just make sure.
I found this.
I think it's better.
It's a little bit better.
I got to work on this.
I didn't sleep very well last night for a number of reasons.
The first is that yesterday was another one of those 16 hour days where, you know, I was,
I, you know, I get up.
Yesterday we did the cruiser cast and around four o'clock.
That's when San Francisco wakes up.
Everyone was back from a long holiday.
Thanksgiving weekend.
And lots of calls.
And actually, I got really excited about some of the conversations we had yesterday.
We had everybody in the office on it.
And I was on it.
I call in on a conference call or Skype.
Sometimes I do video depending on where, however, you know, we have multiple ways of connecting.
And we had everybody.
We had software engineers.
We had designers.
We had promotion marketing, sales, accounting, controller, finance, operations.
And of course, what we're going through is the couple of initiatives, the audition, which
will be hearing more about very soon.
The podcast, the Pod Show podcast, delivery network, which we're also going to tell you about
very soon.
I mean, really in detail, we'll unleash some announcements about that.
Yes, damn announcements coming.
And really how everything all kind of fits together.
And how podcasters who are interested can grow their audience.
And eventually with some luck and a lot of hard work, elbow grease, quit your day job.
But that wasn't the main reason for my unrest, just because of the excitement and, you know,
my brain still spinning by the time it hit the pillow.
I just kept on going and going.
But I'm not quite sure.
I tried to explain to Patricia this morning.
Actually, the minute I woke up, I said, oh, Matt is sleep very well.
And here's why.
And she understood it very well.
It has to do with negativity and positivity.
It's a rollercoaster ride that I witnessed every single day online.
There's something about the human nature.
And I'm not quite sure what it is, but it is without a doubt human nature.
First of all, everybody lives in their own reality.
I have my reality.
This moment, my reality is completely different from yours.
You're in a different place.
You're in a different head space.
You're thinking of different things.
And by the way, you are the center of the universe of your universe.
And I'm the center of my universe.
And when these universes start to collide, that's when interesting things happen.
And one of the most interesting things that happens with this incredible growth of communications that we've seen
is that people who rise to the top get kicked down.
Or there's people ready to kick them down or drag them down.
There's other people who are willing to push them back up based upon that dragging down.
That's why I say this roller coaster.
It's almost like a yo-yo effect.
You can see great examples of this, for example, on podcastali.com in the forums where people are talking about pod show.
You can see this happening with Google now.
Remember Google?
Remember when it was the coolest shit and we loved it and it was fantastic.
And these guys were finally doing the right thing.
Well, now it seems if you listen to the noise and the signal to noise ratio or something you've got to look out for.
It seems that Google's evil, all of a sudden, particularly the people who said they would do no evil.
And when that's kind of baseless, most of this is baseless, but it's based upon someone else's reality of the situation.
And that's how you read an article, how stories told to you, how you read an article is different from how it's written.
There are all these things that kind of fit together.
And one thing that Patricia and I really learned when we moved to the Netherlands and just before the millennium, 1999, the end of the year,
is that this is really propelled.
And it is a direct result, I think, of so many people being able to have their voice heard, which is great.
I mean, I love that.
But it comes somewhere, this is what Patricia's take on it.
And I should get her in here to talk about that. Maybe we'll do that tomorrow, we'll have a broader discussion.
I'm just kind of brain farting at the moment.
It's not necessarily people who spew negativity or flame.
There's lots of people like comic strip blogger on thecurry.com comments, the same deal.
I think that if someone is unhappy about their own universe, regardless of what that problem is,
and you see someone else who apparently is happy, then there's this automatic humor.
I do it too, by the way, everyone does this.
You want to say, ah, you know, screw them and you just lash out at somebody.
And having been a known figure for a long time, I've learned to deal with this.
But it has gotten really, really intense, which means a couple things to me.
The first one is we're doing something really good because people are taking notice.
And they're questioning and they're coming up with a lot of conspiracy theories, literally, which is pretty funny to read through.
But just so you know, when you say something in your podcast or write something on your weblog or something's written in an article or, you know, if you send an email, it does hurt.
I mean, it really does, which is, which, of course, is my problem. I let things affect me.
And of course, if someone writes something really nice, then it feels really good.
But the frequency of that is just, it's, the frequency is going up.
So the roller coaster is really, it's vibrating almost.
And this is why you, I think, why you see celebrities, particularly new celebrities, people who burst onto the scene.
They get the same thing and they get it predominantly from newspapers and magazines and entertainment tonight and all these entertainment based shows and stuff on the internet and pictures.
That's why you see them freak out.
You see them.
I've rock rock roll stars used to trash hotel rooms.
And I believe it is for this very reason for this, this, this, this weird clashing of universes and positivity and negativity vibrating amongst
them all the time. It's, it's a very weird sensation.
And as I said, I've been in the public eye since I was 19, I still have not gotten used to it.
But it also has gotten progressively, the frequency has increased progressively over the years with the amount of communications that we have.
And by the way, you know, let's not, let's not forget that only 10 years ago, no one knew what a fucking cell phone was almost.
You know, this was a luxury item that maybe you had in your car.
You got a card and a cell phone, you got a car phone, text messaging.
All of these things combined.
And yeah, I don't know.
If you have any thoughts about that, I mean, it's, it's got to be something much larger.
It is a part of human nature. I'm not quite sure what it is.
And I don't take it, you know, well, I do take it personally, but I understand.
I do understand where people are coming from.
But I think that in general, everyone is a nice person.
I think probably another part that.
That had to do with my unrestfulness was my brain processing this fantastic book that I read called God's debris.
It's written by Douglas Adams, who is the Gilbert guy.
It's actually available for free on the internet.
You can buy a hardbound copy, but he put it out basically in a kind of open source.
Maybe, I don't know if he has creative commas on it, but it's, it's a fantastic book.
It's short. It's a great read. Tom Schuiting, who maintains the fabulous Korean vaninkle archive.
A big archive, a big part of my professional life sent me that.
And I was just totally blown away by the concept in that book.
And maybe that has something to do with.
And I don't, I don't really want to get into explaining what the book is about.
But maybe that is something to do with this reverberation of positive and negative energy.
And perhaps we need the positive and negative energy.
Maybe that's the, the great equalizer.
Maybe it's something that's necessary.
I don't know. And of course, there was also the foxes who were out in drove last night,
rummaging through the trash.
God, that makes so much noise.
You're supposed to put your bags out in the morning, which we do.
But someone put their trash out last night.
And then the foxes who, of course, are coming closer to civilization every single day.
So I'm going to go through the trash and make an all kinds of noise.
But anyway, so I'm awake though.
I'm feeling pretty good.
I want to thank everybody, by the way, who's participating and contributing to the show notes.
You can always find the show notes.
I link to the show notes from from the podcast at dailysourcecode.com.
It's great because people are now actually embellishing and coming up with their own words as to what's being discussed in the show.
For instance, yesterday, 21 minutes, 55 seconds.
Adam comments that the concept of touchscreen navigation is an odd concept for a pilot.
Since as a pilot, you never touch your instruments.
That would be your navigation instruments.
Since you'll get oily residue on them.
And then you can't read them at night.
And you'd die in a fiery crash.
So I obviously didn't add the fiery crash part.
But that showed up in the show notes.
That was a nice touch.
Here's another one.
So he's going to start the show in the parking lot outside of combat.
And no, the cable he bought wasn't one of those packages.
You can't open without a plasma torch.
I think I said scissors, but I like the embellishment.
It really works.
And thanks again to everybody who was contributing to the show notes.
I think it's a fantastic.
You know, Michael show note.
I'll call him that.
Mike show note.
I believe he's trying to start kind of a business or a service for podcasts.
I support that holy fully.
And I think it's fantastic using a wiki for show notes.
I'm really, really digging it.
A little dismayed actually.
I saw once in a while I checked in on the wiki wiki pedia.
And I look in podcasting.
Dave and I have almost been written out.
It's all these other people who have successfully created podcasting.
And I congratulate you for doing that.
Thank you very much.
I had a great slow morning though.
Oh, check out the Potio music rewind episode number 10 is out.
Kick and ass as always.
What a fantastic show.
Give that a listen if you have a chance.
Hey Adam.
It's Swippy from Skepticality.
Hey Swopster.
I've been catching up on back shows sitting at a borders in downtown Atlanta.
Sucking up the coffee and the Wi-Fi while there.
Because it rehabbed during the day.
And low and behold, I hear you talking about my buddy Slaw.
And this new Christmas song.
It just so happens that our friend,
and musician George Rabb, just finished recording his fifth CD at Slaw's B Sharp Studios
in Historia, New York.
And to celebrate the release of the CD entitled,
in Terabang, George held a concert at which Slaw appeared and also performed.
Derek and I were supposed to be there.
But since we couldn't make it, George sent us some pictures.
One of it includes Slaw.
I thought you might enjoy seeing it.
George also plays drums on the Christmas song
and contributed some backing vocals as well.
George says he still gets traffic on his site
and sails of his CDs from the podcast he did with us.
And that was way back in the summer.
So pot safe music is definitely good for artists.
And it's good for podcasting too.
Skepticality ended up in someone's liner notes.
How cool is that?
Yeah.
See you Adam.
All right, Swopie.
Thank you.
Say hi to Derek for me, please.
Please hope everything's going well.
And good to hear your voice again.
Here on the Daily Source Code.
So today I will finally get it done.
Let's go to Xmas.podshow.com.
Kicks off today so that by tomorrow the first of December
you'll have a new Christmas song every day
right on your computer.
Hey Adam, this is Joe.
This is sofa coaches.
I wanted to send you a promo this week.
But when I sat down with the other sofa coaches
and tried to put together some ideas,
things got a little out of control.
Take a listen and see what happened.
Do you think we should tell them it's only an hour long?
Absolutely.
Well, we go a little over an hour.
Yeah.
I mean, you can't say what how long we're going to do every time.
Most of the time we shoot for 60 minutes.
Absolutely.
Yeah, but we always squeeze at least 10,
15 minutes of going material into that hour.
The most important thing they should know what a sofa coach
actually is.
I don't get it because we don't sit on a sofa
and none of us are coaches.
So what's the story here?
Well, we are.
We're slots that know everything.
We're so precodious because we didn't know anything after the fact.
Uh, we do know everything.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
You know, another good point to bring up about the show
is that it's audio only.
And there's no video feed.
So nobody has to worry about what the original is.
Yeah.
We don't have a shot.
Then that's for sure.
We all got faces for radio.
Speak for yourself.
By the way, is there any music on this show?
Every once in a while, we play some pot-safe music.
Yeah.
But where do we do?
Who cares about the music?
We're sports shows.
All there you have it at them.
That's about how things go when we talk about sports, too.
So be sure to tune in.
You can find this in the iTunes music store.
Just search for sofa coaches.
Or you can go to our website.
Listen.
True is not false.com.
Adam, please give us a little move.
Pot show.
No one does chicken like Pot show.
Hey Adam.
It's a long time listener of yours.
I go back almost to the very beginning.
I know how you occasionally become irritated with lawyers from time to time.
Don't deny it.
I know it's true and I don't blame you.
It's a lawyer myself.
I too become frustrated with lawyers from time to time.
In fact, it's how I spend almost every single day.
You can probably guess the way I've chosen to work out my frustrations with a legal profession.
That's right.
With a podcast.
The legal underground podcast, which I started in January 2005.
With a short test episode that you ended up playing in full on your show.
Thanks for that.
Now here we are almost a year later.
And I thought it was a good time to check back in and say I'm still out here in the pot of sphere going strong.
Our friends shows every week or two that are either short form called law-related things that suck.
Or a slightly longer form in which I discuss legal news and a little politics.
And in a reverent way that's probably going to have the lawyer police knocking on my door very soon.
Your thing must lawyers wouldn't know a podcast from.
I don't know.
They're own cold hearts.
So to conclude, it's the legal underground podcast.
You'll find the feed at my weblog.
Evan Shafers, legal underground at www.legalunderground.com.
Meanwhile, Adam, keep up the great work at the pod safe music network and all your other various projects.
You know, with all you've got going on, you're a walking full-time employment act for lawyers.
Would it be wrong of me to thank you from the entire profession?
Well, thank you, Adam.
And if you listen to my show, thanks for tuning in.
Adam Curry Rocks.
Well, actually, in Brazil, Adam Curry Sambas.
Easy.
All castors are connected to the daily source code source code.
I so want to go to Brazil.
It's not funny.
I've been to a lot of countries, a lot of continents, a lot of places.
I've been very, very fortunate that way.
Never to South America, though.
I definitely want to come to Brazil.
So that is in the medium-term planning.
And I know that there's a huge podcast community cropping up there.
I'd love to learn more about it.
So how do you, Brazil?
How are you doing?
Comersta.
Yeah.
I used to know some Portuguese, which is what they speak in Brazil.
No more.
Hey, for those of you who are new to the daily source code,
you may have heard of the sound-vertising experiment.
This is where I anchor your thoughts to a certain sound
or visual and anchor a thought to it.
So what actually started off kind of as an accident,
every single time I burped.
Senseiho would come into your mind.
Then we moved on to another trick, which I'll do it right now,
just in case your brand knew.
If you already know what I'm about to do, then close your eyes and
I don't think it'll work either.
Whatever you're doing right now, look at a point where you are.
It's maybe a house, maybe a tree, maybe a sign.
It could be the current front of you.
It could be a person.
Now look at that object, Senseiho.
So the concept is, whenever you see that object,
in fact whenever you even think of that object,
you'll think of Senseiho.
It works.
I think everyone who was participated in this willingly or unwillingly
knows that this sound-vertising, this anchoring, this Vulcan mind trick,
actually does work.
But it has no real benefit, particularly not to me in the Senseiho case
because Senseiho is not paying me for that.
Now of course I don't mind doing the experiment,
but today I received an email that completely twisted my mind
backwards about this and I really love this.
I can't believe I didn't come up with this.
So this is from Mark Zeta who says,
Hey Adam, Senseiho ads are airing here in Australia as well.
So Senseiho now is kicking up their advertising.
They're kicking it up.
It's in the UK, it's in the US.
It's of course the Netherlands where it comes from.
It's in Australia.
And Mark says, when I saw it, the first thing I thought of
was the Daily Source Code.
I was expecting either character in the ad to do your trademarks
and say, oh, burp.
I think the sound-vertising could go a long way.
Thanks for your show.
I'm loving every episode of it.
Mark, okay.
So all of a sudden like,
No, this is fantastic.
This is it.
I am now utilizing the ad budget of Senseiho
to promote the Daily Source Code.
How freaking cool is that?
And the cool thing is everybody can do it.
So pick a product or pick a service or something
that's being advertised very, very heavily on television and radio.
Anchor your listeners to it.
And then every single time they hear or see that
advertisement, they won't be able to help themselves
but think about your podcast.
How cool is that?
Tell me if it works.
Happy freaking holidays Senseiho.
This is Natalie Brown,
wishing the Daily Source Code listeners a safe and happy holiday season.
This is Chris from the Financial Aid podcast.
Wishing you a safe, happy, and financially responsible holiday season.
This is us online at financialadpodcast.com
for money saving tips this season.
Happy holidays, everyone.
So by tomorrow, make sure that
a special greeting from the Go and Deep podcast
I'm the kid along with Mr. Clean.
And we'd like to wish you and yours a very happy holiday.
Oh, no, no, man. You can't say happy holidays.
Why not? Why can't I say holidays?
Because it's happy, camel to days.
Yes, that's right.
We can't say Christmas.
We can't say holidays.
We can't say how to go.
We can't say quansica.
We've changed it to happy camel to a day.
And we hope everybody has a happy camel to a day.
To you and yours.
From Go and Deep with Get in Clean.
Visit the website at www.godeepwith.us.
And have a happy new year.
Yeah, man.
New snow angels rock.
So by tomorrow, make sure you subscribe to the feed at xmus.podshow.com.
So that every single day will be a happy camel to a day for you.
For the pod save music network, this is Carmen Tyler.
Pick this one up from accident hash.
I'll be there on camel to a day.
Oh, it's Christmas time again.
How I miss you.
I wish I hadn't been so far away.
I'll be coming home.
How my heart so longs to see your face.
You'll take care of us reminding me of lovers with truth.
So why your patiently waiting to remember this.
I'll be there.
Don't see us.
I'm sorry.
I'll be there.
I'll be there in your heart.
Oh Christmas day.
How I love this time of year.
Joy and laughter.
The holidays are here.
And I know.
As this season now begins.
You'll see lovers underneath the mistletoe.
I ought to thank you for having me on.
Children snuggle in the bed.
I waiting for the time.
To hear Santa's reindeer from their window right outside.
I'll be there.
Though it seems I'm so far away.
I'll be there in your heart.
Oh Christmas day.
So here's to you on this holiday.
May your every wish come true.
You and far away.
My heart will be with you.
I'll be there.
Oh I'll be there.
Though it seems I'm so far away.
I'll be there.
I'll be there in your heart.
Oh Christmas day.
Is it possible?
I'm falling in love again.
Carmen Tyler.
What a beautiful voice.
I'll be there in Christmas day.
And my apologies for the pilot error midstream there.
But we landed safely.
We walked away from the airplanes and that constitutes a good landing.
Apologize.
Hey, speaking.
Of course, it's from the podcast music network.
Potset music.
Yep, not best.
The podcast music network.
The podcast music network dot com.
Mike O'Leary sent a wonderful email.
Adam, I was checking out clips of the songs on the candy butcher's album.
Hang on.
Mike in iTunes in the music store after hearing what to do with Michael on your podcast.
Love the song.
Anyway, in the top right corner is a list that says listeners also bought.
That's the recommendation engine.
Look at what's listed and see the power that DSE has to persuade and influence not only one,
but a multitude of musical talents.
Brother love and the list of these bitties are listed right there with the candy butchers in one swoop.
So the question I have now is when does the Adam Craig recommends playlists go up on the iTunes page?
That's interesting idea.
Actually it's a damn good idea.
Hey, let's call the iTunes guys about that.
But that is proof.
That is absolutely proof.
So listening to a podcast music on the podcast actually creates sales.
Gee, what a concept.
I love it.
Time to wrap up the,
Emma the Logitech MM50 naming contest that we'd be doing for the last week or so.
Let me see.
First one is an audio contest.
So Adam Jason San Diego.
You said you wanted audio comments on the same MM50 instead of the emails.
So I'm going to stop writing you the 10 or 15 a day that I've been sending you.
Hope you need read them on the air.
So I'm going to just give you some ideas I've been thinking about bouncing up the wall.
See what sticks.
You know, playing that little game.
MM50.
Let's see.
Music maker.
Music box.
Music.
Music with two ends.
How about the,
My personal favorite.
The eye match with two ends.
So it's image not to be confused with eye match.
Or we could just call it the 501.
Any of you.
Give me a call.
We'll do lunch.
Yeah.
Call my people.
Okay.
Well, yeah.
Thank you for the feedback.
No, I think the winner and it was really close because I really like the port of
Potty, the port iPod.
I thought that was good, but it may not be.
I don't know.
It's a great name, but maybe not quite as commercial because there already is a port of
Potty, and that could create all kinds of problems.
But I think Greg Milligan sent in a really good one.
Greg is from Coventry, which I, yeah, presumed to be the UK.
Yeah, Coventry.
And he says, perhaps the MM50 should be referred to as the sound slab.
I like that.
The sound slab.
That sounds, that's nothing to do with MM50, but I do like it is.
It's a slab of sound.
So Greg, congratulations.
Send me your address.
I will send you an MM50.
It might even be my personal one.
I hope we have another one left.
Everyone like walked off with these, the minute they were in the office.
Okay.
What you heard briefly during Carmen Tyler's wonderful Christmas song was some feedback,
which is very long.
I'm not going to play all of it from Eric.
And he has something interesting to say.
It's about feed, hijacking.
So if you're a podcast or if you have an RSS feed at all, pay attention to what he's saying here.
And I'll interject here and there and I don't think I'll get to the whole thing.
But listen to what he says about feed, hijacking.
Hi Adam.
Thank you for having me on the show.
I really appreciate getting the chance to talk to some of your listeners about what I regard as a tremendous threat to the whole podcasting infrastructure.
My name is Eric Marcus and for a bit more than a year now, I've been doing my podcast Eric Steiner.
At the time that I started, there were fewer than 50 podcasts available.
And my show was not only the first one to tackle the subjects of veganism and animal rights.
It was also the first podcast to talk about food, recipes and cooking.
Now, over the past year, Eric Steiner has grown steadily more popular.
When I started out, each show drew only about 100 listeners.
But by last month, my audience had grown to about 1,500 people per show.
Now, this is not a Howard Stern sized audience clearly.
It's not even a dawn and drew type audience.
But Eric Steiner does appeal to a niche audience.
And I think that if I can do a show that reaches more than 1,000 people,
interested in vegan eating and farm animal protection, that's a fantastic use of my time.
Oh, by the way, I just want to interject.
I think if you have more than 1,000 that you can probably start to make money on that if you're interested.
People have emailed me to tell me they've become vegan as a direct result of listening to my show.
I even had one guy right and tell me he bought an iPod specifically,
so he could listen to my show during his drive to work.
This past month with my audience creeping up toward 2,000 listeners per show,
I thought I was ideally positioned for further growth.
I figured that if I kept working hard to produce a quality show,
5,000 listeners was just around the corner.
Instead, everything I spent this past year working on has suddenly collapsed.
My RSS feed has been hijacked by someone I've never met or even heard of,
and every single one of my subscribers through iTunes has been cut off.
In consequence, my audience has dropped overnight by 75%.
Now, a lot of people know what domain hijacking is,
but even as a podcaster, I'd never heard of RSS hijacking until it happened to me.
As I'm about to explain, RSS hijacking involves a different and much simpler technique than domain hijacking.
See, not only is RSS hijacking easy to do,
it also doesn't involve the overacts of law breaking that usually need to occur in order to hijack a domain.
I personally regard RSS hijacking as the greatest threat that the podcaster community has encountered to date.
So let me explain how I discovered that my podcast feed was hijacked,
and why I think RSS hijacking is so insidious.
A couple of months ago, I read on slash dot that Yahoo had released a new podcast search engine at podcast.yahoo.com.
I went to that site and was pleased to see that Eric Steiner already had a listing.
But on this listing, I noticed that the RSS feed listed for my show was not hosted by my website vegan.com,
but instead was hosted by some website I'd never even heard of called podkeyword.com.
Now, what happened was obvious.
And random guy up there owning the podkeyword.com domain had created an RSS feed on his site
and pointed it to my RSS feed.
And somehow Yahoo had picked up his RSS feed instead of my own
and inserted it into its directory listing for my show.
Now, I'm not the most technically savvy person you'll ever meet,
but I could immediately recognize the danger here.
Over time, more and more Yahoo users would subscribe to my show using an RSS feed that belonged not to me,
but to a third party.
Now, I'm from New York and perhaps overly suspicious about people's motives,
but I could see it at glance that this feed hijacking had extortion written all over it.
In getting his URL for my podcast, carried by Yahoo's directory,
the owner of podkeyword.com was establishing himself as the gatekeeper who could control all traffic to my show
from listeners who were subscribed through Yahoo.
Now, this is really interesting.
This is rampant.
This is happening all over the place.
If you register with audio, if you register with any multitude of directories,
perhaps it is even true with podcast, Ali.
I'm not sure.
We'll have to look at that.
You know, this claim your feed shit that I see everywhere, where you claim your feed,
so then you get a new feed, like an audio feed.
These are where this is where it goes wrong,
is that these things get exactly what happened to Eric here is that that feed got sucked in by Yahoo
and Yahoo for all intents and purposes today.
That's my feed.
You know, that's the right feed, no problem.
I don't think there's any malicious intent here, but it is a problem.
This, by the way, is the same thing that feed burner does.
You know, yes, feed burner is great.
Feed burner has a lot of benefits.
It's very easy to use, but if feed burner crops out, if feed burner decides whatever they decide,
they effectively, you know, have control over your RSS feed.
iTunes does the exact same thing.
Ladies and gentlemen, they also, in effect, hijack your feed and then they create their own special feed,
so you have to keep coming back to them and you don't get it directly from the source.
And we all know what the issues are there.
If iTunes messes up, well, caching your RSS feed, then your podcast doesn't download for,
sometimes for four hours.
So this is not the way to do it, and I think that we've known this,
the people in the RSS space have known this.
It's a bad way to do things.
The best way to do this is to register a domain name.
A domain name that you can then point anywhere you want.
So you should be able to put in a redirect.
So it would be atomspodcast.com slash RSS.xml,
and you should be able to redirect that anywhere you want,
so that if you wake up one morning and decide that you're not happy with,
with your infrastructure, all you have to do is just change a couple of parameters,
and everyone will stay subscribed.
You've really got to look into getting a domain name.
You don't take that lightly.
It's very, very, very important.
Erick's comment goes on for another four or five minutes,
but I think it's very clear what's happening here.
And I suggest that you look at getting a domain name,
and redirecting to the infrastructure that you're using.
And of course, when the pod show podcast delivery network comes out,
we'll have those options built right in for.
Hi Adam, this is James from JamesB.com.
Here in Utah, in the US, we have a slightly different vernacular
to express ourselves when we're mad,
allowing me to demonstrate.
I'm mad as heck, and I want to quit my fetching day job.
I'm bored out of my freaking skull with it.
Dang!
What the flip do I have to do, gosh darn it?
Oh boy, if my mother could hear me now.
If you thought of Napoleon Dynamite when you heard that,
let me state for the record that my mother was from the west side of Prestonite home.
So Adam, don't forget about us, poor Utah fellows,
that never learned how to properly work blue.
This is James from JamesB.com, Navalcast,
and my new podcast, face the music, saying,
God, I can't wait to quit my day job.
Hey there, my name's Krantz.
You can find me at a couple of different places,
namely, frikogonvenus.com.
The Sunday fun message that was downloaded
into my ears on Sunday,
had me rolling.
But it is also very, very true.
The reason I spend most of my time listening to podcasts
and ignoring the radio,
and even television really,
is because it's a bunch of shit.
I'm tired of hearing the same song every two hours,
I'm tired of, and I am mad.
I am mad.
I'm a human being Goddamn,
and in my life has value,
and I'm mad as hell!
And I want to quit my day job!
I'm mad as hell,
and I want to quit my day job when I quit.
We all know the atomic bomb is very dangerous.
Now, we must be ready for a new danger.
Hey, I'm Jack Elias from the Get Jack podcast.
Get Jack.Honomus.com,
and I'll spell it out for medically in a minute.
Um, God, you know, you're teasing us now.
And we want to quit our jobs.
Some of us actually,
my wife says that I need to keep working at my job
until such time that this pays more.
Which is fine.
I totally agree with that,
but hey, you know,
I care it.
A tidbit, a taste.
I hint.
Something.
Please?
Get Jack.Honomus.com
That's hotel alpha,
alpha,
Sierra,
dot com.
Kind of like Christmas and on,
I got all rolled into one.
Konnichiwa, Adam Curryson.
I'm Terrence Young from the Kobe beef show
at www.cobey-beef.blogspot.com.
Since the music industry won't let us have
our hit test and backtracks podcasts,
how about a quiz using material
they can't control the Japanese language?
I know you know you're Dutch,
but how's your Japanese, Adam?
A while back,
I sent you a promo,
which featured the word Botakuni,
which means Ribbon.
I hope you remember.
Yeah.
They agree at least.
Now it's time to learn some new words.
The game is simple.
My trustee,
imaginary cow sidekick,
Teibontaro,
will give you a practical Japanese word.
Three answers to choose from,
and you guess the answer.
Take it away, Teibong.
It's...
Let's guess Japanese.
Hi.
Today word,
Kurija.
Kurija is...
A.
Rare Japanese glam found in the Japan Sea.
B.
City on Southern Island of Kyushu.
C.
Nickname for Love button.
Found in another region of every woman.
I'm going to go for sea.
I'm not bad.
I know that hard one.
But I hope you guess right.
I hope you guess sea.
I'm going to go for love button.
Yes.
Kurija is Japanese slang.
Floor Clitoris.
Kuriya is shockening of work.
Kitoris.
Browns.
Kuri, Dori, Su.
In Japanese.
And John is invomer ending.
Usually added to people name.
So next time,
you are love snorkeling with Patricia.
You got affectionately caught her.
Love button.
Kurija.
You try now add-on.
Yeah.
Very good.
Hope you enjoyed that add-on.
I know it's nowhere near as polished as the hit test.
But I hope at least you got a chuckle.
And a new word to use with Patricia.
Kurija.
A regular new hongo time lessons.
And my rants about life in Japan.
Please check out the Kobe beef show.
At www.kobei-beef.blogspot.com.
Also, Dear Pod Showgun.
Tibon and I are definitely excited about the audition
and getting hooked up with the Pod Show.
So we'll be back soon.
With another additional.
What is it, Tibon?
Nyongo quiz time.
Kurija.
That's right.
All right.
See you again.
Mata ne.
All right.
Bye bye.
And I'll see you guys tomorrow right here on the source code.
Bye.