Good morning, Adam, Darrell's Chanderow here from blindaccessjournal.com.
Hey, just listen to DSC number two, nine, or one, and notice the missing introductory
heading for the podcast and the explanation as to why you may that change.
I sincerely hope that you will change it back.
I am a blind podcaster and blind listener, and I really, really, really miss that heading.
Verbaly telling me, as I come to your podcast, what, in fact, it is.
Many of us, myself included, formatted the beginning of our shows,
by using DSC as a model, thus the show title and the show number, and really, please,
do not stop that, I'm not able to simply upgrade my eyes to working models, and so upgrading
from a shuffle from an iPod shuffle to something else would not help a blind listener.
Also, other reasons, you know, a lot of people listen to these podcasts while
commuting to work in their cars, wouldn't want to have an accident because somebody was
messing around with their MP3 player looking at it to see which podcast they're listening to,
while the same time trying to drive, so a lot of things to consider there, please, please, please,
do go back to Delta Sierra Charlie, do 9 or 2, and so on and so forth, please, please don't,
don't stop, don't stop doing that, okay, please do us a favor there. Thank you,
keep up the great work, this is Dale Shandra with blindaxisjournal.com, bye bye.
You took it from me, but it's all right, yeah, well, you took it from me, and I'm feeling bad,
but it's all right, oh, oh, yeah, well, you love that you give, yeah girl,
my goodbye, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, this is our home, oh, oh, and, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
When I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and
When I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I am a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I want to be a fucking stone and when I grow up I am a fucking stone and when I grow up I am a fucking stone and when I grow up I am a fucking stone and when I grow up I am a fucking stone and when I grow up I am a fucking stone and when I grow up I am a fucking stone and when I grow up I am a fucking stone and when I grow up I am a fucking stone and when I grow up I am a fucking stone and when I grow up exercise exercise exercise exercise exercise exercise exercise exercise exercise exercise exercise
everybody how you doing welcome it's daily source code it is episode number
two ninety two and today is Tuesday just got back from London town with my
bride thanks to I was it I forget it was a Darren was a Darrell oh man oh
and I have to go check it again the morning at him Darrell Chandler here
Darrell alright Darrell got a couple more comments about the voice tags pretty
much similar to what you just heard oh no tags it's not about iPod shuffle
datum it's about not needing to look at the display whether you're in a car or
just jogging it's much better to hear it like it's great because you can do
something else while getting that information please put the tags back thanks
says grug okay gotcha check mark I just thought I'd change something makes
sound different but now that I think of it it really is kind of important I
guess if you're driving doing other stuff so we had a really good time in
in London we left the early this morning all 10th already that's pretty early
for us to be dressed in out the door outside of need taking Christina to school
of course yeah I get up and I'm ready to go alright no no work needed it was really nice
we took the train to Waterloo Station Patricia and then we hopped in a cab
person went to herids oh man is that place amazing or water Christmas it's just
it's a it's paradise it's beautiful and there's no mad Christmas rush yet I mean I
have not been in London the week before Christmas but it seemed like everyone's kind of
chilling out a lot of stuff was already sold out though people are doing Christmas shopping
early this year in at least at herids then we went over to bond street region street
Oxford street no region street and bond street and new bond street and James street
well we walked all over the place and I really I'm not looking for anything I said hey
if we happen to be in region street we might want to stop in the apple store but somehow Patricia
successfully steered us away from that that of course would be my version of porn man I witnessed
a lot of women porn today just uddles of bags and and bling and shoes and of course the new
thing is these high really tight calf you know boots that go around your calf really tight and
and I said to Patricia I said dude this is porn this is just this women's porn this is what it is
it's just amazing all the fragrances and hadn't been in department store with her in a long time
at least not one where I kind of let her loose and just tagged along behind it was nice you know
I had a nice little buzz going so I'm just tripping along and it was really it was pretty cool it was
good to be in the city just good to get out and good to be alone the two of us just Patricia me
and the blackberry yesterday there was news all over the place even the BBC reported about it
about this outfit called the association of independent I think it's musicians they call it aane
which I think is kind of unfortunate because that in my mind is associated with ale instant messenger
um here it is the association of independent music is selling six month worldwide licensed deals
for its members music to be used on download radio programs great guys the headline is
indie music available to podcasts so I've been I've been watching their site diligently up until the
time that I started doing the show today there've been no official announcement on on the aim website
which is indie music dot com but they are really you know I it's it feels a little fishy to me you know
they they pop the news the BBC publishes everything except of course exact details because it will
be a four pay license and as the as this BBC story says at least and it will also be a limited time
license so I don't know what that means I mean we have to delete the show after six months how much will
it cost I'm all for for paying to play you know that's absolutely you know problem some of the
artists included our block party stereophonics the white stripes the strokes basement jacks Paul
Weller Arctic Monkeys I recognize at least three of those names Richard Thompson Billy Bragg
so that would be very cool but I I really would like to see the details and I'm a little
disappointed that you know they have this heat going and people were talking about it for a second
there and and there's you know they haven't released the entire license I have a feeling that
maybe someone talked a little bit before they were ready to go to market with it all which uh
it's unfortunate but we'll keep our eye on it um something else happened here um by the way this is
UK organization I should point out it's uh organization of uh UK independent record labels and yesterday
the uh Ricky Jervais podcast launched Ricky Jervais if you don't know who that is he's the boss
in the British version of the office and all of a sudden and actually the it kind of been
bubbling under for a while I think what I don't know if he actually he says he's not getting paid for it
but it's being launched by the guardian newspaper uh who do lots of uh actually lots of music licensing
deals very often the the UK tabloids the newspapers will include a CD um with golden oldies or
whatever you know they have a two-volume set so you get one on Saturday and you get one on Sunday I think
yeah um and so this uh Ricky Jervais podcast um was uh or as being promoted through the guardian
online guardian.co.uk I was man I was really disappointed first of all I'm a big fan of Ricky Jervais
but when he's doing the writing himself or when he's not writing what he's just talking um your
expectation is very high you know you're like oh this is gonna be great and he's supposedly had
two of his I was best friend writer comedians on and um it didn't do anything for me um which is
okay because maybe I have to listen to a couple of episodes and he has to come into his own but
I don't know if you know that he used to do a lot of radio work and it almost sounded like he he just
went right back into his BBC radio mode there um so it didn't really compel that much although
they he was very loose and the guys were very loose it you know just kind of talking and shooting
the shit so I did appreciate that but what was disappointing is that Ricky was interviewed um on
ITS I'm on ITV on the afternoon chat show and there were some repeats in the BBC also um
ran a couple of pieces I think during the news and um you know Ricky was sitting there saying well you
know it's so easy even I even I configured out you just to go to a guardian.co.uk and you click and you
listen I was like oh man couldn't someone to brief them a little bit or prepped him just a little just
so it's funny because now the BBC is saying it's the new thing it's podcasting
well the where's the BBC actually were the first mainstream media outlet to jump on the whole idea
and bring it uh to attention of the masses when the culture show I think uh interviewing the
in Belgium we were still at the castle so uh they should have an internal Wikipedia so they know
what they've talked about in the past so Ricky Javez podcasting uh good to have a big name come in
unfortunate that um we couldn't have helped him a little bit with being able to explain what it is
and what the what the real big you know what the real cool things are he did have a lot of it though he
said you know the freedom is great even though he has a lot of freedom with the BBC um but nothing
really about the convenience of it automatically being delivered to your iPod so that was uh that was
too bad but uh I'll give it a I'm subscribed so I'll give it another couple of listens and see if
if anything cool pops up he just has to kind of slip out of the mainstream mode a little bit
hey uh special little feature here we have the strange accents now on the daily source code
hey Adam this is Boris Kojirski from PositivenessAchishay podcast I'm making a new episode about radio
what it was and what it is now I would like you to give an opinion for my listeners what was so
valuable that disappeared and doesn't exist in the radio anymore thanks in advance and best wishes for
all your podcasts whose to part notion of free communication between people yes Boris I will have
the secret code delivered to you or fired a usual means Boris where are you from Ben you sound like
you're from Russia Boris well what was it it was so valuable um a good question you big
would he everyone can listen at the same time I think those were valuable things but what we really
lost clearly and people say this all the time but I really do believe in it we lost the passion we lost
the not everywhere not every show not every radio station but I think we in general lost a lot of
passion we forgot so much about what you can do with audio we've it's almost like for a while
there we believe that iPods really only were from music and you know we then we started to find out
you could do other things with your iPod so the same goes with podcasting there's other things
you can do there's other things you can do with audio I hope to show you some of that very soon
we're working on a couple of shows that we're putting together specifically for podcasting that are
really not the typical podcast that you would hear working on that with Mark I was your motor
name call I said his name right I shouldn't do that too often feeds his ego way too much so we had
Boris from Russia and then in comes Alex and Alex is from Germany and he's he calls himself
just a regular listener but he's been doing some pretty pretty interesting work over there
hi Adam this is Alex from Munich Germany and I want to share with you some short insights
on the German podcast listener if you want to I'm doing a podcast so called come you team intro
with focus on podcasting trends and business marketing and communication since beginning of the year
which is available on www.pimpmybrain.de but sorry to say that it's only German spoken
last October I did a survey on the German podcast listener to learn a little bit more about their age
the gender family status the so called social demographic data and also to learn about their
needs experience regarding podcasts and the use of podcasting in general so now as I mentioned
in my mail here's the pot far the summary the 30 year old mail mostly well educated and wealthy
podcast listener looks forward to a 20 minute weekly entertaining and informative podcast
which he's willing to pay for euros for per month or accepts topic related advertising
he listens 3.6 hours a week and subscribe to 8 podcasts although there are only 11
percent women listening they listen 20 percent more intensive to podcasts up to the age of 30
and 25 percent less intensive above the age of 30 than their mail counterparts so um you can see
we got two very interesting target groups listening to podcasts over here in Germany the one is
male intelligent and the wealthy the others female young and looks for earbird entertaining
sorry to say that there are only 38 percent female singers but 50 percent male but them
that doesn't count anyway I think we are glad about every listener tuning into the
evolution of communication you can I think you can find more details on the results of the survey
on my weblog pimpmybrain.de as mentioned and I will provide a link to the English translated results over there
now that's it from Munich thanks for having me on your show and Merry Christmas to everybody out there
in the potosphere. Throlic of Inahtin hey did it it's pretty interesting um 38 percent women 30
affluent did I hear him say good looking to good looking German chicks oh that's pretty cool I guess
he did the survey amongst just online so it's kind of like an opt-in thing and there's all
bunch of statisticians who will tell you how good that is or not but it sounds about right it certainly
I think there's also how man there's there has to be such a huge Latin market that we haven't
reached yet this uh I'm hearing a couple of countries really bubbling up where podcasting is starting
to work the UK by the way is um I think was a little slower to catch on but um and there may be
less that is for this satisfaction with with the radio here but uh I it's just I get so much
male from UK podcast listeners and and we're thinking of starting a podcast and a lot of it
revolves around music then we have friends I think basically you can say any country um and maybe
this is even a part of it think about it both friends um and Canada uh I know have rules about how
much national product has to be played on the radio so I'm talking about music in this case um
and I think that they're quite high so there's not a lot of um not a lot of Britney Spears
or maybe that's the one uh you know the 20% they can play that's foreign and god imagine all
being Britney Spears so I think it's pretty obvious that podcasting will grow rapidly in uh in
countries like that in Germany I don't know if they have commercial um radio stations I somehow I
don't think so they certainly have a lot of big public infrastructure both for television and for
radio so I think that that'll be a country where it uh where it'll definitely start bubbling up and
there was something interesting in your in your survey there um Kurt was it Kurt Alex why does it
Kurt Alex there was something interesting in your uh in your survey where you said that women
listen more intensely and I was thinking about that the other day this you know when someone listens
to a podcast uh let's just say radio versus podcast but I think that when you actually have the
earbuds stuck in your ears and you're thus blocking out all um all external noise I think there's
there is going to be almost an automatic much higher intensity of listening when you're doing
that versus listening in the radio on the speakers now I know a lot of people listen to podcasts either
with uh you know one of those wires that you hook up from your iPod to a Yucacet player lots of
people burn CDs in fact I've kind of gotten the habit of that I'd like it now that I
didn't know that CDs were that cheap they'd got really really cheap I bought a hundred CDs
for nine pounds no boxes just one of those cylinders and so uh you know it I've always
it's always been difficult for me to toss a mouse you know it's like oh well yeah I'll keep it I'll
just store it I'll file it like I'm ever gonna look at it again at least now I've gotten to the habit
of writing down with the she's been saying oh writing down with the felt stiff pin exactly what it
is uh that's on the task but I do believe that that intensity it just has to be much much more
when you have the shit sticking in your ears which I think uh well what do I think well I don't know
what I think it's good I guess it is good so um Germany keep it coming I've seen a lot of
uh German podcasts ping ping dot indie potter dot com to which an indie potter dot org that's kind of
interesting so there is uh there's definitely a German community seeing the French community we have
the pom pom pom pom pom pom pom pom podcast and a couple other ones from France and congratulations
to everybody's favorite bloated Jewish angry lesbian Madge Weiss and Weinstein celebrating
her first year of yeast I think it today could have been yesterday if so then I'm sorry Madge the
present came a little bit late but um happy to uh still be able to listen to you every single day
love the aggregator by the way that whole qpotter dot org that the Madge set up is just phenomenal
and the aggregator is a video podcast aggregator that is just phenomenal you know I um through that
I found uh have you ever seen daily planet TV Lucien? I have no idea what is set up is but it's
a daily planet TV dot net and I I watch them religiously as a short video podcast which really works
for me four or five minutes but he has this super super imposed thing going and it's completely
self supported and he's starting video clips and he's showing you um pictures I'd love to know how
I put that together I'm thinking that he does some of that imposed or in post production I'm not sure
but um what he's got going there is very cool is basically a one-man television shop so uh Lucien
give it up man what's the secret how does it work and um a lot of talk about Wikipedia so it seems
now that after uh several disputes and heated debates over Wikipedia dot org that the rules are
now changing I read actually yeah and I'm not sure what the definitive rules are by now there's so
many uh threads going on about this but I read somewhere that um it is uh I think actually read
on Wikipedia dot org that it is frowned upon to edit your own bio like that doesn't make any sense
I read something in my own bio yesterday which I didn't start on Wikipedia that said that um
I registered MTV dot com in the early days of the web well no that's not true I registered it before
there was a web there was only go for and I set up the go for server in fact the university of
Minnesota um who developed the the go for protocol uh at the time this is a this is an old story
I think I've told this before at the time um they said hey look you know you're using this uh
this mtv dot com that's commercial I said I'm not making any money off it it's only cost some
you money well we still think that you should pay for commercial license which at the time was $5,000
like dude uh uh uh uh first I don't even think I had the money at the time so I don't have five
brand to just spend on a license and you know what am I doing here I'm not using a commercial
manner and so they talked it over and this was really the first time that someone you know outside
of academia had used the go for protocol I guess I guess I can't be too sure but it's certainly
seem like it was new to them and then we finally struck a deal and the somewhere someone has a picture
of this I know it's online we struck a deal that um if I wore a go for a minis you know university
minis sold a go for t-shirt on mtv that they would uh wave the license fee and of course I did it
uh if you have a picture of that that'll be great I'd love to see that again but now it does seem like
the rules are changing another article that someone sent me is that uh one of those two I think
I guess there's two guys who uh who co-founded wikipedia and apparently one of the co-founders has
many many edits uh to his record of editing the history of wikipedia uh at which many points
he's edited his co-founder out and this just brings me to the only thing that uh is really
been on my mind is what is the truth you know the truth is I don't know if there really is a
truth for anything I've I've noticed so many times that um you know even with my wife you know
we'll be talking about something I'll totally believe that that we were talking about the discussion
from one uh point of view a mine of course because I'm the center of my universe and she's the
center of her universe although she's much better at making herself not the center of the universe
um and you know but then you'll find out like oh wait a minute you told it to
understand what I was talking about or or something that'll happen and and I'll recount the events
one way and she'll recount it another way and for her that's the absolute truth and for me it's the
absolute truth you know but there's so much that you don't pay attention to if it's usually
if it's not about you you're not gonna you know notice things is quickly so although I uh I think that
there will be an interesting process that comes out of this I you know just saying this is the
truth and this is the way it is it's a real tough one man it really is so the rules are changing
and uh I guess that proves that for every uh action there's uh there's a complete uh equal and
opposite reactions I guess it was good I think this is all the good thing that maybe we'll figure
out how we make the Wikipedia actually work uh because I do use it often but you know or I used to
use it often and it is a great resource and you know I think in general uh lots of stuff that's in
there is it's pretty much the way it went or the way it was or how it's supposed to be for every one
of the 850 thousand articles but still what is the absolute truth I think that's that's something
really hard um I think the really um yeah what is truth I guess uh uh you can only get truth in
mathematics then I presume or physics I guess I should have paid more attention in school
hey monk remember him from uh invasion of the pod people well he uh sent something to me
which I'd like to share with you right now I'm pretty sure if it's not in the pod safe music
network well he will be putting it up he says I really like that the pod safe release
Christmas tune but let me give you something to really rock your brain too huh just stocking
on monk on the daily source code
I'm not free till I'm stuck in the door it's up to hanging over me
when I like something I can keep got enough socks with my own sheep
night night night night's fast red Ferrari if I can't have that guess I'll have to take it
by me she's on the way home to bring you read the world I know I can't but I want to see
you're stuck in on yeah that's a Christmas gift right there
you hear that? there's damn foxes again I'm telling you it's funny I said that the foxes were
coming closer to civilization last week on the show and I got an email from someone who said
they're not interesting it didn't civilization move into their neck of the woods first
I'm like yeah I guess so but without the excuse me oh man I still have that little bit of the
cough Patricia got the cold now she's completely stuffed up without the fox hunts the foxes
fox eye the foxes have just come much closer to us now and they rummage through the garbage man
it's funny though because foxes are really afraid of humans they're afraid of even
dogs and well dogs depends on how big but they're afraid of cats and I think if they can eat
trash they'll eat trash but they eat worms and nuts and stuff like that it's not exactly
what you think of foxes would be into it's not you know foxes do not regularly it's must be
some kind of fable but from everything I've read it's not like the fox gets into the henhouse
and then eats them all up they're afraid of everything everything that jumps and bounces the fox
will run away from um yeah there's anything I can ask on this show and I immediately get
so many cool comments um I talked about oh the crackling fire log that's what it was
and I got a link here let me see it's uh this is about something called the java log
coffee based log burns cleaner but no Starbucks smell so apparently uh there is a biofriendly
log the java log that is made of primarily coffee beans and produces 85% less carbon monoxide
okay that's not a big deal I mean that'll kill ya but only if you have the windows closed
last year and within 2 million java logs were sold okay I haven't found a place to buy them
over here in the UK but I'll definitely have a look around I'll try it up just to clarify something
I you know not we bought the curry cruiser people are saying that you know I pretended to be a
greenie and I turned out it turns out I'm not well I'm not really the biodiesel thing is just an
experiment I'd really like to try hey it is kind of catching on by the way this biodiesel thing
I'm here in all kinds of you know good good noise from all over the world Volkswagen
their next cars will all be certified to run on biodiesel albeit only 5% biodiesel but still they'll
run on it there's been some reports of more efficient ways to create biodiesel efficiency of
10 to 15% or times 10 or 15 times more efficient in the production of biodiesel biodiesel fuels
so I totally intend on getting and I have a parking space at the condo in San Francisco unused
so if if you're in San Francisco and you have a diesel I don't care what kind of diesel it is
you know it probably the older the crappier the better I would like to buy it from you if it's
for sale and I'm talking about something that just drives right it's got to be street legal or
you know whatever it has to kind of work but I definitely I'm looking for something that we can
just fill up with vegetable oil see how it runs we'll put some big pod show stickers on it yeah
yeah I'll drive that cool and also if you have and here's this is a this is another very serious
request and I know there's lots of graphic designers who listen to this show and maybe
comic-strick blogger could even help with this one you know when Christina got was it was going to
get her tattoo which of course I was against and Patricia said oh well you know let her do whatever
she wants to do it's it's the kids these days I said wow what are you talking about it's a tattoo
dude she's 15 so I lost that battle usually I I do pretty well on the field but I said look if you're
going to get one then I'm going to get one and so I've been thinking for a long time about what kind of
tattoo I want to get and I was thinking maybe a combination of like wings you know like pilots
wings and for my for my upper arm right I like my shoulder or my my ample biceps
pilots wings I don't know what you're going in the in the middle though you know so I kind of want
to represent my passions there so flying and then a microphone would be cheesy but maybe something
that represents you know media or free media or podcasting or whatever it is you know if you
haven't even thought let me know because I'm really looking for some designs at this point I'm
completely convinced I'm going to do it I know who I'm going to have do it for me I just I'm looking
for some designs and another fucking controversies unbelievable um what's this did I have
what is this comment hold on a second let me see I had something oops I had something teed up here I'm
not sure if this was in regards to the feed hijacking hold on let's listen hey Adam this is Darrell
Fallen over law school podcast calm was listening to your DSC 289 actually stopped this so I could
record this message to you it's now creating a domain name I have my own domain name of course
and our seat oh and so this is this was kind of a lead into the to the feed hijacking now here's
what's interesting about this and and I thought it was kind of dying down but it seems like it is
not gone away yet and I know these two guys one guy from the vegan cast and one guy from pod pod
keywords.com I believe both of them started on podcasting pretty early but there's this huge
riff that is that is come up I think mainly because there's a little bit of a lack of understanding
what's happening and how pod key works and how feed caching works and you know and I think we could
probably see the same misunderstanding with feed burner and I know we've seen this misunderstanding with
iTunes where was I just I just did I just hear a podcast or just that was I listening to
was I watching some oh no it was rocket boom that's right Amanda from rocket boom was saying
that iTunes was considering changing the way they deal with RSS feeds I don't know what it means
but I'll definitely try and get some info from from from the campus for you to find out what's going on
and so the I guess it really the heart of the matter here is two issues one
that is probably not a good idea to replicate your podcast feed anywhere else that you don't
have control over over the server so in essence that's like creating a Microsoft Word document
but letting someone else make a copy of it and then distribute it even if that's what you agree to it's
still is not a good idea I mean there's a whole bunch of things that can go wrong in the process
and why would you you know why wouldn't you just send that word document directly to someone so
that's the one part is the caching now of course there's a huge marketing opportunity in there
which is I think what what keywords was initially invented for but I don't think there was ever
business model put around it and I've never really been a fan of keywords myself you remember we
had that whole um that whole craze was that with netscape you could buy keywords and you could just
type into your into your browser window instead of a URL you just type maybe that's still works I
wonder if that works with one on a second um let's see let's just take a random keyword the
random keyword would be sex because I'm sure if it has keywords enabled it'll get it and it goes to
sxetc.org a website by teens 14's that's fantastic oh my god oh my god okay sex et cetera
so that's I type that in Firefox that's pretty interesting what if I just do
what should we do travel that's another general keywords what happens if I I wonder if keywords
travel loss that is where it goes to that's interesting so are there still keywords available
in in browsers well anyway that's where the the pod key I think that I believe the pod key idea
came from so there's that issue and then there's really the issue of um was there a
ransom a real hijacking you know I guess if it working back from the so many memes in this
hijacking of feed and asking a ransom these are pretty strong words but the meme is definitely
caught and I think that I may be partially to blame because I played an audio comment from the vegan
cast podcaster who who talked about this and now I was sent a file of the David Lawrence show which is
also I think it might be on the radio but certainly a podcast interview with the uh with the I'm
just using their their show names okay uh using I had an interview with the the podcast keyword
dude and completely different viewpoint so I think that the controversy will continue for a while
but now I think it's just gotten personal and I think it's uh we should try and focus on the actual
issue which is you know how do we make sure that this stuff um doesn't happen um and the the number one
way is to I guess you know before it's way too late is to you know figure out what best way to set
up your feed because your feed really is quite important and so to answer the question for that comment
that was that I started to play just before I got into this whole thing I believe that the really
the true way to do it is to register a domain name so that you can change the DNS to any server you
want and then um yeah then basically you have control over your RSS feed um but you'll still need
control over the server that it resides on and you'll need control over the DNS um which is a domain
name issue so really I think if you put those two things together that's we know so it's much better
to be uh atomspodcast.com and then I can put anything behind that to be my RSS feed then it's to be
atomspodcast.odio.com more atomspodcast.podshow.com for that matter um now I happen to control the
DNS on pod shows I'm not too worried about it last night we had the um the final episode of I'm a
celebrity get me out of here the UK version and as I predicted as I'd hoped uh Carol Thatcher
mother to the iron a daughter to the iron lady herself um one and it was it was just a really
interesting um series to watch I really enjoyed the personalities uh I didn't know any of them really
was great to um kind of get to know Jimmy Osman who I knew as a little Jimmy Osman the long-haired
lover from Liverpool um Sherri a cido one who uh thank you podcast Paul yeah it's said is uh it
couldn't be more cocky you're right I guess and he used to play an East Enders go figure the
show I watch almost religiously uh so Sherri said and Carol were the the three finalists and um it was
I don't know it was you know what it was it was no controversy or I should take controversy
no controversy at all in uh in the show um this series but what there was it was a real um human
mutual respect and um and helpfulness and there was just something really beautiful going on and I'm sure
that the producers of the show were saying you know damn it you know we don't have any any spark
there's nothing going on here no one's fighting no one's angry but uh maybe that's exactly why I was
able to look to really watch the whole thing was just good and um uh and I think that Carol Thatcher
will be uh a very interesting uh new voice on the scene uh because of course now uh should be uh
bustle through the entire media gateway and should be talking to everybody about everything uh and
I think she'll do fine it's just it's wonderful to listen to her just listening to her talk is so nice
um you can tell that she's been in basically and yeah I just had a great upbringing
her vocabulary is incredibly expensive and you know she will never answer a question where yes or no
she'll she'll just come out with a whole slew of beautiful words that like oh yeah read the yellow
pages to me Carol please wonderful congratulations speaking of that according to Oxford's new dictionary
word of the year it's podcast let's check in with Heather and Jenelle so one thing Jenelle and I
totally agree on is that we love to argue oh very true okay when I think of voice I think uh drama
I like my boyfriend almost so it's more fun today it's so much less drama yeah definitely so go
to our site down those that ask me a dot com and tell us if you're going to type that
the first steady boyfriend or dating a bunch of guys download with Heather and Jenelle is
sponsored by Accu view brand contact lenses for the life of your eyes
all right this is PW Fenton creator of digital flotten and I'm here to wish a happy
quanza happy hannaca happy christmas and to all podcast listeners a very happy December
we back when when we didn't have to think come on until we take the boys on the bottom
meaning on on the banks of chubcry we're not happy stop that oh you can
ruin it let me alone woman this is and from the chubby cheek show chubcry hello kid I want to speak to
Anne it's Anne it's Adam and Murray it's Adam Curry hi it's a chubcry whatever Adam Curry for
anyway I've been listening to your show I actually sound like a wounded cat
it's awful anyway I'm talking to Anne and there's something wrong with your voice you don't
sound normal because it's not and I gotta tell you that I don't want to I've been listening to
your show on the eye pocket it's an eye pocket I'm gonna tell you I love the music that
you're saying but I wish you put more of the your old songs like snowbird on the show and
uh you know and I'm gonna listen it but it takes hours and hours to listen and you all you're
talking about is your smash up senior there's no more people that put vegetables in your car
and an a waitin for you to get to the point why do you gonna get to the point I want to know
what's the source code what are you gonna tell me anyway I've got I haven't got time for this so
anyway I'm not buying another Anne Murray album and to curry until you reveal the source code
and you don't have to do it every day there can be like a weekly somebody shoot while you're at it you can
visit the chubby cheek show chubby cheek dot com hi I do an atom to stay down from madpod dot
com and since you can't play the the old hit test and stuff because of the music stuff going on
I thought I'd come up with the new DSC Adam Curry voiceover hit test see if you didn't recognize
your voice backwards here we go with number one number two
number three and you get a bonus number four is it safe I do like the coffee he does
like the coffee all right well time for the answers here we go with answer number one
my foot is wrapped up before they're number two pod people take an over answer number three
I did it I did a family would I said right and the bonus track once again is insane I do like
the coffee all right that is the first DSC voiceover hit test hope you enjoyed it don't forget
the tune in to this week we have Nick Gilder hot child in the city it started with an old
wardrobe four children opened its door and found much more than coats and mothballs
beyond the wardrobe there's a world of adventure mystery and magic
join me as I take you to the kingdom of Nanya to explore the hidden secrets of the lion
the witch in the wardrobe you've read the books you've seen the movie now it's time to subscribe
to the secrets of Nanya a new series of podcasts by father Rodrige find it on iTunes or
surf through the Star Quest podcast network on sqpn.com
and Rodrige starts a new show every month it seems like
oh man it's so good to have him around but I'm subscribed father f f to the r f to the r father to the
roaderick from the Netherlands to wind it down today a couple of things about the the man the evil
man the r i a a a they sent a letter out nay not a not a letter a warning to David Bern this link has
been circulating around the net for a little while so you may have seen it if not I'm sure
it'll show up in the show notes show notes that info of course you can find a link from daily
source code dot com a curry dot com David Bern of the talking heads wrote on his website David
Bern dot com the r i a a a should me a warning based on a previous radio playlist he does a
streaming station online that featured all missiele at all the time the digital millennium copyright
act the mca which was passed by congress 1998 was a hastily thrown together measure in my opinion
which aim to protect the music industry from the impending apocalypse well some parts of the
law seem reasonable other aspects when someone overboard to protect the interest of the industry before
folks even knew what would be developed invented or what half the terms actually meant and this is a
really good piece that that I encourage you to read because you're going to see here um what really
this digital millennium copyright act meant at the time and it was if you really read to the
DMCA I hope we can get a link to that in the show notes as well you'll see that all these little
stipulations are in there so literally um according to the DMCA which applies to streaming only
not to podcasting but to streaming you cannot play more than I believe it's four um tracks by the
same artist back to back from the same CD because otherwise people might be ripping it off and
there's a whole bunch of really weird stipulations in there by the way if you know um if you call
the record company and say hey can I get a waiver for that they can issue that you know you can issue
that right over the phone so you don't have to deal with it I think that that happens at some of
the satellite stations certainly on this one that you may be listening to this podcast if you are
checking us out on serious satellite stars 103 um stay tuned Pacific Coast hellway is coming
up right after this followed by uh Madge Weinstein with East Radio Don and Drew then we have
attention tech um I don't know if we have PW Fenton on tonight or certainly some McCool
Podsake music after that so those of you listening on serious I will uh see you tomorrow here on
the source code and those of you listen to the podcast here comes the bonus piece this is where
we get to talk a little bit longer so let me just see if there's anything else cool in this um
well let's just say here uh you cite Lawrence Lessick's book free culture uh here's something
to come back in the day I use my boombox to tape things off the radio all the time that's how I found
out about music I didn't know about and eventually I not only bought those records but ended
up promoting them too which made a fair amount of money for some record labels but not for me
not complaining though so you know read that and then you'll see how really broken the the DMCA is
and of course the fact that we don't have anything in place for podcasting which I like I really do
I'm glad they can't classify I can't figure out what to do with us um and ask God be in my
of very very helpful really like it when it comes to the music licensing because as far as I can tell
so so far really the only performing rights organizations that will allow their the podcasters
sorry allow artists to uh to assign um specific licenses for performance uh to individuals or
groups and um Mark Zeta sent me an email uh see he's from Australia so what are we had now we've
had Austria friends Germany the Netherlands now we're in Finland we've had uh this is Australia
they have uh the APRA which is the Australian equivalent to ask at BMI um he's quoting from the
website when you become a member of the APRA you assign your performing rights in all existing
and future works to us this is the right to perform the work in public and the right to communicate
the work in public when we administer these rights on your behalf this means we enter licensed
agreements for the performance and communication of music and lyrics we monitor the use of music
under these agreements and distribute the royalties we collect the copyright owners whose material
is identified as having being used so Mark feels that that translates to that if you join
APRA your whole performance rights as an artist go to them that that's exactly what it states
and it seems to be that uh in Europe uh this is the case as well so um if you're a musician if you're an
artist uh in Europe uh or in Australia the countries that we've been through so far if not check it
out your local rights organization if you're a member if what you've done is actually signed your
rights over then I think that yeah I think there's an issue I wonder by the way can you as a
European artist can you just sign up with ask at BMI and won't they collect from in Europe for you
doesn't it is not how it works or could you do it through a US company something's got to give
because you know this isn't the pod save music revolution is not going to make it just
based on US music alone we really need music from all over the globe some I picked up for PMN
some totally different kind of like uh early 80s kind of discoy funk vibe
dread days as one's called Love Life
if life's a follow with you have life in love for my view if life's a follow with you
every single day I think God for what comes late I really hope with no delay I
this is what I have to say what happened to the love and over good words now I'm seeing
things what I've been never heard before that was long stone I've been a good love
or you want more what you're gonna do when you have a life I hope you don't think that you're
gonna do when the spot will be you're not really you're not I'll be in this pocket
looking alive I want you to fly in the shot to handle this really you're gonna be hard
but I'm not a pocket in that night you know where that mean I'm from the green
and I stay cool when I stop on the same stuff I just want to see
if life's a follow with you if life's a follow with you if life's a follow with you
just me way past it I can draw the stars you that turn to some like racing your arms
fill up the warmth of my life when I get away you show you what I'm made of
a cover mystery sweet and a leafy brand new discoveries never buddies to be
because with these other days love is true and they knew how dreams of one day come true
make decisions like it was in the rain to relieve the child from his pain so clear my vision
even in the rain I don't want to be even in my under way around to be a person's in the draw
don't you like the sunshine and the rain moves the memories with the nice toes
that's the scene man that is so so stop calling their phones yeah this is a love man
I'm somewhat glad I'm going back with you every day I'm made
when I said you're here I love me I said true life was a push out my shoves me
so we're going to cut the guy down in my dick I can bring the dark I never in the 90
and run the black I never bring the white dick I know how the nerves you're gonna fight me
I and left for love you Bonnie was cruel whatever part of loved you
they tried to find a way through love one more
their lives were very true love blind, love you
it's my fault a reshoot I and left for love you
they tried to find a way through loved one another love a love you
they tried to find a way through love one another love you
It's life's blood to be true
You know what I mean? Kind of the early 80s like
Shack attack type day
Love life and life would love you some true words right there
Everybody so
Take care of yourself. Don't let your feet get hijacked until we see you again my friends
I didn't know there was an ending to that
I was just gonna say wouldn't it be we should do
Like a mainstream news media story, you know like
RSS feeds hijacked
Then again, maybe not
Hey tomorrow's Wednesday will be at the hump. I will gladly see you there to care everybody
Pot show the rate no party like a pot show party