Yeah, Bunny, Bunny, Rabbit, Rabbit.
This is March 1st Daily Source Code.
Oh, justing.
It's Adam Curry.
Hey, everybody.
That's right.
First of the month, welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Oh, yeah.
New location today.
We are downstairs in the kitchen here at the Curry Cottage.
Reason being, I just don't have enough time to get it all done.
Patricia is on a business trip.
She's gone for two days, which means I'm Mr. Mom and podcast pod, father.
Sorry, life's getting to the way of all the fun stuff.
Man, I, you know, there's a lot to do in this household.
Stuff that I hadn't realized, especially having been on the road myself for almost two weeks.
Yeah, you come back and then you kind of forget all the stuff that goes into making a household
run.
Let me just lower down the opening theme music here.
So, because I'm going to have to take the headphones off or actually remove the ear buds
so that I can walk around.
And I figured I'd do my chores while talking with y'all today.
And the chores, well, they'd all started this morning.
And of course, moms who are listening or stay at home dad's will probably be
chuckling right now, saying, you know, curry, what the hell is wrong with you?
Yeah, this is like, welcome to reality, right?
And aren't podcasts pretty much about reality in many cases.
Let me see, get everything else set up here.
Okay.
There we go.
Right, let me just take the headphones off.
So, it started this morning at 6.30, the alarm went because I had to get Christina off to school
and that, you know, that entails making a lunch.
Well, actually, we still have the two dogs and the two cats.
So they all need to be taken care of in the morning and have to be let out and walked
and fed or, you know, they all drink lots of water.
You know, shoot the water bowl as empty again, hold on a second.
And then there's a dishwasher, which I haven't emptied out yet.
There's lunch that has to be made, then I drove Christina to school, I actually considered
starting the podcast this morning before we went to school, but maybe I should, I thought
that maybe I should ask Christina before I just did that.
Like me, she's not really a morning person.
We're not very good in the morning.
So you can just imagine us two grouches kind of scouring over breakfast at each other.
I didn't get to bed on time, or at least, you know, I wanted to be in bed around midnight,
but the way it works out with the time differences, five hours difference between East
coast of the US and the cottage here, Gilford, which means that if you want to have, you
kind of like a regular morning conference call with anyone, which, you know, it's like, you
know, 10 or 11 o'clock, it's already three, four p.m. here, Christina comes out of school
at three, thirty.
And so what I've been doing is I've basically had the car service picker up and bring
her home.
It's only like a 10 minute ride, but, you know, it's just right at that inconvenient
time.
And I do like taking her to school, because we always have a good laugh in the car in the
morning listening to the radio or sometimes we'll listen to podcasts and we'll talk, talk
while it's going on at school.
This morning was an interesting conversation.
We listened to the radio and there was some report about some middle school in the UK.
I think a little bit, it was in London or another suburb of London, and talking about
how many kids were bringing knives to school and other weapons, some joke like, oh, you
know, weapons of mass destruction said, oh, you know, what's with the guys at my school
of knives?
What?
So, you know, like pocket knives, like, you know, like, you know, this long, it's
you could actually tell me how long the knives were and what, you know, they have silver
bladed, but as well, what are they using for?
Well, in case they get into a fight, they said, you got to be kidding me.
So, well, that's never really actually happened, but it's kind of like a, it's like you
got your iPod, you got your knife, you know, it's like Jesus Christ.
And then I kind of thought back to, when I was a kid going to school, and I went to a,
a, a Christian school, the Christian, the Christianly say him about the Felbert, and we had
all kind of, we were always carrying shit.
We had knives and, you know, stilettos, you know, which, you know, the switchblade, which
kind of like swings out and locks, and the other stilettos, which comes with shoots out
of the blade, kind of like a taxi driver thing.
We had all that shit as well, and it was just posturing, I guess, oh shoot, I don't know,
and I haven't, the gate is open, which I have to close, because otherwise the dogs would
run out to the front of the house.
So, it's about three degrees centigrade, it was snowing this morning.
It's not quite as cold as the rest of some parts of Europe in, in Holland, I think it's
like five below, and last night it was definitely freezing here, and I'm, I'm going
to more and more dismayed with the house that we're renting, it's so cold, you know,
it's like, we pay, we pay a lot of money to rent this place, but you actually have to,
probably add another two to 300 pounds a month on to the bill just for the extra heating,
because, you know, these non double-pain windows, you walk past any window, you can literally
feel the cold just flowing over, it's not very handy, okay, so let me just start by
clearing out the dishwasher, another crappy feature of the rental home, the dishwasher sucks,
and it's too bad because we had a great dishwasher in Belgium at the castle, which we
could have taken with us, but the one here looked to be okay, but there's a couple of things
that just really aren't right, the knives slide through the knife, or the silverware container,
and then, so they're like jammed down into the down below the rack, so it's impossible to take
the bottom tray out and then it derails all the time, just these little things, and I don't
know if I'm really a believer in washing machines anyway, you're basically handling everything
twice, and you become really lazy, particularly if you have one of these dishwashers that
empties itself automatically, have you ever seen that? Yeah, the way it works is Patricia
does it, that's why you don't realize what a pain in the acid is until you do it, okay, let me
see, so a couple of things I'm going to talk about today on daily source code, some of them
obviously podcast related, let me see, I have the line up here, we have, I'm going to talk
about some commercial podcast efforts that are popping up, talk about the iPod directorie,
I'm going to talk about Father Roderick, he has some exciting news, and of course there's a
hit test, which is always fun, so let me just put the earbuds in for a second, because I received
Sid's mashup of the day, while you're here in the background, by the way, that's Radio 2,
that's Terry Wogan, does the morning show on Radio 2, and I think he starts at 7 or 730,
and he goes until 11 o'clock, it's a pretty long shift, but it's a fun show, very,
it's kind of like a podcast in a way, I have to say, he's just talking crap and he has his,
it sounds like he has his buddies there, it's not like a hot rock in flame through and morning show,
but he's just, you know, responding to viewer comments and has talks to people on the phone
and plays really, really good songs, at least songs that I like, you know, but of course I'm
an old fart and 40, so let's see, Sid sent me a track by John Wignal, aka DJ Wig, quality,
not too good Sid says, oh, that's too bad, but a brilliant mashup, beds are burning by midnight oil,
and this is how we do it, my Montel, Jordan, totally made for each other. Later this week,
oh, this is, oh, Sid is now teasing stuff, the 80s porn version of back to life, sold to whole, okay,
so we'll look forward to that, Sid, the mashup, pimp daddy, but right now this is how we burn the beds.
Oh, I don't know, oh, this is how we do it, this is how we do it, it's Friday night,
and I feel all right, the parties here run the wayside, so when each for my party and I turn it up,
there's a glee that got me taking the keys to my truck, it's a shock as I'm faded,
but he's in the street saying money, oh, we made it, it's so good, and I live tonight,
but so much less hurts, and we're going to sleep for a while, looking back,
he's got about the time I buy, he got to get you through, but oh, you don't get paid,
so tomorrow we'll come and throw your hands up, and let me hit a party, I'm kind of buzzing, it's all because
South Central does it like nobody does, tomorrow my neighbors are getting much flavour,
let's flip the track, bring the old school back, this is how we do it,
this is how we do it, all hands are in the air, and away from from here to the air,
if you're in our team, that's what I want to be playing, you can see the hood's been good to me,
ever since I was a lower-case cheat, but now I'm a big cheat, look at what I see, I got to money,
I'm not a middle-chore, you feel right from where I'm from, where I'm from, and you wouldn't know,
then I gotta get mine and a big black truck, you think it's yours in a 6' hole, whatever it is,
the water is a better way, so tip up your cup and throw your hands up, and let me hit a party, say,
I'm kind of buzzing, it's all because South Central does it like nobody does, tomorrow my neighbors are getting much flavour,
let's flip the track, bring the old school back, I'm kind of buzzing, it's all because South Central does it like nobody does it like
why in me, it's C-C, I'm my hobbies, I'll never come back on it all school tracks,
check it out, once upon a time in 90, my child made no money and my child was so, and all that I said was 6'8",
he's doing, and people don't know the music that he made was good, the lipid DJ and Paul was his name,
he came up to money, this is what he said, do it without jail, I don't know about it, some guys,
sell a million records and we'll make it the day, oh, I'm buzzing, it's all because South Central does it like nobody does,
all my neighbors are getting much flavour, I'll never come back on it all school tracks,
I'm kind of buzzing, it's all because South Central does it like nobody does it like nobody does it like
always part of time, straight up coming from the west side, oh, she's got the flavour, yeah,
and money does it like nobody does it like nobody does it like
quality wasn't too bad, this is how we burn the beds, you heard it here on the daily source code,
it's the first of the month, remember we said, bunny bunny rabbit rabbit which is supposed to
be the first thing out of your mouth on the first day of a new month and it's supposed to bring you
health and wealth and fame and riches and all kinds of groovy stuff, so I said it for you all,
since I've got all that and I'm really happy and feel extremely privileged, almost done with
three, I can't believe it, the two of us made that big a load for the dishwasher, that's just
ridiculous, I'm learning, I'm learning, okay, time to load it out, speaking of mashups,
lots of responses about the news that the Battalica site was shut down, and of course,
none of them from lawyers as far as I can tell, but a lot of different opinions about what can and
can't be done, I'm going to, oh, let me just walk over to the, to the power book, so one of them
is from Eric, he says, he says, if you record a song as a parody of the original, you are protected
from copyright infringement, because on to say, we're the link of each show that's to be true
when he recorded parody songs that when he asked the original artist for permission first and they
said, no, he did it anyway because you're allowed to do that as a parody under fair use.
I would think that Battalica presenting Beetle songs in a parody format started like Metallica
would fall under this as well, but Battalica should check with their lawyers, yes, of course,
Eric, from the soundhouse studios, I agree, they should check with their lawyers, and unfortunately,
you got to have lawyers for almost everything these days, and then other people have sent an email
saying that, you know, you can do that with almost any song except for basically the Beetles,
the Rolling Stones, and one or two others, I'm not quite sure, I think that
there's probably a lot of strong arming going on with this stuff, and it's really a shame,
I mean, if I were Metallica or if I were who owns the Beetles, it's still Michael Jackson,
who owns the Beetles catalog, I'd be ecstatic, you know, I'd be like, how do we release this stuff?
How do we, basically, repackaging of already great material, we should be able to make money on it?
And the oops, shit, no, and the Battalica musicians as well,
that's weird times we live in, that's not sure, okay, almost done loading up the
mornings breakfast, this is our breakfast mashup here, okay, what else do we have?
Table, oh, Christina, I didn't take her lactose pill, she's a little bit lactose intolerant,
although that's gotten much, much better since we moved here, I don't know if there's
well, I'm sure there's different types of cows, I don't know if the milk is different or whatever,
but she really, it's not that bad, whereas you know, if you had like mashed potatoes and put
even a little bit of milk in there, it would trip around, it really, it's sad because it, you know,
she gets a stomach ache from it. Okay, see, a derailed again, fucking you.
Good, done, I'm getting there, I also have to vacuum the place it's just a stye, man, it really
is. How does Patricia do it? How does she keep up with all this crap?
So last night, before I went to bed, I actually had a little phone call with
Madge Weinstein, who had emailed me a press release that she was putting out or was about to put out
and wanted to have my okay on it, about the Madge Weinstein iPod Shuffle Contest,
which is just an amazing thing that she's doing, went out and spent, well, must have
meant at least $5 or $600 of her own money to promote the yeast radio show, yeastradio.com.
And I guess the deal is, it's starting today, you have to listen to all of the yeast radio
programs or whatever podcasts are being released for clues and every week, one lucky listener
will receive an iPod shuffle, the 500 gigabyte, a gigabyte, whoops, that would be a shuffle.
A mega shuffle, now the 500 megabyte and it will come preloaded with all of the Madge Weinstein
yeast radio podcasts, which I think is great and actually in the press release, she goes in this whole
tire rate about, you know, so what if Bono and YouTube have their iPod, Madge has their
Madge pod or yeast pod or whatever it is, and she sent me a promo, which we're going to have
a listen to right now. Hello everyone, this is Madge Weinstein of yeastradio.com with an
important announcement, starting March 1st, I am going to be giving away one free iPod shuffle
out every week for the next five weeks, but you have to listen to yeast radio to find out how.
Along with this iPod shuffle is going to be a full collection of all the yeast radio shows to date.
You have to listen to yeast radio to find out how to win this, and this is not a free iPod
scam, I have all five iPods in my possession, and they are for you, my general audience. So listen
to yeastradio.com very carefully for instructions on how to win the iPod shuffles.
The shuffles. Excellent, great promotion, great contest. And this is not like one of those
get a free iPod deals. You know, she actually went out and bought the iPods and is probably
still in the process of preloading them. So this is a real deal, and as you certainly get her a lot
of listeners or extra listeners, and hopefully you will subscribe as well. By the way, the yeast
radio program is certainly not safe for work. So we look at the paper for a second here, what's going
on in the UK? The paper I like is the Financial Times, or as we say here, FT. I don't know what
it is about the Financial Times, but it really just seems to always have the stories that I'm interested
in. It's a mix of business and finance and world news, but right at the top here, Jackson's TV
thriller, celebrity trial gives a boost to courtroom television page 12. There's a whole thing in here
about reality television. Here, people are going to court TV and other broadcasts are hoping
for a big boost to the audiences from Michael Jackson's trial. That's right, and it is going to
be huge, and it's kind of disgusting. I hear news reports everywhere, and there's so little respect
for Michael Jackson. Here they all call him, well, I guess Wacco Jacco is pretty much
universally used around the globe, but I've been in that position, not in, obviously, not in
Michael Jackson's exact position, but it sucks, man, when people show no respect, and it's
I don't know. There's so many, I think recently even we're seeing more and more people posting
about how inaccurate the press really is, and this is no news to me, because I think I've been interviewed.
Well, I've been in newspapers and radio television interviews since I was
16, but really since I was 19, half of my life has been in show business. I don't think of
ever read one single interview that was entirely right, and usually there's just all kinds of
mistakes in there, and what you learn is that it's really your fault. It's not the media's fault.
It's how you, you have to be a better storyteller. You have to explain better what you're talking
about, and it really shows how little people understand when it comes to two-way communication,
and I've come to the realization more and more that sometimes I'm really not a good communicator,
and people just really understand things differently, or to have a different take on them, or we're
thinking something else at the time when you have to look for the clues, which I don't really
like doing phone interviews. I like talking to people face to face, so you can really see if they're
understanding what you're talking about. Okay, hold on, let me just, I've got to do the countertop.
One of my using here, Mr. Mussela, a Johnson and Johnson, a family company. That's great.
Johnson and Johnson, a family company. Mr. Mussela loves the job you hate. That's a registered
trademark, by the way. It's the kitchen, dissolves grease, kills bacteria. Let's give it a shot. Meanwhile,
Spandole Ballet is gold in the background, on the Terry Wogan Show. 8 million listeners that guy has,
that's pretty massive. Of course, the infrastructure, BBC radio is nice. People really do listen to
the radio in the UK, and that's probably because satellite and cable still hasn't really made it all
the way into a foot, I mean, it just hasn't penetrated the way it hasn't. In other countries like the
states, and sky satellite has only been around for 10 years or something like that, so it's just
not really peeking into massive availability, and it really works very well. But before that,
people will just listen to the wireless, and they'd enjoy it.
All right, the almost done here. Let's start to look like a, almost look like the way Patricia does it.
Okay. Let me do that. Kitchen table, and then we can talk a little bit more.
See, it's really hard actually to clean and talk at the same time. I can't concentrate on
two things. I'm not multitasking like life. Okay. Here we go. By the way, a lot of people want to know what
Patricia was doing. She has a cosmetics company called LePy Cosmetics, and she's doing some
rather large deals with it over the next two days, and it's cool, you know, it's good for her to get
away as well, and just be doing some stuff with other people, even though it's hard work and she's got
all kinds of early and late meetings to move. Right. Okay. Back to the computer. What do we have?
Ah, Scriss tomes would Chris, a Chris said. See, notice the, it's ever since you discovered
the world of podcasts and his trips to the iTunes Music Store have been much less. It's also,
he says, save me tons of cash. And I wonder if other podcasts listeners have the same experience.
Giving the limit of time that he has to plug in the iPod on the way to work and the car on the
train, his time is spent tuning into a half a dozen or so podcast on a daily basis. Hence,
less time to listen to music and the need to line the pockets of Apple.
So does podcast equal less Apple iTunes downloads or will it have no effect or will
the more popular podcasts sell their souls to iTunes and charge 99 cents or whatever to download
them. Good question. Very good question. Well I thought I think we talked about that the other
day that we're going to see all kinds of services popping up. In fact, not a day goes by
that someone doesn't send me a link. I've actually, you know, I decided that I'm probably
just going to create a category for this in the iPod or directory of podcasts services.
Which is pretty much like a weblog service. In fact, it's just two sides of the same coin.
So what you see is everyone pretty much has the same idea. You know, you a place to
upload your files to manage them, to manage the ID3 tags, to create your feed, maintain your feed,
maintain your show notes and it's all all different versions of that. What I don't see is any
real or any realistic pricing on on bandwidth, which is where I think a lot of these, you know,
great ideas and great services and you know, the idea is there and it's really going to help
people, although I still think we need something much simpler. There are probably hundreds of
thousands of people out there who want the podcast, but have no, no, what I call it, just really
don't want to know about ID3 tags. They don't, they won't mind entering in show notes, but I
think that's it, you know, it should be click record, enter some information or what we call
show notes and that's it, you're done, you know, it should be out there, it should be working.
I am about to give you a live demonstration of the San Seo. I haven't talked about it in a few days.
Mine is getting a little bit cruddy actually and if you don't, you're not careful when you
close it, then the pressure or it doesn't seal properly and then the pressure builds up and
it spews out the side, which is always a fun effect. I freshly washed cup, washed by yours truly
in the machine. So I got my pod in there and I have the cafe crema coffee pod, medium roast.
Let's see what this packaging says. You know, I never really pay attention to the packaging.
New. Oh, a new way to enjoy great coffee. We seal for freshness. Individual soft coffee pods
provide exactly the right amount of freshly brewed coffee. Can we use an any coffee pod,
crema machine? Excellent. Okay, so that's how long it took for the water to warm up. It's done.
Hit the button and now the freshly brewed taste is dripping into the cup. It's coming out of two
spouts simultaneously. It's going to give me exactly the right amount. I like to put a little sugar in
and they also a little bit of milk in and I usually do that while it's still just a safe time,
but it's not fast enough for me. I put it all in while it's still dripping into the cup.
And now it's just about stopped. Perfect. Okay, okay. So bandwidth. Yeah, that's going to be a big deal.
Now I've been doing some calculations and it gets pretty gnarly pretty quickly. So the question is,
man, I wish Bitcoin wasn't under such heavy attack. I'm so worried to start talking about
or implementing Bitcoin because just the fact that the name Bitcoin has a real negative connotation
with the man with the authorities these days, but I think it is certainly a solution to the ban with
issue. But what I don't really see is, you know, there's a couple of ways to look at podcasts.
One is in the kind of like as an audio blog post. So crack the mic and just talk and then this
people who are kind of making little pieces of art and productions and shows and whatever you want to
call them and it takes a lot of work. It really does. By the way, I'm just wondering around
it's kind of like what I'm on the telephone and do the same thing. Are you a wanderer on the
telephone? I can't sit still when I'm talking to someone. And I guess I'm talking to you. So I'm going
to wander around. I'm in the in the dining room now trying to collect my thoughts about this stuff.
I haven't really seen anyone come up with the grand idea of how we can actually make money on podcast.
All I'm seeing is rehash of traditional models, which is great, but not for a number of years.
There's just no way there's going to be enough listeners to podcasts to really make a dent with
any kind of advertising dollars. So we'll have to figure out either some other way or some kind of
bootstrap or what I think is working very well for me, at least, is find a product that you're
passionate about or make a product or a service that you're passionate about and use your podcast
to talk about it and build an audience. So it may not be very big audience, but if it's an audience
that's buying a product or the one that you like, it could certainly work. I've really been selling
coffee machines. It's unbelievable. And I didn't really think about it. I always talked about the
coffee machine and then decided to, at least to put a link on my web blog. So if you want one,
you can buy one yourself and I've sold. I should take, well, I don't want to fire up fire
fox now, but it must be close to 30 at this point. It's really unbelievable. And also I get credit
for people buying the pods and other accessories. I want to talk about Gmail for a second,
interesting the other day, Gmail, I'm going to sit down, you know mine. Gmail went down the other
day. I had never seen that happen. And it was a little frightening for a second, I'm like,
oh my god, you know, and you come to realization, what if Gmail loses all my shit? That would
really suck. I'm sure that they've probably got their data, backup situation or whatever under
control. It seems like the Google grid is one, humongous raid. So the data is probably reasonably
safe, but it does suck when the, when the service is down. And I have to say, compared to other
email services, it's not bad. I mean, I've seen Apple's email go down severely. I mean, I have my own
email server, which I've run for years. And, you know, there's always some shit that crops up with
that, too, you know. And then, yeah, the biggest problem with, with most email systems, if you,
if you use a laptop and you're roaming around is, you know, that damn port 25, you know,
SMTP port. So you can't send mail unless you've got the, you know, the proper authentication
authorization, which the web mail stuff, of course, works beautifully. And I like it very much. I am
seeing, however, a tremendous amount of spam that Google isn't catching. Now, you have the report
spam button, the keyboard shortcut for that is an exclamation point. And I do it all the time.
And all the spam that I get, I'm very consistent about that. And still, it keeps coming in,
you know. And, and, and so I don't know if, uh, if there's, there's no setting to tighten it
up or anything like that. But I think that Google has to kind of relook at some of their,
you know, some of their, we call that, uh, algorithms. There you go.
I do think it's kind of funny though how, and the funny and maybe scary at the same time.
So I received, uh, an email from a venture capital firm, uh, with some very, you know,
like some suggestions, obviously. And you look over to the right in your Gmail and on the right,
there's all these ads for, you know, looking for funding. You know, uh, and like, wow, man,
that that's pretty intense. It read my email and started giving me links to go to places
based upon the content of my email. And for some reason, I didn't really feel too bad about it,
you know, because I, I do consider email and anything I put on my computer to be just, you know,
completely open and eventually accessible to anybody. I don't think there's, you know, well,
you see this logo on my weblog. There are no secrets on the information you don't yet have.
But anyway, it would be nice if, uh, if Google could work a little bit on the, uh, on their algorithms,
get a little less spam coming in. Uh, then after yesterday's, uh, uh, little talk about, uh,
people to maintain, it's time to spark up your home.
Hello.
Yes, today's plea for editors for the, uh, uh, iPart.org directory.
Well, though, thank you very much. Lots of people wanted to contribute. Really, really,
love it. Um, and so I've already handed off at least 10 nodes this morning. I still got a lot to go
and people are also coming up with new nodes they want to add to the directory. Um, if you're interested,
it's iPart.org. Uh, iPart.org slash contribute tells you how you can contribute to, uh,
creating this directory. And as I said yesterday, uh,
Marcus's work, Marcus Maloe, I've been working with for, for many years, is working on, uh,
expanding the directory so that each individual node, um, you know, every editor of a, of a
category, which I call node managers, uh, will have a whole bunch of tools to really make that,
well, it'll be a weblog all by itself. You know, so that you can, um, really promote that category.
You should be able to, uh, work much closer with the, uh, with the people who are providing,
podcast for that category. And you should also be out, you know, be able to recruit and go out and
find stuff and not just wait for submissions. You know, let's really build this sucker out. That's
going to be fun. Um, so thank you all very much. If, if you're looking to do an OPML file to add
into the directory, um, although in the, you know, the iPart.org slash contribute, there's lots of,
options and explanations about how you can do it. I mean, you can even create your OPML file by hand.
What we're seeing though is that, you know, people who are, for instance, will do it by hand,
which is just so beautiful. This, um, A that it's simple enough for you to be able to edit this by hand,
but B that people are willing to do that kind of work. Uh, you see that in, you know, like,
note pad on windows, it adds all kinds of funky characters when you save it out. So trying to stay away
from that and for the time being, I still would suggest you use, uh, radio user land, uh, which
has a great OPML, uh, it's, uh, the whole thing is OPML. It's inherent to the program. And it works
perfectly on Macintosh and on Windows. And I was thinking, I saw that Steve Kirk's, uh, I guess
is the product manager at user land. He, uh, he, he heard the mention yesterday. I'm thinking Steve,
you know, why don't you help everybody out here, since, you know, maybe there's a discount or something
that people can get if they're working on the, on the iPod or directory, just a thought.
I don't want to beg or anything like that. Have you got to move along here? This, uh,
has 35 minutes into this. Um, wanted to plug a project of a real good buddy of mine, Peter Ford,
uh, Peter Ford was, uh, Christina's, I want to say six grade teacher. And this was the guy who sent me an email
or a sent home a letter with all the kids saying, you know, I'm Peter Ford, your, your son of
daughters, uh, uh, teacher. And if you have any questions, send me an email. And this was,
to what was this, uh, um, six years ago, five or five years ago. Uh, and at the time, I was like,
wow, you know, that's pretty cool. Have a teacher, you know, being, you know, soliciting email.
And with him, we got the whole concept of web blogs and school started, uh, at least at the
British School of Amsterdam when we started, uh, doing project web blogs, where each student
created a project in a blog, which was great because all of them had this built in audience,
not just of their peers, but their parents and brothers and sisters and grandparents and friends.
And it was very successful. And from that, we built school blogs.com, which is still running today
with thousands of, uh, free, um, uh, school blogs for teachers, students, schools, uh, you know,
all educational stuff. And he's got something else going on. He says, uh,
wonder if you give a shout out on your blog. Well, this will be the next best thing. Of course,
everything is in the show notes. Uh, to the Keepers Poetry Project that he set up with Oxford
Brooks University. Basically, use the web blog to have kids collaborate with real audience,
purpose, et cetera. You know, the educational score. Yes, I do Peter. I would love to see podcasters
include their own Keepers poem in their podcasts because it would give another twist on the whole
poetry performance angle. So there's a link to it to, uh, to, uh, actually, to his, uh, web blog where
explains everything, um, and then, of course, he winds up saying a beer or Starbucks coffee is long
overdue. Yes, dammit. It's been years, Peter. Where the hell do you live? I forgot what you live.
I'm sure you don't live in your gulf or you probably live up in the sticks. All right. Let's, uh,
got a couple more things to do here before I get out for today. Um, a promo. Yeah.
Hey, this is Ferd from AirFerg.com. My wife and I do a podcast about once a week on some random
topic that we pull out of our butts. And, uh, here's a little taste of something we did for our
Valentine's Day show. Do your dick chain. You don't know me, but I know you. I see one TV and then
pictures online and I just have to let you know that I think you're hot. I'm sure that some people
would call it a crash, but I'll leave it up to you to figure out what these feelings are. I've
admired you from afar ever since you came into the world spotlight in 1999. You're probably saying
to yourself who me and I say yes, you. I think you get the idea. If you want to check us out,
go to airferg.com. That's A-I-R-F-E-R-G dot com. Thanks for listening. Bye bye.
Airferg. Hey, I'm about ready and got my, uh, on my crap together so I can start
emptying out the MP3 feedback at gmail.com account. So once I've done that, then you can start submitting
more promos. It's been nice to have a little bit of a rest though from the promos because such
credible amount of work to go through them all and yeah, and it's also, it's a bit disturbing
because people get really pissed off when, you know, like, how can we didn't play my promo? Well,
we only got 40 minutes to do so. Oops, come here. Dogs have to go out. Come here. Jessie,
are you lying on the couch? Oh, come on, girl, go. Come on, come on, buddy. Come on, come on, come on.
Now, you won't believe this. The dog is laying on the beautiful couch
pausing the air on her back, giving me the big wide-eyed stare. Come on, girl. Come on,
come on, come on, come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
There you go, good girl. Come on. She speaks Dutch. Well, actually Dutch and any English. Come on, girl.
Push them. Swabber? That's her other little dog. Come on, come on, guys. Oh,
the door is still locked. Come on, one out. Take Christina to the school.
Yep. There you go. Good girl. Come on. Swabber, yeah, go. The other one speaks Dutch too.
Swabber, Z-W-A-B-B-E-R stands for mop. That's the Dutch word from mop. He's a little
Yorkie, Yorkshire Terrier. Yes, go ahead and bark. I just saw the nail arrive.
Where we have here. We have, oh. Everything happens at once now, who's calling?
Junkmail, junkmail. Oh, man, that's another thing about a rental home. You get so much mail for
previous tenants. It's not funny. And you have to kind of keep it
because I do tend to drop by once in a while and say, hey, have you seen my nail?
I was really excited about the Catholic insider podcast. Talked about that yesterday as well.
Father Roderick with his podcast, sound seeing of the Vatican. He sent me an email. He says he's got
some great news. He is being allowed or has been given permission to do a sound seeing tour inside
the huge power of Vatican radio. And that's not all. I'm reading this directly from the show notes.
I'll read the way he wrote. I've been talking here about podcasting and I thought the Vatican
should get into podcasting. You know what? They totally dig it. They immediately saw the great
new advantages of subscribing to an RSS feed, the possibility of getting high quality audio
to the listeners, the idea of getting people the opportunity to listen to a show whenever and wherever
they want. So I've been invited to head over to the Vatican again today. Talk with their webmaster
to explain to her, wow, there's women in the Vatican. How to set up an RSS feed and how they can
start podcasting. Ain't it cool? I almost feel like I'm not only an evangelist of the gospel,
but also a podcast evangelist, absolutely father of Roderick, you are. But in the good news about
podcasting in Vatican City. So the sound seeing tool will be up later today. It's going to be awesome.
Got to see places where no tourist has gone before. Now that is cool. And the minute it's out,
I'll add it to the sound seeing tours.com podcast feed. Very excited about that. And I really,
really do enjoy your podcast father Roderick. I love the most is when you say, oh my gosh.
I hear that a lot. Oh my gosh, he says, yeah, right on.
Hi Adam. Hey on. This is hit test number 17. Oh man, we're moving. Before we start,
let me say that I really didn't know that you had that many listeners. What do you mean?
I saw that there were 50,000 in November. All right. If that amounts,
what does grown to 80,000. Wow, that's really a lot. I hope that the hit test has contributed to that.
Yeah, yeah, it will not really contribute to that. I mean, it's it's creaking the dot
Mac infrastructure. Well, okay, the hit test. Let's start right away. This is number one.
Not hit me. Oh, I know that one. And once again.
Chuck a con. Ain't nobody. That was easy.
And this is number two.
One more time.
The Tina Turner, maybe?
It sounds like a Tina Turner production, but I don't know what it is.
Unfortunately. And now the final one.
It's short. One more time. One of my favorite songs. Without a doubt, that's talk, talk,
life's what you make it. But I don't know what number two is. So maybe we got two for three.
It really shouldn't be too hard. This is answer number one.
It's roofers and chuck a con. Ain't nobody.
Still a great song. 20 years old.
I remember I just got to stop it for a second. Reminds me of a really good friend.
And we just moved to New York in 1987 and Dan Hartman. The guy from Me Light My Fire.
Man, Patricia and I went to see a Joe Cocker show with him at the bottom line. I think
it was the bottom line. Because he and Charlie Midnight had written and produced Joe Cocker's album.
This they had just done James Brown living in America. These guys were on top of the world making
super hit records. And we were driving back to our apartment on 56th and Broadway. And Dan was driving.
And I don't know if we were drunk or a little bit high. But it was, I just remember him going
off on Chaka Khan. And he was doing this whole Chaka Khan rap. And he imitated the way she talked.
It was so, so funny. That just flashed into my mind hearing that. Unfortunately, Dan passed away.
Oh man, I think that he must have passed away 10 or 11 years ago of AIDS. And I miss him. I miss him.
Every single time I hear a song, he wrote, he sang or produced. I should, I should play. I can dream about you.
Let me see. If I have it, I'll play it for you right now. That would be just wonderful though.
Oops. I don't know what that is. Hold on. Let me see if I hope I have Dan Hartman.
I know I'm interrupting the hit test here, but... shoot. No. Okay. Well, I'm going to plan that for another
day, because that's just one of my favorite songs. Okay, back to the hit test.
And number two in today's hit test. It's Donna Summer. And dinner with Gershwin.
Ah, oh, I'm sorry. That was a hit.
Good song.
Donna Summer. The second answer in today's hit test. It's also a song without a specific chorus,
so it's a bit hot to edit with Gershwin. Answer number two. And this is the third and final
answer in today's hit test. It's talked off. Yeah. And life's what you make it.
Where did those guys go? What a great band.
This is sooo good. Talks talk. And make it is the third and final answering today's hit test.
Well, Adam, I hope you did well. Yeah. And to be honest, feedback is welcome at hittest.gmail.com.
And you can find the information about the hittest and the hittest podcast at www.yompolets.nl.
That's J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T-Dutch-N-L. Well, Adam, see you next time for another
edition of the hittest. Bye-bye. All right, young. Thank you very much once again for
lovely hittest. It is kind of the highlight of my day. I have to say it's fun to get the brain
working. Okay, that's it for the source code for today. A little bit longer than normal. Thank you
all very much for subscribing and for listening. Comments are welcome at Adam at curry.com.
You can always check out the latest podcast, the archives, and the podcast feed for this
at dailysourcecode.com. My weblog, where you will also find show notes and other ram links,
www.curry.com.
So next up for me, vacuuming, then I got some calls to do. And Christina is going to go riding it for
clocks. They're going to pick up a school and take it to the stable. And we got to eat dinner
on time, which I will be preparing, because there's a teacher of parent conferences tonight
starting at 7 o'clock. So plenty to do. Oh man, maybe I should podcast the teacher of
the conference. That'd be interesting. Well, we'll see if we do that. Anyway, I'll see you tomorrow
right here on the daily source code. Take care everybody. Thanks for listening. Bye-bye.
I'll see you all in the next one.