Using just a tin can, a ball of twine, a package of burpy flower seeds, and a nine-volt
battery, the single-handedly-invented podcasting, supported by an army of queers, purverts,
child molesters, and white supremacists, he is marching towards podcasting dominance and
forced commercialization.
The secret goal is to control the world by owning all access to the internet.
Soon, if you want to podcast on this planet, you will have to go through it.
Who is this man?
Now I'm falling in deep, pray, and for sleep, three hours and night ain't enough.
Yeah, just call their baby, Lord help, baby, and I'm just a little, a little in love.
Something tells me there's no such thing, a little in love.
Here the next thing, you know you're out by an array of myths, got to be strong, and I'm
trying to hold on, but be in that tough dream, because I'm all about her, one thing's
for sure, I'm just a little in love.
Everything's rose, neighbors getting notes, she's been over three times this week,
and last a little swim, every time I see her, I'm thinking that I must be, little in love.
Something tells me there's no such thing, a little in love.
Here the next thing, you know you're out by an array of myths, got to be strong, and
I'm trying to hold on, but be in that tough dream, because I'm all about her, one
thing's for sure, I'm just a little in love.
Well, I guess it sounds crazy, it's too late to say, be a note there, I know, bro.
Something tells me there's no such thing, a little in love.
And the next thing, you know you're out by an array of myths, got to be strong, and
I'm trying to hold on, but be in that tough dream, because I'm all about her, one thing
's for sure, I'm just a little in love, I'm just a little in love, I'm just a little in love.
I know a lot of you may have shuddle, pat, hold on a second, sorry, didn't mean to have all that going on.
I know a lot of you must have shuffled past that song, but I can't help but there's something inside me that just says,
yeah, country, I kind of like it. This guy's great. He showed up on the podcast, music network on Saturday.
I played it Saturday night, Patricia went, hey, that's pretty damn good. It's actually from the album titled
Songs for Saturday Night, so that came across just at the perfect time. And he looks good.
I mean, this is a country superstar, as far as I'm concerned, anyone else that I've seen on the country,
country music awards, come on, step on up, take the challenge with this guy. Excellent, really, really dug it.
So welcome, everybody. I thought that was the perfect way to start off a Monday. I don't know, I just got my blood flowing.
This is the Daily Source Code, Delta Sierra Charlie 2, 9 or 1. I've stopped doing the tags at the beginning of the show.
We used to do that solely for people who had shuffles and didn't have a readout.
So I hope you don't mind if you have a shuffle. You might want to consider upgrading because I got tired of doing that at the beginning labeling.
The label is on the, on the, on the file. There you go. So we had kind of a interesting end of last week.
You can imagine that I took a lot of time over the weekend to reflect and just chill out and hang out with the girls and we watched a shitload of television.
I have, I must admit, I, here's the shows that I'm completely into. This still, this, I'm a celebrity getting me out of here.
The, we're down to the finals, which is tonight. Oh, it's getting really scary. And in here are still,
Carol, a, thatcher, who was Margaret Thatcher, the Iron Ladies daughter and boy issue,
Shari, if we get her last name, she's a footballer's wife and an actress, but she's just, they call her smurf and she's just fantastic and cute and fun.
And then there's Sid Owen, who I believe is New Zealand or Australian actor and Jimmy Osmond left last night.
Little Jimmy Osmond, remember him, the long-haired lover from Liverpool. And it's, you know,
even though there's no big controversies this year, no one having sex and no one fighting.
It's actually been very nice to watch because of the bonding of this group. It's just, it's been, it's been great.
Unlike X-factor, if it's coming to the States, it's Simon Cowell's new version or his version of American Idol,
which, of course, is called something different in every different country.
It's called, what does it call pop idols here in the UK?
Yeah. So the X-factor is they're supposed to choose, and it is all based on singing and performance,
but it's supposed to be chosen upon someone having the X-factor.
And I think the only guy who actually had the X-factor, this guy Chico, I got voted out this weekend as well.
So that's, that's unfortunate. Anyway, so we watched a lot of that.
And it listened to a lot of podcasts.
I'd always try to listen to as many podcasts as possible on the weekend,
or when I'm traveling, as you can imagine, it's pretty damn hard to listen.
You can't listen to everything, but I really try to get a good sampling of most,
what people are talking about.
And so this weekend, I went into the,
Godcasters network, you know, that I enjoy inspirational messages.
I've talked about that quite a bit.
Listen to the one-year anniversary show that Steve Web did.
He interviewed me on that show, which was nice to hear.
Listen to a little father, a little rev Tim.
You know, these guys got great inspirational podcasts that always lift me up.
And I think it was a week ago, maybe two weeks ago,
that I played you a promo of something called InsightWorks.
InsightWorks.com with a Y, actually.
So it's Indian, November, Shira, Yankee, Tango,
Delo, Whiskey, Oscar, Romeo, Kilo, Sierra, dot com.
That I had, and actually when I played that promo,
I believe I said, hey, I'm subscribed.
And so I ran across their show.
And I heard them talking about me on this particular episode,
and they were referencing back to something they had sent me in email.
So I immediately went to the Gmail box to the search and loan behold on red, of course.
There was a message they had sent me.
And I wanted to share that with you on today's daily source code.
As you're up, and this is Suzanne.
We are InsightWorks.com.
That's I, N, S, Y, T, W, O, R, K, S, dot com.
And we just wanted to respond to your show yesterday.
It's a roller coaster ride that I witnessed every single day online.
People who rise to the top get kicked down,
or there's people ready to kick them down or drag them down.
Well, Robin and I had a very interesting dialogue.
After he said, honey, you've got to listen to what Adam's talking about because he is unwittingly
and unknowingly describing shadow and its projection.
So Adam, we would like to share these terms with you coming from a depth perspective,
and until these are youngy and terms, the work of CG young, and it's applicable to every person out there.
But let's start at the beginning.
Next we have our persona, okay?
That is our social mask.
That's our psychological clothing.
The way we want to be perceived by the rest of the world.
And ourselves.
We try and come.
And ourselves exactly.
And then we have the ego.
And that's all of our conscious material.
But then anything that is too painful for us to own about ourselves is relegated to the shadow.
So what happens to all that stuff that we shove in the shadow?
It's like a real shadow.
I think it's that bag of stuff that we don't want anybody to see that we drag around behind us.
Yes, I call it the invisible ball in chain that's attached to our angles that we don't acknowledge
that there in other people constantly are tripping over our invisible ball in chain.
That's our shadow stuff.
And when it's too painful for us to own, what do we do?
We project it.
Our planet has gone through two world wars because of shadow projection.
There can be individual projections.
There are cultural projections.
National any kind of group.
Right.
Any type of group.
There can be neighborhood projections.
Neighbors can get together.
And they pick one person to carry the collective nastiness for the group.
The black sheep.
That's who gets it.
Adam, you're being singled out as the online neighborhood black sheep that everybody's projecting
their stuff on.
So Adam, the people who are projecting their negative stuff onto you.
Don't claim it.
That's their stuff.
Anytime somebody projects something onto us.
Or we project onto someone else.
It's always beneficial to step back.
Look in the mirror.
That takes a lot of effort.
And that's what we say in our podcast series that looking into ourselves through depth
psychology leads to healing.
So all those people that are projecting their shadow onto you.
They should take a look at themselves.
And it takes a lot of work.
Yeah.
It's very painful to look into ourselves.
So Adam, don't claim it.
When people make these comments about you.
Yeah.
Just know it's really not about you at all.
It's more about them.
Yeah.
What's in their shadow?
Before we close, I would just like to quote something of Robert Johnson, who was a later
disciple of Young's.
Johnson says the shadow gone autonomous is a terrible monster in our psychic house.
Another quote that I want to give is from you Adam.
But I think that in general, everyone is a nice person.
This tells me the behind your social mask behind your persona.
You are a nice person.
Yeah.
And that's the golden your shadows.
The congratulations.
Thank you so much for opening up this dialogue.
And that's what we believe is that insight really does work.
Robert Johnson's book on a new shadow is available through our website.
We also have a previous podcast on the 9th of September about projection.
Check it out at insightworks.com.
I am S.Y.T.W.O.R.K.S.
.com.
Thanks for sharing the journey.
Adam and thanks for listening.
Tailwims.
Hi for Neil.
Who's guys?
Tailwims.
Hey, Robin.
Thank you very much.
I was really, really nice.
Robin and Suzanne.
You can imagine.
I spent a lot of the weekend getting my own shadow and check.
And it was really wonderful to have that message come through through a podcast.
It was perfect.
You know, it made so much sense.
And it saved me hundreds of dollars at the shrink.
Happy center class, by the way, if you're in the Netherlands.
Today is December 5th.
The day that the Dutch version of Santa Claus.
I'll just call it that.
It's not entirely fair.
But this guy shows up with a white horse.
Oh, we've talked about this so many times every year, I guess.
Two, two times so far, then, perhaps.
I talked about a lot on the weblog.
He shows up on his white horse.
He has his what they call black peats, which has always been a topic of discussion.
But he comes from Spain on a big steamboat.
And then he and his trusty steed go from rooftop to rooftop filling.
The little boys and girls shoes.
He used to be wooden shoes with all kinds of presents and goodies and candies.
And if the boys and girls were bad, then the black peats pick him up.
Put him the bag and ship him off with him back to Spain.
And so what has come out of that holiday is that traditionally families get together on this day.
They draw lots or straws.
And you have to make a surprise present for another member of the family.
And then each member of the family has a little list of stuff that they want to have.
And there's a top price limit on what everyone can spend.
And it's great.
And I do miss that.
I must say, although we've never done it ourselves.
Because we celebrate, well, I guess Christmas even for us is.
It used to be really important when Christina was young.
You know, big, you know, presents underneath the tree.
Now I think we all just kind of dig the tree, the egg nog, the fireplace.
They've got these great new fire logs, by the way, called Crackle logs.
I'm not allowed to burn wood here in the cottage, Patricia won't let me.
But these crackle logs, they burn for three hours.
It's a traditional, you know, fire log.
One hunk of biofuel probably all kinds of shitty chemicals in there.
But it now crackles too.
And it sounds just like real wood.
And that's, and that's really, really nice.
It's really a religious celebration for us at all, but just just a time to,
to warm up to the fire and snuggle with you loved ones.
By the way, that, that comment and that whole series.
And I did listen to the September 9th, September 9th,
or 7th podcast that they suggested about projection and shadow and all that.
It sounds very much like a book that I read when I was a kid.
I came, I remember the, was it,
oh, it wasn't the incredible journey that was about animals.
But it was about this, this group of people.
It was definitely science fiction,
trekking through landscape to some version of kind of like an Oz.
And everyone had a burden on their back.
And, you know, the bigger you're burdened,
that was all the crap that you wanted to throw behind you,
but it literally hung on your back and would drag people down.
Some people had enormous burdens, and some had very, very small.
And again, I really appreciate that, that helped me a lot.
Yeah, of course not everyone was as kind.
Witness, mark,
and become one of Nashaconda,
and then the Pacific Coast Hell Players from Pacific Coast Hell Way.
Because we never know when to leave well enough alone
and let a good bit die with dignity.
I bring you,
porn versus Adam Curry.
So this is the difference between porn
and Adam Curry.
All right, got it.
All right, here we go.
Porn versus Adam Curry.
I prefer my porn to be straight.
The porn I like usually has as little hair as possible.
Hey, porn versus Adam Curry.
Just like porn,
you can be in Adam Curry if you're well hung.
Oh God.
Hey, porn versus Adam Curry.
In sheer numbers of guys stroking it to one or the other,
porn still holds out a slight edge.
Oh.
Hey, porn doesn't call you up stone
in the middle of the night,
crying how you won't return their tortured love letters.
Hey, porn versus Adam Curry.
German bondage curry.
Not on my Christmas gift list.
Oh.
You know,
another difference between porn and Adam Curry
is that porn is still legal in most states
and let's just say that Adam Curry
lives in the UK for a reason.
Oh,
porn versus Adam Curry.
Hey, let's face it.
You'd probably be a lot more embarrassed
if your mom walked in on you watching Adam Curry.
Oh, God.
In turn, guys, was that yours?
That's good.
Get me some soup.
Okay.
Hey, porn versus Adam Curry.
Both made this year's top 10 list
of things that give boners to the incarcerated.
Oh.
Oh, porn versus Adam Curry.
The San Fernando Valley
isn't littered with the broken dreams of cocaine
addicted teenage runaways who are in Adam Curry movies.
Oh.
Porn versus Adam Curry.
Given the choice,
Madge Weinstein would rather be in porn.
Oh, God.
You know,
I've heard that Ron Jeremy refuses to perform
with Adam Curry on moral grounds.
Oh.
Hey, it finally.
Porn versus Adam Curry.
Adam Curry show is not made by some
CD characters in Southern California.
That's our show.
Check him out at Pacific Coast.
Hellway.com.
Mark Yoshimoto Nemcroff in the Pacific Coast
Hellplayers.
Thank you, guys.
That was nice.
I hope, well, I actually, I'm glad my mom
isn't listening to this.
Hey, by the way, so I didn't get out
over the weekend wasn't able to go.
Wasn't able to go flying.
So that's screwed everything up.
I'm not going to go now until probably in the new year.
No, I'm sorry.
Just before Christmas.
Don't tell my mom if you know her.
Patricia Christine and I are going to fly over
going to surprise her with a surprise visit.
So that'll be the next trip.
So no traveling in the in the Charlie 182 for a little bit.
Unfortunately, God was so looking forward to.
And yesterday was a beautiful day.
Today was fantastic.
But I had to move everything around.
So I didn't get around to that.
That story that I talked about.
The vegan podcast, the the the podcast,
whose feed was hijacked.
That's quite a story now.
I'm reading about it everywhere.
And as always, there are multiple sides of the story.
I don't.
I really don't think there was any tremendous malicious intent.
I think this sounds like a lot of communication.
Confusion as it comes to ransomning and all that kind of stuff.
But there is a real problem with with RSS feeds.
And I've even noticed myself now that on the pod keywords,
which I don't believe I registered for.
They have a version of my feed there.
Who knows how many times people have subscribed there.
Audio, which I've I don't think I've claimed my feed.
But I believe that there's multiple feeds over there.
Now, of course, at issue here,
forget all the hijacking stuff.
Just the idea of caching feeds.
Very much the way feed burner does.
There is an associated risk with all this.
And I guess that's just never a good policy to be working on a copy of anything
than the original, which could change at any moment, even if it sucked in.
You know, witness all the issues we've had with iTunes and people not being able to
change their feeds.
And yeah, there's automatic ways to do it.
But with still many podcasters, there are a lot of people falling off the edge
and just not getting stuff done.
And that really does bite.
I don't have any clear cut solutions for it.
But if it all possible, once you have a feed that is your podcast feed,
keep it what it is.
And the best way, and a lot of people, I don't know if you understood what I was talking about
by getting a domain name.
But that really is the best way to make your feed be able to migrate.
Excuse me.
I didn't say hell.
Do in that, you know, because when you see that sense of
commercial and television, you're going to think of me.
That's a daily source code, at least.
So, I have the most fucked up feed in the world.
What is it like?
Weblogs.com slash zero zero zero zero zero one four zero something like that.
Slash category is it's horrible.
But the folks at user land have told me that when I'm ready for it,
they'll be happy to put a redirect in, which is going to be very cool,
which I totally appreciate.
Speaking of hijacked, I don't know if you were following the story about
podcast pickle, which is podcast directory.
Someone hacked into podcast pickle.com into their servers.
And from what I read online, apparently someone actually did hold
the guys at podcast pickle ransom for like 10 grand
to, you know, to give them their code back.
God, you know, I'd like some of those smart people that I've read from
this weekend to go and, you know, track that guy down.
That's a real asshole Christel mighty.
So apparently podcast pickle is back up.
They're back on the air, but they lost their forums, which I think is really
a travesty because forums are such an important piece of, you know,
recording the, the community.
And so, you know, there'll be no way to get back to, you know,
what the, the social community at podcast pickle was talking about.
They've never, all those links that go to forum articles, Google
and other search indices.
Oh, man, that's, that's really, really nasty.
Let me see.
So we unleashed pod say for peace.
If every day we're Christmas, already the most played song on the pod
safe music network, just going gangbusters.
I put a link to, to the page, so you can see which podcast of play
to misjust outrageous.
So it's number one for the month already.
I think it'll stay that way.
So I think the support is, is just phenomenal.
I believe slow is in the process of getting the web page up for,
I think it'll be at pod, pod safe for peace.
And today we're all over the iTunes music store calling,
trying to get them to, let us put that song in,
hopefully on that.
I think they do uploads on Tuesdays or maybe on Fridays or something like
that.
So instead of it taking weeks, as it does with most independent music,
we probably, I think we'll be able to slip it by it.
It'd be great if they would help us and support.
I know the folks over there listen and we're going to put in some calls today.
So that you could actually buy it.
And it's not for the DRM that we would put up on iTunes,
but solely for ease of purchasing, I think, is what it's all about.
There's just no way we're going to get any type of purchasing
up and running on the pod safe music network and time for Christmas.
Yeah, maybe around Christmas, which wouldn't make a lot of sense.
But if you have a podcast, please go over to the pod safe music network
register as a podcaster if you're not already.
And I give it a spin.
You'll find it under pod safe for peace.
Some people have had problems finding it in the PMN.
Something that I noticed, someone's got me an email about this as well,
is that if you have more than one show on the pod safe music network,
it really doesn't work for you because when you report back,
you report back on your show, which you registered with,
which in my case is a daily source code.
So we have to come up with a way to add another show to your account.
Which I don't think is a hard thing to do.
Because I was putting together the pod show Christmas podcast feed,
which you can find at xmus.podshow.com,
which I'm having a great time doing.
Lots of fantastic feedback.
I decided not to put one song per episode.
Even if it had a Christmas greeting over the intro or anything like that,
I felt it would make a lot more sense to put two back to back with a greeting
in between.
Because we don't want to just be sending out the MP3 files.
It's kind of defeating the whole purpose of allowing pod safe music
to be played for promotional purposes.
So now there's already six songs out there.
They come in pairs.
And I think that if you subscribe to the feed and then maybe make a playlist
to only of those portions of those song bits,
those bytes, those chunks that come in,
throw it on shuffle.
I think it might actually work.
I think we get like 10 or 15 in there to be 30 tracks.
And I think the repetition won't even be too bad.
If you've heard the transition a couple of times from one song to the next.
And gosh, there's so much good stuff coming in.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
So regarding the pod safe for peace,
we've received comments.
I don't know if they're all,
I think most of them relate to pod safe music.
Let's start with Howard Greenstein first.
It's Howard Greenstein from the confessions of an integral podcast
with Barry Coral.
Barry Coral.com.
And I'm giving you a little audio feedback about UNICEF's response
when Slaw or whomever asked for an endorsement
of the pod safe for peace project.
What you might not know,
even though you've known me on an office since the on ramp days,
was that at the Twin Towers Fund,
where I was at for two years after 9-11,
I managed over $168 million for the families of fire police
and emergency workers killed on 9-11.
And we literally got hundreds of off
from independent artists to donate the proceeds of records
to the families.
And most of the time,
we couldn't accept it.
In fact, the only thing that I recall really accepting
was the big Sony Madison Square Garden concert
that generated lots of millions of dollars.
And the reason was not that we didn't want to support
these independent artists,
but basically not for profit law and lawyers
and accounts need to audit projects
that are endorsed by a charity under American law.
Now, I'm not sure how UNICEF works,
but I suspect it's similar.
And again, I'm not a lawyer,
but I have a pretty good perspective on this.
Charity accepts a donation of a record proceeds
and is that grosser is that net, et cetera.
They need to be able to audit it.
They need to be able to make a legal agreement
that says you agree that any proceeds of gross or net
will come to name of charity, et cetera, et cetera,
and lawyers have to sign on both sides
and agree what the grosses and what the net is with it.
Anyway, it becomes a big deal.
And therefore, that's probably why UNICEF
when hearing that you might get a couple of thousand dollars
to them said we love it, please send the money,
but we can't officially endorse the project.
It would just have too much legal and accounting overhead.
So for anyone wondering why they probably
couldn't endorse this project, my suspicion is that's the case.
One other thing I wanted to just say
that the project sounds great,
what if every day for Christmas is a great song,
we've created the Slaw and all the artists that did it,
and you for coming up with this idea,
and I hope that a whole bunch of money
goes towards UNICEF's way,
because that would really be a wonderful thing
for the children in the world
who would benefit from this money.
So thanks for working on the project.
I thought the listeners might find that useful,
and I'll catch up with you soon.
Take care. Bye-bye.
I'm great Howard. Thank you.
Yeah, I kind of figured that,
and I saw when I had actually discussed that.
By the way, two more credits need to go out
Orlando, the co-writer of the song along with Slaw,
and also we've got,
when I premiered yesterday to mention John Hammond,
who also played as a great musician,
who I met at the in Ontario,
the podcast,
the portable media expo.
Yeah, it kind of figures that,
I don't think it's so much that UNICEF rejected,
because we couldn't bring in a large chunk,
or couldn't guarantee a large chunk of money.
I think it's more because the vibe you get immediately
is more of like, you know,
who you guys trying to take our brand
and trying to propel yourselves into something.
That's the vibe that I've gotten before with charities,
which is kind of funky.
I understand it's all protectionist-based,
because I'm sure there's a lot of people
that want to say, hey, listen to me,
listen to me as an artist,
because I'm doing something for UNICEF,
and you should promote me,
and here's my UNICEF tag,
and I'm sure that that can be a real issue.
Let's so be it.
You know, everyone's hearts in a right place,
and I think that's really what it's about.
And if not, it's awareness for UNICEF,
that helps to boost excellence.
Did I have something here?
Yeah, a couple more audio comments.
Hey Adam, this is Avi.
One thing I've hated about traditional radios
that they play Christmas songs back to back to back.
And so when you announced that you were doing
some Christmas song,
what if everyday were Christmas?
I figured, oh dear,
just another thing to fast forward through when I listen.
But then when you were done, I figured,
well, I might as well actually listen to what
once and see what it's like.
And so I heard it,
and it's been what three days now,
and it's totally stuck in my head,
and I can't get rid of it.
And then you were talking about how when you were
figuring when you first heard of it,
you said, oh, you know,
we could do a weird,
the world kind of thing with this,
which of course got that song in my head.
And then the two songs just kind of
bred together and came out with this mutant thing
that kind of ends up like this.
We are the world,
we are the children,
we are the ones to make a proud day,
so let's start giving.
There's a choice we're making
what's even our own lives.
There's true make a better day,
just you and me.
So, yeah?
Well, I have a Merry Christmas
into those two mid-applies.
How can I make a semiaf?
And I'll see you around.
You know, that's a mashup,
is what you just did there.
That was good.
I like that.
Oh, man, most excellent.
And now the pod save for piece song
has even been covered in another language,
a Dutch version showed up,
which I'm not going to,
I'm not going to bother you with that,
but it's on the pod save music network.
Let me see if I have the link here.
We'll drop that into the show notes,
obviously Dutch pod save for piece.
Hold on.
I actually created a link for myself
for the artist details.
I'm going to make sure I tell you.
A Berry and Uly.
Our Dutch podcasters,
who occasionally write songs,
they made a Dutch cover of pod save for pieces.
Shit, you know what?
I'm here anyway.
I'll just click on the listen button,
so you can just hear a little piece of it.
Mine as well.
They did their own track too,
by the way.
It's very cool.
So, you know what?
I think if there are Dutch pod save
and music artists,
go for it.
I'm sure Slower would be happy
to help you up with some tracks.
And if there's any other languages out there
that any other people speak other languages,
they want to put that together.
Dude, it's cool.
Look at how look at what we're doing.
This lays me.
They're out of my name's Scheme.
I'm a teenage podcaster.
I just got my podcast,
the Nodcast started like three weeks ago.
And I got to say,
I am just loving being part of this community.
I've been a listener since
I'd say middle of the summer sometime
when I discovered it and decided to check it out
in iTunes.
And I just,
I just loved being part of this.
I think this new Christmas song
that just came out is great.
I'd loved playing on my show.
It may, oh man,
it just made me kind of,
sent shivers through my spine
when I heard it on your show.
So, I've been listening to
the Daily Source code for a while.
Since I've been listening to podcasts.
And I was just wondering,
you,
from what you said,
it sounds like,
if a song is licensed under
Asked at BMI or whatever,
then you can't play on a podcast.
So, if your license is this song,
under that,
then doesn't that mean I'm going to have to pay
if I want to play it,
or that I just can't?
Because I don't know whatever.
It wasn't on a PMM.
So, I'll just probably play it anyway,
but I don't know much about this,
obviously,
but I was just had that question.
Also,
not necessarily,
in regards to what Madge had to say
the other day,
I have been having troubles
with iTunes.
It's not that my show showed up
and then disappeared,
but I just cannot get it to show up.
Because I submitted my,
my feed to the music store before
and had anything in it.
Got an email from the music store
saying that I had abused my privileges
or something like that,
and that there was a problem with my feed,
and I needed to fix it,
and then resubmit it.
Well,
there's obviously no way to resubmit a feed
to the music store,
because I've put something in my feed
and resubmit it,
and it says it's already been submitted.
So,
I've been having quite a bit of trouble with that.
I tried calling Apple a couple times,
and apparently they put it under the heading
of computer technical support,
and they're going to charge me 50 bucks
just to talk to someone about this problem.
So, I don't really know what's up with that.
I've been trying not to exactly rely
on the music store for showing up my podcast,
and I've been just trying to work around it.
So,
on a lighter note,
I just want to thank you for putting up this
Xmas.podshow.com thing,
and for putting out the original idea
for the pod save for peace song,
which I love.
And,
I guess that's about it.
I should be making a promo soon.
I'll definitely send that to you,
and submit it to promos.podshow.com.
Anyway,
thanks for definitely being one of my main
inspirations,
and it's great to be part of this community.
Thanks.
Yo, Shme.
Okay, first of all,
what I really liked about that feedback,
listening to Shme.
That's me.
I can tell.
So,
enthusiastic little podcaster there.
Shme, fantastic.
And welcome.
I'm glad you're digging it so much.
Let me work backwards.
Regarding iTunes,
yeah, that is a problem.
So, first of all,
I hope that spending this promo or this feedback
on the source code gets you some exposure,
so that's the nodcast.com.
And I know the folks over at Apple
listen to the show,
so maybe they'll be able to help you.
And I guess the only other thing would be
is to to resubmit with a whole new feed URL.
I know it sucks,
but this is,
you kind of fell in between
between the cracks,
you know,
I wish I could help you,
but this,
you know,
yeah,
you have no idea how many people
call me or email me about this problem.
And,
you know,
all you can do is just put it in the queue,
it's hard running a huge directory
as a single entity.
It really is very,
very hard.
Let me see.
Oh, yes.
So, now about AskCabbyMI.
Even though I've gone over before,
I want to go over it one more time.
And this only is applicable
to music that is licensed for performance,
so that's broadcast and performance otherwise,
through AskCabbyMI.
It appears that in most other countries,
certainly the ones we've heard from in Europe,
are the Netherlands,
Germany, France,
Finland,
and I'm sure most others,
if you sign a deal with them for your performing rights,
then you actually can't play it
even on your own podcast
without paying that performance rights.
So that's a whole
another can of worms that we've got to work on.
But in the States,
if music is licensed under AskCabbyMI,
and the person who registers that
with the pod save music network owns everything else,
then you have a license to play it,
because it's a special license for you
and AskCabbyMI recognize that.
Subsequently, if the song,
just like if every day we're Christmas,
which is registered with AskCabbyMI
through SLOW and Orlando,
if that is played on the radio,
then actual money gets paid,
and it'll go to a SLOW and Orlando,
and they promise that they will give their proceeds
to UNICEF,
and SLOW is also promised to clarify
exactly how the mechanics of that work
once he gets the website up,
and I'm confident that that'll be very cool,
no problem.
The thing that isn't allowed though,
you can't come into the pod save music network
as a broadcaster,
like a radio station,
or television,
or movie company,
or any other thing,
and download a track,
and then play it on the radio,
without permission,
because that is not stated in the terms,
so that would be a violation.
And I think that's right,
although I'm sure that anyone who gets that request
will probably want their song played,
but then they also might want to consider
registering with AskCabbyMI.
So I hope that clears it up,
I mean, good luck with all the items,
Crapola.
Hey Adam,
this is Zach from the Sounds with Einstein podcast,
that sounds with Einstein.com.
First,
I wanted to say thank you for playing my promo
on Delta CR at Charlie 284.
That was just really cool to hear myself
talking about my podcast on your show.
And I'm also want to thank everybody
for downloading it.
I had about 200 downloads on that.
It was pretty cool.
Anyway, I had a couple of questions for you.
First one,
I'm a student out here in Las Vegas.
I got a UNLV,
and I'm studying radio production
and communications.
And I want to get a job at one of the local
radio stations out here.
Now, of course,
as you know,
in order to get an on-air job,
you have to send them an air check or a demo.
So I wanted to know what your opinion was
on using a podcast instead of an air check
or a demo.
Fair enough.
And my second question is...
Hold on, I guess I should answer that now then.
So first of all,
you're in an interesting position.
I also studied communications and radio
and broadcasting in college.
And there was nothing that I learned there
that I didn't learn much more about
while actually being on the air
at the radio station at the college.
WIT to be everybody.
We're in Debonghits.
Let's see, I'm college.
Salem West Virginia.
The rhythm of West Virginia.
10 watts.
Son up to sunrise.
Sunrise to sunset is what I'm in.
Now, I wouldn't use it.
I would not use it as an air check
because you're talking about two different worlds.
There's no way.
If you've never seen Howard Stern's movie
check it out.
There's a certain point
when Howard Stern gets hired at WMBC in New York
and the program director
brilliantly played, by the way, in this movie.
Calls Howard into his offices.
He says, look man, you're not saying the call
that it's right.
It's got to be WIN!
But he'll see.
And then he'll Howard's going to put in
his finger in his ear going, WIN!
WIN!
And it's true.
So you're not going to like it.
You're just not going to like it.
I think that you're in a unique, unique position
and situation to use what's being taught.
And I'm sure there's a lot of audio skills
and management skills.
Use that for your podcast.
Get the podcast cranking.
Forget about the local radio station.
I think you're really not going to like it.
Certainly not.
If you've witnessed the freedoms of podcast
and you are not going to enjoy it.
But of course, then you could do a podcast.
About becoming a radio DJ and talk about the differences.
That could be interesting.
But I would not suggest using your air check.
Your podcast is an air check.
If you don't care about getting the job,
sure, let's see what he says.
But I think you do care.
So you probably want to give them what they want to hear.
But not let them know about your secondary agenda.
Oh, shoot.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to continue playing.
Oh, my God.
Hey Adam, this is Zach from the Sounds of the Einstein.
I think pod safe music.
Okay.
Instead of an air check or demo.
Second part of his question.
Fair enough.
And my second question is,
what do you think about playing pod safe music on the radio?
I know that you already do that on pod show, on serious.
I'm talking about terrestrial based radio.
Do you think it's a good idea?
Do you think it's a bad idea?
And if somebody were to want to do that,
how would they go about doing it?
Should they just download the song and play it on the radio?
Or should they contact the artists and get their permission?
Anyway, so those are the only two questions I got.
Other than that, I invite everybody to listen to my podcast.
Sounds with Einstein.
It sounds with Einstein.com.
I talk about local vagus news and construction updates and events
and stuff that go on around here,
as well as I'm playing music from the pod safe music network.
And local artists from Las Vegas,
as you know that there's a incredible music scene out here,
because of all the musicians that are in all the shows.
And I got a couple of CDs from guys that are in the blue man group production.
And all that.
It's some of the most amazing music I have ever heard.
So I invite everybody to check that out.
Sounds with Einstein.com.
And thanks for listening.
My name is Jack.
Okay, actually for a second there,
I thought you'd found a bug in the terms of the pod safe music network.
And then I realized we don't actually play individual songs on serious.
Serious is a collection of pod cast that already exist in which songs are included,
which is a collective works.
So we're actually playing pod cast and not pod safe tunes by themselves.
So you heard my comment earlier to,
to what's his name again.
So you know,
probably not a good idea,
but contact the artist and ask him,
then it should be no problem at all if they say yes,
and maybe even say,
hey, can you hold on just a second or two until I get registered with Ask AppDMI?
Makes a lot of sense.
Oh, man.
Excuse me.
Enough talking, hey.
Let's, yeah, yeah, let's play some Christmas music.
I'm not going to play if every day we're Christmas,
because that's getting plenty of pod play.
But I found this one that I really like very much.
Beatrice Erickson.
This is Christmas without you on the source code.
Look and through my window the snow is falling down.
If only I could find a way to turn back time.
All those colored lights reminds me of you.
We sure could find a way to make it through.
Not alone in night without you,
this crystal.
Now the stars fall down.
This Christmas.
So much cooler now than I do.
Let you spend my Christmas without you.
Christmas without you.
Silent memories in a silent night.
Takes me back to days gone by.
Used to love this time of gear when I had you.
I wish I find a way to make it through.
Not alone in night without you,
this Christmas.
Now the stars fall down.
This Christmas.
So much cooler now than I do.
But you spend my Christmas without you.
I wish I find a way to make it through.
Not alone in night without you,
this Christmas.
Now the stories fall down.
This Christmas.
Now the stars fall down.
So much cooler now than I do.
But you spend my Christmas without you.
Without you.
Beatrice Ericsson.
Christmas without you from the Podsave Music Network.
You find it at Podsave Music Network.com.
Over the weekend I told you I was doing a lot of reflecting.
I read a lot of interesting comments on the web about me.
I think that analyzing all that.
There's a lot of benefit that I got from reading a lot of the comments.
I've kind of slipped into a very old bad habit.
Due to the fact that these days,
the daily source code is Simulcast on a serious satellite radio.
Stars 103.
So you had the Howard Stern channels and then we're next,
which is I think very cool because I know that we're picking up a lot of listeners.
People going for Howard Stern,
hitting the button to change the channel once and then dropping into either the source code.
But probably more interesting for that audience,
specific host hell way,
Mads Weinstein,
Don and Drew.
And we have many more on the show.
But for that reason, I've been making the show 48 minutes and 30 seconds.
Or alternatively 49 minutes.
And what happens is the variable in making the time work.
And this is how you do it on the radio is you kind of pattern your speech.
And what you're talking about to fit into the time slots that you've allowed yourself.
So you can still get to everything that you lined up.
You know what?
That sucks because I drop stuff.
I forget to talk about things.
I don't take the time.
So in about 10 seconds, the show on serious will end.
And you will be greeted by Mark Yoshimoto-Nemkoff and the specific host health players in specific host hell way.
So enjoy that.
And those of you who are listening to the podcast.
Yes, you get all the juicy bits.
Exactly.
Also, what I've decided is out of the hundreds,
and the thousands of audio comments and promos.
Just go look at promos.potshow.com where people actually take the time to register and upload and then post their promo online.
There's, you know, there's tons there.
Just imagine how many people fire me off and email with an MP3 file attached.
So I think that most of the time, although it's hard, you miss a lot.
They do scroll by and you can miss them.
And please, your subject line in any email is the most important advertisement you can make for getting it read to anybody on any email system.
I'm going to become very, very selective.
It used to be where, you know, it was kind of like almost a non-democratic thing.
You know, it's like, okay, I'll grab the first four here.
And I found look at the time lengths and listen to them a little bit.
And then really, I like to respond to them in real time on the air.
But I just don't think that works anymore.
So I'm really going to do a lot of screening for the promos stuff that I like.
You know, I think it'll be relevant or something that promotes something that's new.
It won't just be random promos, which, believe it or not, is kind of what I've been doing.
Because just to grab stuff and get as many promos out as possible.
But I think that does hurt the quality and the listening experience.
Okay.
Big story in the financial times this morning here in the UK,
that cable system NTL is going to acquire virgin mobile.
870 million pounds, I think, so it was at $1.5 billion.
And the paper here, but the funny thing in it,
and you, I've talked about virgin mobile extensively.
In fact, I checked this morning, my phone is still blocked.
You know, it's still unusable after I dealt with customer service for a week and then finally gave up and despair.
And I went to team mobile.
The funny thing was, is that it said something to the effect of NTL is so historically bad at customer service.
They really need the virgin brand to help them drop it off.
Oh my god, if you have a voting share in this top, that's not true.
Virgin mobile is, you know, is a horrible customer service.
At least from my experience, and that's well documented.
Virgin Atlantic, fantastic, love it, but not virgin mobile.
My god, something else that I've been reading a lot about now is that Tevo,
the service, is offering podcasts.
They have a module that I believe only the newest or latest edition of the Tevo boxes can handle.
And I don't know if they have their directory or what they're sucking in.
If anyone has any info on that, please let me know.
It sounds very exciting.
Because primarily, I'd say, for video podcasts, because, you know, that's what's going to be.
That's what I'm enjoying so much about that front row stuff that that software that comes now with the new iMac G5s.
I use it almost exclusively for video podcasts because you can use the remote control.
And just, you know, boom, you go into a podcast.
I actually have a playlist set up and it just, oh, that doesn't work, right?
It doesn't.
Hello?
I see fingers.
Hey, baby.
Hi.
You coming or are going?
No, no, no.
I just want to give you a couple of stems that I have.
Stamps.
So you can do your.
Oh, God.
I hate that so much.
No, you do.
How many of you get me?
No, these are only four.
Not get you.
Four.
I need like 20.
These were in my desk downstairs.
Okay.
You're going to get more.
I'm going to get you more.
Thank you, hun.
That's it.
Okay.
Tell them that I have a call again.
Oh, if you show the first defense.
It doesn't work.
The nose spray we talked about.
Yeah.
It doesn't work.
No.
It can't help.
It just can't help you.
Oh, God.
I'm going to talk.
Please come close to the microphone.
Super Margaret for example.
Oh, man.
We watched.
You know those.
We went shopping Saturday.
Yeah.
And we didn't hear a guy.
People sneak.
And we're looking at each other and we think.
Uh huh.
How many meters?
27 meters.
The spray.
Yeah.
That's the sketch.
So high.
I do anything.
You know, I eat a lot of vitamins.
It just doesn't help.
It's not that I'm sick.
But it's so annoying.
Yeah.
Oh, very annoying.
Especially because you had the whole photo shoot so you were tired.
Yeah.
And then that she says jumps on you.
After that boom.
Boom.
Okay.
Well, so far you're doing okay.
You're doing better.
Yeah.
And we're going to London tomorrow.
Yes.
We are going to see the Christmas light.
I went to London.
I told Patricia that it was beautiful.
We never go.
But we do go now and then because we went for, you know, a couple of weeks.
We're going to have a train ride.
Yeah.
That's fun.
Very romantic.
Yeah.
We're going to have tea.
And it's interesting.
Interesting.
How last night could Patricia kind of turned this into a.
Yeah.
And we're going to all kinds of great clothes for you.
I'm like, wait a minute.
Did I just get rangled in the clothes shopping for me?
No.
I don't think so.
Oh, you hate it.
Oh, God.
I don't care.
I just really don't care.
And I know I remember in Holland people was thinking that you.
You are such a cool guy.
You always wear it.
He's wearing this, you know, the right clothes and the right hair.
And he's so vain.
Not.
No.
That is that is just the.
Absolutely not you.
That is the aura you built up around me.
Well, you know, if you do you performance on TV or you.
Yeah.
You're a parent.
You have to look good.
And I always say, you know, where this.
Where that.
But I know that you are absolutely.
Absolutely.
Not interested.
That's correct.
Yeah.
Although I must say that when you're charming guy.
Well, thank you.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Natural charm.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
I love you.
All right.
Bye.
The depudations.
The runners podcast.
Steve runner.com.
Folks.
Something tells me that the first mouse trap wasn't designed to catch mice at all.
But to protect the cheese from burglars.
Steve runner.com.
opinion.
There is nothing.
So tragic.
As seeing a family pull the part.
By something as simple as a pack of wolves.
Steve runner.com.
Observation.
You know, it takes a big man to cry.
But it takes a bigger man to laugh at that man.
Steve runner.com.
And rambling guy.
So I'm not afraid of insects taking over the world.
It would take about a billion ants just to aim a gun at me.
Little little fiery.
And you know what I'm doing while they're aiming at me.
I'm slipping off to the side.
And then kicking the gun out of their hands.
From holes to during distance.
Long, long.
I'm Steve runner.
And if you love to run.
I'm training for a roader.
It's your marathon.
And have a need for filling your iPod or MP3 player.
And even worse than static.
Then subscribe to Fitbitations.
A podcast for runners.
That's Steve runner.com.
You'll hear me each week.
It's I trained for my next marathon.
Running out of breath through the back roads.
It's central Massachusetts.
We'll talk about running training in the injuries that spite us.
As I'm out.
I might be getting long runs.
Listen in as a middle-aged middle of the pack.
Slightly asmatic distance runner.
Hits the glycogen law.
Mumbling incomprehensibly.
As he wonders aloud.
Exactly what the hell I'm doing out here.
Fitbitations.
The runners podcast.
Steve runner.com.
Running.
And take her.
Yeah.
I'm a spectrcajiao from the typical PC user podcast.
www.typicalpcusier.com.
I wanted to send you this because I heard this.
That was played a Gilmore game yesterday.
And I wanted to do kind of a
Translation of the official ad in the spirit of truth and advertising.
So here it goes.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
Okay. Translation.
If you buy earthlink, we'll make sure all those assholes don't send you spam.
Or do all the fishing scams on you.
We're earthlink.
We believe your personal information should be just that.
Personal.
Earthlings are not going to jack your running.
Give your email address to every Tom Dick and Harry comes knocking at the door.
Sign up with them.
Your information remains private.
And we believe your internet should be a friend.
Not a fo.
We're earthling.
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthling.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthling.
We revolve around you.
Translation.
We care about you.
The customer.
We're not doing you a favor by being your internet provider.
Some come sign up.
Don't get the spam.
Be protected.
Enjoy your internet experience.
Remember earthling in the old days of modems.
We all used to be on it.
Come back.
Okay.
And on that's it.
That's my truth and advertising.
This time from Earthlink.
They keep it simple.
No bullshit.
Go to them.
Let's reach you right.
You'll get good service.
This is Victor Kahial of the typical PC user podcast.
www.utificalpcusier.com.
Come on over to the site to bring all the newbies with you.
I'll show you how to use computers.
Instead of computers using you.
Merry Christmas from Cape Town Stripes at Cape Town Stripes.com.
America has fallen in love with distorted view daily.
Well, I guarantee you you just show that they first amendment rise.
You guarantee even idiots free speech.
Haven't been listening to the show.
Here's what you've been missing.
She's over his stuffed anus.
He topped it with a cherry tomato.
Nice.
This is the plural of cactus cacti.
Do not anchor the dark lord by correcting him.
But actually think you're right.
I think he is cacti.
I can fly higher than an eagle hairy boasted.
I've also got a ten inch uncut cock to fuck the shit out of
the shid out of thorny ass bitches.
And there's Harry fucking the shid out of thorny ass bitches.
You were just having cyber sex with a 14 year old girl.
You know what that makes you that makes you a pedophile.
I'm, I'm, I'm meets the skypeer.
All right, and that's punishable by law.
Hello.
Over 220 shows later and I'm still acting like a complete jackass.
To start a few celebrates it's one year birth day next week.
Where will year two lead us?
Join us at disorderview.com to find out.
Chants it's our.
It'll have something to do with stuffed anuses and cheese.
It's ten minutes of your life you'll never get back.
More like 20 minutes really.
Come for the news of the weird.
Stay for the audio pornography.
What?
It's the just a distorted view show.
We were doing so well up until that point.
Won't we?
Tim Fantastic Ben.
Love the show.
You know, I'm subscribed.
And although your promo's may not be the most family-friendly.
A happy birthday with your one year anniversary.
I'm subscribed to this podcast, which is a video podcast called Crooks and Liars.
And I'm shoot man.
I'm now I'm looking for this video that I found.
I don't know why it's not showing up here.
Hold on.
Just go for the whole thing.
And it was a piece of video from.
Gosh darn it.
No, I don't have it.
I don't get it.
Wait, maybe this is it.
Let me see.
This could be it.
Hold on.
I'm not a good authority to be honest.
Not about a run.
Well, I wonder if I should.
Well, okay.
This makes it horrible that I don't remember.
Stop.
The quiet.
Thank you.
Okay.
The point of what it was.
It was a reporter who was in the field in Iraq.
I guess he was still in Iraq and he was on the phone.
He was being asked about President Bush's claim that there were, and I'm just paraphrasing.
I don't know the exact facts anymore.
About 40 Iraqi units on the front line fighting side by side with the US forces.
And this guy said, hey, look, I was there at the time.
And I don't know if this was a year ago or a month ago or a week ago.
He said, but, you know, those, those, the Iraqi guys are, you know, not at all fighting side by side.
They're being told what to do, the green berets are in charge.
And he really was discrediting the Iraqi forces.
Okay.
So having been there and having received the grand tour by the Dutch Marines, they took me around
to several different camps where Iraqi soldiers, or to be precise the ICDC, the Iraqi civil defense coalition.
I think that's what it stands for.
And the Iraqi police were being trained.
Now, this was February of 2004.
So we're coming up on two years.
And I'm not quite sure how long they had been training them.
You know, so the claim is, hey, they ran these guys through three or four weeks of training and then they're good to go.
Now, I don't know what boot camp is for for US Marines and US, quote, security forces.
But when we were there, we received several demonstrations.
And I have to say that, I don't know if you remember the series, Dad's Army.
It was very much like Dad's Army.
You know, someone would call a right face and then half of them would turn left and half of them would turn right.
And then they were reloading their.
So the drill, the drill sergeants in front of all the troops, and then the command was to reload their AK-47s.
And like, you know, they're like pointing the thing in him and throwing magazines in and out.
And everyone's freaking out about how unsafe that was.
So I don't know, but two years certainly, two years ago, I was not at all impressed by the Iraqi forces at all.
And I think that if they kept on training that way for two years, well, they certainly must be good enough to participate.
They all seemed dedicated. That's for sure. And they had their own ranks within the leadership of the men.
And they were, I thought they looked like damn good soldiers, just.
They, they certainly weren't by, by no means, as far as I'm concerned, ready to go into combat to win.
What to do anything effective.
So I just wanted to, you know, spin that back since, since I actually was there.
And like I say, I'd have to know a little bit more about what, what missions President Bush was talking about, but certainly two years ago, no freaking way.
All right.
One more song.
Oh, I feel so good about doing this. Now the show was balanced.
I can end with a song and it will be done.
And it's not a Christmas song.
Yeah.
This is a hollow horse, beggars town.
I've become what I'm most despised, even I believe.
Oh, my old eyes, but I've fooled no one.
Now I'm biting my old tongue.
I'm not off the right.
But once again, I'm wrong.
So good to blame on me.
It doesn't matter anymore.
You say the damage has been done.
I see I love what's already flowed.
In beggars town.
No love this matches.
Everything I'm though and love.
I was hoping I could forget.
You are a mealist to me now.
There's no cure and I'm addicted to you yet.
Who can I depend upon?
To get me out of this.
You've got this sweetest smile.
Can such a part of this kiss.
My hands are shaking with rage.
It's too late now to negotiate.
For all the love that's turned to hate.
And it seeks without a trace.
Oh, the blame on me.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Because I've been here so many times before.
I feel ill and I'm heart sore.
In beggars town.
No love this matches.
So this is what we are.
And this is what we've been through.
I've been nothing left to give.
I keep everything I has to you.
Be yourself.
In beggars town.
It's like a minute.
It's a surf, I'm just a swimming pool.
So, around the long podcast for today, what is it now or an eight minutes?
Just because we're going to ignore the serious 48.5 mark, doesn't mean that they're all
going to be this long.
Just on a Monday there's so much to talk about, so many things that happen over the weekend.
So they may even be shorter, which I think is also good, and then what we'll do on
serious is we'll fill that up with Podsake music, so that we maintain the absolute
highest quality possible for the podcast.
Alright, daily source code.com is where you can find the latest episodes and the podcast
feed, at amacurry.com for all your feedback.
And of course, there's promo.podshow.com.
We can upload your promo.
Still need some holiday greetings, because I just need more as many as possible for the
Christmas Podshow podcast at xmus.podshow.com, so you can upload those there as well.
And I'll meet you back here tomorrow for another edition of the daily source code.
There we go.
I'd say that was a pretty successful broadcast.