POT show the podcast cool kids go for Delta Shara Charlie 2 9 or 8
They're on to your room and pack up a suitcase we got a lead for hotel out of this place we got a move
Yeah I mean move I got dangerous men hop on my heels there's a damn shame where ain't got some faster wheels but there's a wheel
She's gonna have to do it's time I have me a heart to heart whether you
I got some good news and I got some bad news on it either way I've done this wrong
Well I could tell you but we'd better start running because the good news is the money is gone
When the game began I had a handful of cash I was up a couple grand when my luck just crashed so I borrowed from the bank
And I drank and I drank what is can't look good girl I know what you must think
I got some good news and I got some bad news on it either way I've done this wrong
Well I could tell you but we'd better start running because the good news is the money is gone
Yeah I got some good news and I got some bad news on it either way I've done this wrong
Yeah as we heard about that dress I said I was gonna buy it
Maybe we could skip rodeo drive and think more like rodeo style or something
We could start drinking the generic beer for a while
You know we evaluate our taste and steak and go from quarter house
The jack in a box or something like that Sean Patrick McGraw and the good news is it's from his songs for Saturday night
You might remember him from little in love I'm a sucker for some country man from the pod safe music network which you can find at music.podshow.com
Hey everybody how you doing this is the daily source code coming to you from curry condo in San Francisco California I had a great day
It is actually it's Wednesday now in San Francisco technically it's Wednesday. I was actually really really late for me what a fantastic day
It started off just well it started off great 630 there's the alarm clock because we're starting at 8 o'clock every single morning everybody's in HQ because we had so much going on today we started I mean God it was just it was so good everything really finally
Started to come together you know it's so exciting when you're when you're building a new company and and also it just starts to click you know
And of course we had our move today to the new offices
Today was the first time I drove to work in Trinity and Trinity of course is my new bio diesel beast
Oh, it's a one had a name for it
The pod not was it pod pod cruiser
Oh, no pod racer that's what it was yeah the pod racer nah I like Trinity much better that's her name and that's what we're going to call her and
And got lots of lots of feedback and if you don't know what I'm talking about this is the Mercedes Benz
1985 Benz station wagon 300 turbo diesel that runs on biodiesel. I've learned so much just today alone about this about this engine which indeed is five cylinders. It's completely right
The engine takes nine b99 or that's what it's what's in it right now. It'll actually it'll take almost anything b99
Which is 99 percent night I think even 99.9 percent recycled vegetable oil and it runs like a char it just it works
I found out that the place in Berkeley in Berkeley, California where I can go fill her up with b99 is the Berkeley biodiesel oasis
I can't wait to go meet these people it sounds like they've got everything that you can buy big gallons full of this stuff and take it with you
And they've got special you know, I don't know they got all kinds of stuff which we're going to find out about
But I did some reading on their website and gosh, it's it's just fascinating
So you have the 99 b99 you also have the SVO which stands for straight vegetable oil because you can indeed just you can go get a bottle of vegetable oil and port right into the tank now the danger with that is if it gets too cold outside
Wherever the car is or wherever you're driving and I guess the SVO can start to gel and then of course I would clog up your fuel lines and then it wouldn't function it would just stop
So that's why you have the b99 or you can go and get a kit which will heat up this this SVO
So I'm learning more and more about about how this all fits together how it works, of course you can always just throw in you know diesel oil if you want
So excited about this not because of you know some kind of I'm not a greeny by by any standard I do care about the environment
But I think what I'm most excited about is there's no more dependency you know, it's like we don't have to depend on foreign oil
Any oil for that matter. It's completely screwing everything else up. I love it. That's in fact
I just realized that the movie water world with Kevin Costner makes no sense now not water world
I'm sorry, I'm not thinking I am thinking about Mad Max
You know these guys didn't need diesel oil to you know oil based petroleum to to run all their engines off of they could have used corn seed oil or cotton seed oil or
Oh my gosh, I think even hemp oil would be wouldn't that be great. It's so easy to grow
I got a couple emails regarding Trinity from Malcolm and Dubai. I add them your picks of Trinity make me wonder if this car was imported to the US after serving in Germany as a taxi
The color seems to be the unique shade used by taxi operators throughout the federal Republic
Following your biodiesel adventures with interest in planning a podcast. We remain here and do buy your loyal listeners. Thank you very much Malcolm
I don't know the color
Someone wrote someone on a combat that the color is eggnog yellow
Eggnog with rum actually
That's about the color of this wonderful machine and it could be
I don't know how would I find out if this if this machine was imported is there any way to see that and the VIN number or anything like that
Is any way to trace its history I guess is what I'm looking for
Good old match
sent me a short note she said what you need for the cars a new song kind of like Chitty Chitty bang bang
Oh, yeah Trinity definitely needs a theme song and then
Joe McLaughlin says hey man, you should definitely pimp that ride west coast customs
I don't know where is west coast customs let me click on the link here west coast customs.com
Are they in San Francisco or are they in California or in Los Angeles let me see
T-shirts
The hell does that one if they just tell me where they are
Okay, no idea
Doesn't say on the site actually
Wait corporate site maybe that's at 310. Okay, so that's going to be
That's going to be Los Angeles too bad here contact info. Let me just check and see what their
Jesus Christ man, don't you just tell me where you are where you're located
Okay, 310 is definitely not here in San Francisco, but I'd much rather pimp it out with
With some source code listeners who were out there who in the Bay area
Who have some ideas I've gotten lots of great photo shops and all kinds of great
I you know great logos and versions of the car in different colors
But is there anyone who can really come here and do it Steve web by the way from the
Life Spring podcast he shot me off a really short email
Earlier today and I actually did know that Steve's what Steve does for a living
This is a fantastic inspirational podcast that I certainly suggest you listen to if you have time
Steve during the day when he's not podcasting for a living he repairs car windshields
And I have two like major stars right on the on the windscreen and
I'm hoping that we can hook up and Steve can fix that. I actually don't even know how that works
So we'll do a little a little instructional podcast of saving trinities windscreen
Brett Viren says Adam, you know, yes, they were talking about the new razor that I'm trying out this Wilkinson for blade
Now Brett sent me an email was something really interesting. I don't know how this can be true
He says for the past 10 plus years I've been using the same double blade razor all through that time
Those two blades have happily cut my throat
Mange, mange, mange, throat, mange, mange, mange, mange, mange,
Truath is that once it gets a little dull the blades don't get any dollar
Is that really true? I mean when when blades get dulled, do they stay at that same dullness they don't get any dollar any
Razer blade technicians out there that can fill me in on this is that really true
And I don't know I have always just tossed it after a while
So I'm okay now it's dull and now it's time to get rid of it and arguably does work
Arguably, it does work, but how well does it work and does it maintain that same level?
I don't know. Let me know, Adam at Curie.com.
Found another great song on the Pods Safe Music Network.
Oh, I just let me say one more thing about how great today was and how excited
I have and how everything really started to come together.
It was so good today that Ron and I have scheduled to do or have scheduled
ourselves to do a strategy cast tomorrow night, so that will, to whom will that
air? That'll air, I guess Thursday or Friday.
I mean, we'll keep it for the weekend, but I think we're going to record it
Thursday night and I'm very excited about lots of the things that we're going to
be able to tell you. And so we start peeling back some of the, some of the
layers of the, of the nasty smelling pod show onion. And that's only because
Chris Rockwell is not doing the poop cast, you know. So he's got to be doing it
somewhere within the onion. On the Pods Safe Music Network, I came across a song
which I will dub the wiki PDF blues.
I take a look at my enormous penis and my troubles start to melt into a bow.
I take a look at my enormous penis and happy times are coming to stay.
I got to sing and I dance when I glancing my pants and the feeling like a sunshine day.
I take a look at my enormous penis.
Everything is going my way.
The Vinci's notebook. It's just a sample. I don't know why didn't put the whole song up.
An enormous penis. Fantastic. That really made me smile. I got to tell you. Great.
Okay. You may be listening to this show, The Daily Source Code, on serious satellite radio,
stars 103. I want to play a song for you that regular listeners to the pod
cast have heard many, many times, certainly because if they listen to this show, I'm sure
they listen to other podcasts.
The reason why I want to play it right now is because this song is the proceeds of this song,
which include royalties, performance royalties, which are paid through ASCAP and BMI,
go to UNICEF that's been graciously donated by the writers and producers of the song,
Slough and Orlando. When I play the song on the podcast in the satellite window,
that coincides with serious satellite radio, that gets written down somewhere.
I don't know. I have no idea how much it is, but it's definitely some money that goes to UNICEF.
I can't tell the other members of the pod squad of the serious line-up, of course,
after the Daily Source Code, is when we roll out Pacifico's railway, then we have Madge Weinstein.
Madge doing a full hour now on serious, followed by Don and Drew and then we've got Pida,
we've got Wichita, we've got Frank No, I think he does some Frank Truth in there.
We've got the music pod casters. I can't tell them what to do. I can't, I don't want to tell them what to do.
However, if they do play this song and it's played on serious, then that definitely counts towards money going to UNICEF.
In addition, I'm hoping that some of the terrestrial broadcasters and other serious satellite radio
and personalities and producers will pick up on it and maybe we can get some more airplay.
You can check out the whole backstory to this on HotSafeRepeat.org.
If every day we're Christmas.
Christmas tree. People are shopping for them loved ones.
I'm making plans for a Christmas feast.
But it all goes by and then we have to wait another year.
What if every day, Christmas, what are one of the more?
This one tree.
People never feel blue. We make all our dreams come true.
If Christmas were every day.
It was time to bring out the good people.
I just look around now and you will see it. Everybody's nice and full of life.
And they give to those who aren't me.
What if every day, Christmas, what are one of the more?
This one tree.
We make all our dreams come true.
If Christmas were every day.
It was time to bring out the good people.
If Christmas was every day.
Christmas, what are one of the more?
This one tree.
We would never feel blue.
We make all our dreams come true.
If Christmas was every day.
It was time to bring out the good people.
This one tree.
We make all our dreams come true.
If Christmas was every day.
It was time to bring out the good people.
They are not competing because they think they can sing.
If Christmas was every day.
They are not competing because they think they can survive.
five in the jungle.
All right, you better get me out of here.
Hey, guys, guys, guys.
Guys, they're competing because they think they've got
what it takes to make it in the biz.
The biz is a new kind of reality show, only online.
Watch as nine finalists battle for the best job in America,
running a one-armed music record label.
They'll take on tough challenges and even tougher.
Each other is they try to impress music industry,
heavy hitters, and artists like Fallow, Jason, Ramsey,
and many more.
The biz, it's serious competition.
And it's only online free at almusic.com.
And you'll never have to miss one minute,
because every minute of the biz, past and present,
is on demand.
Episodes are already online.
Go to almusic.com now.
I was thinking, listen to that spot there, I was thinking,
what does it mean when they start doing reality shows
about your industry?
That can't be a good thing.
It just can't.
When we're doing reality shows,
and by the way, an audio reality show is also something
that's very interesting, when they're doing that
about your industry, that means your industry is a mockery.
It really does.
So how long before we start hearing, oh, I don't know,
the reality shows about, oh, gee, reality shows
about radio stations, now I guess we already had that.
WKRP and Cincinnati, I wasn't a reality show
was more of a soap, but when we get reality shows
about disjockeys, then you'll know it's really over.
Excuse me, for those you listened to the podcast,
we're about to lose our satellite window on serious.
I'm to continue, I got cool stuff to talk about,
talk about blank media taxes and different countries
around the world, got some feedback on iTunes
and their top 100 and how that works.
I'm also some help being offered for my Macintosh woes,
once I get back, you know, by the way,
since the community Mac blew up at home,
I put the studio production, I Mac downstairs
and the kitchen, it looks beautiful, by the way,
fits perfectly.
Patricia calls it her station.
She's got her flat screen TV, the next to it
she's got her eye Mac, she's so completely happening.
She's got eye chat up all the time
and the presence thing really works
because she moves the mouse whatever in the morning.
She's checking mail regularly,
she's sending mail regularly
and we're actually having little chats back and forth,
before she had to walk upstairs into the studio,
the second bedroom, what I call the studio
and she would basically have to either log in
or just have, it would be a whole chore.
Now, the kitchen is really where we,
I think that's the room we hang out in the most.
It's really, well, the kitchen is really the community room,
it's a nice big long kitchen,
we have a breakfast milk,
which is really where we enjoy all of our meals,
Patricia cooks every single day
and I am often invited to help out,
which I like very much.
I am the sous chef of the Katage and it's just perfect.
So she's there, she's in full communication.
So of course, when I get back,
we're gonna have a little issue because
I'm gonna have to pull the needle out of the main line.
So I gotta order her, her own eye mat,
come to this, this is the old one,
the older model that I never, of course,
switched for the new one, which I should have done,
kinda got bone done, buying the last ones in stock.
Well, anyway, I'm gonna get her a new one
with a camera built in and then she'll be completely cyber,
my cyber bed and she's gonna get a Bluetooth headset
that works perfectly with Skype.
I've got this little Motorola Bluetooth thing
that you hang onto your ear, which is really meant
for the blackberry, but it paired up perfectly
with Bluetooth on the eye mat and it just works like a charm.
Coming up next on the serious stars 103,
if you're listening to the show on the satellite,
it is a specific coast hellway
with Mark Yoshimoto-Nenkov.
So enjoy that and I'll see you tomorrow.
And those of you who are still listening to me,
you get all the good shit man, this is the podcast,
this is where we can go for as long as we want.
I've changed it now, you know,
imagine how it has an hour,
so I'm just taking half an hour on serious
with whatever commercials and stuff they put in between,
I only have to do, what is it, 24 and a half minutes.
So that way I can also shorten the daily source code
a little bit, it really felt to me
like it was just running too long, you know?
And I want to make sure that,
I mean, either I'm gonna do a long show every couple of days,
or I'm gonna do shorter shows every single day.
And it's also is really, really draining.
And by the way, I feel like crap from this jet lag,
somehow it really hit me hard this time around.
It's a day for the first time in God.
I'm gonna say easily, easily eight or nine years,
but first time I actually had an alcohol cell tower.
This is the unit that got to the world
and I can maybe let it go hit in all news of the CIA.
It was supposed to be part safe metal manual,
Saturday nights at우 intévin fossil,
rockcom.
See you back to Clara, Snapchat.
Cause obviously no, she didn't know.
Uh hah hah ahhhh
hah hah hah hah hah hah hah
Hi, this is Larry LeCost.
And this is Chris Delucas with the Daily Journal podcast.
We want to wish you happy holidays.
Hey Adam, how are you doing?
I know you're always doing fine.
Hey, this is a happy podcast from the Netherlands.
And by the way, my name is Mark Bosch.
And why am I so happy?
Because I can make my own show on a podcast.
There's no boss behind me saying, hey, you can't say this only.
You can't say that on there.
I used to work for local way of stations.
And even the local stations, they will have a boss saying,
what you're getting, what you can't do.
And here I can do whatever I want.
I can play the music I like.
I pick it myself from the pot-safe music network.
They even sent me emails when I played it.
Thank you for playing last song and that's so cool.
I never received an email from a dollar saying,
thank you for playing last song when I was on radio.
It's thinking to answer it.
That's a little difference.
In the test, there's a big thing going on here.
What I particularly like is that I can create my own podcast.
And I didn't think about this.
I just wanted to be in there.
And I started my podcast.
I do have to think of a team.
But I didn't do the jet.
I started in talking about my gadgets,
talking about my technology, all the things I like.
And I do have listeners more than I even expect it.
OK, I will come up with a team.
And I was thinking about that top 40, maybe,
and like a tip of it, like Spartan came up with a tip of it
in the Netherlands for conventional music.
But I was thinking about the tip of it for pot-safe music.
The pot tip 20 or something every Friday afternoon.
How cool would that be?
Thinking about all those concepts.
But for now, I'm just doing my thing, doing my music,
doing talking about the things I like.
And I do have listeners.
I do love podcasting, the new medium.
And I just wanted to let you know that.
This is another heavy potcaster from the Netherlands,
wishing you a great time in California.
And he done sick.
And Michael podcasts is available on the websites.
www.markpast.com.
www.maarka.rs.com.
I really just wanted to play that because any podcaster,
who says it's a happy podcaster, just makes me smile.
That's great.
Cool idea, man.
There's lots of people doing all kinds of shows.
We've got the pod-safe music countdown.
We've got the show.
You know what I haven't seen show up in my...
My playlist recently is the ultimate mix pod cast.
I wonder if I still hang it in there.
I really like that one. That was a great show.
Once again today, another 40-50 songs uploaded to the PMman.
It's just fricking outrageous.
This is catch and fire.
It's really, really happening.
Let's see, what was I going to talk about?
Oh, yes.
Okay, so back to the Macintosh that busted upstairs.
A couple people sent me the same information.
I basically said,
Give up on Norton.
Everyone else did.
This is from Kurt Lewis.
It says Norton was the tool for the old Mac OS,
but not in Mac OS X or X or X.
They like stuff.
It sucked the sweat off right nossorous testicles.
I recommend disc warrior by Alsoft.
It fixes problems.
This utility can't.
Thank you very much everyone who suggested using that night.
It disc utility recognizes the drive.
The smart status is verified,
but it can't mount the drive because the B3 catalog is hose.
So I guess I'll get a copy of this warrior.
I really hope I can because there's some shit on that drive.
I'd like to say,
I'm getting a warning from it, man.
It went boom.
It was gone.
It seems like three, four years.
And there are IBM drives.
They suck.
So why only three, four years?
Can't you send me an email that you're going to fail?
Let me see.
Andy Masters from Edinburgh.
Oh, this is about the iTunes top 100.
He says, I subscribed to,
this is, remember I talked about in business.
So when I'll send me an email saying,
how can a business be in the top 100
if they haven't done a show in months?
So Andy says he subscribed to in business recently
because although there's no content just yet,
I want it here.
I want to hear it when the new series starts up again.
So it's getting subscriptions based on people's expectations
of future high quality content.
So it almost makes sense.
An interesting that something as simple as the top 100
can actually be implemented in lots of different ways.
Yeah, no kidding.
Dude, have you ever even talked to anyone who knows
about voting and how votes to be counted?
And, oh, man.
Yes.
Top 100s can be done in many different ways.
Should it measure change as it does at the moment?
What about unsubscribes?
Or the raw number of downloads should a podcast
that transmit seven episodes a week at seven votes
compared to a once a week show?
Good question.
Podcasting asks a whole heap of new questions
to people trying to measure if something is,
quote, popular or not.
The really important thing that whether or not you're in the top 100
may just be vanity for content producers,
but actually effect what kind of content they produce.
He says he knows about it because he did a show
and he dropped from 57 to 99.
So whatever he did there, he won't do it again.
Yeah, you know, I think the list are really good.
I like all these different top 100 lists and top 10 lists.
I do think it's almost required
that the publisher of the list really explains
how the list is compiled.
Otherwise it's just, you know, that's crap.
You know, because it's great to be able to use it for feedback.
But what does it mean, you know?
Every single award or every single ranking
comes with an explanation.
I must say it's, I don't think it's right that iTunes
doesn't at least explain how it works.
That would be nice if they had some kind of a
fact about that, some fact document.
And to witness who about the taxes
levied on blank media,
I was incorrect about what I said about Australia.
Mark Zeta corrects me.
Adam just a correction on the last episode.
Australia does not have an iPod tax at the moment.
Some parliament MPs tried to pass a similar
levied for blank media to cover piracy.
But as far as I know, the Australian Senate did not pass this bill.
Ironically, our equivalent of the RIA, the ARIA, the ARIA,
discouraged the idea of a tax levied on blank media and MP3 players.
So yeah, luckily the ARIA does care about
our rights as a consumer.
So the whole point here, and I talked to a couple
people about it some more today.
I said, you know, how in the world it's going to be legal.
Let's just look at the states.
Or it can't be legal for only the RIA to take money
from that levied or from those taxes.
It just can't be.
I mean, anyone who produces look,
but I have, I'm doing something creative.
It has a defined value.
It's the same format.
It is actually more of the same format than most songs.
So why wouldn't podcasters be allowed to get
some of that money?
I mean, come on.
And by the way, I'm very serious about this question.
That could be free money for us, you know,
and then we all register with some organization.
And then we get money from every blank CD or blank,
or iPod or whatever taxes will be levied on.
But certainly on certainly on CDs.
There are plenty of examples and lots and lots of proof
that people burn podcasts to CDs.
So you tell me what is the difference between someone burning a song
to a CD and someone burning a copywriter work
and someone burning a podcast to a CD,
which is a copywriter work.
They're both in the same format.
They're both created by human beings with creative talent
with computers.
Because one is a song.
They're allowed to get some of this money.
And because another one isn't a song.
You're not allowed to get that money.
Come on, lawyers.
I know you're out there.
Help me out on this.
This is highly interesting to me.
And if anything,
it'll be fun to figure it out if we can stir up some shit.
Dig it.
All right.
One more song.
Who are those bands?
Don't forget where you came from.
I'm a little confused.
About all this enemy fire.
About drug loads and holy walls.
And people freaking out over what they want to freak about.
Oh, so tired.
There's nothing on my radio.
Some little girl who laughs and sleep below.
She tries to sing.
How she wants to dance on me.
I sometimes wonder what they came to me there.
It's unbelievable you came from.
No, I won't.
Don't forget where you came from.
Don't forget about all the people.
You left into your head.
Did I never know?
Did I ever know?
Did I never know about all the people?
Did I never know?
Did all of you came from?
Did I never knew?
Did I never know?
Did I not know?
Did I never knew?
Did I never know?
When I think my girl got a call to shoot her time, go by, got a little too husk
You're blaming all I don't mind, yeah, I'm just easier, a little scarier
Slow down, never going to burn it down, when the grass is green
You were so obscene, maybe your sight didn't look like mama
I won't walk, yeah, I don't want it
Don't forget where you came from, no, I won't
Don't forget where you came from
And don't forget about all the people
You left into your head, no
And don't forget where you came from
Don't forget where you came from
And don't forget about all the people
You left into your head, no
Cool water's band, don't forget where you came from
From the rose pedal to the metal CD
You can find it all on the pod safe music network at pod safe music network.com
Or if you prefer music.podshow.com
That's it for me, for the day of the source code, we back tomorrow
As I said, probably with the strategy cast, although we might delay that to the weekend
But definitely with a regular episode of the source code
Feedback, adamantcurry.com
And check out all the show notes of daily source code.com
I just gotta leave with this song one more time everybody. I'll see you tomorrow
Take care now and feel free to sing along
Silence like a sunshine day
Take a look at how you normally be
Never think everything is going my way
I show.com, makes no claims regarding the quality of its pod shows
Or the sanity of its producers, listen at your own risk