Daily source code, 126-2005.
Like, you know, does Adam Curry
cup his hand to his ass fart and then smell it?
Adam, the listeners of the Daily Download want to know.
Autistic, it's Adam Curry.
It is Thursday, January 27th.
The power of the door, the door, the door.
Everybody, how you doing?
Is Adam Curry coming to you from Curry Cottage
in the affluent Surrey Subber?
Sorry, Surrey Subber called Gilford.
It's almost 10am.
It is Thursday, January 27th.
It's 2005.
I was just a little snippet from the Daily Download.
The answer, of course, is yes.
Of course, I'd love to be on your show.
I cannot imagine anything higher in life for me than you.
Sitting in my bathroom studio,
Skyping to your bathroom studio.
I mean, that would be fantastic.
All right, today's source code, as promised,
a little bit different today.
We're not going to do a sound scene tour.
You know, we try to vary the format from time to time.
Today is just going to be a conversation with Ken Clark.
I told you about him.
He worked at MTV for 20 years.
Now, I've worked with Ken for at least 15 of those 20 years.
Maybe even a little bit more.
He's, we have a state mogul right now
of in Portland, Oregon.
And we decided that we would just shoot the shit a little bit
about the old MTV days.
Actually, it started with the Carson Daily song
that I played the other day, where we wanted to figure out
where all the MTV VJs have gone.
It turns out there are actually 37 different VJs
that can us work within the past 20 years.
A lot of this conversation, I got actually
let Patricia listen to it yesterday.
Some of it's a bit inside.
But let me know what you think about it.
We should continue because, of course,
we only got like eight of the 37 people.
So if you think it's worth continuing,
let me know at curie.com.
Enjoy this.
On the Skype call now is someone who literally lived in my house
more than I did for a number of years.
Who, who nannied me when necessary.
And is one of the unsung heroes of the breakthrough of MTV.
My friend and colleague, and this thing was gentleman
from somewhere with the West Coast, where the fuck is it?
Portland.
That's Portland.
Portland, Oregon.
Canster J, Ken Clark.
Welcome everybody.
Yeah, I'm here everybody.
So I actually have Skype recording for the first time.
Maybe it's the good karma you're bringing me.
Well, we'll see how it goes.
Immediately it started skipping.
Of course, of course.
Okay, Ken.
Let me set this up.
In our bad weeks with Skype.
Yeah, this is going pretty good so far.
Let me set this up.
I met you in 1987, Halloween around Halloween of 1987.
When I arrived on Ellis Island from from the Nether regions,
the lowlands and with my girlfriend, with my girlfriend,
she wasn't even my fiance then.
She's my girlfriend Patricia.
And that's when I started at MTV.
And what was your title at the time, Ken?
Was it, what was the official title?
It started.
I was probably VJ coordinator.
I'm going to crank your level up a little bit here.
VJ coordinator.
That's a sucky title.
Well, later I, it was, uh, I got promoted to manager of on air talent.
Did you get a, did you get a pay raise with that?
A little bit.
MTV was never famous for paying well though.
I actually told everyone the other day.
Yeah.
Yeah, I heard you talking about it.
You did okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I heard you talking about it.
You did better than me, too.
The very first VJ started for like 4550,000 bucks back in 1981.
1981.
August 1st, 1981.
Yeah, and by the time you guys came around, everybody, you know,
was pretty staggered that it had gone way over $100,000.
Yeah.
But I think I made the most of all the, uh,
I made more than Julie Brown.
Tell me I did.
I think you probably did in the end.
Yeah.
You guys both ended up with kind of weird deals.
You were only doing certain shows, certain things.
I mean, I had no show.
I got fucking fired.
We, I got fired 25 times.
Well, yeah, but I mean,
we did go back after a while and
I feel like a week.
I didn't do them like the top 20 countdown once a week.
Because they couldn't find anyone to do it.
Well, yeah.
They still haven't apparently.
But you already work out for one then, right?
You already working for me.
So what happened is Ken?
Yeah, that point.
Yes.
When did you start?
This is, we're never going to be able to fit this in 45 minutes.
When did you start at MTV?
Because it must have been a couple years before I got there.
I started at MTV on New Year's Eve, 1984, 85.
I flew into New York like the day after Christmas.
I was supposed to start in January.
They called me up on New Year's Eve day and said,
We're short staff.
Come down here.
We're doing our live New Year's Eve ball.
That was 1984 and 1985 New Year's Eve.
Goddamn.
Wow.
And so that was with the original guys.
Oh, yeah.
Everyone thinks I'm one of the original VJs.
And I keep telling him, well, you were around two.
Yeah.
But that was when MTV really exploded into 40 million households.
Definitely.
You guys were there for that.
The first group.
But you know, Martha stayed on.
I think longer than anybody else.
But the majority of everybody else were gone within the first five years.
And it was.
Off to a lustreous careers elsewhere between Channel 66 and 68 UHF.
Well, it's interesting.
I made a couple of years ago, MTV few years ago.
Actually, MTV brought me back a couple of times to do those.
I was an MTV VJ specialist.
I know you came back to.
It was one of them.
Yeah, one.
Yeah.
What was that?
It was was it some anniversary.
It was an MTV VJ two.
And you were at on ramp at the time.
And I was already here in Oregon.
I flew back to do it.
But for that show, I had prepared a list of everybody that I could think of.
That I had worked with as a VJ over the.
I was 10 years that I was there.
So I come prepared at least with a list of people.
Because there's names on this list.
I don't even remember.
I remember like who the hell was Tricksie.
Tricksie.
I remember Tricksie.
Sure.
Andrew Dado.
There's another one for you.
He's on the list.
I've got him on the list.
Ah.
You know.
I'm sorry.
Wendy Westbrook.
Oh, she was cute.
Wasn't she in like a kind of a.
I don't know.
She was.
Yeah.
No, no.
She was.
She was someone.
It's Wendy Westbrook.
Everybody.
I do it.
Yes.
She was a radio chick.
That's why yes.
Like kind of a Tom Boyer's thing.
Yeah.
Radio chicks are kind of Tom Boyer's.
Well, there's a long list of names here.
And the post MTV successes you pointed out.
The other day has been pretty disastrous.
Well, it's so hard.
You know, it's like, you know that once you've been an MTV VJ, you basically can't
be anything else but that.
It's certainly not in show business.
I don't think I got what I got on the swamp thing.
I had a pretty successful radio career.
But that was.
The thing I hate about still have that somewhere.
God, the swamp thing.
I'm sure I have the video.
It's a great episode.
Christina could watch it for the longest time because it actually scared her.
It scared her.
Yes.
She thought it was very crap.
It was funny crap.
But it was crap.
Awesome.
I was.
I was good.
Like washed up rock star.
Uh-huh.
Talk about your type casting.
But yeah, I mean, you know, there have been some people like Daisy.
You know, he said, she had a lot of success.
Certainly after she hooked up modeling.
What's his name?
Miguel Luis Miguel or whatever.
Yeah, but she was already doing it.
I think she was a ravlon girl.
I've always, always, always love Daisy.
I did too.
She was a really, really cool chick.
Yeah.
And she was gorgeous.
And she let me feel her.
Yeah.
We had Nina Allen, Mark J.J. and Martha were the original five MTV VJs.
Martha has retired and is got two kids and lives in Malibu with her husband.
Really?
And commercial soundtracks and Martha really doesn't have a big desire to work.
She's really happy being a mom.
Would she live in the cage?
Well, we were not to fast, not to fast.
Okay.
Does she live in the colony?
Of Malibu?
In the colony?
Yeah.
I don't know exactly.
They just moved to Malibu from the Hollywood Hills this last summer.
Hmm.
Okay.
How old are kids?
So kids are like eight nine from like that?
Oh, God.
You know, I just don't know with Martha and the kids at this zoo.
No, her youngest is like three or four.
Probably three-ish.
And then the older is six, seven.
For extra points, what are their names?
Maizee and Dylan.
Oh, okay.
Cool.
And we're talking out at the Central Park Zoo.
And our husband's nice, school.
Yeah.
Jordan Tarlo used to be the guitarist for a band called The Fuzz Tones, which were an early 120-minute
MTV band.
Oh.
Yeah.
They met, you know, it was funny because everybody thought Nina was the party girl.
And Martha was the girl next door when, in fact, Nina was born.
And it was the home body.
Yeah.
And Martha was going out with stiff baders from large of the new church.
Oh, that's right.
What was this?
What was the song?
Stuff in Martha's muffin.
What was that?
I can't remember who did that.
It was.
Fuck.
Wasn't that from the Georgia's not Georgia satellites?
When it was me.
It'll come to me when Roger.
George Thurgood or something like that?
I don't know.
Brittany Spears.
Abba.
So that's Martha.
But of the remaining four Nina Mark and JJ all ended up going back into radio.
You know, Nina spent a couple years on entertainment tonight.
And I think she did solve it.
Wait a minute.
Didn't.
Was it with Martha one second?
Didn't she do a nagsima commercial?
Yeah.
That was she did.
She did a few commercials after she left.
Did she ever do like time life?
Time life things.
Collections CDs.
She may have.
I know Mark Goodman and Ellen and Ellen Hunter both did because I remember sitting up late party
and at like two in the morning and watching my my buddies.
Fuck time like time life products.
I never did.
I placed paid the extra money so I could fly first class.
I just thought, you know, I did certain places.
I, you know, if you're a celebrity, you just have to.
I can't find it.
Well, there was a day when MTV flew all of their talent first class.
And, you know, that was before they got cheated.
It was corporate and they ruined it.
It was so much.
There were stupid rules.
You know, like if the flight is less than three hours it has to.
I remember that.
Oh, yeah.
And here was the caveat.
And less.
There's another VJ on the plane.
Who is entitled to first class?
It's that point.
I was to bump the person in coach up to first class.
So anyone.
Everyone wanted to fly away.
No, they take you aside and they say, now you just don't ever put a VJ in coach on the same plane with somebody in first and we don't ever have to go there.
So yeah, exactly.
Certain people got to fly with their makeup artists and, you know, did their makeup artists fly from them.
Julie Brown.
And you know, I love Julie, but I spent a great deal of time negotiating crap over who flew.
Where?
Oh, my.
I remember that.
I remember the angst.
I remember seeing it on your face.
It was just ridiculous.
You know, I was just like, get on the plane.
You know, you got to show.
I take it on the plane.
Wait, you're going way too fast.
I mean, listen, we got to talk about Ted Demi.
We got to talk about Rick Kalman.
I mean, we can't just talk about the VJs.
I mean, there's a lot of people.
I guess I was following up on your point.
The track record for VJs has been made.
That's right.
Let's go.
Let's say when say there is certain people like Nina Allen.
Well, JJ died.
Nina Mark and JJ all got into radio.
JJ unfortunately.
Yes, passed away last March.
But the original for a VJ is now three minus JJ and Martha, who's retired are doing a serious
video network best of the eight.
Are on on one satellite channel?
Yes.
Interesting.
And so it's like 80 all eighties.
Yeah.
I keep getting those offers.
I get offers like that all the time.
People want me to, you know, host eighties.
Everything from eighties, sock hops.
Well, I tell you they, you know, they pay what they pay really well.
Allen I've been talking to.
Allen's the whole other story.
That's interesting.
He owns a film company.
I remember because I hooked up with him with that.
I was an MTV VJ too.
And he was telling me about it.
It seemed like he was into some pretty interesting shit.
Oh, Allen's rock.
And he's got a hell of a place set up down in Birmingham, Alabama.
How about that's where he was from.
And, you know, Allen's doing really good.
But he said, you know, he sits down once a week.
And he does the segments there and his computer.
And they get, you know, voice over IP, off the serious.
And, you know, that's it.
Done boom.
That's a thanks man hour.
Right.
Jack's Berlin.
Cool.
So that's pretty much it for that group.
And then there was.
But do they identify themselves as a high?
I'm not a good man.
I'm sorry.
Allen Hunter.
I doubt it.
I'm out on Hunter.
And I used to be on MTV.
Can they say that they were on MTV?
Do they do that?
And not show?
Because, you know, that was a big problem.
They probably do.
They must.
But you remember when you do 100.
Do you remember how pissed off everybody was coming?
I'm sorry.
You're my guest.
Please go ahead.
Well, I stepped on you.
All I was going to say is if you go to serious.com and look it up.
It's like best of the 80s.
And it completely identifies them as the original MTV VJs.
Okay.
Now, do you remember how much shit I got from MTV?
Because I would be identified as Adam Curry from MTV on the radio.
Yeah.
But at one point it got negotiated that you were allowed to mention your TV guy.
I think.
Oh, that's right.
I was on the on TV.
Yeah.
And then in return, you would plug your MTV shows on your.
I was probably the top 30 hit list.
Yeah.
God.
I negotiated that.
Yeah.
Very good.
Carefully negotiated cross mentions.
You know, can by the way.
Once you with me.
Uh, during the MTV.com lawsuit.
Oh, goodness.
Yes.
Yeah.
You, you, you, you, you still have all that crap can.
I moved it with me.
I have all that fucking shit.
The cases of files.
Yep.
I haven't even the, the three and a half inch floppies.
All the printouts.
All the legal documents.
Joe Donnelly.
Remember him?
I was just going to say that lawsuit proved one thing if one thing only.
It really pays to have a really, really, really good lawyer.
Yeah.
And we really pay him a shitload of money too.
Well, I don't know.
We're like $250,000.
I don't think MTV thought that, you know, you would, I, I think, you know,
Viacom and MTV typically in those situations.
Expect the little guy to curl up in a ball and say you win, you win, I give.
You know, they should have just asked for the asked for it.
If they'd asked me, I would have given it to you.
You didn't.
You know, I think you surprised them because you didn't curl up in a ball.
That's, that's I think we can probably say that.
But I totally pulled it.
David and Goliath in the press on them.
That work pretty well.
Exactly.
And in fact, it was the pressing me.
It was probably the best thing for, for getting you in the press and launching your new endeavor,
which was the web and on ramp after MTV.
The press that came out of that was the best press that money could buy.
That's right.
You haven't even been looking good no matter what anybody said.
You came off looking good and it came off looking good.
Like fucker.
Yeah.
Do you have any press clippings still?
I've got boxes of stuff.
Do you have any of those particular press clippings?
Yeah.
Then I'm not sure about that.
That was in a separate file.
We're depressing.
I'm sorry.
We're digressing.
That would be somewhere else like in a curry co-on ramp.
A few ideas of file.
I've got the MTV files here.
Yeah.
Okay.
I still have boxes and boxes of three quarter inch tape, too.
And there's some really funny stuff on them if they haven't molded.
You know, I have the outtake reel.
I have, that's the one that we're Julie says.
Kiss my clip.
I have that one.
It's a great reel.
I love that reel.
And Kevin Seal.
Kevin Seal is like,
She got all Dave Diner account too.
Yeah.
Dave Diner.
That's right.
Dave Diner was a four manager.
I like Dave Diner.
I liked him.
He reminded me of my dad.
He was very dry.
Very dry.
He was cool.
Yeah.
He was all right.
He made me laugh.
Gosh, man.
Well, some of them were poor in our camera.
I wonder if Warren is still on camera.
I bet you.
Warren or Celeste has probably still there.
You know, shriveled up in a corner.
Camp.
It's got to be on a handheld with a tripod.
You know, because MTV, they wouldn't really want to do things to you.
Either you aged at twice to speed or it stopped you from
aging during the time you were there.
That's right.
For you, for the good people,
it stopped us from aging during the time we were there.
Yeah.
Well, you know,
you were talking about the camera people.
Operators.
And not only them, but, you know,
Jeff on Cairon, you know,
the, the Cairon is the,
that's what they bring, you know,
the letters they bring up.
So, you know,
with your name or whatever.
And we had a great guy,
the Cairon operator Jeff,
because he couldn't spell.
That was like,
You know,
like the first required because it was,
it was, you know,
and Rick would audio and just a feedback with the crew.
Otherwise,
you're sitting there and a fucking dead studio.
Talking shit without seeing the videos, you know?
Have you talked to Rick recently?
You keep sending that.
I mean,
I have more recently than I have, I think.
I looked up a couple.
He visited you once in Amsterdam.
I think that was,
That was, oh, that was a well back, but I saw him in New York and we kept in touch a little bit, he's a sex-fiend.
I got, he's in all kinds of...
Yeah, I don't know.
He's always into somebody.
He's married for a long time and had a lovely wife and a lovely relationship.
Joe and I decided he wanted to have sex with lesbians.
And I'm like, yeah, I get it.
Lesbians Swedish made.
Yeah, she was cool.
Anyway, so, um, who was next?
Then I came in to talk about women.
You, you, you don't have never asked you, will you?
I've never asked you exactly what that was like from your end.
I remember coming in.
I remember my first day.
I remember what it was like.
But I don't think you've ever told me what it was like on the other side.
Because, you know, they've apparently hired some geek.
I remember you and Julie and Daisy and Kevin Seel starting probably more than anybody else,
because down the road after that, they kept turning over.
And you know, I hear a comes another one.
So, who did you come in?
Oh, Kevin Seel came in first, I bet, right?
Because that was a part of the...
Kevin Seel was the one they did, the Great College VJs.
Right.
When to college campuses around the United States and auditioned people and out of thousands of people,
somehow they ended up with Kevin Seel.
His audition was truly brilliant, although as it turned out later, he may have been on mushrooms at the time.
Kevin Seel is one of the most talented comedians I have ever met in my life, and he is completely disadvantaged.
He is completely deranged and podcasted by the way, would be perfect for him.
Last I heard from Kevin, he was married, he was in Seattle.
I believe he had kids, and I think he had gone and done something.
Remember, he was an engineering major.
He was fucking brilliant.
He was brilliant.
Well, yeah, but I think he's actually building bridges or something.
Did...
He was hanging out with Bernie, right?
Remember Bernie?
Hmm.
Bernie, our receptionist, our emergency.
Bernie does it.
Yeah.
The emergency were friends, frankly.
And they probably still talk.
I've lost that baby.
She was great.
She was a hoot dough.
Oh man, she was so cool.
She was whacked.
Well, how would Stern used to call our studio all the time in the morning live?
And he would talk to her, right?
And try to get through to Steve leads.
And Steve leads emailed me.
What's he doing?
He's consulting for serious.
He probably got...
Of course, there's a link.
He's like, you got marches out on the ground.
We'd remember going back to your question of what it was like when you guys started.
I mean, it was really strange because, you know, original VJs had left.
And it was family.
And everybody was really kind of very nervous about how this was going to be.
And what it was going to be like with new people.
Right.
And I can't remember whether you came first or Julie or Kevin A.
I don't know.
But I remember, you know, Julie was on TV and...
She wasn't...
Like a dancer on television.
Yeah, something.
She was...
Yeah, yeah.
She was that.
And she was also doing like TV AM or something.
And they had flown her over to do an audition.
And I remember coming over and being very British and very nervous.
Really?
Really.
You see, the thing with Julie Brown, the thing with Julie Brown.
Sorry for interrupting you, Ken.
Is that she was...
The perfect example of why MTV was fucked up from day one.
We're not from day one.
But, you know, when these...
When the new people came in because Julie off camera was fucking hilarious.
I mean, we...
Very much.
We had to stop.
I mean, people were in stitches dying on the floor.
It was just so hilarious.
And the foul mouth...
I mean, she...
No one had anything on her.
And it was funny.
It was really...
Funny.
But, you know, that was not the stuff that MTV aired.
What they aired was...
No, they were...
The...
It was boring.
And then she turned around and said, okay, it's my clip.
And it was like, ah!
She was...
Jennifer...
And Ab Fab...
Way before their time.
I'm just...
Well, I'm sorry, not Joan Rivers.
But she was before Ab Fab.
She probably already had stolen a lot of her...
Or...
But it was influenced by a...
By a lot of that British humor that I'm seeing here.
But she was great.
And that just never made it on the air.
No.
Unfortunately, the funny stuff didn't all go on...
Oh, and Julie, by the way, is married to a...
For foul player?
No, no, no.
Baseball?
No, nothing like that.
Oh, like a guy with boats?
Like a guy with boats?
No, he's...
Yeah, but he's like a real estate guy.
I...
Yeah.
It's got money.
Like a developer.
Yeah, he's got money.
Yeah, right now.
And he has a daughter that was very, very young when he and Julie got married.
So Julie's basically raised his child as her own.
And Julie, I think, is probably one of the world's best moms.
And is very, very happy.
And not doing a lot of work either.
She...
They're in California.
Wasn't she married to that model?
First, can, like, some male model that she was with?
I don't know.
She was actually married.
Whenever married there, that was her fiance, Chris.
She was from England with her to New York.
Oh, that's...
And during the time that they were in New York together,
he, in fact,
funny sidebar.
But back, before Mariah Carey was Mariah Carey,
she used to work at a sports bar on the opposite side of Manhattan.
Yeah.
And he was on some rugby team.
Right.
I remember that.
She'd always have to go pick him up after he played.
Right.
Well, apparently, she...
Julie caught Chris in Demariah Carey.
Let me tell you.
If I had to line him up next to each other,
I'd totally go from Mariah Carey.
Oh, totally.
Totally.
But I bet you, Julie.
But Julie, I bet you was hot in the sack,
because, you know, she did Billy Idol.
I mean, that's pretty cool.
Anyway, Chris ran off with all her money
and started to succeed this week.
No.
We clubbed in California.
Oh, that's horrible.
What happened after that?
He ran off with her in the street.
Well, she didn't have any money.
She didn't have any real money.
But she didn't have any real money.
I mean, she was living paycheck to paycheck like the rest.
Actually, she did.
I mean, she...
She...
She'd saved up some money in England,
and they owned a house.
And, you know, she was...
She was doing okay there.
MTV is...
Well, and...
Hmm.
You and Julie, I think, were probably the two that...
I have no idea if they pay like they used to.
And I'm sure, you know,
oh, people like Carson Daily got to a point
where they were proud.
He must have very good money.
He must have been made to know that.
At least 200,000.
I bet he was making 200,000.
Not much more.
But, you know, that's why...
You did make at least 200,000 to live like a neighbor.
Like a neighbor in Manhattan these days, so...
Yeah.
Well, but, you know, you get all your appearances,
and all the other shit if you...
I never really did that.
I only did that to promote my radio shows.
I didn't do fucking store openings.
Although, I did do...
Like the Popeyes.
The Popeyes, yes.
The Popeyes chicken grand opening.
Okay, fuck you.
You weren't going to bring that up, can.
He...
Where was that?
I don't remember where it was.
It was down the south, like New Orleans...
No, no, New Orleans was great.
You'd have to fly off and do another silly radio promo.
And I think I learned an awful lot working for you in those years
because there are no silly or people, and there's no silly or business
and syndicated...
I said the kid in front of you.
Everybody, how are you doing?
I mean, that is silly shit.
Christina says hi, she can't hear you,
but she's in the room.
Yeah, it's Ken.
Yeah, Ken.
Your buddy Ken.
Well, tell her I said hello.
Yeah.
He says hi.
For people that didn't sound very enthusiastic,
it's hard to explain to people the relationship I have with Christina,
which we don't really have at this point.
But I mean...
She loves you better.
She still loves you.
Your daughter and I were very much in love when I was in my late 20s
and she was too.
Right.
And let's just explain because at a certain point...
Quite enough fair.
When did I ask you to come work for me and leave MTV?
God, I was really fucking with him.
Right.
93.
Really was that late.
So it was like...
92.
93.
It was around there.
Right.
And so...
When was the occasion?
Why did I need you?
You had fired...
Ivan.
The Joan Jet People.
Oh, right.
Kenny.
Kenny Laguna.
That was so ugly.
That was so fucking ugly.
But you know...
Kenny was a great guy.
But Steve Lieber was hard to deal with.
Well...
There were arosimists.
It was the one that they fired.
Yeah.
You would come to New York and you had done the appropriate thing.
You had hired publicist.
You had hired agents.
You'd hired managers.
And you know, I think at the end of the day,
you realize that maybe you don't need all that crap.
No.
You can do yourself.
Yeah.
Exactly.
There's no point in paying somebody a percentage like that.
But a lot of people have done.
And you were actually pretty early on in doing it.
But you said, I don't need all these people.
I just need to hire somebody.
Yeah.
On staff who can take care of a lot of those day-to-day functions.
And then keep the agent because they only make a percent if they bring the money in.
Yeah.
But check this.
You also hire the manager.
It makes a percent of everything you make.
Right.
Fuckers.
Fucking bandits.
So you walked into my office one day.
And I was, you know, I'd been there for nine years.
And the vibe of what was going on at the channel had changed considerably.
Who was running the show then?
Because we should talk about that one time.
Who was running the show?
What light switch was the operation light switch?
Was it this time?
On what level?
Ah, who was, what was the production?
What were we doing?
Remember we had all those different phases that we went through.
And we had the blue screens.
And then we had, you know, five seconds of talking.
You know, that shit.
Remember how we went through all that?
I think we'd kind of almost come full circle.
We were, we had gone down to 42nd and rebuilt a big real life set again at that.
That's the new studio.
Yeah, those were nine.
Yeah.
That was cool.
And, you know, things had gone a little bit back to, you know, normal VJ day parts and actual segments that, you know, were more than two seconds.
I bet you the radio guys were backing.
What was his name?
Andy, Andy.
Who was programmed right?
Andy.
Something.
He was.
I bet you he was in.
Because it was running like radio again.
Yeah.
He was a guy that it didn't care.
Andy's shown.
Yeah.
Because he had.
He had known Kennedy.
Kennedy, by the way, is no longer in the business.
I think she's, she's, no, we know what Kennedy's doing.
No, no, we know what Kennedy's doing.
I'm just going to show some kind of bad.
TV show somewhere.
Always kind of, you know, the hip Republican as it were.
That's why I hated her.
And they said, well, they've, they've really dusted her off.
Remember when she fucked up my ass?
Can that?
Why did you fuck up your, do you remember that?
Well, I told the source of listeners who was my thigh.
It really was my thigh.
Yes, I heard it.
And yeah, I do.
I've forgotten about that.
That was fucked up.
I don't think I was there at the time.
I was at the beach house.
That was very cool.
The beach house concept was fucking great.
The first time.
Yeah.
And you know, that always pissed me off because those fuckers never let me come.
Never let you know.
That was like the VMA.
Because there'd be one or two of you at the beach house.
And everybody else would be back in the studio.
So they felt it was better to have me back at the studio than out at the beach house.
We needed you to run the ship to Ken.
We needed to know that there's strong firm hand was on the wheel at all times.
Yeah.
And besides that, we just haven't too much fun.
We're having too much fun.
I'm on our old makeup artist in New York.
On the last year.
Do you meet?
My trips to New York.
I was walking through the village.
And there was Keon before me.
Oh, Keon.
Oh, my God.
For Keon.
Yeah, of course.
How's Keon?
No, of course not.
Don't touch me.
Be honest.
Well, no.
Your wife was the only one that was led to do your makeup.
Yeah.
And my hair.
And your hair.
Well, you came in done.
And you were always funny.
You know, everybody else would come in and sweat and take an hour and a half to get
ready.
You'd come in 30 seconds after you were supposed to be on the set and just kind of walk in the
door and throw your jacket over the stool.
I always be like 30 seconds late.
Right.
I just strolling.
Well, you were always calling from the tunnel.
You know, you're right there.
We're like ready.
You know.
You're ready.
We're always in the tunnel.
Right.
But the time you ran out of gas in the tunnel.
Oh, dude.
Oh, you're in a Rolls Royce.
Let me tell you.
A quick way to make yourself really hated in New York is to run out of gas in a Rolls Royce
in the afternoon.
I broke down to the Honda, but everybody thought, sorry for me.
And they come out with this god awful yellow thing with these two big, big bumpers
and literally just bump their ass out of the way.
It just bump you all the way.
And the Rolls when it's not when the engine's not running, you have no power steering.
And so it's like this little, this little wheel like this grandma thin wheel that you know,
you're pulling with all your might and it's like, you know, the thing is creaking
and the tie issues.
That was a horrendous experience.
And everyone that wronging and flipping the urge caused me a great deal of stress over the many years
that I worked for.
Shit.
Well, I had it for 90,000 miles.
That Rolls caused me a great deal of stress over those 90,000.
Why?
Just because of all the payments we had to make for it.
That we could never make.
It was a very expensive car.
And be even to have a spark plug change.
It was like thousands of dollars.
I paid per spark.
You know, they'd have to import the spark plug and the wrench and the guy to turn it from one to two.
Oh, that was funny.
Oh, man.
Hey, listen.
Remember you traded that hand on, what did you trade that for?
I did trade it.
I gave it away.
All right.
But I mean, you switched to a Ford Explorer then.
Yeah.
One of the kind that blows up.
No, those didn't blow up.
They tipped over.
The tiptoe, right?
Yeah.
It was a national emergency.
No, it was a drive.
I'm sorry.
Medical emergency.
Which dot com license plate.
You better have your ass ready.
We're going to work.
I'm like, are you crazy?
It's a state of emergency.
It was the blizzard.
Remember we wasn't at the blizzard that we went that we drove in.
And everyone was was putting pictures up on the web and stuff.
Yeah.
What was that?
The blizzard of what?
Ninety.
Fifty six, seven.
Ninety six, ninety seven, summer, was nine six.
Ninety six.
Nina's shorty of six.
I had the dot com license plates.
Then it was.
Ninety six.
Ninety six and nineteen.
Right.
And Lou, to our housekeeper.
Were you able to take a charitable deduction for that?
No, fuck it.
It wasn't worth more than $5,000 by the time we got rid of it.
It was shot.
They still drive it around.
Fireman and then.
It's still driving around for a moment.
Yes, yes.
Absolutely.
I'm so excited to take it out.
The Duchess, they still call it.
That's not it.
Listen, Ken.
It's been like 30 minutes to tell you what.
Why don't we continue?
And do some more like another time and make this into a series.
This is great.
Wait, I didn't say that, right?
I would love to.
Oh, that's so surreal.
That's seriously because you trained me.
Ah, I trained you so well.
I would love to.
Well, Adam had a thing.
Anybody that worked for Adam.
If he asked you to do something, he wanted you to respond.
I would love to.
No, that's not true.
What are you talking about?
It was the joke.
It was a joke.
But he was an ongoing joke.
Yeah, just either say no or I would love to.
I would love to.
Did I ever tell you that Barry Nelson who was my assistant at
Think?
When you were running the traffic department.
Your final good assistant.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
That he was on.
You had it run there.
He was on who wants to be a millionaire?
No.
Yeah.
And he had me listed as one of the people's calling case.
You needed to help line.
Yeah, I think he did.
It was like, I never saw that.
Well, I didn't see it.
I presume it aired.
But he was on.
So he called me and he was like really excited.
And see, can I kind of list you as a number?
Yeah, fuck an eye.
Of course, the time they were taping was like three o'clock in the morning.
My time, right?
And so I went to bed at night.
They call you up and get you ready to do it and stuff?
No.
Eventually around around three a.m. or whatever.
And I'm like, oh, my God.
I'm going to suck.
I'm like completely.
I go.
Oh, I know.
Here you are in the air completely asleep.
Yeah, but it was.
It was Ed.
Yeah.
Calling to say that, you know, they wouldn't call me because Barry.
He got like, I think he did $12,000 or was it $8,000?
What's the level?
$8,000 or $12,000?
I have no retention for numeric.
Yeah.
And that's and that's all he did.
And I never heard again from him.
I'm sure he's okay.
He'll get in touch again.
I'm sure he's out there somewhere.
But yeah, we'll have to continue this because we didn't even.
You know, I made a list here.
There were 37 members of the MTV air talent.
No.
That I weigh.
Thirty or seven.
Eight.
Unbelievable.
Oh, my God.
But there's so many other things we can.
We should do this.
We should give this a name and just do this from time to time.
And just shoot the shit because between the two of us,
we have what?
Twenty years of MTV history we can talk about?
Yeah.
Wow.
We can get zipped cream to sponsor it.
I could still use some.
Right.
Right on girlfriend.
I'm still at a lesson.
Okay.
Well, good.
Let's do this again tomorrow whenever we feel like it.
Whenever we hook up.
This is fun.
Okay.
We could just call out the MTV Chronicles.
Something like that.
Something like hokey.
The MTV Chronicles.
You're going to write a book.
You're going to do a book.
Was it going to be called?
I know.
Oh.
Clean the title.
Inside MTV.
My life in the trenches.
Yeah.
Excellent.
Or my time in the trenches.
But no.
It was inside MTV.
My time in the trenches.
It was going to be my personal book.
No.
There's a book to be written somewhere.
It's all about time.
Yeah.
Well, that's why this is much easier.
I mean, you don't even like shit on a book anyway.
What?
If somebody's going to pay you a big advance and still write the book.
And they have bought your time.
Then you can afford to sit there for the months that it would take and write.
Other than that.
I don't got time to do it.
I'm going to make some money.
Well, well.
Hold on a second.
Listen.
You know, fucking.
Mr. Real Estate.
You know, Mr. Donald fucking Trump of Portland.
Let me.
Let me ask it.
How much.
Would it take to write the book?
What kind of advance would you need?
I don't know.
We'd have to talk about that.
I have no idea.
I mean, I've given a great deal of thought to it.
And would it really be a best seller?
Do you think it would really, it would really, the people really give a shit?
Mmm.
Seriously now.
Probably not.
I don't know.
There's, there's three or four different complete angles.
You can take at how to do the thing.
It has to be scandalous.
Otherwise it's not going to be, is it the scandals?
You know.
The thing is, everyone thinks that there was, you know,
MTV was, you know, one big drugged out orgy.
And, you know, guess what?
It was fun, but it wasn't that fun.
It, it became a well-oiled assembly line.
Basically cranking out assembly line television, you know,
seven days a week, 24 hours a day worth of television.
And a Monday through Friday, you know,
seven, eight hour work day.
Yeah.
There was a science that cranking it out.
The sure thoughts and quirky personalities that, you know,
Yeah.
Added to the mix, but it was by no means a big drugged out party.
What was it, Linda?
Linda?
What's her name? Linda?
Love lace?
Yeah, that's the one.
All right.
I listen, I'll talk to you tomorrow.
We'll do some more of this.
This is cool.
This is fun.
Okay. I enjoyed it.
All right, very cool.
Thank you.
Talk to you soon.
Love you, Ken.
Okay, bye-bye.
Well, there you have it.
The very first episode of the MTV Chronicles
with my friend Ken Clark.
Let me know what you think.
If you want to hear another one of these in lieu of regular daily source code,
or should we make it into a separate feed, a separate feature.
Add them at curry.com or MP3 feedback at gmail.com.
And I see that the BT bus is parked outside.
That means that they're going to hook up the four megabit line today.
Ooh, yeah, everybody.
So we've back tomorrow for the thank-out of Spide 80
for the daily source code.
Thanks for listening. Hope you enjoyed it.
Take care.
Bye-bye.