Well, good morning everybody from Seattle, Washington in the north-western part of the
United States.
Welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Today is June 23rd, 2005.
It is 1120 in the morning here in Seattle, which I have this great watch I told you about
the Patricia Bach for me, which means it's 220 in New York and 720 in the United Kingdom,
820 in the rest of Europe.
Now that you know that I'm your world clock, welcome.
I am really excited.
Excuse me, I just opened the windows here.
Got in last night, Flu Direct, we're not direct on force, and the Flu from London to
to Seattle via Chicago, which made for a very interesting flight.
Was nice about it, it was United Airlines, and United Airlines on Channel 9 has, if it's
gone, and usually you can listen to the cockpit and listen basically to the communications
between air traffic control and all aircraft, including the one you're on, and also aircraft
to aircraft communications, and that was actually funny because I was pretty tired and we
left like one PM, and I liked you know, down one glass of champagne, which of course they
always hand you in a little plastic cups, and then I fall asleep just about as the engines
are revving up on the runway, and I had my headphones on, actually my ear buds, my
Sony in earphones, listening to Channel 9, so I knew it was going on, I could hear about
all the bad weather in New York, and I actually woke up two hours later because something
some instinct in me said, oh wow, hold on, I'm not hearing anything else, and I'm hearing
the radio, and of course we were over the, over the ocean at that point, so it was logical
that there was a lot of air communication going on.
But here for Numbdix, which today it's seven o'clock as registration, a little pre-party,
and then Friday and Saturday is the big, well it turns out it's going to be quite a big
conference, I don't think it's actually, I don't think it's a, I don't know how many attendees
there are, I don't think it's really big, it's been sold out, they actually had to get
another room to be able to handle some of the overflow and be able to let more people
into the conference, but I feel that we're at a tipping point, and really the million
listener March has begun, and we're going to see a lot of announcements coming out,
some of them already happening today, which just made me so incredibly happy because we're
at this tipping point that I've been working towards my entire life, or most of my, certainly
all of my adult life, where the listeners are coming, and this is something that we've
talked about before on the source code, and Ron and I have talked about it in our strategy
cast, it's all about getting the listeners in, that is step one. Oh, but actually there's
something much more important than I'm excited about, congratulations to our operations officer
Brian Longus, a pod show, his lovely wife Jennifer, their twin boys, because they have another
addition to the family, Mason Andrew Longus was born yesterday, eight and a half pounds,
woohoo, for Jennifer, Lociento is what Brian will be saying, fantastic, couldn't be happier for
you guys, that's great news, so our pod show family has been expanded by one in just overnight,
so that is really one of the most exciting things. In order to understand why I'm so excited about
what is happening right now, I think I should go back a little bit and just tell you a bit
about myself, which I don't think I've really done the whole story in chronological order on the source
code, but I've been a broadcaster all my life, it's funny, it's a day-winder, throughout a
comment on his web blog a couple weeks ago, you know, Adam's just a DJ. Well, in many ways,
I am just a just a DJ, but my experience in radio and broadcasting goes back much, much further,
and I want to talk a little bit about that so you can understand why I'm so excited about
what is happening right now, and what the reasons are for the excitement, because there's a
whole bunch of things just happening in succession, boom, boom, boom, one after the other is,
just stuff is just spitting out right now. When I was, well, first of all, I've always been into
into sound, and when I was six years old, I can recall two things from my, from my past,
I'm just loading something up here, I want to share with you in a minute, and there's actually
a picture somewhere of me sitting in my parents' closet, and I'd found an old real-to-real
recorder, and I don't think it actually worked, but I was sitting there with a microphone,
just in the closet with the doors open sitting in between clothes that are hanging up and playing
with this real-to-real recorder. And I also remember there was a kid on my blog, he was 13,
I think I was seven, and this was when you're still living in the States, and he had a miniature,
it was a red plastic real-to-real recorder. These, these reels were no more than dollar
pancake size, really, and actually you could turn it on, you could record your voice,
you could then rewind it and listen back to it. And that was the first time I heard my own voice
on tape, and I'm sure that anyone who's heard their own voice played back from recording
for the first time is always like kind of freaked out, because like, wow, I sound like that,
I sound like a girl, which of course at the time I'm sure I did sound like, because I was just a
little, little take. I actually remember saving up four weeks' worth of allowance to buy this tape
recorder off of this kid, and it was a messed up little machine, because the batteries that would pop
out, and if they popped out, it was almost impossible to get it to work properly again, so I had to go
back to him five or six times, until he got fed up with me, and then he wouldn't help me any more,
with fixing it. But after that we moved to the Netherlands pretty quickly, so the tape recorder
got lost somewhere in the mix. By the way, I'm pacing around the room, this is what I like to do
when I'm just yapping away, and this is going to be pretty much just a talk source code.
So we moved to the Netherlands, the Netherlands up until the 1990s, so the Netherlands,
you know, Amsterdam, we lived right underneath Amsterdam about 10 miles south.
Up until the 1990s, the Netherlands had government or state run radio and television,
which is not easy to conceive if you've grown up in the states with commercial broadcasting,
but most of the world actually still to this day works in this manner, where the government controls
the air waves, and they determine who is going to utilize those. And in most cases, in the
Netherlands, it's a very small country, you know, size of Rhode Island, probably a little bit smaller,
completely packed, 17 million people, all speaking one language, by the way,
certainly at the time when there was like 12 or 11 or 12 million people many years ago,
it's all Dutch. And the way the Netherlands chose to do it is they said, okay, we're kind of like
a social democratic country here, what we're going to do is we're going to let, we're going to
parcel up the air time on these frequencies based upon popularity of religious groups,
which is just an amazing concept when you think about it. And to this day, they still have all these
different broadcast organizations who are allowed to, who are allocated time on these television
and radio frequencies. And at the time, there are only two television stations and four radio
stations that you could listen to, but they were national, so there were transmitters all over the
place. And to this day, you still have at least five or six different religious groups
who have time allocated to them based upon membership. And membership, interestingly enough,
was measured by subscribers to your TV guide. So here's the wacky thing, I don't want to go into
that too much, but you know, the TV guide is the TV guide, everyone knows what's going to come on
because everyone publishes their information. But all the articles and the additional information
and really the concept of becoming a member, a member of a group that would allow your group
by having more membership to actually get more air time was very compelling at the time. And
it worked well for many, many years. But you can understand that at a certain point as the
world started to open up and more communications became possible and people started to cross borders,
that there was a real need, a real demand for other types of programming than what we're available
at the time. Now, please understand, as a kid, one is only one radio channel, one frequency
you can tune into that had the, quote, popular music and it started at 7am and ended at midnight
and it was basically controlled by all these different religious groups that that wasn't necessarily
compelling for everybody. And quite honestly, that just wasn't enough. There wasn't enough choice
or enough diversity for it to really work for anyone. So although that model I think was probably
valid at the time, what we have to look at is the frequency distribution. That's really what
it's changing here underneath our feet and from this distribution change comes many, many, many
derivatives which is going to make life extremely exciting. So I, without really knowing it was probably
one of these frustrated teenagers and I was very interested in broadcasting. Don't ask me why
don't ask me where, you know, if that's a gene that you're born with or if it's a reditary or
if it's something, I don't know, I just, I always like broadcasting and I certainly was no looker.
So I always felt that radio was perfect for me, you know, the old, the old adage of the perfect
face for radio. Well, that's totally how I felt. In the 70s, there were a number of
older people, I'm talking 20, 20, 30 year olds who were also very frustrated with the media
landscape, not just in the Netherlands, but all over Europe. And believe me, this is still to this
day is happening. The airwaves are regulated by the owners of the airwaves. That is the country
that the airwaves are broadcast in i.e. the government and of course having that type of
power to decide who uses the media landscape is power. It's big power. It's political power.
It's very, very important to the government to know what is being said and who's saying what.
But there were a number of, you know, so the music scene was just, that's really where it came from.
It was exploding. We had, you know, we're just coming off of kind of flower power hippie,
you know, the Beatles, and I didn't really, you know, I got into the Beatles very late because I'm
just not old enough. The purple, Led Zeppelin, you know, heavy, heavy ass rock, and then of course
disco came along. But music was changing very rapidly and lot was going on. And it wasn't getting
the exposure. Now we didn't have, you know, iPods and iTunes and digital radios and satellite radios.
You know, we had, you had a radio. You probably had a transistor radio and you had a record player.
And, you know, you have parties and you bring over your suitcase full of records and you take turns
playing, playing the music. So it was a frustrating time or unsatisfying. Let's put it that way.
So a number of people who felt that they also had some kind of calling or mission to be broadcasters
with the help of interestingly enough and backing, financial backing of radio manufacturers started
these pirate radioships in the North Sea. The North Sea sits right off the coast of the
Netherlands between the Netherlands and the United Kingdom. And they had found kind of a loophole in the
law, which was if you're on, if you're on international coastal waters, then there's no law
that applies to you. And so they were there broadcasting on mediumwave AM, basically broadcasting to
well, like radio Caroline, we were broadcasting to the United Kingdom who had similar issues with their
BBC public, you know, their government-controlled airwaves. And there was radio Veronica and me and
me go and radio North Sea and these guys were all sitting on shitty ass boats and some great
radio to listen to, by the way, you know, when big storms on the North Sea and the anchor
broke loose and they were made a call and then these guys the competition got so fierce between them.
They started throwing bombs at these other ships and it was pandemonium. And of course,
eventually they figured out a way to outlaw that. And the North Sea is not that big so it's kind of
hard to outrun and you know, and believe me again, the awesome power of airwaves is a very important
issue to any type of government. So they came on shore and radio Veronica basically did something
really smart as they said, you know what, we think that we have enough power, we have enough people
who are interested in our type of programming which is religion, agnostic, you know, it's all about
entertainment, fun, music, being there, being a part of it, being a part of this cool club,
we think we have enough to qualify to get a broadcast license and they mobilized on the 18th of
April 1970, Paul, I forget the actual 70 year, they mobilized, I think more than a million people,
I believe, to march on the government in the Hague and the Netherlands to demand that radio Veronica
receive a slice of this airtime. Now there's a whole bunch of, you know, there's a whole
lineage that keeps on going from there, but that was really the start for me, where hey wait
and then here's something new on radio, they only had a couple hours a week on the public broadcast
frequencies but it was exciting and it was fun and these guys were yelling and screaming and playing
great songs and just having a good time and I totally felt I want to be a part of that and the
mystique of the man behind the microphone for some reason just really struck me. Now of course I was
14 years old, there was no way in hell, I was going to get on the radio, but I had received from
my parents a radio shack 101 project kit and I'd probably still sell something very similar to this,
which you know, then it was just transistors and diodes and capacitors and now it probably
includes integrated chips that you can manipulate and build applications with, but it really was an
application kit and you had little wires, different lengths, red, white and blue for a different length
of wire and you could clip these into little springs and create things and one of the things
that could be created was an AM transmitter and the transmitter was very, very weak, it didn't go
far at all but I had learned enough through this project kit to understand that I could probably
also build an FM transmitter which I did and I built a little FM transmitter which really doesn't take
a lot of components to create that and it can run off a nine-volt battery and then of course
it all comes down to how good is your antenna to really get your signal out and the distributed.
So I'll be tinkering away and also at the time I was heavy into CB radio so I knew a little bit
about again there's that radio thing, I knew a little bit about antennas and how they worked and
and just had learned a lot just by fooling around with it and using it and I built an FM transmitter
and immediately told my mom, come on mom jump in the car we got a drive around and see how far
the signal reaches and man it was good you know I could see where there were some dead spots in
in my broadcast but it was cool and what I would do is I'd just try to cassette player plug that
straight into the transmitter and you know so it would roll on for a bit and would listen to it
and so my mom was nice enough to drag me to drive me around and see that a couple of times she
got tired of that eventually of course but um a day or two later I heard through the neighborhood
and then we lived in a small village maybe only 800 people lived in this village just south of
Amsterdam that other kids had heard this because the frequency the dial wasn't jammed you know
there was there was only a couple of stations so there's lots of free spectrum interestingly enough
just unused at the time and they were listening and they said hey that's pretty cool man we
we heard the signal that you've been putting out and so immediately I was I was I was I was hooked
and I was the next thing I did oh that's right then I figured well wouldn't be nice if I could
you know do just like the big guys and I could play a record and talk and then play another record
and I had a microphone so that was no problem but essentially I had to figure out how to mix
all this together so bought a couple more books you know got the soldering iron out bought some
a few components some potential meters basically faders slider faders and built them into a
wooden cabinet I was no woodworker by any means but it kind of worked and I had a mixer and I
could mix stuff and I started doing broadcast and you know and it was totally harmless so I didn't
have to really worry about any local FCC getting on my butt about it but I was I was I was I was
like wow look at this feedback people are listening to what I'm saying they're hearing the
music I'm playing they're responding to it and that gave me a great feeling and I really wanted
to do something with this when I was 15 I saw an ad in the local newspaper that they were looking
for on air talent and engineering talent for the the nearby located hospital the tulip
possible hospital in umstulfane again south of Amsterdam I jumped on you had to be 16 but I
cleared it when my parents had said yeah I just lied to them you know you can just say or 16 if
they ask if you get caught well then you're out of luck but we think it's it's a close circuit
radio station which means you have a very captive audience it was it was quite a trip but they
had a professional studio and they had you know a big mixer and they had you know they had
everything except the transmitter actually transmitter was just wires running through the entire
hospital so people would listen in on an earphone they had a choice of you know the four
national uh nationally run uh stations and then a fifth station which was this radio tulip
power tulip radio and it would come on at six p.m. and it would go off the air around nine or
ten and we had different groups working that and it was all um volunteer work and I was accepted
I wasn't accepted as an on air host I was accepted as an engineer first off and so I was
running the board as we say it for um and stringy at microphones for the different shows and I do it
as much as possible in between homework and and school work and I'd go to the station I really
learned my chops there and that's where I was introduced to many different techniques of presenting
there were a number of people there who were very very influential on me and as I was building my own
craft but it was a great place to get my chops down and I met a guy there called Yurumfen
who I'd later I went on to create many many great radio shows with who was working at a pirate
radio station in Amsterdam now so here and this time I'm 1617 and you know mobile had a had a
a moped which kind of looked more like a motorcycle and oh boy who's this oh boy oh no one second
I just got to take this I'll be right back and go anywhere okay sorry about that uh interrupted my flow
okay um right so I met this guy and um and he was working for a pirate radio station
in Amsterdam and this was a much bigger operation these guys had 150 watt FM sender
sender transmitter they had a huge antenna on top one of these canal houses and they were broadcasting
from Friday afternoon until Sunday morning and it was the rhythm of the city it was decibel radio
it was fucking amazing and we had a tremendous reach because of the height of our antenna and
we were playing and this is you know eighty eighty one I think yeah eighty eighty one and we were playing
Madonna when the one her her record first came out that included borderline in holiday and it wasn't
until two years later that that became a hit we were playing and this is in the days of fun boy
three in banana ramma it was Johnny Gill and Stacy Lada saw it was really music you just could not
get anywhere else and we were major heroes we were all fucking geeks and we were you know basically
shun you know from from social life but we would all converge on this little station which you know
we had we had advertisers local advertisers we had enough money to pay rent and we had enough
money to kind of keep the operation going we still had the all pony up for the drinks and for the coffee
but it was one of the most fun periods of my life we were just creating complete free form radio
doing whatever we wanted the only restriction we had basically was our own lives and there was
no way that we were making enough money to pay ourselves to do any of this but man we were having
a great time and the feedback loop through the to the phone line and through just people on the
street it was great and from that day I you know I knew this is well I already knew it but
I wanted to be a broadcaster parallel track I was a oh man what do I have I have like ten I
went to I'm at the pause this and continue a little bit later but it'll be worth it because
I really want to get some of the story out so parallel track I was working at a computer electronic
store on on weekends on Saturday selling components and stuff and the first computer started
to come out and I'd already been introduced to the Apple 2 my dad had one which I didn't
really use but I kind of tinker to run with it the common or VIC 20 came out and I learned a
lot about you know just how data flows through a through a computer and there was another guy there
who was a friend of mine he was a little more technical than I was but together we came up with
our own modems that we built so essentially it was a 75-bod modem which and it was acoustic
and he said I had a little kind of like acoustic coupler made out of cardboard boxes and you
we dial each other up and then we put the phones on to our cardboard box acoustic couplers
and if I hit the A key on my terminal like a second later or so it would show up on his terminal
and so we had a way to communicate and I think it was from that day because I keep coming back
to the modem story that I knew that there was going to be a way to broadcast remember I've been
doing everything illegally or at least not on real frequencies up until that point I knew that there
would be an alternative way to distribute that would allow for radio to happen in different ways
what we'll just call it radio it's really audio distribution of audio but we'll just call it
radio to make it much easier and it was throughout the next 15 almost 20 years that this just
kept staying in the back of my mind I knew that there was going to be ways to do this when the internet
happened when it started to to pop onto the scene and I was introduced to the internet in 1980
788 when it was you know there was no worldwide web yet to get a slip account in order to dial in
it was all unix it was something completely different than what we see it today although
structurally not really that different just it was presented in a different way we hadn't developed the
web browser etc. I kept playing with ways to distribute audio was the most logical one because
I've been a Mac guy all my life and I've been playing around with quick time for a long long time
and understood editing and digital editing I got it completely you know it's a copy paste right
that's that's really what editing is you don't need much more so since I since I was 14 I've
basically been honing my chops on on this audio stuff and I remember when higher speed modems
came out and my first company had just started up it was called on-ramp and the technology portion
was based in an apartment in San Francisco where the guy who I'd met from son micro systems
called Jacob and his brother Chris and so they had a couple of sun servers with a T1 line which
was a big deal to get it into their apartment there and on in barca deero and we were you know
serving up at that point not even yeah I think we just started serving up mosaic web pages that's
right mosaic was out and I remember when the first 9600 bought modem came out and Carl would sit in
San Francisco and through the I think was the PCM codec was basically streaming in real time audio
to me now it would come through you know choppy and it would have to re-buffer and it would break
but you know he had him on the phone he said okay check this out and he would start up a little
units process they would be blasting out this you know in a one song or whatever I think I think
was this I got I wish I remember what song it was and it would come through on the other end
I was like god this is fantastic we just went across the country and it was transmitted through
you know through these wires and I was freaking out I loved it I knew that it was going to happen
now of course I didn't have any of the technical knowledge or understanding of what that you know
what that really meant you know what the bandwidth considerations are what the scalability was
of it all but it wasn't long after that that you know I had actual an actual office in New York
had one employee Brad Sirling who we were sitting in an office together I got a call one day
yeah I'm gonna finish this part of the story then I'm gonna have a quick lunch and I'll come back
and I'll finish it I got a call one day from a guy he said hey look my name's Ron Bloom
I'm in Los Angeles I think I have an idea and this is 1994 so I think I have an idea of how we can
do something with the Grammys because I know the guys over at Narris the National Court Academy
of Recording Arts and Sciences and I think that we could put together what he called a cybercast
which was at the time you had simulcast remember those from the 80s we could watch the
concert on TV and the radio station would broadcast it in a beautiful stereo sound
said we could do something really cool where the Grammys are on TV and we'll provide a
separate broadcast which will consist of web pages it will consist of pictures Casio just come out with
their first digital consumer camera that they were trying to get into the marketplace and I said
I think we can also interview and do some audio I'd also hooked up with progressive
networks which was Rob Glazer's company before it became real networks and so he came into New York
the next day you know we talked about the idea I said it's great I'll see you tomorrow in LA so we flew
out to LA we went to the Grammys and we said hey you know we want the license to be able to do this
cybercast and and really at the time the Grammys was you know there weren't troubles a very broken
brand it was all you know considered old fashioned and certainly not hip and so they liked the idea
and they said well that's fantastic we'll give you a license for a million dollars and we said hey
that's really cool but we were thinking zero dollars because we have no money and we talked them into it
and we were thinking that the way we would monetize it is that we could go to their existing
sponsors and sell on a little sponsor ship and as we're walking out the door with our free license
they said oh one more thing you can't approach our existing advertiser so we had a couple of months
of real you know real starvation there trying to figure out how we were going to make this happen
and we teamed up with a great sales company who media america who helped us sell this to advertisers
of course was a lot of it was experimental budget at the time but we got it done and we had to drop
a T1 into the shrine auditorium these days I'm sure the shrine auditorium has plenty of fiber all on
its own you know we flew like a team of seven or eight out there all people who are you know
still very dear to my heart and we've worked together for a long long time we had a great time three
days of the Grammys and we were actually streaming audio and we were doing CUCMe if you recall that
CUCMe video it was it was it was it was just fucking phenomenal we were creating content on the
fly that was written it was pictures it was captions with the pictures it was streaming audio it was
CUCMe it was all little bits and pieces but together it really made a beautiful broadcast environment
it was a very exciting time for us and we went back after the Grammys and we just you know okay
now everyone's gonna call every record producer all the artists all the labels the television
stations anybody who has anything to do with content is going to is gonna start calling and we sat
by the phone four days and heard nothing but fucking crickets not a single person called
now we did actually start a company from that because we did at one call from a gentleman
called Bob McColley who worked at the Anheiser Bush and he said he'd called up and he said hey
I saw you guys at the Grammys we're really interested in some of this stuff and we'd like to know more
and do you have you know do you provide these services and of course we put on our other
hat and said well yes of course Mr. McColley we provide these services for you and we we essentially
went out and to St. Louis and created Budweiser dot com that was the first of many initiatives
but we were creating content we had the Bud guy on the road who went to all the races
we had the born on date if you look at your Budweiser bottle or can you see that it says this
beer was born on that was something that we that we came up with by um there's always been a
barcode which can tell you down to the quarter hour when that actual beer rolled off the the assembly
line and you could input that code into a little web app we had made and would tell you when
your beer was born and that turned into an actual branded thing on the on the Budweiser cans and
bottles so but that's beside the point there was it was just it was not going to happen we were
not going to be able to create our own content and distributed and at that time I'd after MTV dot
com we had metaverse dot com the vibe which was you know just all kinds of great stuff that we
were putting together ourselves we had no way to monetize it except selling it through to corporate
corporate entities who wanted to use that to make themselves more attractive to their core audience
now that was what eleven years ago ten years ago and now and of course the the big problem was
we really didn't have the audience there was no audience to speak of and now as we fast forward
I think it was Peter Day actually let me I think I have this bit Peter Day the BBC
he really said it right I'm going to you've heard this in a million times I'm going to play it for you
again because I don't always think get that listen to what he says it is so true this is this is
you know this guy's been in broadcasting for thirty five years listen to what he says
something remarkable is happening here radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who
managed what you can hear since radio is invented it's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with
something or nothing to say so exactly the gatekeepers and they're called gatekeepers but I don't
think you know anyone who controls the frequencies that were allowed to broadcast on allowed to use
for distribution they're not necessarily all evil but it's a big power game there's a lot of
things that's stake in that so now with what we have we have the bandwidth to be able to do audio
we certainly have the bandwidth for audio but only barely I'm telling you we're going to run into
some interesting situations with bandwidth and we still have to figure out how to handle that better
because there is a very definite cost attached to distributing this audio over the internet
we have the iPods MP3 players we have this mobile mobile radio that we can take along and it's
almost like history is repeating itself you see companies who have the radios they're investing in the
pirates so you're seeing Apple trying to get podcasting into the mainstream audible is actually a
pirate by themselves I would say initially they're you know but they have done a lot of work on
on creating a lot of these well creating the first the first real player I think auto
will can be credited with and bookmarking and all kinds of stuff like that but they really
pioneered that space Microsoft real networks the distribution is about to blow open wide and what's
interesting is that they're still and I think certainly also hear it at nomdex a lot of it's
still about the technology audio just launched a public beta yesterday and I of course I'd
signed up for an invite and I got in and although their creation tool isn't working yet
they're providing a way for you to it's a sample to browse to sample and to subscribe to podcast
and what was the most enjoyable thing you think oh well you know he's this is a competitor
and I'm not gonna like what I see and how do we go and you know how do you fight these guys
not true at all oh no way I've always said we have to bring in the listeners it has to be made
easier we have to bring in the hundred million listeners in order for this to really start
to to be something exciting and we're at that tipping point because what do I see on Odeo's home
page I see the daily source code I see three other shows that were involved with all being
distributed through Odeo so it's fantastic I couldn't be more happy about this stuff
Apple is what they announced are doing something with the Sundance Festival
Robert Redford and you know of course Apple has all these big Hollywood contacts that's great
I want hundreds of millions of people to hear about podcasting and to go sample it wherever you can
because my mission and our mission has always been to get this great content in to nurture this
content help people who don't who have something to say who are communicators but don't know how to
handle the technology don't know what to do with it maybe are just a bit intimidated by creating it
that is that is where the magic is finally we can create our own content and get wide distribution
and the good stuff does always rise to the top and when I say good stuff it's good stuff to you
if you're looking for something and you're interested in a particular topic very much like
web logs you'll find it it's going to flow through through a number of different ways of course
there'll be some traditional marketing and advertising that that always helps I've been working
very hard on pushing podcasting out to the public thank God we got a name for thank you
Danny Grigwar we got a name that you know helped the the traditional press glam onto it
and you're going to see in the next few weeks an incredible amount of traditional already existing
content or people who are already stars and celebrities they will be podcasting they're
it trust me I think the clear channel who own many thousands of radio stations
that they're going to do a deal with it could be Apple I don't know that would make sense
and they'll be podcasting all their stuff and that's great I want lots of people to come in
where we're going to shine is when we start bringing stuff that you've never heard before
and that's of course what people have really glomed on to particularly in the United States is
this fresh content fresh ideas exciting ideas unregulated ideas boy that's a real big one there
but also there's no time constraint except for the fact that I have a lunch hold on a second
let me see what this is hello hello be right down okay shoot you know what you're just going to
have to wait for another three seconds before I finish this up wow so what was only three seconds
for you this is double time-shifting technology it worked my friends was three and a half hours for me
I'm now back in my room the phone call you heard me get was uh Don Katz uh from audible and uh he's
in Seattle and so we had a quick a well quick yeah like an hour long meeting over a quick lunch
and after that I went to real networks who are located headquartered actually in Seattle
Rob Glazer who well we talked about that earlier who have known for many many years and there's
another company let's add a fourth to our list who are going to help us with our 100 million subscriber
March 100 million listener March and we have a ways to go but I can't tell you how excited I am
about all these companies that are basically going to open up the path to listeners and it's going to
be very interesting let me give you some numbers here for a second um and we're already at about 37
30 eight minutes I think yeah 38 almost 39 minutes I want to wrap it up pretty quick um according
to a article I read today Apple iTunes so this iTunes music store reached 1.7 million households
in March okay seems like a big number it's a spit in the bucket when it comes to what broadcast
radio and television networks reach it's really nothing I think we've discussed the Wall Street
journals reporting earlier that all online music sales all online music sales that includes
rhapsody that includes iTunes music store it's it's anything you can find that sells music online
is only about 2% of the entire sales of the whole music business so we've got quite a ways to go
and what we're going to see is that as listenership opens up and it's going to be up to you I mean
this is the beauty of it is if you want to just create a show I think every every podcast has a minimum
of 10 listeners because that's going to be your friends your family you know your your boy scout
group whatever it is you know and which of course will be very feasible to do very economical
because you just it's you know those prices are coming down fast enough and there's some great
services out there of which pod show also would be providing services but if you want to
really go out aggressively and get listeners and it's one thing to do it in a if you're like a
a common entertainment base show and you just want to have a broad appeal which I think is very hard
to do by the way it's very hard to appeal to a big mass audience or if you're doing a beer cast
and you just want to talk about beer your your listenership is going to grow let me just give you
some other numbers the daily source code which has currently approximately a hundred thousand
downloads per show a hundred thousand downloads per show of which the numbers actually increased a little
bit now it's about 25 to 27 percent of the daily downloads are through subscription which means
it's automatic that costs me or pod show in this case about three hundred fifty dollars a day
okay so it's not free and and there's many many ways that that can be dealt with and many many
economic models that can be put into place lots of them and that's exactly what we're working on
with all of these companies which is why I'm happy to talk to all these companies and
people have different motives different reasons for going out and doing podcasts and actually going for a bigger
audience some is for promotion of something some will be because of the nature of it you can say
what you want be free and some will maybe you know have ulterior motives and deals actually let me I
want to you know give you a quick little taste of a podcast that is a co-production that we're doing
that will be launching in the next week or so it's Spike Lee just listen to a little bit of the Spike Lee
podcast and I think he'll he'll totally get it how what how he's using this medium here he comes
we want to make the best fucking film post wait a minute what did that stop oh is that my
Mac again acting up of course this is interesting I mean people ask me what's the worst thing
as a director and a lot of times I make a knowledge between sports and films because also two
of my interest but the worst thing in sports is when you have an athlete only cares about his
statistics the team is about me me me how many points I'm gonna shoot I'm gonna shoot
Kobe Bryant it's pretty cool how many balls that don't me now listen carefully because in this is this is really
Spike Lee doing a podcast you know he's just talking in the unedited voice of Spike and it's in his
production office in Brooklyn and you can hear the air conditioner running in the background so I can
like a hot summer day and act and then film it's like the act who so Spike is another person who is
sorry about that that was my microphone and I just just don't want to put that right on oh
there's another guy who is who's on a mission and I think that we're we're here at nomdex
and there's a lot of excitement building it's a very geeky a lot of it's about RSS
Microsoft will be announcing their plans with RSS now I know exactly what it is I was asked not to
talk about it it seems that it's pretty much common knowledge and a lot of people were told with their plans were
audible will be making an interesting announcement also involving podcasts subscriptions and RSS
look for big big big Hollywood companies to come in I don't know if I can't remember if we talk about this
but I'm sure that clear channel yeah I do we talk we did talk about this who own all these
radio stations they're going to be taking their content and podcasting it that's great you know that's
fantastic but if you look at those numbers and you see that we have an audience that is growing but we
need to move towards the hundred million listeners where is the next great content going to come from
it's going to come from you it's going to come from all of us who have ideas who want to get those
ideas out who want to share with people and you know it may you may be intimidated by the technology
you may not have all the pieces together for the format and if you want to monetize it commercialize it
that's what I want you to come to us for come to pod show for that send an email to atamercareer.com
and be more than happy to help help you out because the listeners are coming the hundred million
listener march is on its way I think it has already been underway but after nomdex there's going to be a
lot of heat and a lot of big companies mentioned them all in this podcast who will all be moving
towards bringing their existing listeners in exciting new listeners to come in and when they come in
it's not going to be just about content you could have heard on the radio it's going to be about
this fresh new exciting group of voices that have great ideas and just haven't had the opportunity
to get it out there or may not even have known that the opportunity existed so that said we're going
to wrap this up we have the registration party which I think Google is throwing and kind of the
get together the evening around seven or eight o'clock so I'm going to go to that and of course
I will have more to report as I will be podcasting from from nomdex in Seattle
stay subscribed daily source code dot com if if you haven't done so already you can definitely send me
feedback because I said add them at curie dot com and if you got some ideas and you want to
be there for the hundred million listeners that are going to show up soon then
you know who to contact and with that I will end with our signature
another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
you