Delta Sierra Charlie 2-6-8
You know the weird guy in the corner of the office who always has his headphones on?
That's you!
Ah, Joe!
There are no secrets!
Only information you don't get out of!
Adam Curry!
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass!
Then the next generation radio content in my ears!
We don't need no sticky ingredients!
I like to think I'm flying into the future!
Just take it!
It's Adam Curry!
And it's Thursday only two more days like get to go home!
October 27th!
I was looking for that clip of Dorothy saying,
I wish I could go home!
I could only just click my heels together three times in my Ruby Red Slippers
and I'll be transported back and forth!
Eight Thursday everybody!
Good morning! How are you doing?
Running about half an hour later than usual,
because I've got some chores to do here at the condo.
It's at 9.17.
Once again from Curry condo and let's see.
Well, it's kind of overcast,
but I think it's going to be a beautiful day here in Northern California.
The lateness, I'm not that you noticed it,
because you're getting the show whenever you usually get it,
is because I got the machine room running full speed.
I've got a load on.
I've got a load in the wash.
I've got a load in the dryer,
because I only had underwear for 10-day stay.
That's the power of Curry.
I'm not going to tell you I am so excited.
And I'll tell you what.
In fact, we'll talk about that a lot today.
I had one of those major epiphanies last night.
You know, we just just before you go to bed,
you're like, oh my god!
And then all of a sudden, it all fits together
and everything just clicks in the place that makes sense.
I almost couldn't get the sleep.
That's how excited I was.
I'll be sure to tell you a little bit about the epiphanies.
Let's book up your definition of epiphanies too,
just so we're talking about the right thing.
Hold on, I'm going to get to dictionary.com.
And to kick it off today.
You smell it?
Yeah, that's kind of weird.
I don't know if I should be concerned, but it smells like destiny's child.
And we'll see you back.
You can fix it.
Let me talk.
Friends, you can fix it.
CJ.
Join the night.
Spending night.
I'll see you in the bed.
They want it.
Follow better.
Don't turn.
Take me.
Can you hear the pain of me?
That's so useless.
I'll get with me.
I'll get with you.
Yeah.
I was right.
Big pile of booty lissus here on the floor in the condo.
Mr. DJ remake smells like Destiny's Child on the Daily Source.
Go Thursday 27th of October 2005.
Okay.
So as I said, I was planning on kind of being on my way home by now.
That's a weird pact for.
But all flights fully booked up Saturdays the first.
And I really sucks, man.
At least I wish I could have left on Friday because you lose a day.
So now instead of arriving Saturday arrives Sunday.
And of course, I have no no underwear.
Well, I have underwear, but it has to get washed.
And I got a great machine.
Oh, man.
Hold on.
It's still running yet.
Okay.
I got to keep my eye on it because as I've been taught by my lovely wife,
the minute the dryer is done, you've got to take the clothes out.
Because when they're warm, then you can kind of shake them out and fold them.
And then you don't have to do any ironing.
So I do have to keep my eye on it.
And that may be a short introduction somewhere in the middle of the source code today.
So, wow.
You know, first, I want to start with an apology first of all.
That's what I want to do.
A couple days ago, I got an email from PWFent and PW.
Now, he lives in Tampa, Florida.
And he's been working with me for, since Pod Show was incorporated actually.
He was actually working for a different company because this was all pre- Pod Show.
And he is been responsible for the production of everything that happens on serious
satellite radio.
So we work a lot together.
But we work mostly via email and text messages.
And once in a while a Skype or a phone call.
And so here's the context that email fucking sucks, man.
You lose all context.
And also the mainstream media sucks.
And that's why I get to my apology.
So PW sent me an email a couple days ago and he said,
you know, if we're to lose power because of, because of her arcane here,
then I really need a Windows laptop in addition to, you know,
it's other gear that he has because it,
well, there's a whole bunch of technical reasons for it.
But the bottom line is that then, you know, he'll be mobile so he could still
complete the show and get it off to,
you know, it's all done through networks.
You know, all through the internet to get the show up to,
up to serious.
And it's pretty cool the way it works actually.
And of course, I had no problem with that.
But I'm like, you know, I wasn't kind.
It's weird because I understood what he was saying.
You know, if the electricity goes out,
and then of course my mind went immediately to the next step.
So what if the electricity goes out,
but it goes out for 300 miles.
You know, I'm just thinking like,
I know what I'm talking about.
So what's our backup plan?
You know, do we have the files somewhere else?
So someone in a different location could do it for instance.
And we kind of went back and forth and,
and we're like old women on email, man,
we can bitch and moan each other.
It's actually, it's a very lethargic.
Lethargic is it the right word?
No, that's not the right word.
That's some sort of the wrong word.
It's, it makes you feel good
to yell at someone over email.
As part of that person doesn't take the shit and yells back.
And so I kind of let it go, you know,
and I figured, all right,
so I'll figure out the laptop and electricity problems,
whatever.
And I'd seen, of course, on television,
just about the only coverage I really saw of Hurricane Wilma
Florida was this clip that's been played over and over again.
And although very funny,
to see Al Roker fallen his fat face,
I know Al Roker, I've met him many times,
not a nice guy.
At least that was not my experience.
So that was kind of funny,
but it wasn't until yesterday that we're sitting in the office
and Ron comes in and he's crouch behind his computer
and he's like, where?
And I'm like, what you talking about,
you know, he's talking about all this stuff
and something was fucked up.
And what's wrong?
He says, well, you know,
there's 2.8 million people without electricity in Florida,
which includes a lot of his extended family,
his wife, Martha's family lives there in Miami,
and they have their condo,
which has been without power for,
so it's been, at least a day,
maybe even more.
And I'm like, what?
And then you start to think about it.
You know, what happens if there's no electricity?
And I think what happened in my mind is,
sure, I've had power go out.
You know, we used to live in Jersey,
and we'd have a blizzard,
and then the power would go out,
but it would come back on, you know?
But that's a blizzard.
That's a little different, you know,
where a power line might come down
and it can basically be repaired
reasonably quickly,
but when it comes to the devastation of a hurricane,
just imagine,
just imagine for a second that the power,
see what I mean?
See how fucked up that is?
And then that would, you know,
power would go out,
not just for a second there,
but for 24 hours,
48 hours,
you know,
think of the stuff that starts to happen,
think of the stuff you can't do.
Besides not being able to create
or listen to podcasts,
I think there's a lot more.
And so now,
now it's clicking in my head,
I'm going,
oh,
okay,
you know,
of course,
PW was way more involved,
you know,
living in Tampa,
way more preoccupied with what was going on,
and I really wasn't sensitive to that.
And so apologies PW.
There you go honey,
I love you.
You know I did.
Terry,
yes,
Scott Sloan from the Alaska Pod Show,
way up here in Anchorage,
Alaska.
I have a question for you,
but before I ask,
I'd like to thank you for plugging us in
to show number 265,
but this leads to my question.
I was speaking with a promoter today
from an artist that is listed in the pod
safe music network.
One of the questions we had
and we were discussing
was when it'd be great to collect data,
to see how well the pod safe music network
is converting for the artist,
musician or even the podcaster.
It would be nice to know what kind of impact
the pod safe music network is making,
and if this data is not available,
maybe it's something that can be plugged in
to the membership side of the pod safe music network.
Maybe a simple survey
that everyone could fill out
and learn or communicate
how well the pod safe music network has served us.
That's all I have for you today.
Have a great day,
take care of yourself,
and from Anchorage, Alaska,
this is Scott Sloan.
Scott, thank you very much.
Well, very good question,
and I have a couple answers for you.
And of course, you know,
the pod safe music network is so dear to my heart,
and I think it's extremely,
extremely successful.
I think it's important to what we're doing
with pod casting.
So let me address those for that question.
First of all,
yeah, we do have data,
and we have some really interesting data,
and we're going to start making that available very quickly.
The first piece of data is the spins.
Now you can go to the homepage of the pod safe music network,
and you can see the top spins of all time,
the top listens of all time
and the top rated songs.
What we've done is,
and we've been kind of evaluating the list,
we've created top spins for the day,
top spins for the week,
top spins for the month,
and top spins for all time,
a spin being when a podcaster plays the song,
and then reports it back to the network.
Which, by the way,
you do have to do.
If you sign up for the pod safe music network,
and you're using songs from it,
you have to report when you play it.
And we're going to have to,
I guess,
well,
we have a couple of ways that we're policing as the wrong word,
but fuck it.
We sign an agreement,
the pod safe music artist put their stuff up there for you to use.
All you have to do is report back to the network.
So that data is going to be made available.
I'm very pleased with what I'm seeing,
and so that's the first conversion,
I guess,
you can say,
here's these songs actually being played on the different podcasts.
So that will be the first metric.
The next obvious metric is conversion to sales,
because that is really,
I would presume the way most artists are going to gauge their success,
is,
you know,
whatever I've done,
have I grown my audience,
and the best way to really measure that is who was purchased my CD or tracks.
So that's all part of this unlabel thing I've been talking about.
So,
you know,
that's on the way.
Today is not the day to talk about that,
but that's on the way.
So I think those will be the two most important pieces of data.
And it's,
and of course,
so there's always,
so the spins is important.
There's a couple of different shows doing,
I love hearing this,
doing the pod safe music network top 10.
In addition to that,
today actually,
I'm going to play a piece from the pod safe music rewind.
The pod chose pod safe music rewind show,
which is a compilation,
a weekly compilation of all of the pod safe music shows,
or not all,
but the top pod safe music shows,
and just a song from each of those.
It's a really tripping out to that yesterday.
So we'll talk about that in a bit.
But it's very much like what the,
what the,
the business is today.
Only we've eliminated all the complicated crap.
And keep your eye on it.
So the Nick,
I don't know.
So I can't,
I just had this usually a text message coming in,
so I just want to make sure that I don't miss the blackberry,
vibrating across the floor.
Let's see.
Now,
it's a brawn call me.
Come on, man.
I'm in the middle of the show.
You have no respect for the show.
All right.
Let me get to John here and then,
and we'll continue.
Hey Adam.
This is Dr. John from the Arborxonist podcast,
coming out of Louisville, Kentucky.
I've heard you talk about doing media outlet interviews,
several times on the source code.
And I wanted to send you some feedback and ask you,
if you had any tips for being interviewed about pod casting.
See, a reporter from the local newspaper here,
the courier journal has contacted me,
and I'm the first podcaster in our area that he's talked to,
which makes me both honored and a little bit nervous.
I'm wondering if there are any techniques that you've come across
to explain things,
if there are any sort of pitfalls that you've commonly read into,
or any other tips or pointers you could give me for sort of
dealing with the press.
This is going to be the first story that has ever run locally.
And I want to do my best to get pod casting out there
and push it out to a wider audience.
And so, I figured who better to ask
than the pod father himself, Mr. Adam Curry.
I'm also wondering if I could just do a general shout out
to any podcasters or podcas listeners in the Louisville area,
who might want to be interviewed for the story as well
because he's looking for lots and lots of folks.
So if you want to contact me,
I can put you in touch with the reporter.
My email address is AVNEST at gmail.com
or you can go to my website,
which is www.ardvarksnest.com.
That's A-A-R-D-V-A-R-K-S-N-E-S-T.com.
And hopefully we can get some great exposure
for pod casting and find some new listeners
for our million listener March.
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm on with that, Dr. John.
Okay, well, this is very difficult.
There's no way I'm going to be able to tell you
what to expect or how to do it
because it really comes from doing a lot of interviews
that you learn a lot of tricks.
So let me see if I can give you the top line
most important ones.
First of all, you have to really listen to the interview.
Remember, this person is asking you questions,
but their questions will almost always tell you
what they're, what they have in their head
and what they're already thinking
I think every journalist just like every human being
has an opinion about something.
And it has happened to me so often
that the questions will come in the form of an answer.
So let me give you an example.
Someone might say, so most podcasts are really about
pod casting still, right?
They're not really about all different kinds of topics.
Now, when you get a question like that,
that's when your antennae should go up,
way up and go,
because that means that the journalist
already has made a decision in his or her head.
And it's going to be very, very difficult
to take them away from that.
So when you hear questions like that,
you almost automatically know what the angle
of the article is going to be.
And from there, you can start to chip away at it
and you have to be very concise.
And usually just, if the answer is no,
then you should say no.
No, and let me tell you what it is
or how it is or the way it is.
I mean, that, that no has to be right up there in front.
That's, that's the most important thing
because journalists really can get stuck
in something that they believe is true
and they're just looking for confirmation.
And I'm not saying that that's bad journalism
is just my experience.
Now, as it pertains to the 100 million listener
March, and I think we're probably
a tenth of the way there.
And please, you can certainly report that number.
The, the most important thing,
or what I always talk about in interviews
about podcasting is, look, you know,
this demand, because that's really what it is.
It's listener demand.
Podcasting is being driven by people
who are sick and tired of listening to the radio.
They're tired of what they're being given.
They're tired of the limited choices.
They're tired.
It's, it's not even up to technical standards
of, of today's technology.
Look at what we can do.
So, that's what drove podcasting.
I think if you drive that point home
and you can give examples.
You know, we've done that several times here on the source code.
The examples are, you know, you say,
when's the last time you heard a disjockey on the radio?
Go, I love that fucking song.
I'm gonna play it every single day till you love it too.
I think it's been about 15, 20 years
since you heard a disjockey talk about a song at all.
So, those are the types of examples.
And that's the type of stuff that I would focus on.
And just beware.
Beware of the questions that you're being asked.
Listen to them carefully and, you know,
and try and process before you answer.
Why is this question being asked?
It's probably because there's already something set there
that you might have to undo.
Sometimes, of course, you can give out a big yes
and affirm whatever the journalist is thinking
if you agree with it.
So, that would be kind of my, kind of my advice to you there.
Oh, my goodness.
Let me see.
So, I don't have a hit test.
Y'ample that has been very, very busy.
You know, he's setting up this radio school
and he's teaching people how to create radio
and there's a whole podcast in curriculum
and so he's been very busy semini email
and wanted to find this the hit test.
Yes, John.
Of course, I miss it.
No backtrack podcast today.
But something else came in from a apocalypse doll,
which will suffice for now.
So Adam, you think you know your hits when they're home?
It's a homeless.
Let's see how well you know your hits
when they're hummed by me.
I'm popular of style.
This is a hum test number one.
Okay.
Let's get it started.
Number one.
What was that one?
Oh, can you figure it out?
Adam, sorry.
Okay.
Let's go to the next one.
All right.
Number two.
I know that one.
All right.
How'd you do with that one, Adam Curry?
That's like an instrument time.
I like to call it the late 80s.
You bet.
Up next.
That's my three and the last one.
LA guns is what it was.
All right.
Adam Curry.
How'd you do?
I don't know.
Okay.
Let's see.
The first one.
What is this?
All right.
Adam Curry.
How'd you do?
I don't know.
Okay.
Let's see.
The first one.
What is this?
Oh.
Thirty-eight special.
There.
Oh.
Second Humming.
Bad Humdrop.
Number one.
That's.
Hold on loosely by thirty-eight special.
Let's check out the answer to number two.
Mmm.
Uh-oh.
Yeah.
I was right.
Only guns.
Ballet or J?
Baby.
Uh-oh.
Ah, sorry Adam man. I'm kind of reminiscing here. It takes me back to my freshman year high school
That's LA guns with the bow to Jane. I got one up next the answer number three
I'd be like oh
Oh, sorry Adam man. I was into it. How about that by a bit along with? It's a good song, man
So of course, I'd say Duran Duran with Henry like the wolf. All right, how'd you do man?
Wow, you are humdinger or you're humiliated
All right, anyway, this has been a popular style. I'm home. Come over. Number one
All right
Thank you very much. There's all different variations of the format I guess. All right, you're gonna listen to a piece of potsafe
Is it from Brian bucket?
Just gonna take about four or five minutes. I'm gonna go shake out the dry laundry and put the wet stuff into the dry
I'll be right back. This is let the buggy loose on the daily source code
I got to get home to the later my bro
I got no time
It's tight
But I still get the town to not get so tired
It's the same old shit, just a jibbing day let the buggy loose
Let the buggy loose
Let the buggy loose today
Let the buggy loose tonight
In a matter of time you feel it all right
Trim up, put down the seeds
I shed the light on the brand, the day he has stretched my own
To give us a sign
I watched the glass right out of my eyes, I hit out
Down on the tail
No shame and jam and nothing but run out on the road home
Just do the show
All these girls ain't knocking on doors
No worries, money gets tired
But I still get the town to not get so tired
It's the same old shit, just a jibbing day let the buggy loose
Let the buggy loose
Let the buggy loose today
In any old flash away
Let the buggy loose tonight
In a matter of time you feel it all right
Feel it all right, yeah
Let the buggy loose tonight
Let our buggy loose tonight
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah and we got that we'll go
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Yeah,
Oh, yeah, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, I Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Oh, Dear God!
music network, music.pacho.com last night told you I had an epiphany.
Jah came to visit me, man.
I could have said God could have said Muhammad and could have said Buddha, but it was
Jah, you have to know, and I know, you've heard the lighter click, so you know
what my voice is.
And it ain't tobacco.
And I did a documentary of Jamaica.
Pool, this will be, let me just think.
I'm going to say this is about 12 years ago.
Maybe even a little bit longer than that.
And I fell in love with Jamaica.
I completely fell in love with Jamaica.
And learned a lot about the culture.
The documentary that I did involved a lot of Rastafarai stuff.
You know, a lot of stuff.
Obviously, you can't go to Jamaica and you can't get into the culture without
hooking up with Bob Marley's mom and going to Hope Road, which is where his house
is now museum and really getting into what Bob Marley represented.
And I've many, many friends in Jamaica.
And I think since then, we've been on vacation in Jamaica.
I'm probably 15, 16 times.
We got a little, we owe deed a little bit on Jamaica.
So we haven't been back in a couple years, but we've been talking about it just recently
saying, oh, man, we really need to go back to Jamaica.
We're really, it's so nice and so relaxing.
And when I was doing this documentary, I really did start to believe the whole
idea of the holy herb.
And it did wonders from me last night, man.
Oh, boy, it all came to me.
And it just, it just came so fast.
I got out, I jumped out of bed, started writing stuff down.
I was almost ready to call people when I realized it, like, you know,
quarter or two.
So the minute I'm done with the show today, it's off to the office,
because I got some stuff to share.
And I've been wanting to share the office with you guys.
I've been thinking about doing a sound seeing tool.
We've really just been so incredibly busy doing the show in the morning.
And you feel like you kind of, you know, behind the game already,
just because of the time difference and then I'm in the office
around 11, 11, 30 and, you know, I was like,
half the day's over, you know, got a hurry, got to do stuff.
So I really haven't had the time to do the,
to do the sound scene tour I wanted to do.
And I wanted to introduce you to a couple of people who work at Pod Show.
And then Michael Butler sent me an email yesterday.
We did a job cast a couple of weeks ago.
And job cast is basically us saying, hey, here's the people we're looking for.
We've hired a number of people through that job cast.
And he created a second job cast much shorter than the first one.
And normally I would just put that up on the weekend as a, you know,
separately in the daily source code feed.
So you could get it.
But as I listened to this one,
it actually is a sound seeing tour of the office and some of the people at Pod Show.
So I figured, I put it in the show today because it's,
yeah, it really gives a good representation of the vibe,
the feeling.
And if you're looking for a gig,
it might be handy.
So here is job cast number two.
Now let's go over to Michael Butler.
Hi, this is Michael Butler.
And I'm here with job cast number two.
I'm at the Pod Show offices with Brian Longus.
How you doing Brian?
Doing great.
How are you Michael?
I'm fine.
Couldn't be better.
So what's your official title?
VP of operations.
Vice president.
Okay.
Great.
You got to promote.
What would you, I thought you were before director of operations.
Vice president, higher than director.
Yeah, it is.
So you got to promote.
All right.
So what are we doing on this job cast today?
Well, first we wanted to say, hey, the first job cast,
we got an unbelievable response.
We hired a bunch of people, some fantastic talent,
and we're always looking for more.
So just thanks to everyone who emailed the resumes in.
We got so many.
We were flooded for a couple days.
All we could do was really attend to all the resumes and
increase that we're coming in.
So at this point, we're looking for even more people.
And so we wanted to make sure we would let everyone know,
hey, we are looking at them.
Some people we didn't even get a chance to email back and say,
thank you for sending it in.
If don't worry, if you haven't heard from us,
we have looked at the resume.
Yeah, I got a bunch of emails myself, and I have nothing to do with
this other than being the host of this job cast.
I just sent them all your way.
That's perfect.
Okay.
So those jobs, the ones that you were looking for were kind of
already filled.
I wouldn't say they were filled, because we're still looking for more people.
We had a couple of great hires, and we're still looking for more
and technology, sales and marketing, finance, many different
areas and groups.
All right.
So any specific guys you're looking for, guys or girls you're looking
for?
Absolutely.
Great question.
In terms of technology, we're always still looking for those that
have very high level architecture background, even people with
not just PHP programming, but database.
And then we're also looking for people specific in certain areas.
Those that have it had experience with search technology,
telephony, mobile computing, that sort of thing.
So anyone who has specific experience, we'd be really interested in seeing
their resume and having them send in some more information about themselves.
What's the official job title of these people you're looking for?
Is there an official title?
There's a couple different ones, depending upon the positions.
At the moment, we've also not only got the technology people, but we've got
sales and marketing, looking for what we call more
supervisors, people who know the web in terms of web advertising.
I should say media, those also in finance and on the site.
You'll see a particular job description for a controller.
And I saw on the website, I was just messing around on podger.com.
And it said, you're looking for a web intern.
What's a web intern?
Actually, the reason we posted that is we're looking for actually a couple
individuals that have a broad range of skills that are willing to
and would enjoy and have that real entrepreneurial background
and spirit because that's what our company is all about.
We've got really excited talented people here at the rock stars.
If you will and we're looking for what we call a web intern,
so I couldn't think of a better way to explain it.
But they'll be able to be involved in almost every aspect of our business,
helping out in many different ways.
So they do need some programming background.
I mean, like a PHP, my SQL, a Lamp environment,
but they'll be able to touch and deal with different individuals
and different groups.
So I'm taking maybe a college kid if you need to.
Absolutely.
In college, recently graduated, someone who's just really even
self taught if they've got that experience that we're looking for.
That's great.
I'll bet you'll get a ton of response from the college kids.
I'm sure.
Okay, so anything else?
No, that's it.
That's basically, you know, in a nutshell,
we still want to obviously keep people interested,
keep them setting in the resumes.
I mean, we know they're interested because we get so many
on a daily basis of fantastic.
We've almost spent a good, some of us half our day or more
and others just solely doing this because recruiting has been so important for us.
And you sent it to jobs at podshow.com.
Exactly.
Now the people that you hired, are they in the office right now?
Yeah, actually they're here today and I should say this is our
our temp space before we move into our new space.
All right, so let's take the microphones.
We'll kind of like do a mini sound seeing tour of the podshow offices here.
All right.
So here we got the front desk.
Okay.
And as you walk from front to back, got the mini fridge.
And this is the bathroom with bathroom.
The bathroom.
Download is done from.
And then the main area where everyone sits at the moment.
You can see we're cramp because we're hiring so fast.
And there's Chris McIntyre with the eye dog on his desk.
We've got Matt Oliver.
Just recently joined us in the last couple of weeks.
Say hello Matt.
Hello.
Actually, here's another individual Kevin who just joined recently.
And is this one of the recent hires from the job cast?
Yep.
So what's your name?
Kevin.
How you doing, Kevin?
What are you doing on this job?
What's your position?
Software engineers.
Okay.
You've got anything you can tell us about what you've done.
Or is it all top secret still?
Pretty much top secret.
Right.
Everything Kevin does is top secret.
There you go.
All right.
We're going to introduce you to the Colleen and some others at the moment there.
Business.
We're going to top secret meeting.
And actually, as we walk through, we're pretty much to the back of the office.
And now we're back in the very back of the offices.
And Ron Bloom is on the telephone.
We'll see if we can listen in on a Ron Bloom conversation.
We'll find some secret company inside information.
Five.
So.
Who's that Michael Butler?
That's me.
How are you doing?
Well, rock and roll geek entrepreneur.
That's right.
Ron Bloom.
The King of Podio.
The Podio.
The Podinator.
That's right.
Yeah.
At least I'm not the Pod mother.
Right.
You're the.
Let's see.
Adam's the pod.
Father.
We already went through this.
So you would be the.
Marlon Brando.
You're.
You got to be hired the Marlon Brando.
And the pod.
I'm counting on you to work on that branding.
Marlon Brando of me.
So we're doing a little sound seeing thing of the of the offices.
We're talking to a couple of people that were hired from the last job.
Because we figured maybe we would go to the new offices and show.
Or let the listeners hear how big the new offices are.
How cool.
How giant.
There you go.
I'm conceptually large.
It's going to be like an echo chamber.
It's going to be so big.
It's going to be a car campus.
That's right.
The Podio campus.
And we have some.
Fountains in the front.
What's building are you going to building one?
Yeah.
Building one.
Okay.
So we're going to building one of the project.
No.
We're building 42.
Which one of the two you're going to?
We'll start at the beginning.
Okay.
And we're in annex.
We're in area 50.
Something.
Yeah.
Hey.
69.
We're getting.
Thank you for your podcast, man.
Because your your job task helped us get some great people.
No.
Thank you.
All right.
So we're going to go talk to the new hires.
You're working to hear more often now.
All right.
You're coming in and doing some great stuff with bands and things.
Be here.
One week, I think.
One week.
The lower week.
Cool, man.
Because, you know, I recommend you for the job.
Which is one of the reasons why it took so long for anybody to want you here.
I appreciate it.
Okay.
I don't know what I'm going to do here.
But I'm going to do it.
I guess no.
Well, you're doing it.
Whatever it is that you're doing now plus some more stuff that we don't understand.
You need a more coffee.
There.
Yeah.
Which you guys beat me some on the way back.
But that's across town.
Only other campus in there.
Yeah.
All right.
I'll be Simon Eisen years.
Absolutely.
And I'll be giving you the same treatment.
Okay.
Talk to you later.
All right.
A little bit of sound seeing tour and job cast.
Thank you very much.
Like a fun little rock roll.
Get show.
I was cool.
That was very cool.
That's part of it.
I wasn't in it.
I love it.
So while that was playing, I folded up the whites.
And the darks are now spinning around in the dryer.
I have to ten more minutes to go.
So just about at the end of the show.
When that'll be done.
You know what?
That was so much talk.
Let me play some music for you.
This is from the Pod Show Music Rewind, which you can find.
Well, I think we're putting on the homepage actually today of the PodSafe Music Network.
Music.com.
This is Marcus Couch puts this together once a week.
And it is literally an overview of all of the top PodSafe music shows.
And one of the songs that they play.
I forget exactly who show we're going to drop in on, but it will be announced.
Listen to this.
And of course, if you want to subscribe to the show, you can find all of that at music.podshow.com at the PodSafe Music Network.
Music.
Hey, it's Marcus and we are back to present actually my clip for this episode of Rewind.
This is the scenes scene portion of the show.
And today I'm going to feature an artist out of New York City named Queen V.
And basically here's how you describe Queen V.
It's as if Joan Jett revamped her band.
Got a little more aggressive with her vocals.
Abtained an even tougher attitude and took on the militant lyrical style of Pat Benetar.
And you mix that up with some funk, swish it around and some pure rock guitar licks,
a dash of punchy drum tracks, and you've got Queen V.
So now you've heard the bio and it's time to hear the rock of Queen V.
Music.
Time to make the scene.
16 years of harmony.
Get around town, your majesty.
I should've known it twice.
It's way too slow.
Make me try.
You know you never thought I was the idea.
I've got to think it doesn't make it to blow your mind.
And I never thought I'd die.
Come on.
It's a play.
You're falling at our name.
Like a regular refugee
I only know your
Just me and a royalty
We've got as strong as I'm my pride
And know you don't care what I just I
wanna take and live before I die
been a man or...
Come on.
Down like acasting gun.
I got a little bug in your brain
This is where all you've doubt is out there and you'll sit in ties, and we know you are.
It's hard time to make the sea, got my girls to fight for me, couldn't make sure
But you agree, this is how it's got to be, suck it too slow, make you cry.
You know I don't care what you decide, I want to take it to the beginning, one last time, along, blow your mind.
My goodness, checks with attitude, Queen V, love it from the pod show, music rewind, find that a music dot pod show dot com.
It may even be a pod show music rewind dot com, well I got to check that.
Pretty cool, it's an enhanced podcast as well, I just noticed because Megaseg recognizes that and the minute I started it,
I popped a Queen V, a little picture there and a link and this is a great way to discover music man.
There's no easier way for me as a podcaster, I spend lots of time on what we call PMN pods and music network,
scouting around listening to new submission stuff that's coming in, and of course checking out what other podcasters are playing.
Because that really is the validation, you know, once there's a pod cache you like and you've heard some songs on that you'd like,
you just listen, you know, subscribe to the show, listen to it, and you'll eventually discover something that you really like.
It's a kick and ass, I really enjoy that last night. It's not all hard rock and stuff, by the way, it's a really nice mix and thanks to all the,
all the pod showers who are part of that show, really digging it.
So I'm going to scurry off to the office, as I said, I had the epiphany, and I think it was the, was it,
yesterday, the day before someone asked me about the, the secretive audition that I've been talking about,
I actually have to correct that. It's an audition, not an audition, but an audition.
And we will be talking about that in the source codes to come.
Tomorrow, of course, will be Friday. I'd really love it if you got anything that is going to be really up tempo and,
and fun and wacky and, you know, anything you got, send it off to me.
Be happy to share that with everybody because we're going to build a little party because it will mean my last show before I go back home.
I see the girls, it's going to be a lot of fun.
And, yeah, I think that's it. Let me see if there's a, let me just check my list here.
We did a Pita, Wilma, stupid Al Roker, wash, yep.
Oh, everything, the whites are full, I'm just waiting for the dark stuff to finish. Oh, yeah, toilet paper.
Got to steal that from the office.
Shoot, we did it. Perfect.
It's amazing, everybody.
DailySourceco.com is where you can find the latest show and where you can subscribe to the feed.
You, of course, you can also do that through iTunes, free download from macropho windows,
and send me feedback. If you want, add them at curie.com.
Everybody, I'll see you tomorrow for the thank God, it's Friday.
I did it.
Another pod show podcast, stick it in your ear.