Yes, in the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I don't want ever, I don't want ever, I don't want ever.
Space trucks keep falling on my head.
Strange weather ahead.
Ice shells are lending behind.
Feel right, coming out the caps.
And trails filling out the caps.
Anywhere that the sun shines for you.
As the chain flowing through our veins,
cell phones flying up rings, false cornflakes in the aurle.
A song that is living in the shed,
but he's changed his name to friend.
Well, at least that's what he said.
No one ever, I don't want ever, I don't want ever.
Space trucks keep falling on my head.
Strange weather ahead.
No one ever, I don't want ever.
Space trucks keep falling on my head.
If they keep falling on my head.
I don't want ever, I don't want ever.
Strange weather ahead.
I don't want ever, I don't want ever, I don't want ever.
I need to make sure all spring skies are lending shorts.
Cause try to find certain light.
No, only for weapons or any kill.
It's really time to take the pain.
You really have that way.
No one ever, I don't want ever.
Space trucks keep falling on my head.
Strange weather ahead.
I don't want ever, I don't want ever.
I don't want ever, let go.
I don't want ever.
I don't want ever, I don't want 걸.
I don't want ever, I don't want ever.
I don't want ever, I don't want ever, I don't want ever.
I'm not.
I don't want ever.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah
Like this, how do we go, like this
I wanna wake up
I'll ready to go, like this
I really don't like this
I got to wake up
I wanna wake up
I really don't like this
I got to wake up
I keep falling on my head
Space rocks
Keep falling on our heads
It's a way with the fairies
You know where I found that one
The podcast music network
Everybody thank God
Oh shit, I forgot my Friday
Hey, thank God, it's Friday
It's a shitty Friday
Horrible horrible weather
I had a whole flight plan
For a two-day trip of flight training
And hookin' up with some friends
Actually, hookin' up with one of my lawyers
Who helped me get some stuff
Oh, hold on
That's not right
There we go, that's much better
I'm gonna have some drinks with him
In Amsterdam tomorrow
Afternoon
But shit, it's not gonna happen now
Because we have over 20 knots crosswind
Here at the local airfield
At Faroaks, Echo Golf, Tango, Fox Trot
And they expected to go up to 30 knots today
If you know, if you're pilot
Then you know that doing that in a SESNO 182
Even the RG version is just dangerous
It's too much wind
And they're expecting even worse for tomorrow
So it looks like flying will be delayed
Until after the weekend
Hey, guess what everybody?
I am the Kate Winslet of Wikipedia
Oh, man
Talk about space rocks
I came home last night
And like a huge fucking space rock
Hit me right in the head
And I'm like, whoa, what's goin' on?
Oh, my goodness
Well, I appreciate everyone tuning in today
To hear what I have to say about this
Well, I got a lot to say about it
First of all, yesterday
I had a gnarly day trying to get into London
I was visiting Tom Buyers
Who was doing a guest
Stint at the University College London
Which is affiliated with Stanford
And it was two hours to get there
I made the mistake of taking a car service
Instead of the train
Which I should have done
Because once we're in London, man
It was pretty good to look at all the Christmas decorations
But it was gnarly
So I'd love to talk about that
But first, we've got to talk about this
Wikipedia controversy
If you don't know what I'm talking about
Then on curry.com
You can see a piece that I wrote about
At point to some of the original articles
That started this off
But wow, this thing is on fire
It's unbelievable
Here's what went down two days ago
I noticed in
I used a Google reader
And I like it because it's almost like a river of news
The Dave Preaches
What I'm totally hooked on
But not quite
But it works well enough
And it's pretty ubiquitous
And so I've been using that
And I saw a reference to
Maybe it was techno-radi
I can remember one of the other
I saw a reference to
But because of course you know
Every single day I get up
And I go to techno-radi
And search for myself
See if there's any articles about me
And I saw something about the history
Of podcasting
And I hadn't looked at the Wikipedia entry for a long time
And I went over that
I was astounded
But there were names in there
Who I've never heard of
I was like
Wow
Maybe brilliant minds
All do think like at the same time
And I made mention of that
In the source code
Which was at Wednesdays
I think at Wednesdays show
That you know
Neither my nor Dave Wine
There's contributions to podcasting
We're fairly represented anymore
And there were just a lot of
Sexual errors in there
That I know to be
Factually incorrect
And I don't know if Dave heard that show
Or maybe
For somehow he also noticed that
The Wikipedia entries were incorrect
And
So I said, you know
Shit man
And I have edited in this before
In the Wikipedia
And let me just point out
Wikipedia editing is not trivial
Now people think I'm full of shit
Or at least that's what they're writing
But I haven't even figured out how to do my own
Show notes properly
Which is why I'm so happy with show notes
Michael once in a while
I'm able to you know
I can certainly add a line
But when all those brackets and shit
I just have no patience to understand
Why can't it just be like HTML
Is what I'm thinking
But anyway
That's beside the point
Here's what I wanted to change
And I really did start to do this
And I started to write some stuff
Kevin Marx
I actually
And it's kind of weird
Because
I wanted to write the full story
I remember it
Kevin Marx
Well let me start with another piece that I took out
Which is infinitely incorrect
Trade secrets
Was not the first podcast
Okay
Dave and I did try
Trade secrets
Way after he was podcasting
After I was podcasting
After Doug K was podcasting
So and that's something that keeps showing up
Over and over again
And it's just it's not true
It was certainly
Defining moment for both of us
And maybe it was the first
Do-O podcast
When the word finally existed
But it's irrelevant
It was not the first podcast
You know what?
Maybe I should
Why don't I just
I'll tell you what
I'll recount the history
As I recall it
And then we'll get to the Kevin Marx piece
Which is very important
Because Kevin certainly does not get
The credit he is due
Because he was a complete inspiration to me
And that's what I wanted to
Defix actually
So
In 2000
It was
Yeah it was pre
It was either
It was pre-911
I met Dave Weiner in New York
And that by the way is for me
Where the entire
Concept of shipping large media files
Through RSS
Was conceived
Dave had already done all of his work on RSS
And this is pre RSS 2.0
We met in New York
And I was talking about
The concept of delayed
Basically time-shifting
Content downloads
In order to give the user a great experience
By dripping the content
Into their computer
And then only telling them that it was there
Once it was there
So you could have a 100-meg file
Downloading to your hard drive
And
And not even know about it
But then you'd get a message
Somehow that would say
Hey you've got mail
Or you've got
You've got content
And then you'd click on a file
Or however you open it up
And it would already be there
On your hard drive
So the experience would be fantastic
This was at a time when streaming
Everyone was doing streaming
And the quality was just not
Not really valuable
Or didn't deliver on the experience
Like put it that way
And I showed Dave some software
That I'd built in frontier at the time
I think was frontier
I don't know
Five, six
Maybe it was radio
That's possible
I don't remember
And from that meeting
Dave created the enclosure element
And then of course subsequently RSS 2.0
And for four years
We would be evangelizing this stuff
Attaching movie trailers
Big clips
Blogging about it
But I have to say
I was really thinking video at the time
And not thinking audio at all
So that was
So essentially podcasting exist
That ever since
Radio user land
I think was the first aggregator
That did downloads of enclosures
So it was already there
It's just we hadn't quite
Well the iPod wasn't there
That's what was missing
I think the real was there
But that connection really hadn't been made
Let me see
What is the other
And I'm just going to go through my contributions to podcast
This is so ridiculous
We're doing this
Okay, fast forward
To
Just before blogger the very first blogger
Con
And Dave was posting interviews
That Christopher Lydon was doing
On to an RSS feed
A separate RSS feed within closures
At the time I was doing
I was winding down a stint
As I was doing a morning radio show
In the Netherlands
And I was really enjoying
These interviews that Christopher Lydon was doing
They were just
It sounded crappy
It was fucked up
It was just it was not like regular radio
Yet the content was so compelling
Was different lengths
And I was totally blown away by it
And I wanted more
The needle was in
And I was just waiting for this stuff
To refresh
And so it would download to my hard drive
And I would then basically
Drag it over
Oh that's oh by then I had gotten an iPod
And I didn't
I was not that interested in music
But I was heavy into audio books
I did a lot of audio books stuff
On the daily source code in the very beginning
Because I really like audio books
And I was also dragging these
MP3 files into iTunes
So I could sync up with my iPod
And I think somewhere around
Into you number four or five
I thought to myself
My goodness
Wouldn't it be nice if it could go
On to my iPod automatically
And
Marcus Moller
Another person who is not mentioned in the
Wikipedia
Who was worked with me for
For years on schoolblocks.com
He actually created
I think it was a frontier script
I think it was an apple script
He created a little apple script
That would pull the directory
The download directory for radio
And if something new showed up
It would then pop it onto my iPod
So I actually Marcus
Deserves some major props there
Which he's never received
And certainly has an asked for
And he's not on the Wikipedia
So oh my god
What's wrong with the history here
Then we had blogger con
And a blogger con
I met
Oh no shit
Oh man there's so much more
Christ
I don't even remember the chronology now
After
Lidens interviews
I don't know if it was Doug Kay
That I started listening to
Based upon Dave's recommendation
But
At blogger con
I met Kevin Marx
And Kevin Marx had created
An apple script
That would download in closures
Now I don't think
It transferred everything straight over to the iPod
But we certainly discussed it
And I remember asking him
You know I do
We've got to do something with this
This is cool
I'd love that script
I don't think
We had a couple follow on emails after that
But he really completely inspired me
To get into apple script
And I'm like wow
Maybe I can make this whole
Front to Back thing
Because although I like radio
User land
It used up so many resources
That if I wanted to have the whole
Experience of stuff being sucked in
Automatically
If I wanted to have that
Running continuously
It really couldn't be radio
User land
Because it really
Used up way too many resources
On the computer
So I wanted a simpler solution
Something would just go out
And check for the file once in a while
Now I think that's somewhere
Between there
I also experimented with
Some Python code
Either Python or Pearl code
Which I believe
I can't remember who did that original code
If I could have been slusher
Man I don't even remember
Maybe it was Ray or August
I potter X who had done that
I can't recall
But for all intents and purposes
I set out on my own
After BloggerCon
While Dave was doing the democratic
National Convention
And by the way
Those were in my mind
After Christopher Lyd
And definitely the first podcast that I listened to
And they were great
And we talk about it all the time
We talk about
About the microphone
About Mike technique
And Dave would do all kinds of wacky shit
Like leave it running in his bag
Without him knowing it
And he'd post all these files
And I even said to him
I said dude
If you were working on the radio
You'd be so fucking fired
Don't stop
This is amazing
This is great shit
So
Then I
I'm not sure
I guess I didn't get any connection
With Kevin Marx
Which is exactly what I wanted to say
Because if he had had
This script working
All the way through to the iPod
Which I don't recall it that way
In
At BloggerCon
Then I'm not sure
If he had demonstrated that
How come
You know I didn't use that
Because what I wound up doing
Is searching all over the web
For XML parsers
There really wasn't an RSS parser
Perse
For Apple script
I think there was some kind of OSX
AOSX thing that you had to include
Or whatever
Some
There was definitely some other code
Which was all credited and commented
In the original iPod or Apple script
And it's like I'm fucking month
Learn how to do this shit
And I created it
It worked
And then I put it out on iPod.org
And that's when
A whole bunch of developers jumped on board
This was extremely cool
Because I was able to participate
In a software development process
As a user
This is the whole
Users and developers
Partying together thing
Which probably lasted for another month
By itself
Which
And I was very happy
Dave purposely stayed out of that
Conversation
Even told me he did it purposely
Because he said there was something
Beautiful going on there
And it was because
The daily source code
For those of you who are wondering about the history
And the history behind the name of the daily source code
Was really only created
I knew that making an aggregator
That is downloading MP3 files
Is
A lot of thought goes into it
And if you don't have something
If you don't have a feed to test it against
Then it's a bummer
You have to keep creating feeds
Or deleting content and going through it again
And so my commitment to the process at the time
And this is the iPod or iPod or X guys
iPod or lemon
Nimmig
I'm going to forget all of these different names
I can't remember all of them
A lot of Dutch developers
Frankly
So I would do the show
Which I called the source code
Thinking source code would appeal to developers
And I did it
Actually it started off seven days a week
So we called the daily source code
And I'd talk about my experiences
Using their software
And that would be kind of the feedback loop
And it was fantastic
Because they would
They're aggregators
And their iPoders would get my show
They'd listen to it
They'd be feedback there
And it just kind of grew from there
Now early on we had this whole
Who invented podcasting thing
And by the way
Even the name is heavily disputed
The first I heard of it was when Dave Slusher
Saw this podcasting.net
Ork.com
Show up in his referral logs
And that had been registered by Danny Grigwar
And that's to me how the name podcasting was born
But then hammerously of the guardian always claims
That he invented the name
In fact he did publish the name
A year before
Danny Grigwar
But
You know it's like
Okay
So it doesn't really matter
So that's essentially the story of podcasting
As I recall it
And following upon
The conversation we had on the last daily source code
That's my reality
That's the way I remember it
I may be completely wrong
Based upon Kevin Marx's reality
Based upon Dave Wine's reality
You know
I don't know
But when I go into Wikipedia
To go change that stuff
You know
Then for someone to say
Which by the way
I didn't say Adam Curry did all this
Adam Curry this or that
I haven't added any entries about myself
Into Wikipedia.org
To say that I'm trying to grab more credit
Or change history
Isn't the Wikipedia all about changing history?
And quite honestly
This thing doesn't work
This Wikipedia shit is broken
I mean now
I'm even seeing people
Say oh yeah
He was the first domain name
Squatter with MTV dot com
Well you know
That's not the the history of it
You know the history of MTV dot com
Is that MTV allowed me to use it
You know I registered it before there was even a worldwide web
But you know so now that's how history
Will be written forever
I'm the Kate Winslet of the Wikipedia
And I am
The first domain name squatter
Well so be it
I can't help
What you think
Now I do think what we'll be fun to do
Since Wikipedia the whole idea of
Making something editable
And text it's just too easy
As you can tell
Here's the prime example
And now by the way
If you read the comments
Everybody hates me
I'm busted
I don't know what I'm busted for
For using the fucking Wikipedia
And trying to figure out a wiki
Well I was writing this as I said
I got fucking
Exasperated with the whole
Process of writing in a wiki
And the two pieces that I wanted to change
Did wind up getting edited out
But nothing was added in
And that's the piece that is unfortunate
So now you've heard what I wanted to put in
Now you've heard my
Perception of how podcasting started
And you know
Just like in the universe
Just like with let's take a car for example
You can't
What's more important?
The engine or the steering wheel
Now you may say steering wheel
You may say engine
But of course
Every single piece of the car is important
You can't drive without the steering wheel
You can't drive without the engine
You can't drive without
The tire valve
Being in place
You then you'd have
One flat tire
So all of these pieces in the universe
Had to come together
And I'm sure that these people
Who's names I don't even recognize
In wiki pedia
Entry for podcasting
I'm sure they were they contributed as well
At the end of the day
I personally
Really don't care
I mean I've been having too much fun
Working with
Hundreds
If not thousands of creative talented people
You know
Changing
Radio broadcasting
The music business
Yeah
And I can't do this by myself
Yeah, I'm not the one that's responsible
I'm not
I'm certainly not
Ever tried to take full credit
I've given
I've given plenty of credit
Where credit is due
So anyway
And nothing I say here will make any difference
But at least I wanted to have it on record
So the thing that I thought would be interesting
Is to create a podcast of the definitive history of
Wait a minute
The definitive history of podcasting
And I know who should do it by the way
And I think I know how we should do it
Doug Kay has to do this
Doug Kay is the perfect candidate
Everyone loves Doug
And Doug has a heart of gold
And as far as I know Doug he's extremely honest
And a damn good pilot
And what if he were to
Set up a project
And you know I'd gladly help
Or contribute to the funding of this
To the podcast academy
Or IT conversations
Or whatever is necessary
To get this going
We should have him
Interview
All the people who have been involved in podcasting
Now that's a lot of interviews by the way
It's just look at all the Wikipedia entries
Or maybe we go to Wikipedia and look at all the changes
And look up the IP addresses and see if we can trace everybody
Thanks easy net by the way
For putting on the fucking personal information
In my in the right database
That really helps my god
You know I've often the phone has been ringing at night here
It's fucked up
So then you could have all these different versions
All side by side
And I think you'll find that the chronology gets messed up
I know for sure that I have my chronology messed up
You probably have to pull up
It's a big project
But it would be very interesting
If we could create that as a historical document
So that we'd have it
And it would be non-changeable
Because that's the downside to the Wikipedia
And you know it's like
When you've been interviewed in a newspaper
Or for a magazine or for some website
It never comes back the way you told it
It never comes back the even the way
Usually not the way you intended it to be
It's whatever the reporter was thinking
Usually what they already had preconceived
You know and you can massage that kind of stuff
And you can you can work it
But you know so the same thing you know
Then you kind of will distrust anything that's written ever again
Because it's all written from someone else's reality
So that's my reality
I wasn't trying to do anything
I'm not saying I didn't try to edit
Then I saying I didn't want to edit
I'm saying that I did get exasperated
With the Wiki and stopped editing
So
Kate Winslett of the Wikipedia
Anyway, I'm really happy I have all your attention today
Because we have a fantastic project that I wanted to introduce to you
This is something that's been going on for a couple of weeks
We have the pod save for peace Christmas song
Which is now complete
And I have the honor of premiering that right here
On the daily source code
Quick history about this
Slow a member or contributor to the Ponte music network
Upload it a song called If Every Day We're Christmas
And on one of my usual morning scans a couple weeks ago
I heard the song I played it on the source code
And
Hold on a second
That's the phone
I'll talk to you later
Okay
Wow, it's almost like an old fashioned source code
Where was I?
Okay, so I played this
After the song played on the source code
Wow, man, that's almost kind of like a we are the world
Or bandaid
Do they know it's Christmas kind of kind of song?
I said wouldn't it be cool if we had a whole bunch of pod save music artists
All joined together
But not in a physical studio, physical location
But actually have them contribute tracks
To create a similar song
And then hopefully we could
Maybe get to race a money for it
We could sell it somehow
And we could race a money for a worthy cause
Well, this got picked up
Slaw immediately jumped on it
And CC Chapman of course did a humongous job in getting everybody
Or as many people as possible involved
So
Since we don't have a wonderful video
Which of course is something I didn't think about
As we should have had everyone sending a piece of video of them
Recording their tracks at their home studio
Because then we really would have had something cool
He's giving me the lineup
And I'll just go before I play the song
I'll go through everyone who's on it
In order of appearance
And then we'll play this wonderful piece of work
Of which all proceeds if any
We'll go to unicef
So the pod save for peace lineup
Here we go
It starts off with Slaw
Slaw actually put in the
Where these people are from
First one, Slaw New York
Matthew Ebel after that from Nashville
Then verse two, Holler from Miami
May of Oboil from Glasgow
Chance from Los Angeles
Then we get the first chorus
Which is a chance and Slaw will start that off
Then you have the whole chorus joining in
I think this is like 96 tracks of chorus
Verse three, brother love from New York
Josh Cruz of cruise box
He's from Oklahoma City, Kevin Reeves from Nashville
Then the chorus again
Civilist Bitties do the bridge
Then we go into chorus three
Chance, Holler
Oh, I actually has a chance as woo
Holler does every day every day
Brother love, we would never feel blue
All these little improvisation things
Then Josh Cruz comes back and then Carmen Tyler from Texas
Brother love and Josh Cruz again
Do some improvs
Then chorus four Jim Fiddler from Newfoundland
Brother love
Lorina Mirei from Miami
My god, there's so many people on this
Let me see if I've got all the names
Okay, so then we have the break down
God, we're going to put all this in the show notes by the way
I'll try my wiki skills at it
Josh Cruz, Carmen Tyler Kevin Reeves
Jim Fiddler, Carmen Tyler Patricia
She's a lovely Patricia singing on the track
Madsumo from Boston
Donna Machiocia of Amplifico from the UK
Tara Tons Thompson of
Toronto
Henta Ellis from the UK George Rob from Pennsylvania
Brian Page
Cheryl B. Engelhart, Pippa Rogers, Albert Lee Fizz
from Rotterdam, he's from Skycar
Jeremy Gale of just Jacob from Australia
Carl Cabbage, Sonowari from Rich Palmer
Derek Miller from Vancouver
Franco Franco of a potteness
from Italy, Franco from Italy
Sasha Ludwig from Germany
Oh my god, this just doesn't stop
Additional backing vocals
Orlando Pagan and Kathy Rose
Drums, George Rob, Victor Kajiao
Typical user podcast
Or Sympatico on the podcast
Music Network did sex
And slotted piano keyboard
Bass guitar drum loops
And slotted piano keyboard bass guitar drum loops
And percussion
Oh my goodness
Are you guys ready for it?
Okay, you want to crank this up as loud as you can
If every day we're Christmas
This is pod safe
For peace
Like at that time again
To me
From this old town
A Christmas show
And the lighting of that famous Christmas tree
People are shopping for them loved ones
And making plans for a Christmas tree
Christmas trees
Running all goes by
And then we have to wait
Another
What if everything
Christmas
What a wonderful
This would be
You never feel blue
We make all our dreams come true
And Christmas
We're every day
It was time to bring out the good people
I just look around now and you will see
Yeah
Everybody's nice
And full of light
And they give to those
What if everything
Christmas
What a wonderful world
This would be
You never feel blue
We make all our dreams come true
And Christmas
We're every day
So I'm going
For the summer to the spring
I'll take you
We'll touch you
Until then
It's Christmas again
What if everything
Christmas
What a wonderful world
This would be
You never feel blue
We make all our dreams come true
And Christmas
Christmas again
What if everything
Christmas
What a wonderful world
This would be
You never feel blue
We make all our dreams come true
And Christmas
We're every day
It's Christmas
What a wonderful world
This would be
You never feel blue
We make all our dreams come true
And Christmas
What a wonderful world
This would be
You never feel blue
We make all our dreams come true
And Christmas
Christmas
What a wonderful world
This would be
You never feel blue
We make all our dreams come true
And Christmas
What a wonderful world
This would be
You never feel blue
We make all our dreams come true
What a wonderful world
Christmas
What a fantastic song
Oh man
That is just it's lovely
That's really really cool
And I personally want to thank everybody
Who contributed
To that
And so the work is only begun now
Now it's the podcast
First of all
If you work at a radio station
And somehow
Almost
Unthinkable realm of possibility
You have the opportunity to play this song
Please do
Because all Ask Cat BMI
And it will be
If it's not already registered with Ask Cat BMI
It will be
All of those royalties
That come in from playing on the radio
We'll go to Unicef
We're going to try and get this on iTunes
So you can buy it there
I had a thought of
Also seeing maybe we created CD
And put it up at CD Baby
So you can actually
Order a physical copy
And then the proceeds from that
Of course we'll also go to Unicef
Slower's handling all this by the way
And I have every
Every confidence that he's exactly how to
How to put all this stuff together
In fact here's something interesting
He called over to the folks at Unicef
And said, Hey, you know, we want to make sure
This money comes to you and
Here's what we're doing
And their response was
And I was afraid this was going to happen
The response was quite typical
Well, yeah, you know, but how much
How much are you going to donate?
We need to know the number up front
8 million, 10 million
Slower's like
I don't know, you know, maybe a couple hundred
If we're lucky a couple thousand
So
Unicef
With any big nonprofit organization
I think that their name is probably
You so often in vain
That they're very, very wary of who they
Want to team up with. So I don't think we're going to
Any direct help from them
I
Truly styler
Does a lot for Unicef
And I've met her once at a benefit
Interestingly enough, I want to see if
I can get through to her
The old back channels are a bit rusty
I'll see if I can get through to her
And see if we can work something out
With Unicef and otherwise, you know, there's no problem
And donating the money to Unicef
You could even do that right now
You don't even have to do buy anything
Just go ahead and send them some money
It's all done for love and for good cause
And I think it's fantastic
So podcasters, my call to you
Is to play the shit out of this song
Let's see if we can break it through
To to mainstream radio
Wouldn't that be interesting
Instead of them getting
Getting play on podcasters
It's the other way around
And if not, it doesn't matter
We are all entertaining ourselves
Daily source code, it is the Friday edition
Holy shit
Been at this for already 40 minutes
Michael Butler sent me an email
Yesterday that there's a
Brand new record company that is adding tracks
The podsaid music network
Silk city records, welcome guys
Appreciate it about to eight tracks up on line now
It's one of the really liked a lot
Robin Banks, someone to talk to
When it's cold at night
And you're all alone
And you're warm up
Where you know, where I'll be
Sometime baby, they have nothing but need
I still wanna talk to you
You come to my back door
Don't rain the bells
Just walk right on him
Ain't nobody gonna tell me
I'm gonna pick you up
Yeah, I'm gonna rub you down
I'll be your fix at my mark
On the edge of town
There you know, you can count me
Yeah, just call me when you need
It's someone to talk to
It's someone to talk to baby
Yeah, just call me when you need
I'll be your fix at my mark
On the edge of town
When it's cold at night
Oh, in your bed
And a million worries
Running through your head
Where you got my number
And you know your way
And you got no reason
To deny babies
Where you know
Where I'll be
Sometime baby, they have nothing but need
I still wanna talk to you
Oh, still wanna talk to baby
I'll be your fix at my mark
On the edge of town
Yeah, just call me when you need
I'll be your fix at my mark
On the edge of town
Robin Banks, someone to talk to
Soak city records
Welcome to the pod safe music network
And that's about
Excuse me about it for today's daily source code
Those of you listening to serious stars
You're probably saying what the hell is this show been about?
Well, welcome to the world of pod casting
We're a routy bunch
That's for sure
And remember, if you're looking for the Kate Winsle of the Wikipedia
You come to the right place
Alright, so
I guess I don't know
Now my whole day is reconfigured
Since I was planning on flying
I'm gonna see if I can figure something else out to do
I think I probably have to go
Do some more keyword searches on technology
See what everyone's saying about me
I will say
In closing
About all that
This is exactly
Like the mainstream media world
And quote celebrities
What's happening
It's amazing
It's amazing the attacks that I'm seeing
And by the way, people who hate me for my hair
Don't hate me for my hair
You know, I've noticed that most people who make jokes about my hair
Don't have any hair
Oh, what was me?
What was me?
I wanted to play one more song
But I'm gonna cut it short for now
I wanted to play Betty by the list of these bitties
Because they are without a doubt
I think they have a break out to smash with this thing
Everyone seems to be playing it
And reporting back to the pod safe music network
So I'll make sure
Maybe I'll do a show over the weekend depending on what's happening
If not Monday, I'll be sure to play Betty for you
If I haven't heard it, you can find it at
Bittiesforever.com
Or, of course, at the pod safe music network
All right, everybody
I'm out of here
DailySourceCode.com
As we can always find the latest show
Or curry.com
And Adam at curry.com
Free feedback
And once again, please remember
Don't hate me for my hair
Because I'm evil
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear