Delta share a Charlie 216.
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear since
radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
The date is July 28, 2005.
This is your daily source code.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It is human.
That's what you know, I always like to give you the weather report the beginning of the show.
It's nice and humid today.
Got the Converre Rollin here throwing more humidity into the air, but at least it's cool air, right?
As opposed to a dry heat.
Hey, let's do a source code.
I'm ready.
Actually, I'm far from ready.
I just kind of threw some stuff together and said, you know, fuck it.
Hit record.
Let's go.
Which is always my favorite kind of show.
Kind of gives that feel like I used to have on the radio where you got to start, right?
You, you can't do any more preparation.
You've got to start when the time rolls around, so I kind of have to self impose starting time.
I've got to play some pod safe music for you.
I've got some cool audio feedback that I wanted to share.
And I finally did it.
I hit 100% on Gmail.
I guess I have to stop soliciting audio feedback as attachments.
That's just not working for me.
So, so much for my theory that Gmail is actually looking at my account to see if it's time to add some into the infinity plus one pod.
Well, it's actually funny because you can go over your 100% allotment on incoming.
It'll actually go to 101 or 102%.
But then if you reply, it won't let you reply.
I'll tell you that you've gone over your code.
So, I did something I really hate to do, but I went in and I trashed a couple of attachments.
I trashed the backtracks podcast and a couple of hit tests.
I hate that.
But okay.
Hey, ain't that big of a deal.
I'm still loving Gmail.
It's still the way for me to manage my information as best as possible.
Current count, 7,234 unread messages and not quite too pro.
Alrighty, got a mashup that I pulled off of mashuptown.com.
Just to get into the vibe, I really love this.
It's notorious trick on the source code.
I've paid my dues for all that I've done.
And I showed you that I loved you more than once.
They have nothing left that to decide.
So do you eat my trick, me once.
I won't let you trick me twice.
We don't know what they're always doing.
They don't feel like always doing.
We're having an unhappy day.
They didn't even want to wait the time.
They didn't even want to be worse.
They don't let you trick me twice.
They won't let you trick me twice.
They didn't even want to be worse.
And released or anything like that, which is such a shame.
That just proves why the pod save music network is becoming such a huge success.
By the way, do you hear about this about the Sony $10 million fine they had to pay for the pay for play?
This is Eliot Spitzer in New York, the General Attorney General I should say.
I guess he sued them or took them into court or whatever.
Lots of people are asking me, you know, well, we used to call this payola, right?
And it was supposed to be over.
And let me tell you, this is, it never went away.
This has been going on for years.
But it's not like this jockies are being paid everything or anything at all because
This jockies don't even choose the music that's played.
This is done between program directors, music directors, and it's done by something
called independent promoters primarily.
I don't want to, you know, pay anyone black here, but, you know, that's actually a Dutch expression
that may have come out wrong.
But it happens with all kinds of things.
You know, it's, I don't think there's actually a bribe involved or, you know, everyone has a deal with
They say, okay, I'll play this song or I'll put it into rotation if you pay me X.
But it happens with, you know, okay, concert tickets, fun rides, you know, a trip, stuff like that.
And it's been going on forever.
And that's exactly how the music industry has worked.
This is exactly how it's worked.
It's no surprise whatsoever.
And they consume every single radio station that plays music in the United States.
New music that is, because I don't think it really, I don't think you can attribute
that to stations that play oldies.
But, you know, really, it's a part of the new music marketing machine.
And it's just the way it works.
And it varies from very simply innocent stuff like, hey, you know, we promised that, you know,
X will come to visit your station and come on the morning show if you add the record.
MTV has been doing this for years.
You know, it's like, yeah, Michael Jackson.
I've been a part of these deals where he'll perform on the video, musical,
he'll perform on the video, musical awards.
If you do a Michael Jackson weekend, you know, when he coincidentally has a new record out.
I mean, this, this stuff has always been there.
It's the way it works.
Which is why I like the podcast music network because there is no pay for play involved in here.
I mean, I guess technically you could happen.
But first of all, people could be up front about it.
You know, and there's no laws against it.
But it's not that exciting because what we're doing was we're playing stuff.
We'd like and we're playing stuff that other people are playing the game's traction.
So it's much more fair.
And if you check out the podcast, music network, I can't promote this enough,
because it really is working and it's fantastic.
You know, we have now the promotion for songs.
We have a place that we can send listeners of podcasts back to to learn more about the band.
And you can pretty soon we're going to open up the store.
So you can buy it directly online when you get to the podcast music network.
That's music dot pod show dot com.
Oh, if you want to remember that way, or pod safe music network dot com,
which is a little bit more typing, but it's, it can also remember it.
And I want to go through some of the Gmail here that I've been receiving.
Thomas Jeffrey sent me an email. He said he called his brother who works for TSA.
And the only lock that he knows of that they have the master key for is the travel century line of locks.
And this is interesting.
He said, if your lock isn't one of these, then you might have gotten ripped off by a company selling you something
under the guys of being TSA accessible.
Well, let me tell you, the airport is full of locks that are TSA accessible.
This was sold to me as a part of a to me, which is a very expensive suitcase.
They have like 800 bucks for this suitcase, which is supposed to be indestructible by the way.
And so far so good.
And it had big white TSA letters on it.
TSA key number 002.
You know, it can't be more clear than that.
I've traveled with it several times without an issue.
But I think that, you know, some guys are just like snip happy, you know.
Let me snip something.
So of course I don't know if there's any other branding on the lock because it's been cut off
and it's gone.
But I do know that, you know, they're expensive.
And I know that the price of this bag was expensive and that the lock was definitely a part of the price.
So Tom, I'm not sure what it was, but if it says TSA 002, that would pretty much mean it's a TSA lock.
Has a special, it's a combination lock, but it's a special place.
We can insert the TSA key.
And, you know, somewhere there's something being scammed.
So I'd love to know more about that.
If anyone can point to an online resource, a travel centri apparently and that's a travel
centri.org has the only real official locks according to Tom and his brother.
So be on the lookout for scams in that regard.
It doesn't really, it does bother me.
I don't mind people going through my shit.
You know, I understand that and it's all from my protections well.
So that makes sense.
But I want it to be locked up, you know.
So I'm playing the game fairly because how many times have been ripped off because airport employees
have been able to get into my bag?
You know, that's a problem.
So that said, I'm sure I'll get lots of email about that.
And who knows, they will come up with some real information, something we can
can use because I'm sure a lot of people are going through these issues.
Daily source code, audio, feedback.
Hi Adam.
I don't know what the British told you.
I didn't catch that podcast, but there are a few little details about the highway
numbering system that we need to get straight out.
One is that, yes, it was a plan conceived and started by President Eisenhower,
but interesting to note that the main purpose of it was
stated to be for expedient movement of military vehicles and troops and for evacuation of the citizens.
Remember that this whole idea was brought together during those fun fill days of the Cold War,
and we all had global thermonuclear war a little bit more to the forefront of our minds.
Anyway, don't confuse US highway numbers with interstate highway numbers.
US one, in fact, is on the east coast.
But the other things that you point out are pretty much true that the odd number
of interstates run north and south, and they start the numbering from the west coast to the east coast.
So I find runs up and down the west coast and I 95 runs up and down the east coast,
and that the even numbered ones are run east to west.
I tend to be in a long the bottom and I 94 go across the top.
But it's useful to think of them more in terms of running south to north and west to east,
because that's the way the mile marker numbers run.
As soon as you cross over a state border going from the south to the north,
the numbering starts again at one, and similarly going from west to east,
when you cross over a state border and the mile marker numbers restart at every state line,
you'll start at mile marker one.
So if you were to drive there from California over to Las Vegas,
as soon as you would cross over the state line in Nevada,
you'd see mile marker number one.
And while I have you, I want to wish you the half of the rest of the 100 million gathering
marchers and a really, really big thank you for all the hard work you're doing.
This podcasting stuff is really great, and all this techno stuff is just cool.
So there, I'm stronger Jim and the big blue 18 wheeler and that's the view for my left seat.
Thanks a lot at him, bye-bye.
Hi Joe, content that will make you walk the job and kiss your mother.
So what I wanted there really was another fun field history fact about the USA young
the daily source code.
Cool man, from the 18 wheeler, rockin' really appreciated.
That's very, very cool.
I'm warning some geek stuff coming up,
I want to talk about bandwidth again.
So do you hear that, by the way, this crackling?
I think I've overused my mixer hole on.
It was crack, there it is.
I guess the microphone fader is, there it goes, shit.
I got to get some of that spray stuff and that basically means the end of the mixer.
But they're so cheap these days.
What I pay for this mixer, like 150 bucks or something like that.
And I have to get another set up for the condo, the Corri condo and San Francisco.
Yeah, it's going to be basically one big recording studio.
Patricia said something funny today.
She said, you know, for the fridge used to have some bottled water always there and some bottles of champagne.
It's like bottles of champagne.
She said, well, yeah, you know, that's what, that's what every condo should have.
I was like, well, for who?
Or it's just for me when I'm sitting there, I'm inviting all kinds of people to come on over and hang out.
I played this yesterday.
I think I got to play it a couple more times.
I just can't get it out of my head, man.
I am digging this song so much.
It's pod save music.
You can find it on the pod save music network.
It is our anthem.
And mine at least.
Cruise box.
I heard it on the podcast.
Rock and fucking radio.
You want it.
Got it.
Just download it.
I heard it on the podcast.
No one's going to stop you telling MCC to stick it.
Pick it.
The revolution is on.
Do you remember?
You're the first computer.
That piece of shit was like a freaking rotor.
Now we've got Wi-Fi.
Downloading files fast.
This meant to everyone who's ever done on my cast.
It's just me.
Now you're seeing each and every nation.
The radio is got to go.
It's our imagination.
Me that song.
Sing alone.
My sheet of comics.
It's a real fucking rotor.
Now I'm going to fix it.
You're somebody here to call.
Now you can have it all.
I heard it on the podcast.
Rock and fucking radio.
You want it.
Got it.
Just download it.
I heard it on the podcast.
No one's going to stop you telling MCC to stick it.
Pick it.
The revolution is on the podcast.
Rock and fucking radio.
You want it.
Got it.
Just download it.
I heard it on the podcast.
No one's going to stop you telling MCC to stick it.
Pick it.
The revolution is on the podcast.
The revolution is on until the FCC to stick it.
Kick it.
Hurt it on the podcast.
That is cruise box.
You can find them in music.
The podcast.
Music.
And you know it's so cool about what we're doing here.
Radio in New York actually coast to coast with my syndicated show
Once in a while you'd receive you know a platinum record or a gold record on behalf of the you know the band
Thanking you for your contribution. I have a lot of them hanging up in my office because you know, it looks cool, right?
There's no doubt about it, but it's not really from the artist themselves
It's from the record company and
That's a part of that, you know that whole thing I was talking about concert tickets and everything is like, you know
Oops, oh my Mike Stan just sorry about that my Mike Stan just collapsed
You know, it's kind of like hey, you know, thanks for helping out and which of course means next time around Lee help us out as well
You know, I shall take a picture of one of them. You know, I got my my MDA here. I'll take a picture of
The one I got from arrows Smith hold on
All right, so I took a picture I'll post that up there
Great, you see my reflection there, but even though I know that it's well meant and and actually when Cristina was born
All of Aros Smith sent a nice little no-dover and congratulated depotrition eye, but
I got emails from the guys from cruise box, you know, and that was really nice. They didn't have to do that
And you know, they're just as jazz as I am. Oops. What's this?
Hold on
Okay, so I got that that's the me. That's my 15 minute warning. Hey, this MDA is really greatest controlling my life
I'm totally digging it
Let me see, so I do the geeky thing now now I do one more audio feedback and then I'll talk some geek stuff about
Bandwidth. Hey Adam Mark Prince here from the coffee geek podcast and I'm sitting here in b
All Vancouver British Columbia listening to the daily source code as I do every day. Now here in Vancouver
We're known for the
Stuff but personally I don't partake however I am sitting here right now drinking a vodka martini made with Sirrock
vodka and that's kind of my fix. I hope you understand hope you don't mind
What the hell am I talking about? I run the coffee podcast wait Adam my fix my daily fix is actually a nice shot of a espresso made with Yemen mocha
How about some Ethiopian horror how about some Sadamo and we'll finish it off
Let's go to additional we'll finish it off a little Java all blended together making an awesome shot of espresso
And I just wanted to send a shout out say I really appreciate your podcast
I really appreciate everything you do for the community. There's a lot of lot of player haters out there
But I certainly am not one of them you are the pod father and I bow I'm bowing to Adam Curry
I know this is radio and we can't see it right now, but that's what I'm doing and I'm keep up the great work
Keep going with the daily source code keep doing what you do man
You got true believers out there and I really appreciate everything you do for the podcast community
No, that's so nice. Thank you very much. You can tell that I yeah
I found out by the way what all that cutting out is on it's not really mega-seg that is the issue
it's whenever I have a
Network share on my desktop that's when
What happens is I think the Mac is trying to recent can make sure everything's still connected and if it's a network server somewhere
Then it takes a couple seconds to actually find it depending on the the connectivity and the bandwidth and all that stuff
So speaking of that here we go
Now whenever I talk about this issue, I get all kinds of you know a bit torrent like solutions, et cetera
But I you know for the people who understand bandwidth
For those of you that don't I I just want to talk about
The two there are two types of bandwidth that we need for pod casting and this has really been the epiphany that I've come up with
That's saved by the bell or ruined by the bell hold on
Oh, I know this is home
Hey, Chris
Hey, I'm in the middle of the source code. Can I call you right back?
Okay, I'll call you back in in like 20 minutes
Okay, I'll call you later
Bye
Had the phone's gonna ring again. I'm sure for my father clock anyway
Two types of bandwidth
The the bandwidth on which pod casting was originally conceived really dealt more from the consumer side
And the concept was you're streaming sucks and why does streaming suck because
There's really not enough bandwidth primarily on the receiving end although it's gotten much better to have a full blown at the time
We're thinking of full screen experience
Although these days it's you know just getting an audio file you can you can pretty much get that in real time
So when you click on the link and you're kind of downloading it your player will automatically start playing it once it has an update
It to do that and it kind of figures out what's the rate of download? Yeah, I can start playing now it buffers a little bit
But that's almost instantaneous the idea was that even if you had a shitty connection
Now, of course, it's reverse because there's so many pod people who want to listen to podcasts that the the sending ban with becomes the problem
It's not a problem if
If you're subscribed to a podcast because even if it's coming in at two kilobits per second, which is definitely not enough to just to play it in real time
It'll get there and it may take 10 minutes or it may take 15 minutes, but it'll get there. It'll get to your computer
And you don't know that you're waiting for it and it doesn't hurt you because it's happening in the background
You know your iTunes is doing it your iPod or is doing it whatever and as long as these
Pod captures are smart enough that you know if the connection stops for a second to wait or if it breaks
It goes back and tries it again
It'll eventually get there that is the whole concept of originally again
It was from the consumer side, but now we have enough ban with we've run into another problem
Whereas there's so many people hitting this stuff in real time that you need you know like real time
quality bandwidth so
What you what you almost need to have is
a link for
For someone who wants to odd you know just browse a show and listen and say is this something that I want to listen to
And a separate link for someone who subscribes and it downloads slowly in the background
So really I'm now looking at almost a non technological fix. I'm thinking more maybe we need to
Have a way or it's you know change our production processes or basically change whatever link you have on your home page
So that high quality ban with stuff that'll deliver in real time
Is coming from a different source and
Over time as more people learn about the subscription process
It's going to get much better. So there's going to be a shift now another thing we could do is we could
For the real-time ban with we could you know people just want to find out about a show
We could all make promos and post those now of course the the biggest issue that we have now is iTunes because
Although items let you subscribe and there is a caching
For good or for bad there's caching of your RSS feeds which isn't a huge server load
What a lot of people do is say hey. Oh, this is a great podcast. They find it somewhere double-click
It's coming straight from your server and they want and people have come to expect a real-time full-blown experience
Which is getting harder to deliver not necessary that the technology isn't there, but the cost is is very high
So you know right now you're looking at for daily source code and an average cost of 30 cents per person who listens to this in real time
Now you don't want to blow off your listeners by not providing a way for them to get it immediately
But there's all you know, there's a social change that we have to go through either that or maybe the direct links would be bit torn only
You know, so I'm working through all these issues. That's actually what my five o'clock phone call is about so
There's a lot of stuff to think about there
One thing I know for sure is that what we can't do we can't reverse engineered and say oh, you know
Put a helper app in or you know even bit torn has has drawbacks. It really does because
inherently and this has been explained to me by people much smarter and much more knowledgeable than I am certainly on this topic
It's not that hard to hijack bit torrents
You know at a bite or a frame level or whatever the heck it is
So you may be think you're downloading an MP3, but it could be a virus or some
Spyware or some other program which inevitably is going to happen because that's just a nature of people
So I'm thinking about kind of that social change and how can we get more people? How can we incentivize people to subscribe and
Because basically you're hurting the you know the podcaster when
When you're trying to get this in real time and
This isn't an issue if you have 10 people maybe subscribe to your podcast, but the minute you
The minute you gain traction and more people start to listen you start to get penalized and that is bad
So we definitely want to change that behavior so getting more people subscribed
Making it easier for them to subscribe and creating an infrastructure of low quality bandwidth
I mean, I'm even now looking at releasing the source code at a different time of day just because ban with the night is is
While there's less being used therefore I could put that in a different infrastructure
So lots and lots of stuff to think about and I just wanted to mention that here briefly
So that smart people who listen to the show could think with me, maybe we'll come up with some cool solutions
Most of our high spots were coming to us now by TV serious central not this one serious 148 Adam Curry's
Odd show experience the unexpected tell the world
Tell us to everybody for whatever they are
serious central 148. I was just looking through
Let me see if there's anything else we want to talk about that came through on email
Now, I think we're just gonna leave it like that
Keep the feedback coming
If you could go a little light on the attachments for the next couple of days
As my trash starts to empty out on Gmail and hopefully the size of the inbox will start to increase a bit
You can always put and you know, just post a link that always is very helpful and
Much appreciated if you have a promo
I send it off to
Submit at podshow.com if you got a mashup send it to mashup at podshow.com
And if it's pod safe music submitted over at the pod safe music network or send it to podsafe at podshow.com
And that'll be it for today's source code
30 minutes on the nose
Perfect so now my call can come in I can call Chris back up load this sucker
And tomorrow we'll have another full blown daily source code will have some more promo's pod safe music
I think I'm gonna have to play clone box again though because man I'm really loving that song
So I can't stress enough, but I'd really like you to subscribe to this show
I know that you're impatient you sit there clicking on
Non-existent URLs trying to guess what the file name will be for today's shows
So you can get it as soon as it's released
But I really would like you to subscribe
You can go to dailysourcecode.com
That's where you'll find the subscription URL or head on over to iindepotter.org
I'm gonna put that new banner on pretty soon got a really nice banner
And of course there's podcastali.com where you can learn all about podcasting how to subscribe
What applications do you use and what great shows are out there?
www.curry.com is my website my weblog it's where you can leave comments
And it's also where I post other stuff once in a while just what's going on
I'll post this picture of the arrowsmith
What was that it's platinum I guess for 4 million copies sold that was a pump there you go
And of course my address is at um at curry.com
Hope the weather holds up where you are hope you're not in too much of a heatwave as you live in the states
Or if it's not too wet where you are in Europe
Talk to you tomorrow stay subscribed
Thanks everybody bye bye
You
Another pod show podcast stick it in your ear