Delta share Charlie, two-fiber-two!
Please save me from people who've been told what to like and then like it.
In my opinion, if you're over six years of age and you're still getting your music from the radio,
something is desperately wrong with you.
I can only hope that somehow MP3 players and file sharing will destroy FM radio
the way they're destroying record companies.
Then, even though the air will probably never be safe to breathe again,
maybe it will be safer to listen to it.
There are no secrets.
Only information you don't get out of!
Adam Curry!
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation, radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this church.
It is Monday, October 3rd in the near.
Screw that.
In the year of our Lord, 2005, I sort of wanted to say,
hey, everybody, how you doing?
Come to you from Curry Cottage in Gilford, United Kingdom.
That's right, back home with the girls.
This is your daily source code, kind of free wheeling it today,
but I'm stacked up on promos and pod save tunes.
We are guaranteed to have a full show today.
Actually, we had something interesting happened this morning.
I didn't hear about it until early we had a eclipse.
It was kind of weird, because it wasn't, of course, a full eclipse.
You have to be closer to the equator to really get that kind of stuff.
Definitely did go dark for about 10, 15 minutes.
As we were up bright and early, Christina has an audition this morning.
She had one at 8 o'clock, auditioning for a big school play,
which is based on the life of Lizzy Borden.
Oh, yeah, that's my daughter for you.
So it's really weird.
Most of the animals include the birds,
primarily we're really kind of freaking out about this weird,
like twilight that we had around 730 this morning.
And then at a quarter of eight it really started to set.
I think 815 was the darkest moment.
And then it just started to get light again.
And the birds kind of acted up again.
It was one of those freaky, cool nature things.
That, of course, I completely forgot to take pictures of.
And that's why you've got such a small handy camera, you know?
I'm such a dork.
Kicking it off with a mashup on today's source code.
This came from a DJ Quad.
Sorry, I came from Phil who's promoting DJ Quad.
The mashup guy from Cat and the Girl.
And he suggests a mash-off spin-off.
Let's see what their entry is.
When I want to see you,
something's high high.
I don't do very well.
When I feel the desire,
I won't do what I want to do.
God bless.
Oh, man.
That fusing sound feels like me.
My ears are cooked through my butt.
That's really rough.
The full story is that Phil Eugenio is sent to me for the sea.
He said that jam to this broth.
Let's have a mashup contest.
DJ Quad of Keith and the Gorillir vs Art that guy tries to mash up.
He's okay, but lowerly flan of Keith and the Gorillir can mash up.
Like none other.
Just listen.
of mashuptown.com, which is way different from him doing all the mashups that I play.
So I don't think that'll be any competition we want to enter into.
This was kind of cool though, but it seemed like I was missing at least a quarter of the mashup
that just wasn't a part of the file that was sent.
But I liked it.
I liked it definitely, very, very cool.
I'm liking the mashups.
So back now, back for a couple of days, of course I got inside of the morning, I'd slept
for like five hours on the plane, which was pretty good.
Seeing as it's only only a nine and a half hour flight, you know, with your, I was
fall asleep the minute the engines rev up though.
That's, you know, the minute you hit rotation from the runway, when the, when the nose wheel
lifts off, I'm asleep, I'm asleep for a half an hour an hour, you know, and then I'm
going to wake up and get into the vibe and what I watched the movie, the hell that
I watched.
I don't remember what it was, I can't remember what I watched.
But slept well, got in around, you know, the typical 1030, customs was pretty busy, even
for the fast track.
We've talked about that, right?
It's the pink little slip you get and then you can go through a special line, but even
the fast track was slow.
And back at the cottage round 12, it was great seeing the girls.
We had a great weekend, it was great catching up, we just talk and talk and talk and talk
and talk and talk and so much that on Sunday, Patricia, I did a special podcast going
through an hours worth of pod save music that I've played over the past couple of weeks
and basically getting her input on it, which was kind of interesting.
And I realized that you may be listening, you may be listening to that today instead of
this show, depending on what you, what kind of time you had on your Sunday, to listen
to an hour of our, our futsing around, but it was fun.
I love doing shows with Patricia and to maybe I can get on more often, but it did get
a whole, whole thought process rolling in my head about pod safe music and production,
and not talking about audio quality, but, you know, as Patricia would call it, another
set of ears, you know, just someone listening to stuff, which, of course, is a value
ad that record companies and ANR people give to their artists, which, you know, we don't
really have, well, I guess we have a super benefit as it pertains to pod safe music because
you have a whole audience that will work with you on Chris, like software.
There's no, I don't see any difference between creating a software program, you know,
why shouldn't you have a beta of the song?
I think you can definitely have it.
Here's the beta.
We used to call that a demo, but there was really nothing between demo and release candidate.
It was always that's it, you know, you go from, from the O.1 version straight to the
1.0 version.
Maybe we should consider more, had this more of it be more of an iterative process.
I don't even know what that means, but it sounds pretty expensive.
I don't know what that means, but it sounds pretty expensive.
Anyway, just a thought.
And we'll get to that little bit later on.
I have some ideas for the pod safe music networks and stuff that I want to throw out there
and see what comes back.
As I said, plenty of promo is lined up.
I got it a question the other day, someone said, you know, you asked for promo is what?
It is a promo.
I said, well, you should listen to the source code because I play a lot of them.
And promo is basically small little audio vignettes or the column of commercial.
There you go.
It's an advertisement for your show.
It's a way to hook people into, to getting them to listen to and hopefully subscribe
to your show, to your podcast.
And there's many ways to do it.
One way is to play snippets and say, you know, here's the stuff you're missing if
you don't listen to our show immediately and the other one is to really show what kind
of personality you are or maybe have multiple people.
There's a whole bunch of ways to do it.
Ways like, well, you could always use this tactic.
This is John Long.
I am wanting to know whether you understand Hawkins.
As Lucy binangilana, I see Taiwan and Langheil, a healthy alcoholic want to see Lu,
Pyunnamil, J-o, Hong Kong.
I don't understand Hawkins.
For a time, I want to know how much Arthur is most in Australia but I don't know
what the look up Mc Doom is looking for.
She said Mouse, a colored Runner, dio, a可以, a mencioner, a person.
That's her standard, a right approach.
The best way to understand Hawkins is to build a journey.
Lure Theory and Autism Analysis.
Take off your helmets.
Just do it.
And it's too smooth to see.
Reddit and so on.
You have your PE and ANG, H-O-K-K-I-E-N.com, okay, bye, everyone.
So there was just a message out there to all the Huck-In people who understand Huck-In.
I'm studying a new podcast.
I'm studying a new podcast called PenangHuck-In.com, PE-N-A-N-G, H-O-K-K-I-E-N.com.
It's all about Huck-In podcast.
Gender Parts
Bump bridge down there.
There isn't a sûre.
It thrown in the backstage and the acting boss is behind.
H-O-K-I-N-F-H-O.
Content that will make you squeeze the dog and burp your mother.
So, what have you missed in the past month by not listening to the financial aid podcast?
We've talked about, and given you the secrets too, finding over $25 million in scholarships,
you could have gone to college for free.
Financial aid podcast listeners raised over $10,000 in hurricane assistance funds, and you
could have been a part of that.
We had ourselves a jobcast from the opposite end of the spectrum covering four jobs seeking
strategies, six resume tips, and four insider secrets to landing the jobs you want in
as little as two weeks.
You missed eight power tips for increasing your gas mileage to save money commuting.
You didn't get a copy of our scholarship search secrets ebook, distributed only in our RSS
speed.
You missed an opportunity to get a free car from Motorola.
You didn't learn how to reduce the taxes you pay every year with education tax credits.
And you missed the debut of 90 different pod safe songs from artists across the spectrum,
from God Rock to folk via the pod safe music network.
So subscribe now to the financial aid podcast at www.financialaidpodcast.com.
Because otherwise, who knows what you'll miss in October if you don't.
This week on the squad cast, we take on the snooze chewing tobacco challenge.
By the way, didn't you describe what this looks like to the folks at home and we'll take a
serious drag of coffee grind?
It does look like a little tiny.
It's like a bag of coffee.
You can do one or two things now to it.
You can do it.
You know what?
You know what I'm going to do?
What?
I'm going to beg you both.
Unless you both want to die in the next four minutes.
Shut the fuck up.
I've locked mine into the front of my jaw.
You know, it just sound like like a tard.
You sound like you've had a stroke.
They're currently at the number nine show.
Are we after tonight's episode?
We are short to never see the top 10 again.
No, you will.
You just will as the Anthony and Larry Shaw.
Mine is us.
We're going to be late us.
Nancy and Barbara passed out.
I mean Nancy and Barbara.
Brian wants to know which one he is.
Squad cast, squad cast.
Gmail.com.
Squad cast, squad cast, dot com.
Who?
Okay.
Some fine examples of promos there.
That's really here.
Well, I read mainly.
And also here, you know, podcasters about the daily source code and one of the common
complaints is, you know, who the hell cares about Adam Curry's life?
Well, of course, that's not the point.
The point is this is the show where if you're new to pod casting and you want to
find out about some interesting shows, you might want to listen to.
Here's the place to pick them up through listening to promos.
And of course, going to the show notes and you know, finding out where to
where to find these shows.
And the other part is, you know, trying to develop pod casting.
We are not done.
I was talking to Andrew Grummit this morning.
He was on his way out to San Francisco.
He's going to come by the pod show offices.
It's going to be there for a week or so.
And we're going to work on ways that we can work together.
And it's just so much more to do as it when it comes to pod casting.
So, and primarily from the, of course, from the pod cast or side.
The work that we've been doing with Mike on cast blaster is.
I think an example of that, how much and you can pretty much see what we're going with with
cast blaster.
It's going to be a fully integrated solution.
Obviously, you won't have to worry about creating RSS feeds and show blogs and up
FTP and uploading and doing ID3 tags.
All of that will just be built into one simple process.
You know, step one step two and there is no step three.
But on the listener side, we're far from done.
You know, and there's a reason why if you look at, if you look at the television networks this past week in the
States, although I don't have a television, I pretty much know it's always the same anyway.
So, they roll out their new lineup and there's, there's a lot of promo going on there, boy.
I tell you, the cool thing about pod casting is you only have to promo once.
Once you get the person to subscribe to your show, you're pretty much,
sure that you've got them, you know, that's your audience.
And then, if they don't like it, then they'll unsubscribe.
Which, by the way, is one thing that we could really do.
Wouldn't that be cool if you knew if someone unsubscribe?
Yeah, I'd love to know that.
I'd love to be able to say, hey, I saw you unsubscribe.
Is there a reason why?
Is there anything I can do to make it better to bring you back?
And, of course, on mainstream media, traditional broadcast radio and television,
there is no subscription.
Well, there is, of course, with Tivo.
That's, I guess that's true.
But there is, you know, they continuously have to promo to keep your attention.
And there's a reason why stuff comes back at the same time every week, you know, that's, so they can,
so you can be trained.
But now we just train our devices much, much easier, unlike it.
A couple of emails about bio diesel.
Just going through the Gmail here.
Hold on a second.
Let me turn the laptop a bit.
Let's see, this is from Danny Boyle.
Did you know that oil from hemp seeds is one of the highest part in the pun.
BTUs per unit of all the bio fuels and it grows like a weed.
Says Danny Boyle.
Well, of course.
That would make, of course it does.
In fact, I once did a documentary in Jamaica about Bob Marley and met up with,
oh man, he was one of his best friends.
And I've totally forgetting his name.
He runs the the museum at Marley's house in Kingston.
And he said, you know, this, the Oli herb.
It burns hotter than coal.
And I've never forgotten that.
Another thing about, I have to read you this article about bio fuel.
Hold on.
I just got to click on this link.
A couple of people sent me this one.
See, who sent this?
This is from Gary Hall.
Yeah.
And Gary sent me this link about French President Jacques Girac.
I'll just read this to you.
He's joined the country.
France is push to boost bio fuel use.
Converting his own luxury Citroen C6 saloon, which is a huge, huge car.
And many of his official scars to run on cleaner burning bio diesel.
Fuel pumps at his Aleyzay Palace in Central Paris have been modified to provide the alternative fuel.
The President's car runs with bio diesel made from rapeseed.
As do half the Aleyzay cars, a spokeswoman said on Friday.
France, Europe's biggest agricultural producer, has announced plans to become Europe's leading bio fuel maker by 2010.
When it wants, a green fuel is to fill 7% of total consumption.
France produces both bio diesel made from mostly rapeseed.
An ethanol derived from sugar beet or cereals.
And of course, Shirok is a former agricultural minister.
And so he's a big champion of the farmers' causes.
That's a story on the Yahoo, which I guess is what it's at AP.
It's an AP, a Reuters story.
That's pretty interesting, though.
And it isn't detrue.
I've gotten all the details now.
If you use vegetable oil as fuel for your vehicle in the United Kingdom,
you have to pay the tax man.
And there's actually a form that you fill out and send the check to.
TruckerLew from truckerLew.com.
Hey, truckerLew.
In the rain, this thing to your podcast here for about the last month or so.
And you've been talking a lot about bio diesel.
And I'm all 4 bio diesel.
I think bio diesel would definitely be the way to go.
And here in the United States, tractor trailers, or commercial motor vehicles,
are the number one consumer of diesel in here in the United States.
And anything to get the price to drop would be excellent.
I don't have to worry too much about the price of a diesel,
but I'm driving a company vehicle.
So I don't actually have to pay for the fuel out of my pocket,
but my company does.
So many money that they can save means more money in my pocket,
because I can give me raises at a later date.
And diesel is cheaper in the United States,
simply because car, you know,
automobiles use more gasoline here than they do diesel.
And I don't know if it's that way in the United Kingdom,
but I do have one question about bio diesel.
And this would affect the average homemaker or home producer of bio diesel.
I don't, you may have addressed this before, I don't know,
but any United States when you're operating a motor vehicle,
whether it's commercial or private motor vehicle on any public road,
the fuel that you use or the fuel that you purchase.
When you purchase the fuel, you're paying taxes,
as well as paying for the price of the actual fuel,
which can be anywhere from a 40 to 80 cents of tax per gallon.
When you're operating a motor vehicle and you're using fuel
that you have not purchased,
that means that you're not paying the taxes on it.
And if you're not paying the taxes on it,
you're operating the motor vehicle on the highway.
That opens up to the potential of a tax evasion.
And I'm not sure if you looked up the rules on that.
Yeah, that's the way that I understand it.
I could be entirely wrong.
I think it's exactly what's happening here in the UK,
where if you use a certain substance as fuel,
you have to pay tax over it.
I mean, that's something that is nothing to do with the scarcity of a natural resource.
That's just taxes, you can put taxes on anything.
There are taxes on cigarettes, taxes on booze,
so why not taxes on biofuels?
But that's a different gain.
That's something that you got to change at the voting booth.
I'm sorry about that.
Wow, really overmodulated.
Yeah, something at the voting booth that you got to get your guys in there who are going to represent what you think is fair.
I want to come to taxation.
And by the way, even though you're driving a company truck,
higher fuel prices are going to just put strain on the company.
If it doesn't affect your future compensation,
it could affect many jobs.
That's just the way it goes.
It really sucks.
So I'm way, I think it's a perfect way to go.
And then if the government puts taxes on biofuels,
well that's different, that's a different issue.
It's not that the natural resource has doubled in price
in a very short amount of time.
Well, not double, I guess.
Well, actually $60.
I've seen $30 barrel of oil in the last five years,
I think.
So yeah, it has pretty much doubled.
So yeah, if there's a tax on it,
you'll have to pay a tax for it.
But until there's a tax, you don't have to, I guess.
But I figured I just dropped this little voice message.
And see if you have anything to say about that.
And whether or not you've actually explored it.
So there's more things than just making it.
There's a lot of legal ramifications in there.
And by the way, it is the United States of America.
We take matters into our own hands, dammit.
If we want to crap in our tanks to make it go and avoid all those
prices, expensive fuels, we'll do it.
And then if we want need to talk tax, we will.
That need to be, that need to be explored.
So if you get a chance to explore this, taking, putting it up in your podcast
and let everybody know because I'm interested in it.
I do have a diesel vehicle at home.
And if I could figure out a way to cheaply produce my own,
my own biodiesel, I do that for the same way.
I have to be home to do it.
I'm driving a tractor trailer.
And I'm gone four weeks out of the month.
So I'm only home three days or so a month.
Damn.
You hear that?
I thought I had it bad with two weeks on two weeks off,
but home three days of the month, dude.
Whew, that's rough.
You must take a month off somewhere to be with your family, I hope.
That's the backbone, man.
Truckers backbone of America.
Backbone of any country, really, I guess.
That's a rough gig.
Anyway, I just figured I'd bring that to your attention
and see what your input was on that.
And you know, being in the trucking industry,
diesel production is very important to me.
You can check me out over at truckerlude.com.
And I do kind of like a stream of consciousness type podcast.
And so I'm always talking about the trucking industry over there.
So I guess as about all we got for now,
we'll talk to you later.
I'm going to post this up for a file,
and I'm going to email a link to you here.
So I hope you have fun and we'll talk to you later.
Appreciate it.
Truckerlude?
That's another great way to promote your show.
Feedback, that's something we're talking about here.
So everything continues.
I encourage anyone who has links to home-making,
biodiesel websites and kits and organizations.
To put them up in the show notes on the wiki show notes,
which actually a couple of people have come to me and said,
hey, my name's wiki.
So I guess I got to figure out something
for those folks to do.
Who knows?
It turns out it's a pretty common Hawaiian name.
So that was really smart of me, A.
Let me see.
I wanted to tell you a story about something that was relative to.
You know, let me see.
Why don't we take a break?
Why don't we do something?
Let's just break the rhythm here for a second
and get into some non-podsave music.
Hello.
You need to start.
There we go.
Backtracks podcast.
So you think you know your hits backwards and forwards?
No, I just...
Yeah, right.
You're listening to the Backtracks podcast exclusively
on the daily source code with Adam Curry.
Hey, Adam.
Hey, are you doing it?
You're doing pretty good.
We might have to make this a little bit more difficult for you.
Please.
Okay.
Challenge me.
Number one.
I know it already.
Oh, yeah.
Um, that is Robbie Neville with St. Levy.
St. Levy.
Number two.
Sounds like Thomas Goldby.
Let me come back to you.
Time's up.
Number three.
You can hear it.
Car Wash Rose Royce.
I know I got to do it.
Time's up.
Okay, here are the answers.
Number one.
Goldby.
Uh-huh.
Say Love E.
And here's number two.
Oh, okay.
You're coming, saw.
Number three.
Are you ready?
Uh-huh.
Oh, uh-huh.
So how did you do, Adam?
You're out of three.
Not bad.
Thanks for joining us on this week's Backtrack Spotcast quiz.
You can visit Backtrack Spotcast on the web at BacktrackSponcast.com.
Catch you next time.
Backtrack Spotcast.
Spin it back.
I love the production of that.
Uh-huh.
I'm telling you, I'm pretty good at that.
Let's see a couple of emails about my Blackberry.
How's it doing?
Did it work?
Uh, yes it did.
Very, very pleased with the performance of the Blackberry arrived in the UK email work.
Voice mail worked.
Phone calls worked.
Um, I told you I had this whole setup with Skype, which, because of course I have my UK cell phone,
which I would take with me.
I mean, I've, I have my numbers were all over the map and, and the problem really is,
and this does really piss me off, is you can get your, you know, so here's T mobile, right?
It doesn't matter because they all do the same, where there's a vote of phone, orange,
T mobile, you know, or in the States, Verizon, uh, singular is actually the best for us,
and I'll tell you why.
Because I have, so I have my team mobile, uh, my MDA.
I've gotten, you know, my data accounts and everything.
And when you go overseas, you get penalized that to no end, uh, for using your phone,
which, of course, has driven me to, to get a provider over in the States.
You know, it's so stupid.
They charred.
They want to charge me.
See, if I call from London to the US, anywhere in the US, you can pay an extra, you know,
10 a month or something, and then you get 10 cents.
20 US dollar cents, by the way, I give a take.
Uh, which is still expensive to call any number in the US.
Now, when you take your phone over there, it'll cost you 90 pens.
So almost like a buck 80 to call, uh, overseas from, uh, from the US.
So to call back, it cost you a multiple of what it cost to call from the UK to the States.
So of course, we know that's horseshit.
And incoming calls cost 80 pens, a buck 50 buck 60 for an ink per minute.
Per minute for an incoming call.
You know, and so, um, they're losing out.
It's so incredibly dumb the way they do this.
So you, there's no, really, there is no global carrier, you know, and I just don't understand
why they can't get that together.
You know, why the prices, I mean, are they just trying to rape consumers?
Because we're not stupid.
I mean, yeah, for ease of use, maybe I'll take a call or two.
But, you know, so now here's how I've set it up.
When someone calls my UK cell phone, that automatically forwards to a UK Skype in number,
which means it's a very cheap call.
Because of course, you know, when you're using your cell phone over here and calling,
local, you know, UK numbers that are not going to charge a hell of a lot for that.
The cell phone company's finally figured that one out.
But then I have Skype set up so that it forwards through Skype out to my US cell phone.
How cool is that?
So the total charges are maybe per minute.
I think it's two cents, two euro cents per minute to Skype out to the states.
And it's probably about, um, it's probably for the local call, the forward that I'm doing
from a UK local, the UK local.
It's probably about 10 pens.
So it's still, you know, a good $25, 30 US dollar cents to do this.
But, you know, look, the look is making the money.
You know, Skype is making the money on this.
It's totally stupid.
Just can't believe.
And then when I call home, I call the Skype in number.
I got one of those Skype phones for Patricia, one of those cordless Skype phones.
And I call just a US based number.
And it actually sounds better than when I call her over the BT phone line.
It's not, man.
I'm telling you.
It's freaking nuts.
Wow.
It's so simple to see when you're down here in the trenches with the rest of the users of the technology.
Let me see if there's anything else that I wanted to hit here.
There was something about education.
Yeah, it's always nice to see that.
From Stephen C. Graves, I guess it's C.
I guess it's C. Graves.
Just wanted to share a new avenue that podcasting is taking on here.
My university at College of Education has incorporated podcasting to help their students and faculty receive information and training.
It's good content, especially for the future teachers here.
Just want to share that with you.
It's great to see podcasting taken off like this.
And I'll put a link to this in the show notes.
It's EDUC.ttu.edu slash podcasts.
Very cool.
Yeah, I want to be very clear that this podcasting thing is definitely bigger than selling iPods.
There's a lot more to it.
I'm so excited about all the things that are going to come and I can almost predict them.
I can see them happening.
And part of that is about music.
And we're going to talk about that in just a couple minutes.
This is Bob Robinson of the Pan and Community Church Service podcast.
You recall a couple of weeks ago I sent you an email talking about being picked to be an Arbitron ratings family.
Well, the diary's came and we spent our week filling out time.
Hold on, let me just interject here.
So what he did, what Bob Robinson did is he sent me an email that he'd been chosen as one of the select families or persons, I guess,
to participate in the Arbitron ratings.
Are the Nielsen's of radio and the way they're done is by filling out a diary.
So they give you a special diary and you have to write down what you listen to.
And the stations get credit for all kinds of things.
They get credit for call letters.
There's different credit if you can name it air personality that you heard.
There's all kinds of different, different things that the stations get varying degrees of credit for.
And that's how they determine this magical number of how many people are listening to the station by the quarter hour.
Remember, so you're probably writing down on the diary by the quarter hour.
What you listen to from 8 to 8 to 15 in the morning, 815 to 830 in the morning.
I was to get some more background on that from Bob.
I'd love to know what a diary looks like and I've never actually held one in my hands.
So he was going to fill in the podcast that he listened to as well.
So let's see what Bob has to say here.
And a couple of interesting results came out.
First of all, I do notice that I'm more than 50% podcast versus radio listener.
It's been about 60% of my time listening to podcast versus 40 over the regular radio.
And that's just been a past six months or so.
Another interesting point is my attention span for either podcast or radio seems to be about 20 minutes.
So 20 minutes or 40 minutes maybe is a really good time duration for individual podcast shows.
And finally, the arbitron folks did provide a little section in the back of the diary to put down any kind of comments we wanted to.
So I filled them in on what podcasting is and we'll see if it shows up as a blip on their ratings radar.
All right.
I'll leave you with a couple of plugs in the patent community church service podcast and Sunday word come to you both on Sundays.
And friend of mine, MB is the host of the fairytale corner podcast where they do classic original and modern fairytales.
Right now, MB is reading one of her very own original fairytales.
You sure to check it out on iTunes in the family section.
Thanks a lot Adam.
You have a great day.
Oh, I rev.
Nice processing, by the way.
Holy moly.
You got a noise gate there, son.
That sounded bad.
That sounded pretty aggressive.
I like it though.
And that, by the way, that's something interesting to talk about that sound processing really or just audio in general.
We've, so we discovered our microphones.
We discovered with that that hole in your laptop is for and we're putting it to great use.
But just like publishing in print and we talk about this a lot at pod show publishing in print or word processing.
That's a good example.
It's a good analogy actually.
So when you're making a document and you want to communicate something, it's, you know, it's not just words that would be a dot txt file.
But even in that, the way you space things, you know, you might put a bullet point in front of one certain item that you want to highlight and of course if you have a rich document.
Then you have italics and bold and fonts and colors and all kinds of things you can do to really get your message across and this all exists in audio as well.
We're learning all of this stuff which is okay.
You know, it's been around for a long time. There's a lot of what programmers would call prior art would trademark attorneys would also call prior art.
You know, so you can say something and you want a nonciated or you want to, you know, add it like this is an important thing. I want you to listen to it.
Okay.
Sing, say hello.
Right?
Can be used for good and for evil.
And so processing is a part of that.
You're sound, you know, and that could be whatever you want it to be, whatever, whatever floats your boat, I guess.
Now, about the pod safe music network.
Yesterday, while Patricia and I were doing this kind of review of pod safe music that I'd played on the show, we accidentally played a nonpod safe song, I'll explain why.
Because it was a cover version.
Now, in this whole discussion about playing pod safe or nonpod safe music on podcast, here's my ultimate view point. I see that there are really two.
Two types of rights. There's the performance rights, which means, you know, when you use a song, to basically, as a derivative work, I should, why don't have to go into legal terms.
So, if you want to use a song just to sing it yourself and to sing that at a concert or sing it for your friends or whatever, you know, essentially you're using someone else's work.
Now, there's all kinds of fair uses in there. But in my case, as this podcast eventually will start to generate revenue, it's only fair that if you're using someone else's work, it's only fair that they're compensated for that. If you're using someone else's work for profit.
Now, as it pertains to artists, there are lots and lots and lots of artists out there who may not, who may be great artists, but may not have the songwriting or composing talent.
And by the way, you know, I don't look at songs as CDs or tracks. It's a song and a great song is a great song and a great song could be performed and produced and recorded in many many different ways.
And that's really the thing that carries through all the ages is the song, not that particular recording.
There are songs that have been covered eight, nine, maybe even ten times. There are classics that, well, shoot classical music just as an example is basically covered all the time.
And in that case, there's no one left to pay because the copyrights, you know, there's no more copyrights in most cases in the public domain.
Now, as it, when it comes to the pod save music network, okay, so let's talk about so the other right is the fact that you're using someone's product.
So the product, of course, is the song or is the track that is a combination of the musicians, the singers, and also the authors and the composers of the song.
So let's say, and that's what ASCAP and BMI are for is for the, it's for the composers and the authors of the song, don't put that over to the left for a second.
So right now we're seeing lots of artists coming in saying, hey, I'm willing to give up the, the mechanical rights, the fact that you're using a product of theirs in a show.
They're willing to give that up for the promotional value that, that a podcast can bring when a podcast or place a song because, of course, where most of your money is made at the end of the day as an artist is performing in front of live audiences.
Now, if you can get into selling millions and millions and millions and keep that up, yeah, then it becomes a different game.
But by the way, sales of CDs or tracks direct to the consumer, these days are very interesting because your overhead is so low as an artist, you can keep 90% of the total purchase price in your pocket.
And then you have a little bit of cost on actually creating the CDs, but, you know, the physical product or if you want to sell by the track or some other means, it's all possible.
So let's presume that the artists are willing to give up that right for the promotional value, which is pretty much the way it works on radio today.
Radio stations do not pay the record companies or anybody else for playing the song.
They do pay, pay, ask cap and be a mile. There's two organizations and I don't think anyone belongs to both. You belong to either ask cap or be a mile.
And what they do is they track the usage of songs, not of the records, but of songs.
So if it's played in a bar, it's, of course, enhancing the atmosphere of the bar and the bar has revenue.
And so they have a business thanks in part to the songs. And so they pay not, you know, not a whole bunch, but they pay some money, which is in proportion to whatever the revenue is coming in.
It's probably going to be one to two percent of revenue of gross revenue.
And it's the same if you hear music and an elevator. I mean, all of that is paid for.
And they have guys who actually go out on this, they'll go by fairs and, you know, they have their collection agency.
That's basically what they are. They got the rules down and everyone agrees on it.
And I'm not against that. I think that, you know, absolutely.
And I think this fair use, if you're just, you know, hosing around and, you know, and not making any money using the song.
I think that, you know, there should be fair use that you don't have to pay anything. You shouldn't have to pay for something if you're not making money off of it.
Okay. So that's a long-winded wind up to the point I want to make.
And then we really got to move along.
And I believe the pod safe music network should go out. And of course, that's pod show.
And I'm going to talk about this today. In fact, we're going to get on it.
I think we should go out. And we should cut a deal with ASCAP and with BMI.
So that podcasters can use songs as long as they also have the right to play the actual product.
So that way artists can, you know, really introduce themselves to an audience and not just be limited by their own songs, but they can get other people's songs.
And they could use any wide variety of songs.
And we could do that right now. And I think that the pod show can, can figure out a way to negotiate something really well that will probably
work so well that no one who just wants to play some some cover songs, you know, some great songs, by the way, will have to shell out any money at all.
So I'm going to work on that. And just to give you an example of of what I mean, I'm going to play a song, which is a cover version and Brian in, but I know is smiling.
He's from cover, really. Because he has this all figured out and it took me a little while to catch on because
just because it's not the original artist that became a hit, you know, on the radio whenever the song still is the most important part.
This is the song that was on the radio when Christina was born. And I was, it was actually a C section. I was in the operating room.
And, you know, it's, it's a part of the soundtrack of our life. And it doesn't matter if it's the Beatles singing it or if it's Alison Crow.
And I mean it. The emotion is still the same. So it's not pod safe, but this is here to prove a point.
When our places are remember in my life, those some have changed, some forever not for better, some have gone, and some remain, all these places had their moments.
With lovers and friends, I still can recall some are dead and some are living. And my life I've loved them all.
But all these friends and lovers, there is no one compares with you, and these memories lose their meaning.
When I think of love as something you, there are no one ever lose affection for people and things that went to be far.
And all often stop and think about them, and my life I love you more.
And though I know I'll never lose affection for people and things that went to be far, I'll know all often stop and think about them.
And my life I love you more.
Welcome to 101 uses for baby wipes. Here comes the daddy cast.
My name is in the obituary column. And in the now it's time for new parents can use.
In the headlines today, living near freeways causes asthma. Is it ADHD or sleep deprivation?
Riddle in, not method crack, is all a rage on campus.
Test your cartoon trivia skills with the tune test.
Right, too much a one thing can be boring, so a nice mix of news and entertainment works for me.
Sorry, that was just way too much fun.
We're at 101 uses for baby wipes.com, and I tend, and of course, at the pod safe music network.
I'll show a dot com, recommend listening with at least one foot firmly planted in reality.
How many times does this happen to you?
I have fifty dollars.
What game did you get?
I think I was going to film that up in the end.
The new abitually wrong, mister. You see, if you listen to the teen gearing podcasts, they would tell you what games are actually worth purchasing.
Okay, that'll do it for the daily source code for today.
I am very excited about this idea of getting a license for covers for the pod safe music network.
I'll be back tomorrow with another source code from the cottage.
So let me do my sign off here.
Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.