Daily source code February 7th 2005 transmitters we don't need no
Stinking transmitters autistic it's Adam Curry. Hey everybody thank God it's a
Monday. It's a daily source code coming to you from what was actually a very
cloudy and misty and overcast day here in Guilford and Surrey in
the Kingdom of Curry Cottage actually it's a nice day so the birds are
out they're singing and it's time for your source code for the 7th of February
2005. So as long as it was yesterday I'm gonna cut it just a little bit
shorter today do it well I'm gonna try and keep it at the at the 40
minute mark as you used to maybe just a little bit shorter because we're
gonna talk for a little while with a special guest on the show about a topic
that came up yesterday on the source code that is getting a lot of comments
of getting a lot of email particularly about the EU the European Union and so
apparently I'm not that well informed and maybe you aren't either but I
think it's interesting stuff we should talk about.
But first of course some pod save music although I'm not quite sure well this
yeah I think this is pretty pod safe it's it was sent to me in reference to
the Michael Jackson comments yesterday actually I did see that Haraldo interview
and I was not disappointed Haraldo indeed thinks Michael Jackson is being
framed and the problem with that interview is that Michael is so nice and so
clean cut you just wanted to say fuck you motherfucker you know that would
if you just said that you know then I would feel much better it's so clean but
believe me this guy is you know he was he's been raised to be very polite very
nice and I think he's probably getting getting jerked around don't take that
too literally please so anyway here's a tune sure
do you want to buy a backwards and a sec when she's having it even if he is
bad we might fear we'd blame we'd give him fame and we could make him
to subpeer things people here they can't help it it just goes along with being
a star we need a star to be a little star only to remind us how normal we are
when smear it we're out to it it's year when the clear to live it first
alive the hair of the world mean things people wear
so i feel she's your woman
we'll come back with Michael Jackson because I never had a chance to be in the
Neither would you, if parents had you up, they're singing in dance and when you
younger than the drum and from handson, you probably turned out like Marilyn
Manson, friends, and I'm stage without any pants on, even if the
night's strange, they're here, we believe everything we hear, I've brought
about rich and kids just keep in mind, before you sneer, we'll give them the
Korean-based people a weird, can't help it, it just controls a lot of things to our
friends, people who are weird, they can't help it, it just controls a lot of things to our
neighbors, people who are weird, it's like the mean, the president, the start of hitting you
the matter, they're bunching around, they're weird, it's like the mean, the president, the start of hitting you
the way they're out of your mind, the way they're out of your mind, the way they're
weird, it's like the mean, the people who are weird, they're weird, it's like the
girls who are weird, they're weird, there you go, the same as people who are weird,
they're just trying to be a weird, you know what, otherwise they wouldn't be
interested to look at, to listen to, that's why we like famous people, they become famous
because they're different weird, artistic, or whatever, yeah, Dr. Demento from his basement
tapes, volume 12, famous people is the title of that, and you know what February is, don't you?
Shame on you if you don't
I'm a little bit worried about you, yeah, I'm PW Fenton here, as you well know, here in the
United States we set aside the month of February is black history month, last weekend I spent
a day at a street festival honoring Zora Neal Hurston in Eatonville, Florida, the oldest
incorporated black city in the United States, and that inspired me to turn this week's
digital flat some into my black history month edition, it's a little different, but that's
what I try to make every show, I hope you can check it out, yeah, I am so into this podcast
digital flat some, PW Fenton has a great job, he's been doing a lot of blue stuff recently
and just a whole vibe, there's something about this podcast that, you know, I keep thinking
this has got to be on, it's like some repurpose show that's already on radio, but no,
this is a podcast, and as you just heard, the digital flat some podcast is a highlighting black
history month and I'm looking forward to it, because it's going to be some really, really cool podcast.
Again, we've got a special guest coming up who I'm going to Skype in, but first it's time for
the little segment we do every single day.
Hi Adam, I'm Paulette here again with another hit test, it's number six already and I'll try
to make one every day for you, like I told you, I don't know for sure if that is possible,
but I'll do my best, let me tell you that opening a Gmail account was really a great move
because now I'm also getting lots of feedback and I really enjoy that, lots of people telling me
it's a great test and they're having lots of fun playing in with you, that's also one of the
biggest problems for me, because many people have been asking me when I will be starting my own podcast,
well there are two things I really like about this thing, the first thing is putting it together,
editing and recording it, and the second thing is hearing you taking the test,
hearing me suck, if I make it into its own podcast, I won't be hearing you take the test,
so hold it right there, yeah, it's cool, you can make a podcast, it could be the same thing,
you know, whatever you want, that's the cool thing, I don't think one has to exclude the other,
it would be shame, so I'm thinking about what to do about it, if you have some tips or suggestions
please let me know, and if there are other people that have suggestions please send them to hittest at
gmail.com, any feedback is welcome, hittest at gmail.com, by the way the sounds you're hearing right now,
that's the trick that was used, that you played actually in 1991, I think, it's from the second
air check, I played a few days ago, and you're right, it's not a great song, it's not a great
production, but the rhythm track is awesome, so I turn it into a filler, all righty, it's dry,
let's go, I think it's time for the test, right? I'm just a play, are you ready, this is number one,
all right, oh yeah, of course, Robbie Neville, say la b, ever bobbing now,
I love this song, number two, yeah, I certainly recognize it, is this a,
it sounds like a pet child boy's production,
and pet child boy is very good, he really was in the news, stuck with you, man, I must have played this song
a million times, and at least 10 different radio stations, okay, two out of three, not bad for a
Monday morning, what do you say? The answers, and here are the answers, this is number one,
that was Robbie Neville, right? Not a difficult, I think, it's Robbie Neville, with sale of
the y'all American pronunciation of sale of the show on the, yeah, I'm out of that,
great song, you know, this Robbie Neville actually,
Patricia recorded a song called Danger, which I'll play for you one of these days, which he wrote,
it's great, he's a great song, right?
Well Adam, I sincerely hope you had the second one, right? Okay, because I, I hate to find out tomorrow
that today the source code has been cancelled, due to the tragic death of the host,
can you buy his wife? Oh shit, this is an excursion for you, but I buy yourself,
Saturday night, I can't. Oh man, oh man, if Patricia finds out, she's gonna kill me, that's right, I knew I
recognized it.
That's all.
Of course, I was 12 when this was released, right?
There did not, I'd must have been 1970, there he goes, I feel like that.
Oh, well, I hope you're still around tomorrow, I might not be, this is number three.
Yeah, here we go. That is you, we lose, and the new stuff, and stuck with you.
Oh man, I can't believe unless the, you're good,
but I've been down that rock, you alone, we're here, we have the same a chance.
Yes, it's true. Yes, it's true. I don't happen to be stuck with you.
Yes, it's true. Yes, it's true. But I'm so happy to be stuck with you.
You will lose in the news, and stuck with you. Oh man, I'm also very happy to be stuck with you on the daily source code.
I don't know if I will be starting podcasts of my own. Please keep sending feedback to
Hittest at gmail.com. And if you would like to download one of the earlier editions of the hittest,
they are to be located at the following location, www.helpathand.nl slash hittest.
So that's www.helpathand.nl slash hittest.
I'll put the link here else, probably, to be found in the show, and up to the daily source code on
Adam's Web Law. Well, Adam, see you next time for the next edition of the hittest. Bye bye.
Oh, yeah, man, I'm going to be in so much trouble when Patricia finds out that I messed that up.
Oh my goodness. And you know Saturday night, I literally was like 12 or 13 when that song was released.
You know, I hope she gives me a little bit of leeway. That was trick, man. You tricked me.
I've played some 80 stuff that I really, oh, but it did sound like the Pet Shop Boys,
which I guess is a compliment for the production values. That was when she was disco queen,
everybody. Oh, man. It's time to get Patricia back on the show.
Alrighty, okay. So indeed, hopefully there will be a source code tomorrow after this snafu.
Time now to talk about the European Union. Yesterday, I had a long talk with you about my
feelings about the EU and boy, to that sparks some interesting conversation in the comments on
both curie dot com and on daily source code dot com. We had a podcast Paul actually who was
a student of the EU and the history has really been feeding some fantastic information. I've also
received privately many, many emails talking about the history of the EU and it's like it's unbelievable
that we're at the on the brink of signing a constitution, bringing all these as they call them
member states. You know, they don't call member countries. Members states bring them together into
into one union that shares not just money, but laws as well. And I think there's a lot of confusion.
And I'm certainly not well informed. I thought I was, but when I read through all these emails
and all the information I've been receiving. I've been finding it's just very confusing. Maybe
that's something that we can work on. And I received an email this morning. It's about 430
in the afternoon. Actually, I'm doing this on Monday from Raymond Port. And if you think that
name rings a bell, it does because way back when I just started doing the source code. Now,
I was doing one in Holland driving in studio A8 from Holland down to Belgium. You remember there was
a guy holding an iPod up and honking the horn and traffic at me saying, I'm listening to the
source code and was early on. And that was Raymond. And Raymond sent me a long email about
the European Union. And he certainly is well much more versed than I am. So I thought it would be
a perfect opportunity to see if we can get the old Skype system working and have a little chat
with him. So I'm calling him now. I think he's at work. So let's see if we can get Raymond in here.
Let me crank this up a little bit. Make it a little bit louder.
Hello, Raymond. Hello. You're on the source code. Can you hear me? Raymond? Hello? Well, it's not the
first time. Yeah. Well, yeah, I know. I know it's not the first time. I don't know. We know it's not
the first time. That's for sure. Yeah, that's true. So how are you? Yeah, I'm doing pretty great actually.
A lot of things on my mind about the working working very hard. And are you at the office right
now Raymond? Am I calling you at work? Yeah, you're calling me at the work. So I will not let my
boss live here. It is. Okay. Well, I really appreciate you taking it. Well, again, one hour break at a
day. So it's pretty okay. Okay. So this is this is your break then clearly. Yeah, this is my 15 minutes break.
Excellent. Well, I appreciate it. On behalf of the source code listeners, we really appreciate
you hopping on the the Skype. And by the way, kind of just comment on your picture on Skype,
it is very becoming. It's just beautiful. That hell. Hell is on your head, man. What is that?
Yeah, it's a punch ball pad. Oh, that's bad. It was taken in Universal Studios last year.
So Raymond, you were, I was just explaining to the listeners that you were one of the people who sent
me a very eloquent email about the European Union. And maybe you could just reiterate a bit
because you heard my podcast yesterday, obviously. And you had some things to say about the history
where it's coming from. And just what the hell is going on? What is happening in Europe? Are we
trying to create the United States of Europe? Yeah, it's well, it seems like it. Actually, I was
listening to the source code this morning in the car, of course. Of course. And yeah, the thing
you said about Europe at this moment, I think it's really true. People at least in an Netherlands,
they don't, they don't really seem to care if there are elections or anything. Not many people are
voting. And we don't know. We don't know what's going on. On the other end, I cannot really say too many
negative things about Europe because actually European Commission is a customer of mine.
Well, that sucks. Well, but let me understand something here. Because what,
okay, so this is actually interesting. People don't know a lot about the European Union,
which I think is worse than agreeing or disagree. And if you don't know what's going on, that's horrible.
What is there actually is power shifting from the individual countries to Brussels and to
Strasbourg? Will laws be made there that will apply to all of the member states?
Actually, yeah, that is what is happening. And not many people know of it. And it goes pretty far.
I don't know the insight that I've heard. It goes pretty far. And it could be threatening as well.
On the other end, each country is trying to, well, let's say, save its own culture.
Right. So, yeah, it's just very delicate and complex thing, obviously, because every country
and borders France, there is volume. We all know how France is with its own culture.
Yeah, they're very protective of it. Difficulties.
Yeah, you can say that. If you don't speak French, you have a big problem.
Well, so this is one of the reasons, well, that everything is bilingual.
Well, isn't it even so that the European, that the Parliament,
that they, which is, I guess it's all supposed to be in Brussels, but the French,
and this is the way I've heard it. The French complain so much that they set up this other
center in Strasbourg, and now the entire European government, if we can call it that,
literally goes from Strasbourg back and forth to Brussels to make everybody happy, is that what's happening?
What could very well be, actually, I'm not 100% sure, whether it kind of strange that there are two centers.
And people really day, one half of the week there in Strasbourg and the other half there in Brussels.
Even going on commute every day. It's just crazy.
And then they also have to go back to their own country. So they often have to spend that time there,
as well, I presume, right?
Yeah, and it's all paid by the man.
No, no, that would be you and I, dude, we are the man in that case. We're paying for it.
Oh, I don't mean it's all our money. But it was a kind of fun, what you said, and the source,
I guess, that actually it's going back on control now. Europe is all about control and
new laws are being done. The history of Europe, and that's something that's not really much
or many people know, started off with control. The very basic reason for building one big
Europe was actually the wish for some countries to have no more war in Europe.
Okay. Obviously, the middle ages and the 80th century, even Napoleon and the first world war,
which started with Germany and France and the second world war again in Europe, many countries
had to be feeling no more war in Europe and how can we prevent that while we can prevent that by
introducing the euro. And then everything was bright and clear. Yeah, and then it was all
sat and we were all happy. No, but we're not happy. I mean, it just, it makes no sense.
I mean, the fact that people don't know what the hell is going on, that tells me enough.
I mean, I'm American. So the Constitution of the United States is the document that the entire
country and its government, everything was built around. It's a document that every American
oops, I think I just lost Raymond there. Hold on, let me see if I can get him back.
You all continue on my, um, on my rant there. Let me just see if I can get Raymond back. I hate it
when Skype does that. That's so unfair in the middle of me talking. You know, cut him off. Okay,
but shoot. Don't tell me this is not going to work. Come on, Raymond, come back to me.
Hmm. Maybe we'll have to play a song, uh, failed unknown error. Yeah. All righty. We love that.
Let's try it one more time here. Hold on. Maybe that's a connectivity thing on his end. Okay.
Meanwhile, we're about 22 minutes into your daily source code for Monday, February 7, 2005.
Now it says, user not on law. I'll tell you what, we're going to play a little song. See, we can pick
Raymond up, uh, in a, in a minute or two. This is, uh, for my buddy, Sid, Sid happens. He said,
me this wonderful mashup. See if you can recognize it.
It's a funny thing for me to try it. It's playing. I don't feel any more pride. I don't want to blame.
There's no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
There's still no one to blame
Just like you, no one you don't understand
Come and look at the praise and ride now
Your love's coming, look at the praise and ride now
Look at me, look at the praise and ride now
So let's come and look at the praise and ride now
Come and hope me a praise and ride
Come and hope me a praise and ride now
Your love's coming, look at the praise and ride now
You're so crazy, you're lost
So let's come and look at the praise and ride now
Come and look at the praise and ride now
You're so crazy, you're lost
Yeah, look at the praise and ride now
Come and hope me a praise and ride now
Chloe, look at the praise and ride now
You're so crazy, you're lost
Come and hope me a praise and ride now
์
Come and hope me a praise and ride
Come and hope me a Praise and ride now
Come and hope me a praise and ride crown
Thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this video, thank you very much for watching this
all right there you go, did you get them, what the hell was that?
oh, lovely, that's a bit of dawn and Thai yellow ribbon around the old oak tree and of course was it, was it Beyonce or was it Destiny's Chart now it's Beyonce I think Raymond just popped online again, so let's see if we can get him in
hey Raymond, hello, there it was again, what happened did you crash?
well actually I'm using a Windows based PC, well of course, yeah, then we have all the answers right there don't we
you don't want to believe how my desktop looks on on this Windows machine because if you see it it's just the Mac OS 10
well listen Raymond, I can did all the way, here's what I suggest, why don't, of course you did, why don't we want to pick this up tomorrow and we'll continue and let's see what kind of comments coming on this and see we can get a conversation going with some people about this stuff
I don't know, I've got all kinds of shit going off right now, yeah because I've got alarms going off and phones ringing and people trying to get a hold of me so and I really want to spend some time and talk a bit more about busy day again
yeah, well you're busy too, can we can we set it a date for tomorrow maybe and we'll pick this up and we'll continue
yeah, yeah, that will be fine, I'm happy to sit where I am now in the meeting room, I can do my work from here as well, so that's not a big problem
okay, I'll send you mail and we'll see if we can hook up tomorrow then that'd be great
yeah, we perfect, okay, I appreciate it Raymond, it's good talking to you, of course you've been along in this podcast journey for a couple of months
you've, you know, you have one of the, one of the most famous moments of the day being of podcasts
yeah, yeah, boiling, all right, whatever you do, don't vote for anything yet until we finish our conversation, right?
okay, I'll do that
okay, Raymond, thanks a lot, buddy, I'll talk to you tomorrow and ensure the source code listeners will appreciate this as well
yeah, happy, happy to do it and just sit around in the room
okay, great, thank you very much, talk to you tomorrow
my name, my name, my name, my name, my name, my name, my name, my name, my name is Matt Moron
that's all I was like, yeah, go ahead, what do you want to say?
hello, my name, ladies and gentlemen, my name is Sarah Scott, I really have to be here
All right buddy, we'll be talking more eU tomorrow just kidding all right that's
Raymond Ford everybody thanks Raymond talk to tomorrow
Little discombobulated, but that's what it's all about I guess if it was slick
Shit of the on the BBC right that's it for the source code comments Adam and Curry dot com or
Audio comments MP3 feedback a Gmail dot com of course, you know, it's got the latest show in the archives and the podcast feed a daily source code dot com
I thanks to Raymond Ford
We'll continue tomorrow hopefully with less technical difficulties and tomorrow more pod save tunes from those and
You know the typical crab right
You