Deadly source code, April 13th, 2005.
Your DJ has only just begun.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
Hey everybody, coming to you from the Waldorf Astoria.
It's the Daily Source Code.
That's right, this is Adam Curry.
In my hotel room in the big apple, it's officially still...
Wait a minute, did I mess it up? It's not the 13th.
I guess it's officially the 11th.
So let's just say this is for the 12th of April.
Ah, well, you know, Jetlight.
That's what Jetlight will do to you, I guess.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Coming to you from the Beta Cast Blaster.
Which means I'm on the headset right now.
I'm in my hotel room.
And I am completely knackered in a good English way.
So we would say, because Matt, the day started at...
Let's see, I left the house at 7 a.m. Guilford time.
And right now it's about 5 a.m. in the UK.
That's right, it's almost been 24 straight hours for me.
But I feel pretty good actually.
Just got back from a lovely dinner in the basement here at the Waldorf Astoria.
It's the infamous...
What is it? Bare and beer or something like that?
A steak chop house where they basically hang dead cows up for 21 days to dry and cure
and then they throw it on your table and somehow you eat that.
It's pretty amazing actually.
Okay, so it's been quite a journey.
As I said, left the house, left the cottage at 7 a.m.
Hopped on a brand new air carrier.
At least for me it's a brand new air carrier.
Virgin Atlantic never traveled with them.
I actually, I think it was...
Virgin Atlantic started...
What did they start? Probably around...
Hmm, let me think, maybe around 10 years ago, right?
And I do remember one time.
No, in fact, it was 1996 just before we took our company
think new ideas public and we did our European road show.
And we were booked to return back to New York on Virgin Atlantic.
But we showed up like 59 minutes before the flight was scheduled to leave.
It's pretty much the rule. Certainly in the UK, gate closes, gate closed.
You ain't getting on.
So I kind of... I think at that time we swore up and down
and swore we'd never again fly Virgin Atlantic, which we'd never done.
But I gave it a new shot.
And I must say, I was pleasantly surprised.
You know, what a little bit of set dressing and marketing.
You know, just making people feel good will do.
It goes quite a long way.
This really gave me the old feeling of flying back.
Now I'm old enough.
And boy, am I feeling it now? I'm, you know, being 40.
I remember when we used to go traveling when I was a young boy.
I maybe five or six years old.
And my parents would dress me up in a nice little suit right in my sisters.
I would have a little cute little frocks on with the white gloves and the black shoes,
you know, the shiny black shoes.
Because we were going flying.
And a lot of that old school, old world feeling kind of comes back to you
when you fly Virgin Atlantic.
They have the plush, red carpeting.
And the stewardesses have their hair up in buns, even the stewardes actually.
They continuously give you all kinds of snacks and drinks and make you feel right at home.
And I didn't fly in there infamous upper class.
I just can't bring myself to pay that kind of money anymore to lay down.
If someone else paying for it, it'd be more than happy to, you know,
sometimes I will splurge like the last time when I went back from San Francisco.
That was on British Airways, but I got something they call the premium economy,
which gives you a lot of flexibility.
You can change your flights, you know, if you want to.
And you get enough leg rooms that I can actually with six foot four.
I can actually sit down and, you know, and almost kind of sleep comfortably.
Everything was perfect except for one thing.
They have this video on demand service on board.
They have 50 movies.
You can compile your own playlists.
And it's, I guess it's a streaming type of service.
And they started off the flight by saying, if you're, you know,
if you're, if you're in flight entertainment system,
should become garbled or confused.
Just let one of the flight attendants know.
We'll reset your entertainment system.
It will take you 20 minutes before you can watch again.
But at least then you can watch.
So it was something like that.
You're some vague announcement I was like, wow, that doesn't sound very good.
So first of all, I had seat 19D.
And for some reason, I sat down in 19C and I was already pretty much established.
It already made acquaintance with, with the guy sitting next to me.
I was like to have an aisle seat.
And then some other passenger came up and who, of course, had 19D.
Oh, 19C and, I said, well, you know, he said, I don't worry about it.
You're sitting there. I'll just sit on this side.
It's also an aisle seat. No problem.
Well, I wish I had, had gotten my original seat because, of course,
my in flight entertainment system fucked up.
And the reason why, because here it was,
I was completely jazzed because I could watch the aviator,
a movie that I've been wanting to watch for a long time.
Big fan of what Howard Hughes has done in aviation.
And I was about an hour into it and my guy next to me, my seatmate,
needed to go to the restroom.
So, of course, that means that me being in the aisle,
I have to get out stand up.
And when I sat back down, I sat down on the controller
and then the movie started to rewind and I fast forward it.
And then, yep, it started to hose out, which means,
I guess it's streaming.
They must have some kind of streaming server on board.
And it got all, you know, you got all the digital blocking
and the static and it was unwatchable.
So, I rang my call button and they said, oh, yeah,
it's time for you to be reset, sir.
It's like something they clearly have done more than once.
And check this out.
So, I actually heard this on the announcement.
When we reset it, you'll see a penguin followed by computer code.
And I knew it was coming because they reset it
and lo and behold, Linux, right?
Linux is running this thing.
And I wasn't fast enough.
I grabbed my, you know, try to get my camera,
but before I knew what the boot screen had already passed by,
it had like, what was the command that it starts up air seat
or something like that?
Needless to say, it never really worked again.
I had them reset it again.
It was a total of like an hour of waiting for this thing to reboot.
And it just, it didn't come back.
And everyone else's entertainment system was working fine.
So, when I go back on Saturday,
I hope to catch the second half or the second two-thirds,
the remaining two-thirds of the aviator.
So, that was a major bummer, of course.
I did have a chance to catch up on a whole bunch of podcasts.
I want to make a special mention of Michael Butler,
a general geek show.
He did a sound seeing tour of a strip joint in San Francisco,
which was just phenomenal.
It was really funny, Mike.
I really enjoyed that one.
I'm on the headset, by the way.
I'm using the cast blaster.
This is up to beta number five.
After this week, when I get back,
we'll be opening up a small beta amongst,
I think we're going to go for no more than 15 or 20 people.
And I'm going to be selecting a few.
Mike, the developer, I'm working with.
We'll be selecting a few.
So, we can really, you know, just flesh out some stuff before,
before we take this prime time, or at least prime time beta.
So, if the sound is not exactly what you are used to hearing,
it's because I'm on the outtick, lancing headset.
Because it is, you know, almost midnight,
and feel like setting up the wireless microphone and all that.
And that's what's kind of cool about the cast blaster.
You can just, you know, it already has all of my,
the openers and my jingles, and of course, my important effects.
Like like that is already, it's already pre-loaded.
And all I have to do is just put in the stuff that I want to play
on the particular show.
So, I'm in my hotel room here at the Waldorf Astoria,
which is owned by the Hilton family.
In fact, I think Paris has a full-time residence here
with her family, although she may not be here all the time.
I'll be out in California.
Although today was a beautiful day in New York.
We got in to the, I'd never been to the new terminal for,
or ever, you know, it's been new, I guess, for the past three years,
three years ago when they reopened it.
Sun was shining, it was, you know, 75 degrees.
It was just, there was no traffic on the road.
It was absolutely wonderful.
The city, everyone was having lunch outside by the time I got in.
I couldn't check into the room, of course.
Check out time is 12.
Check in time is 3 p.m.
I was in the hotel around 115.
So, of course, I dropped my bag off.
Went out down the corner and immediately got me a big,
a jumbo, a hot dog with sour crowd, and catch up,
and mustard, and a snap-alice tea, and sat down
in the steps of, what's the building that's next door here?
Well, everyone was sitting on the steps,
and just enjoying the sunshine,
and then had another wonderful digital experience.
I bought a tea mobile SIM card for my cell phone,
slipped that in, which gives me, you know,
one, seven, six, eight, number, whatever the heck it is.
Called the 203 number, which is our Skype in,
and talked to Patricia, who was sitting at home in the cottage
for, you know, about, you know, a penny and a half per minute.
I love it when that works.
It's just so phenomenal.
Ron had already arrived in an already done one meeting,
and we had two meetings that we're going to do
before the day was over just to get him in and while, you know,
while we have that afternoon.
So, it really didn't get back to the hotel,
until about seven o'clock,
and I was still in my flight clothes, you know,
so I was pretty rancid by that time.
But this is such a wonderful feeling
to be in a New York hotel room,
because it's all the sounds and the smells,
you know, the, in fact, you can probably hear it.
I'm actually going to disconnect the power supply here,
so we can walk around the room for a second.
You know, you've got the heater slash air conditioner,
which is always on and makes a lot of noise.
In fact, is it on right now?
Let me, there you go.
Put my microphone down.
Near the air conditioning unit,
I can actually open up the window if you're interested.
I'm on a second just to hear some street noises.
Ah.
Oh, I can hear,
so it's pretty quiet outside, of course,
it's almost midnight.
I hear my phone is,
it's my phone about to ring here.
I don't know if you can hear that disturbance.
I'll put the phone down over here.
They don't have Wi-Fi in the hotel.
They do.
It's kind of cold, actually.
It did get cold outside.
They don't have Wi-Fi.
They do have broadband.
And it's, it's a wired broadband.
Kind of like a little Cisco router sitting here.
So I brought the Mac and the tablet.
So I'm using the Mac as,
basically as a Wi-Fi base station.
So that's connected to the broadband.
And I'm roaming on the, on the tablet PC.
Nice and a roomy.
You know, it's just, it's an old fashion.
It's a great hotel.
You know, it's, it's one of those New York hotels.
You just recognize anywhere.
Once you've, once you've been in it.
So I'm sitting on one of the two double beds.
We connect my power supply there.
I'm almost out of breath.
Did some email.
Man, a lot of, a lot of email about these, these English disjockeys.
Almost like, let me pull that up for a second.
Let me see if I can find these jibbrownies.
There's a new site that came online called podshows.com.
I'm going to go to it right now.
Probably, by the way, the, the broadband isn't the best in the world.
Sometimes it's just no connectivity at all.
So hopefully I can even get this show uploaded properly.
So these, these English DJs have started a, like a, I guess a pod cast thing.
Here, it'll probably start playing here in a second.
Radio where you want it when you want it.
Hello, you just found podshows.com.
A little taste of the teacher.
This is the world's first professional podcast.
It's the only place you can find.
So it says,
Sounds like crap.
So I'm not quite sure what to make of this.
They're charging for these shows, which include shows by Tony Blackburn,
who was about a hundred years old.
And, I mean, it doesn't really matter what they're doing.
It's, it's a little disturbing that they're basically taking something that,
you know, we have podshow.com and now podshows.com.
They, they really think that that's going to fly.
And immediately, people have jumped into help.
Podcast Paul has, who is a lawyer has given me some advice.
And now we're going to see if we should do anything about it and what we'll do about it.
But just makes no sense to me.
And also that the, what they're trying to do there, it's not really,
doesn't, just isn't really fitting with the vibe of podcasting if you ask me.
You know, so anyway, check it out podshows.com.
You can see Tony Blackburn's horrible rug.
What else was going on?
Oh, I listened to Don and Drew.
Their latest show on the, on the, on the plane right over.
They've got a new sponsor, directs, condoms and lube.
It was, it was a great show.
Listening to, to Don command Drew to lube up.
I was definitely a trip.
Let me see.
I've got some promos for you today.
And also I selected a mashup, which was suggested by the one and only pim daddy.
It's a combination of now that we found love.
And I guess it's Shannon.
It's called now that we found music.
Check that out for a couple of minutes.
I'll be back with you with some new pod save music and a hit test on today's daily source code.
I thought it was clear the plan was we were sharing this feeling.
Everything went out the house.
But when the music changes, the plan has been arranged.
You went to pieces on it.
We started dancing and love, but I seemed to love bro.
But now it's just somebody to do.
You're like I've got one more thing to do.
I'm going to do it.
You don't get away.
Just get away.
He tried reading, they not necessarily just that there's what I see.
His dancing is way back to me.
It's not just getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold,
it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's not getting cold, it's
You'll get away, just get away
You'll get away, you'll get away
Just be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool, be cool,
Nice mashup of third world now that we found love and Shannon let the music play on your daily source code for the 12th of April 2005, thanks to Pimp Daddy Sid for pointing that one out to us all.
It's just watching TV, saw George Bush an aerial sharon at the ranch and Crawford Texas Man, aerial sharon is fucking huge.
I always thought he was wearing a bulletproof vest that that's why his jacket was so big but the man is just big, he's like a fucking Humpty Dumpty unbelievable.
I didn't even catch the story, now I've got Joan Rivers yapping about being a guest at the Royal Wedding, I caught that actually, the Wedding Prince Charles married to Camilla Parker Bowles.
I got a bad feeling about that, I really do, that just, you know, he was seeing her while he was actually, I guess they've always been in love and I'm not quite sure why he ever married Diana.
He certainly didn't do her justice man, I mean, this thing just has, it does me a real bad taste and I think most of the, most of the British public kind of agrees, you know, they like, whatever.
They certainly will never, we'll probably won't address her as the Princess of Wales, although that is her her official title and by the way, what is the deal with her and all of her hats?
Why didn't you know, can't they pin that shit down to her head? Why does she always have to hold on to it with that trembling left hand, you know, it's like, either you wear the hat and have it bolted down so it sits right or you know, don't wear it, it's just anyway.
Oh, I got some great promos, check this one out, this is a great podcast.
She was blonde, she was beautiful. More than 40 years after her death, she is arguably more popular today than during her own lifetime.
She is the one and only Marilyn Monroe. My name is Melinda Mason and I've been a Marilyn fan and collector for over 15 years.
Join me for my bi-weekly podcast, my Marilyn, celebrating the life of this amazing actress. I'll be discussing her life, current news, collectibles, basically everything, Marilyn.
So, check it out at Marilyn Monroe.ca slash podcast.
I got to tell you, I'm a sucker for sounds and music from the 30s and the 40s and the 50s.
There's another podcast that I'm a big fan of that I've been subscribed to ever since I first found out about it.
PW Fenton does digital flotsom at digitalflotsom.org.
And I've talked to PW a couple of times over the past, well, in the lifespan of podcasting.
And inevitably, married guys eventually talk about their wives.
And I was pretty surprised and was gaffering and chuckling out loud on the play.
When I heard the following opening to the most recent digital flotsom podcasts.
Okay, this is not a normal. If there is such a thing, digital platform.
Every time I do a show, the wife says, oh, that was nice. You should talk more.
You're so good at that. I love when you talk. Why don't you talk?
Well, about a week ago, Adam Curry, the pod father.
Oh, wait.
It says to me, hold on a second.
When you say the pod father got a little boy in a unrelated context, you should listen to your wife.
They're always right.
So you're all in for it. For this week, it's the wife's edition.
Lots of me talking. Longer show, maybe. Lots of wife stuff.
So you really should check out the most recent digital flotsom.
It's the wife episode. It's got great bits in there by famous comedians.
Some wonderful songs.
And PW also talks a lot about the quote production values.
How he does this podcast.
And how content really is king.
And that it's not about the sound quality.
It's about the decisions you make when you go to create your podcast.
And there's some really, some real good nuggets of information in there that I definitely suggest you check out.
There's a beautiful sound seeing tour called On the Wing.
Thanks, Adam.
Now we're more than a sound seeing tour. On the wing is the podcast magazine of birds and birding.
We'll cover the people, places, and creatures that make birding one of the fastest growing hobbies in the world.
Everybody's after looking at how he's trying to get out of dodge.
Oh, look at that.
You got the idea, right?
It's really intimate.
It's left and right.
And it really trips with your brain when you're listening to that on the, uh, your buds.
The April edition of On the Wing is available at on the wing.lipsin.com.
That's on the wing dot libsyn.com.
Those lipsing guys are doing okay.
It seems to be a pretty simple service that's working quite well.
And people are very happy with it.
And in the past, I've mistakenly said, I've mistakenly talked about their pricing.
But it really is not based on bandwidth, but it's based on storage.
And it's got a very interesting model.
I don't know if they're making any money on it, but I do see a lot of podcasts coming through the directory.
By the way, the directory, we're now up to over 4,800 podcasts actively tracked.
A couple new categories have come online as well, which include what we have bicycles.
Also, Madge Weinstein is not doing the gain lesbian node.
There's a category there of podcasts.
Just all kinds of stuff happening.
And of course, you may be wondering what I'm doing in New York here to meet up with a couple of,
the pod show technical partners that we've entered into agreements with.
We are closing a couple of big advertising deals, which are very excited about.
And it looks like the first week of May is when we're really going to start unveiling a lot of the talent that we've made investments in.
Excuse me.
As Madge would say, I'm so bloated.
I'm sorry.
I just got to tell you a little story, a little sidebar here.
You know, Madge Weinstein's got usually has a theme song.
And people just keep sending her fantastic new self-written theme songs.
It really hits home about how cool all this podcasting is.
The interaction you can have with your listeners.
And we were at the dinner table Patricia Christina and I.
And I was mentioning some of the songs and Christina loves it.
She loves talking about being bloated and yeast.
Hey, she's a 14. I'm sorry. She's 14.7. She would point out to you.
And we came up with a couple of songs.
And we were actually going to record one of these Patricia's sister Ivana's coming over in two weeks time.
And together, well, if you had heard any of the stars on 45 stuff for the star sister stuff that Patricia Ivana've done together,
their voices fits so beautifully. They do great harmonies.
So I think we're going to record if you're bloated and you know what clap your hands.
We also came up with what was the other one.
Do you remember the the floaters bloated on?
And there was a Christina came up with a fabulous.
Oh, was that pilot?
Oh, oh, oh, she's bloated.
You're listening to yeast radio.
You can tell who's the singer in the curry family and you can definitely tell who isn't the singer.
So anyway, doing some some meetings and I hopefully I'll be flying back Saturday back to the UK just in time to do some more intense flight training.
I spoke to the wing commander and we're going to try and combine a couple things next week.
When I was in Iraq last February.
So that was February at 2004 with the Dutch Marines.
We did live broadcast with there for 10 days.
If you just look at him curry and Iraq on on Google.
If you Google that, you'll see all kinds of pictures and stuff from when we were there.
It was just a life altering experience.
We did is I left my transmitter.
I do have a transmitter 100 watt FM transmitter.
Left that there for the troops with a satellite dish.
So they could listen to radio from back home.
And since the Dutch Marines have now left Camp Smitty in Iraq.
They are no longer in the coalition there, which was all planned and agreed to upfront.
They want to give me, I think they want to give me the transmitter back.
They do that next Wednesday.
It was at Wednesday the 20th or whatever.
And I think they're going to give it to me in then five seconds later.
They're going to take it back because they basically like the idea so much.
Now they want to take the transmitter to Afghanistan.
So I wouldn't mind visiting them over there and actually doing some podcast.
That would be very cool.
And I haven't spoken to them about it.
But maybe I can convince somebody.
He's back everybody.
It's y'all.
Hi Adam.
There you go.
A lot is going on.
Not only here with me, but you're also on the road.
And I'll try to create a hit test if possible.
But I think it won't be as frequent as we are used to.
That's okay.
But my information about what's going to happen is to be found in my own hit test podcast.
And you can find it at yompolet.nl.j and p-o-l-e-t.nl.
For now, there is one.
So let's start right away.
Rock on.
Whoa.
Oh, yon.
Come on, that way.
I'm just going to use the rewind feature here.
I have no idea what that is, yon.
You may do them in frequently, but they're not easier.
This is number two.
It's a bit longer.
That's, I know what that is.
That's, uh, Donald Fagan.
With, uh, that international geophysical year was the album title.
Bob Bada.
I think it must be steely Dan or Donald Fagan.
Some combination there.
And the final one.
Number three.
Let's talk, talk.
But, uh, let me listen.
It's my life.
I think so.
And it's time for the answers.
And this is number one.
It's Phil Ferran and Galaxie.
This is Dan's in tight.
Oh, man.
I should have known that one.
Great early 80s, too.
That's in tight.
Bill Ferran.
Man, that's an old, uh, decibel radio, too.
My prior radio days, an answer to that.
And so number one in today's hitest is dancing tight.
Phil Ferran and Galaxie.
This is, uh, a bit of a complicated title.
Um, the title of this song is called.
I do why.
Yeah, I got it right.
International geophysical year.
Yeah.
But it's also well known by, uh, not a title.
And it's a wonderful world.
This is Donald Fagan in the hitest.
And so number two.
Great song.
I do what I thought.
Well, this is worth it.
Yeah.
Donald Fagan in the number two.
And this is talk talk.
Always nice to have them in the hitest.
Great.
This is, it's my life.
And so number three.
All right.
See what a three today.
Man, whatever happened to those guys.
It's my life.
Talk talk.
Well, that's it for today's hitest.
Adam.
I think you had a, uh, three out of three today.
No.
At least I hope so.
Two out of three.
Um, again, I don't know what's going to happen in the coming weeks and months.
We just have to wait and see.
One thing it is, uh, certain almost is that, um, uh,
the high prediction values of the hitest is going to drop a bit.
Because I will have to be, uh,
recording the hitest with a noble kind of simple headset.
And not with all the external gear.
I'm using here right now.
And, uh, let's, that is a shame.
And, uh, I'll be okay.
Maybe I'll try to record it in another way, uh,
to, um, maybe I will, um, prepare the hitest, uh,
doing the week and record them all in the weekends.
But I'm, I don't know if I've time for that.
And I, I think that, um, my wife is not going to be happy with it.
Um, listen to the digital plots of podcasts.
Like I said, we have to wait and see.
More information about what's going on with my life and with, uh,
the problems I'm having right now is, so to be found in my own hitest podcast.
Uh, www.yumpolet.nl, this J&POLAT.nl.
Feedback is welcome with hitest at gmail.com.
And I hope to see you soon, Adam.
Till next time, bye-bye.
All right, young, and please take it easy, buddy.
Don't worry about it.
If you can't create it, it's not a problem at all.
And I will be sending you off a, uh, cast blaster, um,
beta in time so that you can, uh,
uh, create, uh, the hitest.
If you feel that you, if you feel up to it, um,
um, and you'll be able to do that, uh,
in kind of the same hokey way.
I'm doing it right now.
But it does seem to work.
Even though, um, you know, this,
and I'm promising myself.
I'm going to pick up a better headset,
because not only is this microphone, you know,
so, so it's not, you know, not the best mic in the world.
Uh, but the headphones are just really booming.
It's, uh, actually when the hitest has played,
I had to remove one, um, uh, one side of the headphones,
just to, you know, get rid of the boomingness, man.
It's just, oh, these,
altic lancings, not at all what I want.
So we're 35 minutes into the show.
I want to play one more song for you.
And this, um, is, uh, a piece of podsafe music.
Um, and I just want to read you, um,
this, uh, this email that came in.
I was really pleased to see this.
Uh, shoot. Now, of course,
the connectivity here really freaking bites.
I don't know if it's the DNS lookup,
or if it's, uh,
or if it's just purely the connectivity,
or what it is, but,
oh, on the second.
It's loading.
Uh, see, that's what you get when you do show notes in, uh,
with your Gmail account. Oh, here it is.
Okay.
So I got, uh,
where is it?
Here it is.
AWS.
Okay.
Hi, Adam.
Says Alan Wence.
Does that ring a bell?
Alan Wence, anybody?
No.
A quick, very condensed bio for reference.
I was the original bassist in Wild Cherry.
Of course, we know Wild Cherry from
Bob Bom, Bom Bom Bom Bom Bom Bom Bom.
Play that funky music.
Uh,
I am now running an independent label production and publishing company,
our newest release,
out of warranty is both accessible,
original and we recently placed two tracks in Maryland,
Mansons,
a, in Maryland, in Maryland's,
Man in Maryland.
I'm butchering this.
We recently placed two tracks in Maryland,
men's a Monroe bio pick,
and he wanted to know if I was interested in playing
didn't play something on the daily source code and I said yeah absolutely please send
it on first of all I said dude I have played a while cherry on so many radio shows
it's just it's great to hear from it because I think you know with that particular song
it is it is kind of that bass that you know really is the music cue of you know that's
the musical molecule of that song and it really really kicks it and what he sent me and I have
to look that up hold on a second totally not organized here the title of the track is
shoot oh how come I can't here it is is this it is it just titled Catherine I think it's just
titled Catherine isn't it I just want to double check I don't I don't want to get it wrong
this yeah I think it is just titled Catherine anyway it's it don't expect wild cherry at all
this is something completely different but it has a I don't know a nice vibe to it
so I wanted to share that with you
she won't be so we've made it out we're not really sure but some more guys have been
the little time we're going to play show and the show and the show is such
damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn
damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn nothing ever happened to me again fucking damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn Damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn my damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn damn
See, I told you this catch, your Catherine and Blue is actually the title.
I'm of course, I'll put that in the show notes, which may be a bit abbreviated for
tonight, because it's, I'm so wrecked, it's almost been 24 hours that I've been up
and running around. And we're at 40 minutes, which means it's perfect time to end the show
for today, of course, tomorrow be back with another source code from the Big Apple.
As always, comments are welcome at a Maccurry.com. I may not respond immediately because, well,
I'm not sitting in my office at the Cottage all day, and just don't have the time to sit
through my Gmail account. Of course, the podcast feed is at dailysourcecode.com.
We can also find archives in the most recent show. So, looking forward to enjoying a
little bit of American culture. It's been a while since I've really had a chance to roam
the streets of New York, so maybe maybe maybe maybe a little bit of sound seeing.
Maybe some sound seeing of Denver, who knows, and would be all over the place. So, thank
you very much for bearing with me, and thanks for subscribing to the Daily Source Code.
Be sure to check it tomorrow. Take care, everybody. Bye-bye.