Delta Shara Charley 2, 5, 8.
Brasmithor, please don't even speak in Transnithor.
There are no secrets.
Only information you don't get out of.
No!
And I'm Korean.
Sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking crazy.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
It's a battle curry.
And it is Tuesday, October 11th, 2005.
I like the new opening, huh?
That's right.
I need more Mexican dialect for my Transnithor's.
Welcome to the Daily Source code coming to you from Curry Cottage in the affluent Surrey
Suburb of Gilford in the United Kingdom.
A little bit dreary today.
I'm sorry.
The jury will disregard that remark.
I just looked outside and the sun just broke through.
It was broken at 4,000 feet today.
And they're completely muddled up at 400 feet, which would have made any type of landing impossible on a non-Isles field.
Can you tell that I'm getting ready for some flying tomorrow?
Oh, yeah, I've got all my taps and my matars and I've even checked the no-tams.
So I'm ready for the trip to the Netherlands.
And you, my friends, are going with me on the road.
As always.
I was thinking, what was I thinking?
It was something about the...
Oh, yeah, it was about the...
Yeah, every show we start off with Delta Sierra Charlie.
And by the way, yeah, sometimes I do slip into the sheriff.
And I don't know why I do that, but everyone seems to kind of get the gist.
The Delta Sierra Charlie just realized the call letters of my...
My sessna actually have Delta Sierra in the call sign at the end of the call sign.
Coincidence?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I think not, my friends.
All right, we've got Podsave Music.
Some interesting news to talk about.
The Podsave Music and Music Rights and the Unlabel.
That's all coming up.
And of course, some promos.
And what would a daily source code be without the new...
The newvo art of the mashup?
I think I might have played this one before, but it's such a kicker.
YouTube versus Janet Jackson.
It's control, bloody control.
And I will separate you.
I'll deliver you to me.
I'll deliver you to my father's cell.
And there's no longer no need.
I'll deliver you to my cell.
I'll deliver you to my father's cell.
The party van experience mashed up you two in Jan of Jackson's control and Sunday Bloody Sunday
bringing you control, bloody control on the Daily Source Code.
Mashed up for your convenience.
Two songs at once have price.
The glitches you heard were not another warning of a bad hard drive.
I accidentally hit I keep a timer running and I have it.
It was a chimoo timer or something which of course is impossible to remember whenever you
want to start it up.
I didn't hit it right when I was, I have to basically act like Nixon's secretary here when I
start the show.
Hit audio hijack pro on one computer and hit the timer and the sound effects.
The starting of the car.
I got to start those at the same time.
Then I have to get my hands on the buttons for that and that effect.
Then I realized in that song that they used the exact same sample in the
Jan of Jackson that car crashes I have here in the Yamaha.
Lovely.
So anyway I was opening and closing Shimoo timer and I gave a little glitch in the audio.
Not that that should happen but oh someone who was it.
I got a great email.
Oh man I got a couple of emails.
I wanted to catch up on today.
I don't have it here off hand.
I'll find out who sent it to me.
On OSX which of course has a Unix base.
You can nice the process.
Meaning you can allocate more processor time to it.
And that really does work.
I just haven't set up.
It's kind of stupid because you can't kind of do it once it's already running.
You have to start the application.
So I'd start megaseg from the command line and you can tell.
This is the beauty of Unix really.
As you can say, hey, give this application more
processor time than the other apps which seems to work very well.
Paul Nichols sent me an email.
This morning he says it's struck me out.
I've been listening to you for one year today.
Is that right? I'm pretty sure it is.
He says it feels so much longer than a year.
I honestly cannot remember listening.
Well it says something else.
I can not remember.
Listen for.
I think he's low life before podcasting.
There we go.
It permeates every conversation and waking thought of mine.
And I have to say I absolutely love it.
Remember you talking about the brand new iPod or an iPod element?
Yeah, that was a while ago, wasn't it?
He says I'm embarrassed to say that it took me two whole months to work out how to record an MP3 file
and how to work out RSS.
Thank goodness things are getting easier for the newbies.
Podcast Paul, right?
Cheers for getting me involved in such a fantastic hobby.
Mate? Well my pleasure.
Absolutely.
I just love it when emails like that come in.
It's so cool the community that we're building here.
And I think it was in San Francisco.
I was talking about free Wi-Fi or using other persons Wi-Fi and that there should be a way
that when you see a node sitting there and lots of people have them just unprotected.
And then plenty of people have them password secured.
So I feel there should be some kind of middle ground there so that you can say,
Hey, you know it's all right if you want to use this bandwidth,
but you should be able to set parameters like, you know,
log in here with a free password and you can use it for an hour
or contact me at this email address if you need more.
And we'll talk about it, right?
That's kind of the social way of doing it.
I said it's social.
So Bob Scott sent me an email.
He said, you know, this is actually pretty simple.
There is a way in the middle.
He says you're idea about allowing controlled access to personal Wi-Fi.
Access point is an interesting one.
I think we're pretty easy to alter the firmware of a wireless router to initially redirect
anyone logging in without a web key as a password to an internal web page.
And that could log there a Mac address.
And that is nothing to do with Apple computers, but with your Ethernet card,
you know, how you communicate with a network, even if it's wireless.
And make them jump through any whoops you like by entering an email address, et cetera, et cetera.
You could limit these guests by bandwidth, by time, connection type,
only HTTP, for example, anything else you want to do.
So it's a great concept when you think about it.
This is very much like when you log into a public access point like TMobile or
or here in the UK BT Open or anywhere, you know, it usually throws up a web page
and you have to enter your payment details, which by the way could also be included in this.
What's cool about it, and this is something I didn't know, is that linksis
have released the source code for their routers under the GPL,
the general public license, or the GNU public license.
So any has all kinds of links and stuff, and there's a source forage project.
But we could actually make this.
And wouldn't it be cool if linksis would then include it in their, in their Wi-Fi routers?
I guess, you know, it's GPL code, so I wouldn't they, why wouldn't they put it in there?
Think about the possibilities. You just have a separate set up panel,
which will be a part of the default when you install the router.
And you can put in stuff like, yeah, anyone can connect to my, to my computer,
but they have to, you know, maybe an email is sent to me to know that someone is doing it,
and they have to enter their email address, so I can contact them,
and we could limit it to, you know, to two hours or an hour or whatever.
That's a really, really good idea.
And interesting, very, very interesting.
And particularly if we can make the kind of standardized and rolled out across all those linksis routers.
Ah, another social project in the making.
Hello.
Hi, to all the Delhi source code listeners.
A big thanks for Adam Curry, allowing me to tell you about a brand new podcast called Ed's Mixed Back.
I'm your host Ed Ovegg.
And if you like all kinds of music, you won't want to miss a single episode.
Every week, we feature a mystery sound contest with prizes.
We're always encouraging your feedback, suggestions, and even MP3 submissions.
Why not go to www.emb.lipsen.com
and download a stream in episode or two of Ed's Mixed Back.
And if you like it, please consider subscribing to get each weekly show automatically on your iPod
or on your PC's hard drive.
Thanks for your time.
And now, back to Adam Curry and the Delhi source code.
Hot show.
Content that will make you squeeze the dog and burp your mother.
The following program is closed captioned for the thinking impaired.
Hey there, pod fans.
This is Christopher Tyler, host of Game Chat Live.
Need your weekly dose of gaming on your way to work or school.
Then tune into Game Chat.
Every week, I inform you of current happenings in the world of console and PC gaming, along with
previous future games and reviews of current ones.
All this is combined with rock and music to help you get through your day.
Check it out at http.
Thanks a lot.
Josa.
Another big community taking advantage of podcasting.
This is funny.
It's funny I was talking to a reporter from the Guardian this morning.
That's a big newspaper here in the United Kingdom.
I guess the story now that this comes in waves and it comes in waves really.
Where the press gets interested in talking about pod casting and they have a different
angle on it each time.
I've seen from what was published just the other day in the Wall Street Journal front page,
actually, as well as from the questioning of this reporter from the Guardian Bobby.
That the angle now is, hey, big business is getting into pod casting because they see
that there's lots of opportunity and listeners in that world.
That's our world.
That's me and you.
Everyone else who's tuned in and listening to pod cast and making pod cast and pod safe music
and having a good time.
That's kind of the angle.
Actually, the reporters are asking the right questions.
They want to know, is can they walk into the space?
Do they know what they're doing?
Is this just about time shifting?
That's the one thing that I just keep coming back to.
Look, we didn't create the demand for this insatiable addiction that people have to pod cast.
That demand was created by an industry that kept competition day by owning frequencies,
towers, and infrastructure.
What is the name of that Danny K movie?
Gosh, damn, I've referred to this many times.
There's a Danny K movie.
I remember very distinctly, and Danny K is the head of a research group and they're sitting
in a university or like a cloister almost.
For years, writing the definitive book on music.
While they're in there writing about Chopin and Bavaldi and Bach and Handel and
you name it, jazz is happening outside.
And the music scene just changed overnight almost, of course, it took a couple of years.
And then Danny K, of course, has this big euphoric moment where he discovers that music hasn't
changed and they're writing the most outdated book that they could possibly think of.
Although history, of course, is important.
I don't want to downplay that.
But what is the name of that movie?
Someone helped me out there.
That's exactly what's happening right now.
And it's not like this doesn't happen.
It's not like, also, music and the music business and the broadcast business.
It never stays the same.
It's always continually evolving.
A broadcasting based on technology improvements.
And music is cultural.
You know, it shifts.
We can't shift very quickly with the way mainstream media operates because of basically.
They just don't have enough channels to get underground currents that are running
along and pick them up and and propel them into something.
And this is very much like, although I wasn't there, Patricia completely agrees with
this analogy.
It's like the 60s.
When FM radio was just starting and there was no business model for it.
It was just wackos playing an hour of songs in the key of G.
And coffee shops and record stores and, you know, back alley clubs.
And we were exchanging music that way and we were building.
You know, we were building our own.
We weren't.
But my parents were Patricia was a man.
You know, being a part of a new sound, new type of music.
You know, and that happens consistently throughout, throughout history.
That's what we're seeing here.
And I'm excited to be a part of that.
Yeah, I'm Gary.
Yeah.
This is Shubi Shubi.
Oh, Shubi.
And I'm a spell check from Potacular.
Have you ever thought of a magazine that would cater to people interested in podcasting as well as podcasters?
Well, me and Shubi think it'd be a great idea for a nice little publication.
Considering that's one of our most favorite things to do is read magazines and podcast.
Basically, what a magazine would do is, since it would be a public magazine, it would get the word out to more people
in a way that iTunes or anything else wouldn't be able to do.
Like, I'll also buy showcasing equipment because that's what they want things.
I really don't know what equipment is available.
And then I'd do a pint like how to better my podcast with better equipment.
And also, just, you know, like with ads, like even publishers podcasts even more with, like, a text ad and a magazine.
Yes.
So, what do you think of this idea?
Can you please, like, tell us, because we think it's an ingenious idea.
We're awfully interested.
Hopefully, hopefully interested.
Spell check.
Thanks, Adam.
Yeah.
Well, first of all, of course, I think you live in America.
You can do anything you want.
You can get your magazine started.
There's enough people who will be interested in that.
I'm sure.
You also might, yeah, I'm kind of torn because you might want to consider becoming a destination on the internet.
If you guys think you can drive a community, then maybe the community will spawn a magazine
that someone will want to have because, you know, there's always a value to print.
It's not like the web is taken over everything.
I buy all kinds of magazines.
I buy flying magazines.
I buy handheld computer magazines, you know, and for a number of reason.
And where I usually buy it when I'm getting on a long haul flight.
It's just a great format.
It's portable.
I love it.
I love the format of print.
It's still nice.
Too bad it's gotten too expensive to, to really do a lot with it.
Good luck guys.
Let me know how it goes.
I'll certainly support you.
Dan Turnbow.
Turnbow.
It says, hey, Adam, love the show.
Been a loyal listener from day one and enjoy podcast so much.
It has changed my life.
First off, if I'm a self listening to very little radio anymore, what I do is fill a one gig.
SD card.
Fill it up.
Listen with my Dell accent while out and about.
Plus, I take all my favorite shows to work with me.
You guys and girls really help pass the time while on the job with me.
I just love the idea of listening to content on my schedule.
And not one of the media wants me to.
But Adam, the biggest change in my life that has come from podcasting is when you turn
beyond to what Don and Drew show said about smoking.
May not see much to many people, but that was the final push I needed to give up cigarettes.
Today I'm happy to say that I've not had a single cigarette since February.
And I really do believe I got them kicked.
If I don't miss them at all here lately.
So I'm closing.
Just want to thank you for changing my life and many others out there.
Well, you of course, you did that yourself.
And I don't think you changed your life.
You saved your life, Dan.
And I wish I had this sound bit.
I didn't have enough time to go through all the archives with February.
You know, it's just that, of course, unfortunately is not a simple thing to do with audio files yet.
But I think it was Don saying that because I, you know, Don and I had talked about smoking.
And she said, oh, I just can't, I can't smoke a cigarette because it was something like smoking a cigarette
just like sucking on the cock of the man and the man being the man.
You know, she says there's so many chemicals in there to get you hooked, keep you hooked.
And it did it for me, man.
I'll tell you, at least for tobacco products.
That's for sure.
This is the daily source code.
Always full of interesting bits, contributions from other people.
My good friend, Jan Poled is here.
Once again, with the hit test for today.
All you casting with Adam Curry.
I suppose you think you never knew the music.
What do you, yeah?
Oh, yeah.
The hit test.
Young Poled.
With your Poled.
Hey Adam, this is a new hit test.
I've been a bit busy and it's going to stay the way for a while.
So I don't know when the next hit test will be.
Fortunately, I found some time to do this right now.
So here we go.
This is number one.
That's so Whitney Houston.
It's Whitney Houston.
It's number two.
Yeah, I got that one.
Depression mode.
People are people.
Good songs.
Good songs, Jan.
Dig it.
And number three.
That's true.
That's level 42.
Hot water.
So I got to remember the Whitney Houston one that I'm good.
And time's up.
And these are the answers.
I know.
How will I know?
Number one is from 86.
It's Whitney Houston.
This is how will I know.
Yeah.
I know.
He's a daughter.
Man, she was great back then.
How will I know?
Just trust your feeling.
Who?
How will I know?
If he really loves me,
I'll lay a friend with every heart beat.
I want to love him ever with me.
I'll have him you.
I'll feel no longer.
If he loves me.
Oh, no.
Answer number one.
Whitney Houston.
What has happened to her?
Great music from the 80s.
Answer number one.
How will I know?
And this is answer number two.
Depression mode.
People are people.
Rather.
Oh, this was the jam back in the day.
But so we'll never recover.
We'll never breathe.
I don't understand.
It's another man.
People are all people.
So what should it be?
You and I should get around.
So what would it be?
People are all people.
So what should it be?
You and I should get around.
Sun from 84.
Depression Mode.
As answer number two.
And this is answer number three for today's hit this.
Number 64.
level 42.
This is underwater.
The hot water.
I feel like an aging rocker.
Marking on bass.
Marking?
1142.
Sensor number 3.
And the song is titled Hot Water.
This concludes hit test number 64.
Again, music from the 80s.
I hope you enjoyed this one Adam and I hope you did well.
As I said earlier, I don't know when the next hit test will be because I'm very busy with different kind of things.
You can read all about them on yompolet.com.jnt.com.
That's also the website you can find info about the hit test.
And hit the spotcast.
And also the iTunes links to all the songs played in the hit test.
As long as they're in the database of iTunes.
And feedback has always is welcome at the address hittest.gmail.com.
Thank you for listening until next time.
Bye-bye.
Thank you, yon.
That was cool, man.
I love that.
Always under 90 seconds of the hits.
By the way, to the show notes maintainers of the show.
I've gotten several complaints.
The show notes are so complete and so good that if you take a look at the show notes before you listen to the show,
then basically the hit test is spoiled.
We have major spoiler action going on with that in the backtrack spotcast.
So perhaps we'll wait a little bit or just put in a link to Yon's weblog.
So that you can get the answers there with another click from the show notes.
And also you can use Yon's iTunes links to purchase the songs that were used in the hit test right from the iTunes music store.
Adam, well I realize that it's not politically correct to mock the afflicted.
Says Darren Wall.
I really, really had a good hard laugh at your screamer frustration at your power book.
You may want to note though, international moment of frustration, scream day is not actually until October 12th.
That's tomorrow.
International moment of frustration, scream day.
Oh, we'll be celebrating that tomorrow, my friends.
It's also the day that Apple has one more thing.
One more thing.
It was funny I was talking to the reporter from the Wall Street Journal who wrote that piece about podcasting.
This is really interesting. She said she had one question for me fact checking basically.
Is it true the podcasting started with trade secrets with you and Dave Wein are doing that show?
And I said, well, no, that's not the genealogy of it.
That's definitely not how it went down or how it happened or there's some important history.
There's some important technological and media history coming together that form podcasting.
And I talked to everybody an hour.
And then you read the Wall Street Journal piece and it says podcasting got a start when trade secrets was on.
It was a podcast that was done by Adam Green Day Wein and I'm like, what the hell is that all about?
But in that same conversation, she was talking about, you know, so this is going towards video.
Sarah, who I spoke to with the Wall Street Journal wrote half the article.
Then I said, well, what are you talking about?
Well, it's the best kept secret that the jobs is announcing the video iPod on Wednesday.
I said, this is the Wall Street Journal. Hello Wall Street Journal I'm talking to.
He said, what, why? Why would they do that? Why would they cannibalize on the nano?
They just released. Just to give me the business reason, besides the fact that I saw the looking Steve Jobs eyes,
where when the video iPod came up in our conversation, he said,
I don't understand it. He says, where's the, where's the content for it?
And where's the headphone equivalent of video? He said, it's just not that.
Build it into a monocle, maybe, and you got something. But, you know, I just saw it.
He doesn't planning on that, you know, and it's, I don't know.
So anyway, the timing of it just makes no sense that it would be a new, a new iPod product.
And I said, you know, based upon the supply lines drying up, which is all over the web.
Everyone's talking about that. I think it's the new power books.
You know, I think it's a new line of pro, pro machines. Oh, really?
She said, oh, just like man, Wall Street Journal. Unbelievable.
This next audio comment that came in really put a smile on my face for a number of reasons.
The one reason is that here's a professional, quote, professional broadcaster, someone who's on the radio.
Here in the UK, the BBC, I recognize the name and I certainly recognize the voice.
Who has discovered the wonders of podcasting?
And we talked about filters, you know, when you're on the broadcast license radio or television,
where whatever you say, you're running it through a certain number of filters that are essentially helping you
to not spew out nasty words. That's an easy filter because we use that all the time in life.
But also political filters, what you can and cannot say that might hurt the network or other priorities that the network has.
And MTV, there was a, you know, we had a lot of that, but it also wasn't live so it was much easier.
And we said a lot of really rancid shit that we just got burned off.
And some of those tapes exist, but our frustration level was pretty high.
Listen to this, you know what I'm talking about.
Hi Adam, it's Lynn Parsons here and listening to the source code last week, I heard you mention the difference between podcasting
and working for a big corporation like the BBC or a big commercial radio station.
And I thought I'd give you my take on it simply because I've been doing just that for the past 18 years and yet I've done nine podcasts now.
And it is such fun. It's freedom with a capital F, you can play whatever you like.
And although I get a lot of bands send me unsigned music, the pod safe music network is just a wealth of treasures.
There's some really good music on it. And when I come to do the show, I just feel that I've had so much input and, you know,
picking the music is just such a big change because of course when you go to work for the BBC or you work for a commercial radio station,
you're given a playlist and you have to stick to it or you get a call from the boss.
And this is cool. This is such a fun. And if you'd like to check the show out, it's Lynn Parsons.net.
And thank you Adam because the reason I'm doing this is because I had a source code about 10 weeks ago and just fell in love with it.
Lynn, now let me say a couple things about this. First of all, Lynn Parsons well known over here, great voice. I love that voice.
You know, she could just read the phone book to me with that accent with that voice and I like the way your voice is recorded.
I don't know where she's recording that. She's doing it at home or if she's maybe hijacking a BBC studio, but it sounds great.
And there you have it. It's, you know, listen to a professional broadcaster enjoying life.
You know, hey, I get to pick the music. Isn't that a fucking surprise? Fantastic, Lynn.
And I just, I just love your voice. You know, we got a lot of great podcasts in the world.
Thousands of fantastic ones. And once in a while you get the combination of a great show, a great entertainment or
infotainment or information, whatever you want to call, and a great voice.
And Lynn is definitely one of those combinations. We welcome you, Lynn, into our world.
If you were just read the alphabet to me, then I'd, I'd open the door to the backyard and I'd have the little combo sitting out there.
Say, Lynn, why don't you just start at eight and go all the way to Z.
And dance with me here.
My dear, I'm crazy for you. I don't know what I should do. Stay here or follow you on home.
I'll make you look for a kiss from your sweet tender lips.
I'll either have your start too long.
Because I can't be around you and be with you.
If you refuse to come with me, I'll go at a long.
I'm waiting for the day when I can finally see you.
My dear, I'm thankful for me.
Because I can't be around you and be with you.
If you refuse to come with me, I'll go at a long.
I'm waiting for the day when I can finally see you.
My dear, I'm thankful for me.
Robin Stein, sweet blossom from the Pod Safe Music Network, my friend.
I went to PMN as we call it Internally Pod Safe Music Network this morning.
What I usually do is I log in.
I look at the most recent additions and there was a whole bunch from Robin Stein.
She just uploaded her stuff.
This was the first song I hit.
It's a blossom.
I'm actually looking at the Pod Safe Music Network right now.
I'm looking at the Bio Info.
Sweet blossom, there you go.
On our debut album, David Robin Stein bruised up a genre-bending blend of original jazz
and bluesy folk tunes with sultry and chanting vocals.
Sometimes it's playful, sometimes haunting melodies.
Her songs sound as if they've...
Sorry, edit that.
Her songs sound as if they're straight out of a smoke-filled room in Tin Pan Alley.
She's like, oh yeah.
She's from Florida.
Very, very cool.
I play that for Patricia.
She's like, oh yeah.
This is good.
The whole thing is good.
It's nothing wrong with it.
That's good.
It's totally Patricia approved.
And I told her about the unlabel that we...
Well, yes, I think we went further than fully considering starting this label.
But we actually came up with some fantastic concepts of the unlabel.
What is a record label that's not a record label?
Well, we had some really interesting thoughts about that.
Yes, they run and I were doing our daily chat.
He's getting the bagels for the office in the morning and it's afternoon here.
We always have our morning catch-up chat.
And now I just love it.
Love it.
Great concept that we basically got to find a couple people now to help us get it up and running.
Because it's yet another piece.
But it's such an important piece.
And it feels so right.
And everyone should be able to contribute to the unlabel, you know, whether you're an artist or not.
And that's, you know, that's our concept all along.
And you hear how Lynn totally rocks the Podsack music network.
This is exactly what it's about.
It's about creating...
This is the coffee shops and the record stores and the...
And the wacky FM radio of the 60s.
This is what we're doing.
We're creating our own superstars through our own networks.
And we can actually build that network.
In that fantastic.
Let me see.
Well, how much time do we have?
Oh, I've got some time left.
Along those lines, you owe the Tassalo.
I'm sure I'm buttering that name.
Send me an email about a new European Union copyright law.
Adam is a very strange law which is being introduced in the EU countries.
I'm not sure if it's been ratified by all the countries yet.
This is the way the EU works.
But at least in Finland has done it.
Finland is Scandinavia.
Yeah.
First of all, the law says that a consumer is not allowed to copy music that he or she owns for personal purposes such as backups.
That's indeed that's pretty new.
Not allowed to copy it even for your own personal purposes like backups.
The other thing the law says which freaks me out is that it's illegal to sell or donate a book, CD, DVD, etc.
Which has been purchased from outside the European Union to another person.
This makes it possible for companies to have local monopolies.
In same prices for the European markets and in Perenz that this is what American companies already do.
So a couple of examples, a person who owns a record store is allowed only to sell CDs which have been published in the EU.
The store may not import rare CDs from other countries such as the USA, Japan, and sell them.
And this is all protectionism, dude.
So that's an interesting law.
If anyone may be Paul, I think he's a lawyer.
Maybe if anyone can look at that and see what the deal is.
It's kind of like the region codes with DVDs.
Boy, is that a pain in the ass?
I even once bought a blank CD.
Even blank CDs are region coded.
You can't play a blank CD you purchase in Europe on a regular playback machine in the US.
It's crazy.
Telling it's crazy.
It looked at the world and wondered how things got to be the way they are.
My name is Matt DeTillow and it's my mission to help you answer that question.
And maybe even launch you on your own journey of discovery.
My podcast, Matt's Today in History, is a short look at the historical events of the day.
You can find our feed at matstodayinhistory.com or in iTunes.
We're standing on yesterday.
Learn something about it with Matt's Today in History.
This is Roger Linder, Tom Castermaster at theTRconnection.com.
And you're about to get familiar with Todd Redburn.
That's not bad.
Oops. Take two.
The Todd Caster is a podcast for fans.
It's an easy-to-be-band.
You might hear from anybody who is a Todd Redburn fan.
Who is Todd Redburn?
If you're asking that question, then this is the podcast for you.
Certainly you've heard.
Hello, it's me.
Or maybe.
Or perhaps.
Then you say, oh, now I know Todd Redburn.
But if that's all you know, then you don't know Todd Redburn.
And you must check out this Todd Caster.
Like the blues.
Heavy rock.
Followed by a light, pretty melon.
Need a history lesson?
Or maybe an English lesson.
Then subscribe to the TR Connections Todd Caster.
You'll find it at TRconnection.com slash Todd Caster.
The Todd Caster, kind of like a little mini hit test mashup all by its own.
Todd Brownman is a pretty good guy.
Actually to help us move the Podship music network forward.
He controls a lot of actually I think it just wields still some weight in the music industry.
He's always seen as a leader out on the front of technology and willing to jump into the fray and give his art up for making the world better.
And by the way, I think that you're pretty safe having read through all the licenses of Ask Captain BMI.
I think that we're pretty safe under a fair use clause.
If you're using less than 60 seconds, I think it's actually less than 90 seconds.
But, you know, please don't get into the legalities of it.
Then, you know, if you're using that to make a point or to accentuate something, it's not like putting up an MP3 in the clear as they say in big media world in the clear.
Or, you know, it being possible for someone to go in and edit out the song.
You know, if you don't actually provide all the source material, then there's, you know, there's not much to do there.
So I think you're pretty, pretty, pretty good with fair use.
And it sounds like this is, I haven't actually listened to the podcast. I kind of like the promo and went along with the conversation of a, a pod save music.
So the Todd cast.
Interesting play on words.
Okay. One more piece of pod save music, which was sent to me via email.
You know, pod save music comes in all forms, all sizes, all shapes, which includes country and blue groups.
And I'm sure this was sent along the lines of the Ed Wright, Wayne Wright, Ed Wright computer computer song that I played last Sunday with Patricia.
This is Tim O'Brien.
And he's got his own computer problems.
What an out of memory.
When I got him, he may have found you darling.
It said, you said me a file.
Was it for the picture?
J fake for me.
But I'm never got to see you smile.
I thought of what you might be wearing.
Just then I served the software from.
I tried rebooting, tried compression.
But it would not have been passed, you know.
My car screen mode even function.
It's one big solid fuel of blue.
My hard driving itself.
My application code.
And I run it out of memory for you.
It said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said
you said you said, you said, you said said, you said, don't you say, you said, you said, don't you say, you said, you said, you said, you just said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, it said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said yes, you said, that, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said, you said,
And I'm running out of memory for you
My cursed streetboat, even function
It's a wonderful field of blue
My heart driving itself, my application caught
And I'm running out of memory for you
From the world of pot-safe music, my friends
So what I forgot to tell you about is that Patricia liked this idea so much
She said, well, I want to sign up, I want to join
I want, she can't, can I do an album? Anything I want?
It's an absolutely absolutely
She said, well, Ron, do the arrangements? I said, I don't know
So you got to talk to the man about that
She said, I want to sign up, I want to join
She said, can I do an album? Anything I want?
It's an absolutely absolutely
Talk to the man about that, but this is so exciting
I just have not had this much fun
20 years, I'm really, really digging it
Okay, if you're hearing the show for the first time
It's called the Daily Source Code
There's a show every single week day
Unless I get busy doing something else when life gets in the way
And you can subscribe to the podcast
Go to dailysourcecode.com
To find the podcast feed and all the information that you need
For your previous episodes and find out more about me go to curie.com
Say, min email feedback, anything you want, add them at curie.com
If you're sending off an MP3 file, please stick it up on a server
Put it somewhere where I can get to it easily from a web browser
And add those ID3 tags, it really makes a difference
These promos float out there, you know, people use that information
So it's a handy if you do
All right, everybody, we'll be back tomorrow with the thank god
It's Wednesday edition
The source code, take care now
Another pod show podcast, stick it in your ear