Transmators, we don't need no stinking transmitters.
Did this is one DJ?
You don't want to f**k with honesty.
It's embarrassing.
It's humb day.
It's Wednesday, everybody.
How you doing?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That's right.
March 16, 2005.
Welcome to the Daily Source Code coming to you
from a sun-bathed curry cottage.
Man, it's beautiful today.
I can see for miles and miles and miles.
Got the windows wide open here on the studio
and we're ready for about 40 minutes of fun.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, yes.
Got some cool things to play for you today.
Gonna talk a little bit about radio.
Gonna talk about world calm.
We've got an extremely not safe for work cover version
of an excellent song.
And of course, we've got a hit test.
I'm recording a little bit on the early side.
I can't, I just couldn't wait any longer.
Michael Butler is not due to be up and about until,
for about another hour and a half.
So what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna pre-tape that once he comes online.
We finally set a date for hit test number 21.
Maybe that was 22.
Anyway, it's the, it's the guitar metal intro's one.
Okay, I've been following OpenPodcast.org,
which is kind of my, my radio station, if you will,
during the day, I have it hooked up
so that whenever something new comes through on OpenPodcast.org
it just gets queued up in my,
my iTunes playlist.
And the stuff that comes through there is just,
just how rages as old conversations going on.
And something I came across, actually,
was sent to me an email as well.
Let me just pull up the outline here.
Of course, all of this is in the show notes for today's podcast.
Yeah, recording, perfect.
Hey Adam, with your years of experience,
you've got natural rhythm,
so I spent a couple hours in front of a ACID studio.
What is that AC?
Oh, acid.
In front of acid studio, I guess,
this is two years of form of software.
ACID studio, I'm sorry, being a dick.
Some of the clips that I chose weren't necessarily the most flattering,
but I did it with love.
Remember the worst thing about being in radio was when the production manager sat me down
to go over my air check each week.
He pointed out all of my stumbles and bumbles,
but I always thought those bumbles were part of my charm.
Exactly.
That's what Patricia used to do to me all the time.
It's when you stumble and bumble.
That's when you become a human for a second,
for just a nanosecond.
So here it is, Scott Fletcher's Adam's groove mix
as broadcast slash podcast on openpodcast.org.
On your power book, it's function,
or on your regular key, it's the control key.
or I don't want to do it.
Shoot.
I just want you to know that.
He drives and we talk.
I don't want to do it.
Shoot.
This is worth it.
I'm doing it.
Rain.
I'm almost out.
Shoot.
What's up?
It's just an hour.
Shoot.
I'm almost out.
I'm almost out of time.
Shoot.
I love having that.
I use that all the time.
I'm almost out.
Shoot.
No.
Shit.
We're the only way.
Shoot.
Form automated.
Filin' forms.
I get it.
Shoot.
I want to say how I do it.
I get it.
I'll take you to the top of the page all the way.
You can take, the top of the page all the way.
It can rotate, um.
Can rotate.
Now I just need to find out how I can actually, um.
You get, you get my drift there.
Um, let's see.
Ah!
Of course.
Remember Ribball Day?
Yeah, probably has an MP3 player.
It's the...
on your power, this function, or on your regular kids,
the control key, the control key, the control key,
the control key, the control key, the control key.
So anyway, and a more good news,
it's actually cheaper if you want to know what this is all about.
You want to know this way to complicated and discuss.
Let's take it some more about, to come over to our side.
You got to listen to the whole thing.
No, I just...
That is the answer.
It's just a great place to get stuff.
No, this is an excellent way to do it.
No, I just need...
Hey, guess what?
No, I just...
reagis all the...
No, I just absolutely...
No, I just...
I don't know, I just...
It just wants you to know that.
Uh...
...
Just like we were in a freaking movie with like...
...This is like a movie set.
My life is like a movie set, which I installed myself, right?
I don't think that's gonna work.
Nothing works anymore.
Bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo, god.
This is sad.
Uh-huh.
It's very frustrating for him, I'm sure.
Well, why doesn't he just use the iPod?
Okay.
The Adam's groove mix.
It's the ego filler for the day.
God love it.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
That's...
You can find that an open podcast that it works.
It's number one, three, four, eight.
Amazing.
One thousand, three hundred, four, eight podcast.
Been pumped through that already.
That's pretty cool.
Okay.
Um, so again, about, about today's weather.
It's, uh, it's giving me a real, real drive towards flying today.
Let me tell you.
Um, and, uh, next week, I'm actually gonna go on another, uh,
I think, uh, maybe I can convince the wind commander to fly me or let me fly over the...
Uh, over the, uh, over the canal.
Um, that would be the channel, I mean, uh, between the mainland and the UK.
So maybe, uh, I'm gonna go to Antwerp on, see, maybe Tuesday,
and then maybe fly back Wednesday or whatever.
I mean, I'm training really, really hard, uh, because somewhere in June,
I will be doing my test for my PPL.
And it has to happen in the States, because I have, I'm doing an FAA certification.
So, uh, looking forward to that.
And then maybe, maybe we'll actually do that podcast from the air.
It's just that we're training so hard.
There's no time to concentrate on talking to you guys.
You basically just have to sit there and listen to, uh,
to William take me through all the motions, berating me.
And it's kind of funny, though, the way he, the way he teaches is he's really, uh,
he's like, uh, he's like, uh, when he's burning, guys.
Come on, man.
I've gotta push the metal to metal is what we need.
So maybe we'll do that next week.
Doug Ritter sent me an email.
He says, um, Adam, let's step into the time machine.
And pretend Christina was actually born Christopher,
which is interesting because that was the name we would have chosen
if Christina had been a boy.
Would you let Chris, do you want to know why, by the way?
Uh, the reason why is because, uh,
Christina was conceived at Christmas time.
And we, we know this for a fact due to careful,
um, archival work of my wife.
He could calculate it precisely back to Christmas.
And it was a loving moment underneath the dinner table.
It was just the do of us that didn't matter.
Anyway, so let's step into that time machine.
Present, pretend Christina was actually born Christopher.
Would you let Christopher stay at Michael Jackson's house with all the, uh,
all the, actually he, he opened it up by saying, um,
you know, this is, uh, you know,
so this is the real question that you should be asking yourself.
And I replied to him, Doug and Philadelphia said,
you fucking crazy.
You know, I wouldn't let my wife stay at Michael Jackson's house.
I don't let my daughter stay, you know,
even at her friend's house, it takes me, you know,
I want to meet the parents.
I want to know what's going on.
I want to know where they're going to be sleeping.
You know, of course not.
I mean, that's just a stupid of these parents to, you know,
to, or cunning as you will, um,
you know, just, there's your answer.
No, of course not.
There's no reason to.
Absolutely no reason.
But that still doesn't mean that Michael Jackson is guilty
just because he's fucking wacky or he's perceived as wacky
because when I met him, he wasn't that wacky.
Yeah, no more wacky than anyone else in show business.
Um, but, you know, innocent until proven guilty.
And that goes for court gestures as well,
at least last time I checked the law I did.
I've been getting some, um,
comments about, uh, this blip at the beginning of each show,
which, of course, I'm hearing it as well.
You'll know that, um, I've moved over to using the iRiver iFP799
as my mastering device.
So essentially everything that happens here in the studio at the cottage,
uh, winds up going through a little cable into the iRiver
and I actually stick my headphones into the iRiver.
So I can hear what's really being recorded.
I can hear the levels and everything.
So I think that that's getting much better.
Um, but for some reason, when I turn on the recording,
and this doesn't happen.
I played back on the iRiver, but only when it converts to an MP3,
you hear this little, this irritating, like, digital burp at the beginning.
And I think there's a way to set up the iRiver,
so that it won't start recording until it receives a signal.
Um, but of course, I don't have the manual anymore.
You know, that got tossed out with the box.
Um, and I can't quite figure out how to do that anymore.
So it's a certain key or button combination.
So if you know how to do that, let me know.
And I'll try that and see if that makes a difference.
Because it is totally annoying.
The only way to fix it would be to, uh,
essentially, uh, export the MP3 and recompress it again after it's already recorded and cut off that one bit.
Yeah, I'm not really looking forward to that.
And I think that, you know, once we go from the iRiver format to MP3 from MP3 to AIFF from AIFF to MP3,
God knows what's going to be left over.
And so another irritating thing is this buzz that I found in my microphone.
Lots of email came in, it came in about that.
And I don't want to demonstrate this again.
You can't hear the buzz now.
I'm trying to mic us loud as possible.
Now when I turn the microphone a little bit towards the ceiling,
you'll hear the buzz come in.
I'll listen to this.
There it is.
And I discovered, uh, today.
So I'm turning it back down.
I'm discovered today that I have the same with microphone two here in the studio.
I'm going to open that one up.
Oh, actually it's not buzzing at all right now.
Let's see. Oh yeah, it's not buzzing now,
but when I turn it towards the window,
let me turn down mic one.
Okay, so that's mic two.
Listen, as I turn it towards the window.
There it is again.
So it actually stayed on.
It actually stayed at the same, uh,
yeah, it was horizontal.
But as I move it towards the window, it starts the buzz.
Now I got all kinds of email and I really appreciate it.
Uh, email saying, you know, do you have fluorescent light in your office?
Uh, no.
I don't have fluorescent light.
Do you have dimmers?
Yes, I've got a million fucking dimmers throughout the entire goddamn house.
Uh, and by the way, I agree with the philosophy that Patricia has.
Women over 15 need dim lighting.
And quite honestly, guys over 40 can benefit from that as well in multiple ways.
So yeah, there's lots of dimmers.
Um, every, I've tried it with everything off, everything on full blast.
I've turned the whole house off.
Um, one thing that came in that I thought was pretty plausible was that it was probably coming from my monitor.
And I have, um, one of those apple, uh, cinema displays are my desktop.
The mics are pretty close to it.
Although the mic, this mic two hours just, uh, demonstrating to you.
I'm actually moving it away from that monitor when it picks up.
So I really don't know what it is until, until I received this.
This is a message for the light form known as Adam Curry.
This is Jill L from the planet VW7.
The button sounds you have been getting in your equipment recently are actually secret messages from space.
Didn't you notice they get louder when you point your microphone through the stars?
Actually, it's becoming very frustrating.
Every time you get new equipment, we have to recalibate hours.
And you seem to buy new equipment every week.
Stop it.
It's becoming very tedious.
Anyhow, what we've been trying to tell you is to go to www.nogagruplex.com
and listen to the bugcast.
After all, Volkswagen New Beetles are actually spacecraft for our invasion, uh, our tourist industry.
So the next time you see a Volkswagen Beetle on the road, smile and wave.
Or we will destroy you.
Once again, listen to the NoGagruplex.com bugcast.
This is Joe L signing off.
Alright, hold on.
I was waiting for you guys.
Let me see if I can do this.
Uh, let me just get the preset there.
Hello?
Let me see if I can get this to work.
Oh, man.
I had it all set up.
How can we done the work now?
Wait, maybe I have to go up to three.
Hello?
No, that's not it.
Hold on.
Oh, dude.
I was so ready for this too.
Okay.
Let's try it.
Let's see if we can turn it off.
Hello?
Hello, bloodcast.
Congrats from reinforced with Victor Dean.
This is YOUR leader talking.
You will follow our directions, I'll give you with us.
Arne Dolane is gorgeous.
Alright.
Now of course it won't switch that.
Oh hold on let me see I can set everything back to the way it was okay how's that now I'll just buy
pastel deal with that later okay I always fund the play with the new equipment I love
teasing you guys with it. I'll talk about radio for a second. I've been a radio guy since I
was really well it really since I was like six years old my parents gave me my first
Sony transistor radio was an FM radio. Wait was it FM? I think it was just AM actually. It
wasn't AM little square transistor radio and I used to put it under my pillow and listen
to like basketball games and that was the thing I could really receive the most and what
I remember most from my youth as listening to basketball games under the with the radio under
my pillow and then waking up with the blasting you know with the full blast of my parents
basically fumbling to try and turn it off. And when I was 14 I started building my own transmitters
from based on the radio shack 100 projects in one box and I would have my mom drive around
the block to see how far it would go. Before you knew what I had an antenna and before you
knew that I had built a little mixer and I was mixing records and you know people around
the block were basically able to listen to a show that I did which was totally legal but
it was pretty harmless. But that's really what radio is about. It's about communities
and when I was 15 I went to work it was not an unpaid job as a volunteer gig for radio
tulipa which was located in the tulip hospital in Omsalphane about 15 miles from where
I lived and several times a week I'd go there after hours and you know I would do well
I started off as an engineer only and then later went on to to do some hosting stuff.
And we'd literally go walk through all the wards and all the private rooms and we get
everyone you know to fill out request forms and we see you want to come down and watch
a show and we had a big auditorium next to the studio and we wheeled the beds down and
we tried to make a party for these people and that was also in in a way it's community and
then I started working for pirate radio in Amsterdam at Dacey Bell, decibel radio which was
we were on 72 hours per week in the weekend only and it was the rhythm of the capital
of the Netherlands. Of course we consider Amsterdam to be the capital not with the government
it's but it's the capital and it was extremely extremely popular in the early 80s again
and not so much about the reach you know we could only really hit Amsterdam but we had Amsterdam
it was our fricking town you know when I was in the hospital I had those patients it was our audience
so that's very much what what web logs felt like when they first came around feedback loops
another great thing about radio is you have instantaneous feedback through telephones that's what
most radio stations based on used to be you know mail in a postcard or letter or whatever now
of course we've got email and really direct feedback loops but it's really about you know the
connection between the person running the board if you will who's on the air at that moment
who's running the show whatever type of show it is and that audience that's out there I think
what what started I also of course is based on cheap distribution radio distribution is relatively
simple you know unless you're trying to reach the entire country and you need a huge network of
stations you know essentially you can get a station going just like it sounds kind of shitty
within the while I set the mic actually I had my settings here hold on
hope you're on my me doing this on your time let me just make sure I had
all my settings right so those two were like that that was a little bit lower this was set
comfort well oh that sounds nice all of a sudden and it that's a little bit on the loud side
so maybe a little bit less there this was set up there we go that was also set up so I can open
that a little more sorry about all this that was set to there that was set up like there and that
was like there two two let's just see if we have a little bit of echo okay perfect oh there we go
and I'd saved it so carefully in memory and I was supposed to let me just just save that now into
memory I'd done it so perfectly I thought right okay sorry so we'll get back to the radio stuff here
um cheap distribution that's what I was talking about totally you know every college in America
I can basically have a 10 watt you know sun up the sun down FM transmitter that basically will
broadcast to the the community that being the school and whatever community is you know surrounds
the school which of course I'm trying to tighten up my mic stand here involves local commerce
that probably caters to the community which would be the students decentralized you know that's
kind of the kind of we've seen the opposite of that take place in radio in the last couple of years
but if you ever been to a radio station I'm not talking about a major market in New York
or Los Angeles or you know a big P1 market radio station P1 by the way stands for priority one
so that means it's one of the stations people will hit first when they get into the car and hit
the preset buttons then you've probably seen that it's usually you know an office
an office suite with the cubby when that cubby holes with the so we're not looking for cubicles
and there's a station manager a sales manager who is probably also the
promotions manager at the same time then you might have a music
director it's probably the program director I mean it's only three or four people that can really run a
station like this because it's just not a lot of money in it and and if you've ever seen these
studios it looks like shit you know they're uh they're beat up uh overused uh studios that are
just you know that just don't cost a lot of money to really put together because radio once you've
got your basics you know it's the more listeners you get the more money you're gonna make that's
all then it's just into comes down to promotions which of course a bit coming incredible art in
promoting it now here's what I think what happened with radio where it started to go wrong
I believe that just as with television by the way certainly in the United States
advertisers started to figure out intuitively that the numbers don't add up the numbers that radio station
say they have in listeners and boy they're graded something they call extrapolation they can extrapolate
numbers in radio just to an uncanny level with you know educated men who listen for three seconds per
day you know you get credit in the ratings if someone remembers your disjockeys name or the name of the
show and it's just all these these little blue poles and things that basically help you get some numbers
on paper but doesn't really add up to what the advertisers were seeing in return on investment
of money spent and this is just based upon my experience in in the business and what I've seen
and what I think so it's not necessarily fact but I really have a strong belief that this is what
happened so we had to get more return on the investment for the advertisers and what works in that
case is repetition that's what a lot of marketing is repetition repetition repetition you're going to
remember the jingle or the slogan or the sign or whatever logo it is that is repeated in as
many places as possible now of course that's not very cost effective that is only for the big boys
for the big brands who really need a shotgun approach or use a shotgun approach and can
basically get away with it so I think that what we're seeing what we saw first with web logs
is a complete understanding of what this could be by radio people I saw web logs in a
quite a minute this is the broadcasting I was always thinking about on the internet only we can't
do it with audio and video yet we're going to do it this way and you can still get an incredible
reach in fact if you go back a couple of years when the very first aggregator came out in radio
userland I actually bought a position in that aggregator so that I would be in the default
install because I knew that if I could just get in and I would be default somewhere that people
basically would just leave it there and hopefully I could you know create enough compelling
content that that it would be interesting and people would not unsubscribe or at least they wouldn't
find it irritating to get rid of the subscription but I knew that we had this broadcast mechanism
for small communities but instead of it being communities of geography we are going we started
with web logs looking at communities of interest and interest being a number of things you know
could be just the interesting yourself yeah I'm interested myself I write about myself
people who want to know about me you can find out about me what we saw a lot of people
become experts on particular topics start web logs about those topics and actually become
quite successful because once Google recognizes you through page ranking that you're an expert on
a particular topic you're going to get all the search results to your web log and you know that's
why we're looking at gadget you know those guys are doing exactly exactly that and their community
is going to be quite large because gadgets is a large community so now that we have podcasting
I believe that we're at least if we want to look at the aspect of who you're addressing it's the
same thing it's exactly the same thing as radio um you're talking to a community of interest
it doesn't have to be very large you have your direct feedback loop you have your distribution
mechanism and if you so choose then you can also run commerce through that in exactly the same way
that it's being done with radio songs live happy to show I'm on say
man it's not noisy outside the studio today so without all the repetition I don't think it's
necessary because you've you've got your pretty qualified audience subscribe to the show you know
so they're going to be waiting to to hear about products and services that will make sense to them
so you know you you want to try and pick and choose what what you're going to be advertising
of course arguably your entire audience may want to cook or Pepsi so that's that's something to
consider um man it is kind of noisy it's like all kinds of air traffic today
damn all right so back to the podcast see it as everyone having a transmitter even though we
don't even know stank and transmitters not everybody has to make money not everybody wants to make
money and guess what very very few people if anybody will make the kind of money that we've seen
in the previous broadcast distribution world I mean once you can lock something out or it's
like someone out or you know make the distribution only available to those who have frequencies etc
and transmitters then you can charge much more so we're on a on a very level playing field all
of a sudden where it's going to come down to quality and how business like you are if you want to
make a business out of this and there's nothing stopping anybody but there's also nothing forcing
anybody into doing that so anyway so um I got to say and that props to Dave on this one when he
came out with radio user land which was one of the I think the first first desktop web blog tool
content management system um immediately I said what this makes so much sense and I don't think
anybody got it I think as it's probably around the Napster time as well people are thinking about so
what are you going to do trade songs and stuff like that and you know I don't think anyone was really
understanding what he meant at the time but it really is with its publishing subscribe mechanism it
really is a radio you know it's it's exactly what we're talking about here um now if we can only
just bake some of this stuff into uh into the iPods or MP3 players and when we've been through that
many times it will be beautiful so anyway that's my bit about radio for today we call it radio
we call it podcasting whatever you want to call it it's about communities bigger small and depending on
your type of community that will depend on where you can go with it so I kind of a
little bit of good news well not really good news but Bernie Ebers is it Bernie Ebers who is the
CEO of WorldCom who was apparently at least partly responsible for the collapse of WorldCom
and subsequently one of the largest bankruptcy filings in US corporate history I guess he was
convicted of fraud 11 billion dollars worth of it and I have to say that one of my companies
the data barn was also affected by non-payments from WorldCom so enjoy your stay in jail Mr Ebers
enjoy your stay. Warning the following song which is not a mashup it's actually something that
would be probably even better for cover real is without a doubt not say for work you may not notice
it immediately but trust me
start to momma they want to run momma mix up and cook them up in a pot of light and gumbo go
it off on a mother fucker like that with a gap that's pointed at your eyes to give it up smooth
you know tell them when I'm down for a jack move here's a murder rap to keep your dancing
well crime record like Charles men to my AK 47 is a tool don't make me act another fucking fool
maybe you can go tell you tell them maybe I'm not getting it good out the box daily weekly
yeah monthly and you the until down down mother fuckers equally that I'm down with a capital CPT
you can fuck with me so when I'm in your neighborhood you better duck because ice cube
is crazy as fuck as I live believe I'm stopping but when I come back for I'm coming straight out
come in straight out of Compton you know Gordon on the source code I love cover versions
like that you know it just goes to show that a good song is a good song is a good song
two new iPod or categories uh putting today and there's a lot more in the queue and also
if you've submitted for any of the categories we're running about four to five days behind right now
some of the categories are are almost immediate but this thing is just growing exponentially which
of course is the way it's set up to grow we have a transportation node now and we have an automotive
node so be sure to check those out on ipodder.org and great news about Lars Ulrich from Metallica
he is actually working on bringing Metallica which is the great mashups between the beetles and
Metallica I should have not even a mashup it's a it's a group playing nice voice mail actually
let me bring up the story here I have a link to it in my uh in my notes home on
I'll bring up the web page and I can actually read bits of it to you because this is uh this was
pretty messed up we actually played some Metallica on on the source code a while back oh man what is this
why is it opening up safari hold on a second I wanted to open up oh man this is not going the way
I wanted to hold on so it's these beetle songs which have been modified in Lyric and obviously
in musical content to sound more like Metallica was doing them hold on let me I've got the
I've got the URL now is he pasted in here we go I was on Boeing Boeing Boeing Boeing dot net here we go
Mr. Lyric Ulrich no stranger to matters of intellectual property law on the internet
we'll get to that piece in a second here we go
Okay as reportedly as reported previously on Boeing Sony music accused
Metallica of violating copyright laws demanded their webmaster pay unspecified damages
and force the bands eyes p to shut down the website but now Lars has volunteered to provide assistance
with legal negotiations for Metallica and asked Metallica's long-time attorney p
paterno to try and diffuse the situation with Sony on behalf of the dudes from Milwaukee so Sony is now
agreed to drop the case which is interesting that Lars is helping out five years ago the story goes on
he stood on the steps of Napster hauling boxes full of 300,000 names all people who said we're
using Napster to steal Metallica tunes but things have changed that debate was about who
profited from Metallica's music he says this one and check this out is about creative rights
at the heart of rock and roll itself. Lars says he believes that cover bands, mashups and the
right to reinterpret art on the internet are things worth fighting for. I'm right I like that you know
where's I with a little down on Lars in the boys this is very very cool so it looks like
I don't know if we're actually going to be able to play Metallica songs anymore but I certainly
would love to.
I got a lot of with y'all, Poles. Okay come on in y'all. Hi Adam I've got another hit there's three of
excellent. I don't think it's too difficult so let's go right away this is number one
hammer. One more time. Oh yeah on this like some horrible stock aching and waterman thing is
I like regassely or something that's and number two is a bit shorter. Once again.
I recognize that piano riff anywhere Chicago stay the night. Ooh within time even.
And this is number three. What's that? That sounds like cool in the gang. The bad drum drum roll
the beginning of every cool in the gang. All right y'all hit me with the answer.
What the answer? Answer number one in today's hit test. It's an oldie and it brings back memories
even for me this is Alicia and baby talk. I told you some bad stock aching and waterman life for
no
answer number two. All right this is Chicago state and I knew I'd get that one really.
Bung I don't want you necessarily
She got it and I can't remember if this is the video clip where there's a car going through
the board.
That's it.
I can't remember.
This is great song.
That one I would certainly.
And to number three.
Cool.
That's cool.
Straight ahead.
I didn't even know the title.
They all start out that way.
And so number three, cool and the gang and straight ahead.
Well I hope you did well Adam.
I'll try to keep looking for tricks to use in the hit this.
Well that's it for today.
As always, feedback is welcome at hitestatgmail.com, you can find this hitest and the hitest
podcast.
And young polette.nl, that's JNPL, ET, that's NL.
So let's see you next time, Adam for a new edition of the hitest, that's it.
Thank you very much.
A young, pretty interesting guy.
You should listen to his hitest podcast if you have a chance.
He's got a pretty interesting background in history.
Well worth it.
And that's it for the source code.
Four Wednesday, March 16th, 2005, we back tomorrow with the update, remember Friday going
to London.
I'm going to be interviewed by the BBC for click online and also doing a interview for Dutch
news television program.
So we'll probably do a sound seeing tour and that's coming Friday.
And I'm taking my bride with me because it's always fun to go to London together.
Comment down at curie.com or on the weblog www.curie.com.
They give a comment about the podcast.
Specifically, of course you can head over to dailysourceco.com for the archives, the latest
show and the podcast.
As if for me I'll be back tomorrow.
Take care everybody.
Bye bye.