Daily source code from Monday may 9th 2005.
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who managed what you can hear since
radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
With $60 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation radio
content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Hi, this is Rachel from audiocollective.net.
You're listening to Adam Curry on the Daily Source code.
Everybody it is Monday the 9th of May 2005.
Oh yeah, brand new setup couldn't resist over the weekend, been playing around with
all kinds of different stuff and yeah, low and behold we have lift off, got new software
that I'm trying out.
It's running across two computers and so far I'm pretty happy.
There's of course as you can see I'm doing my nails at the same time I'm doing this
podcast.
Hey, I hope you had a great mother's day if you're a mom or if you're a son or a daughter.
Hope you called your favorite mom.
We'll be talking about that today on the show.
Of course, hot-save music on the way, got a mash up lined up for you, plenty of promos
and some news from around, just around you know, stuff that I've been doing.
I'm actually standing up doing the show today which is news.
The setup doesn't fit in the green thing.
Yesterday, Patricia and I did a podcast together.
We hijacked a daily source code feed so I apologize in advance.
I apologize in hindsight.
I think I did apologize in advance actually that it was a complete Dutch language podcast.
It was something we talked about doing actually about a week and a half ago what I was
in the States.
There's so many gossip magazines writing so much crap about us.
I said, you know, why don't we do a podcast and we'll just talk amongst ourselves, you know,
the real truth.
You know, just us, you and me baby, turned out great, response has been phenomenal, obviously
only from the Dutch market, but yeah, really, really even enjoyed doing that.
It's, you know, it's almost like our own little Don and Drew show, you know, I totally
dig it.
So let me tell you what I have set up here.
Of course, I have the regular microphone and the processing, oh man, Patricia hates it when
I talk geek stuff about the setup, but I'm using this new piece of software, which I think
I've mentioned before, it's called Megaseg.
Megaseg is essentially it's a scheduling software.
They just released version 3.1.
It's for Mac only for OSX only, I think, even.
But it's really stable and what I've done is I've loaded up all promos, mashups, pod safe,
music, sweepers, jingles, imaging stuff, you know, everything you need for, well, that I like
to have for my podcast.
And then you line it up into playlists and what it does is it does all the transitions
for you automatically unless you insert a break.
So it really leaves, you know, a lot of, it kind of, it's kind of analogous to, to flying,
you know, if you can, if you can lower the pilot load, that's all, it's all like pilot
workload.
It's always a good thing because you probably have a safer landing.
So that's running into the mixer than I'm mixing in my microphone.
I'm actually outputting the entire signal to my other Mac and I'm running audio hijack
pro, which also has a new version out.
So yeah, we may be doing a lot of work on the 97% of Windows users out there with the
cast blaster, but the Mac, although it's all disparate pieces of software that definitely
is a lot of stuff you can do.
So hopefully this will sound okay, normally what I do is I, you know, I record it reasonably
high bit rate and then use the lame brain or the lame libraries, whatever it's called
to compress, you know, to compress it down to 64 kilobit rate or whatever I usually do.
So now I'm using a built in just the, what is it?
It's the low MP3 encoding 64 kilobit per second stereo continuous bit rate.
So hopefully hopefully it'll, it'll sound okay, if not, while you just have to forgive
me.
Let's see, oh, the beginning of the show, that was Peter Day from the BBC.
I'll put a link to this in the show notes.
There was an hour long special last night on Radio 4, which is the, it's pretty much
a talk channel.
It's the, you know, it's where everyone tuned in to listen to the elections here.
It's, yeah, it's the, it's the, it's the talk channel, basically.
And a full hour on podcasting and it's just wonderful.
I don't know how long the show is going to stay up.
Of course, I recorded an MP3, but you know, I've already emailed the producer and said,
hey, any chance of you turning this show about podcasting into a podcast, I haven't heard
back from her yet.
So in case it does go away, I'll have a, I'll have a backup link.
Okay, let me see if I'm doing all this right now.
Hold on, now I thought, I thought we're going to have a mashup play right now.
Let me see if it works.
Shoot.
Hold on.
I didn't work.
What did I do wrong here?
Hold on.
Bear with me now, please.
What's it going to do wrong?
Oh, shoot.
Okay, this is interesting.
What's happened is, oh, wow.
Okay, so this mega SEG, it has a whole database that you can set up, so that it basically
keeps track of what you've played and when you've played it.
And if it, if it encounters something that you've set up a rule for, so for instance,
I said, you know, anything that I play in the, in the mashup category, don't play it
for at least, you know, at least a month because I don't want to repeat myself.
And I'd already done, oh man, everything's happening at the same time, is that Christina
coming home to?
Hold on.
I'll be just checked.
She, not, okay.
So what mega SEG then did, which was correct, is it went ahead and changed the, you know,
what, let me just do this for a second.
Maybe if I can just open up the playlist again, I'm sorry to put you through this, but
it's definitely, okay, let me see, okay, this will work.
Oh, thank goodness.
All right, so I've turned off the rules because it was replacing stuff that I'd
played.
You know, before I started recording, I basically auditioned it and to see if everything
was working well.
But then it countered each audition as a play in essence, replacing all the songs.
Okay, here we go.
This is Golden Peace Frog.
This is my great pleasure.
Reset to you.
That's shit, son.
You're the no-goo.
Never seen it.
See your fear.
Check it out now.
I've worked a pandemic to ain't transformed.
You need to take a list of it's depends on that year.
It's hands on.
What's the beat?
The goal is high, goal cheats.
I'll protect you.
I'll drink, all the way to glass.
Get your shame.
They'll treat the same place.
All the fans depend.
The design for heaven, nationality.
And wrapping the legend with their limits.
That is so much play, but it's all the matter.
We're not all in.
We take it back to the days of that show.
We hold in on to us, go in.
I'm gonna say it's not right to know who it is.
We're not all in.
Because I call it in.
We take it back to the days of that show.
And hold in on to us, go in.
I'm gonna drink, all the way to know who it is.
Never call it one day.
So take the hot thing.
Big breaks that chase at all.
That's for the same.
No name.
You stay true to the fans.
Stay true to the game.
And never bring it to shame.
We take the 12 blocks.
We wrap up.
We're not all in.
We take it back to the days of that show.
We hold in on to us, go in.
We take it back to the day of that show.
We him him.
Running away from us, go in.
We comes back right up here.
Did you catch asey Goldenس Fragu.
cheg on the D.V.
John Mahal.
So it had been there for last year or two.
Wait.
So I can't go right into the show.
The show yesterday.
Come on guys, let's go in through through the show.
open it up. Let me see, when we talk about, oh, what do you want us to do? I'm going
to take a screenshot. I think I can take a screenshot of this. Can't I hold on a second?
Let's see if this works. Yeah. Oh, man. I love the way that does that. Okay. So we've
got a screenshot. I'll post that along with the show notes. So you can see kind of what
I mean with the software. I'm pretty jazzed about it because you can have all the stuff
transition automatically and then you can put a break in wherever you feel appropriate and
the playlist will stop until you hit the Apple key forward slash and then it hits the next thing.
Following program is dedicated to the people and the city of San Francisco from San Francisco,
California. Got a rock. Thank you for the chance to pick out. We are your humblester
and please give us the power to blow people's minds with our high voltage rock in your
name we pray. Come on. You know, it's going to be set strong, strong smoke mode.
Chips, dips, chains, whips. It's the rock and roll. You sure? We're at the base player.
He's married. With your host, Michael Father. I know I got some of you who are reading.
Hey everybody, we're all going to go away. Base player is the key.
And now let's go on location. Here's your host, Michael Butler.
Rock and roll, geek show. And soon to be guests on the rock and roll, geek show,
Ron Bloom, in the role of guitar player and Joan Jett, a special guest.
What's this?
Sounds real here.
Godfather, forgive me for troubling you with such a trivial matter.
Yes, my son. They have come here to pay you tribute and to ask you for a small favor.
I have a podcast that I believe most people would find enjoyable, but I am having trouble reaching
these people. Part Father, you are a man of great influence. Please, part father.
If you can find it in your heart to help me promote my podcast, please tell me what I must do
to gain this favor. All right, real simple, my son. If you've got a podcast send it to
Submit at podshow.com. If you've got a mashup, it's mashup at podshow.com. You got some podsafe tunes.
It's podsafe at podshow.com. That's the unforgettable PW Fenton there. Do I have to
avoid this? Excellent stuff. PWB will be helping me on the a serious show, the pod show on serious.
Okay, I think that is actually my daughter. Hold on. Hold on one sec, I'll be right back.
Don't go away. Well, this is going to definitely be podcasters interrupt us today.
Daily source code. That wasn't even there, Christina. That was the window washers.
Just never know what goes on. Mom's are important when they're around. They get a lot of
shit done in the house. Unfortunately, the next problem that I'm going to play is late, but I didn't
want to, you know, I didn't want to hold back on. I just didn't even see it in the promo inbox and
didn't actually realize that it was was timely from Rev Tim. And that'll be followed by some feedback
from arthritis central news. And then I want to talk about my own mother's mother's mother's
name. Hi, this is Rev Tim from the Rev Tim podcast. I've a special request. I'm putting out
to the podcast listener community. I'm putting together a special mother's day podcast to be
released Friday evening. Sorry. So what I need you to do is to call our voicemail comment line
at 815 301-8600. And leave a message that describes what it is about your mother that makes
her special to you. Okay. I just want to stop that for a second. I'm really sorry, Rev Tim. I mean,
you know, you got to shoot me a personal email. They went into the promo box and I just never saw
a man. I apologize. And you could also share a special memory or just leave a message to your mom.
So give it a shot right now. It won't use up much of your time. And I'm sure it will make this
podcast very special. So the number again, it's not told free. So use yourself. If you need to,
it's 815 301-8600. Thank you from Rev Tim and the Rev Tim podcast. Hey, Adam, it's Dr. Joel Ritzkin,
and our thread is central.com. I really appreciate you playing our promo on your own podcast.
It's interesting that you commented about the marijuana and how that might be helpful to co-paying
a study. It was published just two years ago in the Dr. Illinois American Medical Association,
addressed the use of one of the derivatives of marijuana called CT3. And it was used to control
severe nerve pain in patients. And it worked. Patients on this marijuana-like drug did better than
those without it. The side effects were gizziness, sweating, fatigue, dryness of the mouth,
and even problems concentrating. So the question is, will this be something that can be used to
control other forms of pain, including arthritis, fibromyalgia? Now, in your case, your own marijuana
use it. You might not even feel it if a truck was on top of your chest. So it really depends on
how much you're using, but it looks like it might be something promising in the future as far as
marijuana derivatives in rheumatic diseases. So I know you were kind of joking about it, but it may
actually be real and you're right. And the idea is to control pain and give people some quality of life.
We'll continue to follow this that are throughout the central.com. We'll try to keep you informed
down the road if there are any new developments in this area. I'm sure it's something you're interested
in. And your listeners may be interested in it as well. You take care and appreciate your
help and support. You're doing a great job. Thanks again. All right. Thank you very much, Dr. Joel,
from the arthritis news and views podcast. So I just want to touch back on that again and my
apologies to Rev Tim that I messed that one up. But what was interesting is now, if you've been
listening to the daily source code for a while, then you know that last year, just actually between
Christmas and New Year's, my mom had a lung removed. She had lung cancer and she is now officially
a survivor. In fact, they sent her home, you know, after 10 days and said, don't come back for a month
and then they said, don't come back after two months. And so it's been about four or let's see the five
months now. And of course, it has altered not only her, but everyone's life in the family.
She does have a lot of pain from, well, this basically, this huge incision that they, you know,
they cut her open all the way from her back around to the the front of her chest. And it's been
buggerner, as you can imagine. You know, it's like, as she tried to explain it to me, I can hardly
imagine what that, you know, what the pain must be like. I think the fact that it's just constant
and there is probably what drives you crazy, kind of like an itch that you just can't scratch.
You know, you can't get to only like way more fucked up. And so, and I kept saying, I said, Mom,
you know, try some marijuana. You know, of course, she wouldn't be smoking it, but she would be
perhaps putting it into some food or drinking it as tea. And she called me last week and she said,
all right, I'm ready. I'll try anything. So I called up my, well, taxi Eric, of course,
called him up, had him make a little delivery in, come on, my mom lives in, in the Netherlands.
And, and first she, she'd found all kinds of recipes on the internet for, like, soup and some other,
yeah, liquid food or whatever. And, and she used up about five grams and said, I don't feel
anything. It's not working. He said, well, I don't believe in all this soup shit. So just make some tea,
you know, just boil up some water, boil it with with a nice bud in there, then make yourself
for like half a cup of nice fruit tea or something that'll taste good, a little sugar, and then just
strain in this, this boiled water with, you know, with cannabis and it's strain that into your tea.
And, and that should work. And she called me last night, Sunday night, and she was laughing.
It was so funny. She said, like, I don't know if, if I'm stone, but the pain is certain,
I'm going to hit the pain. That's like going off. The pain is certainly, it's almost gone.
And I haven't heard from her today as she was going to call me, but she said that she was feeling
great and the pain was completely gone. And I'd say we had a very, very, very successful experiment
there, and it was good to hear from Dr. Joel. Hey, I'm not all that bad. You know, it's, yeah,
maybe a mini van. I wouldn't feel it, but a truck. Yeah, I probably feel there.
I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it.
I love it. I love it. It's love. I've done the next wax flat. I really had a heart attack
Like me, but meant to somebody sucks me
Such a mother, got to find a love
Got to find a love, got to find a love
After all now
I'm out in the throne of mine
We know they're gone
I don't think I had was gone
After all now
I'm out in the throne of mine
That's love, it's love, it's love, it's love
It's love, it's love, it's love
It's love
After all now
I'm out in the throne of mine
It's love, it's love, it's love
I don't think I had was gone
After all now
I'm out in the throne of mine
It's love, it's love, it's love
It's love, it's love
You're in backstacking
It's love
It's love, it's love
I want to go to Paris.
Stay at the hill tonight.
No kiss.
For Paris, no phone.
So, Paris comes clean.
You are one station.
You come clean.
You just let the rest of us your love.
You can let us win the last one star.
You love Paris with the last win.
You can let me know as well.
So, Paris,
forget your millions go and just come clean.
You can let us pass your love with much of one star.
That came through on openpodcast.org.
Excellent promo for Mad Weinstein, useradio.com.
Okay, I just noticed that in my new software set up, I had Skype still open.
So, I think you heard the phone ring throughout the pod safe tune there.
I apologize for that.
I got to work on this stuff.
And do two more tests since we're messing around with software and recording stuff.
I'll also do two things.
One is I'm going to throw this show up on the pod show server instead of the dot max server.
Since it'll be a little bit shorter than normal, I can be 30 minutes, I guess.
And see if our bandwidth can handle it.
So, you know, if you didn't hear the show, sorry.
And I'm also working, that since I've been talking about Bitcoin as a bandwidth solution,
a lot of people have been sending me emails, setting up stuff.
So, I'm going to try and put up not this show, but what I was thinking,
PW and I are creating basically working throughout this entire week to get ready for the pod show,
launch on serious on Friday the 13th is coming Friday.
And what we'll do is, once we get all the sweepers and all the stuff in which is being created as we speak,
we have one out, one or two hours all put together.
Then I'll put those up as a torrent.
So, A, you can see if it'll download into your iPodder through a through a bit torrent,
which it should.
And B, you'll have an idea of what we're actually planning.
By your house, radio.
Hey, this is Jim gets a firehouse radio.
If you like excitement, then you have to check out the Firehouse radio show.
Action, talk, music, and more is what you'll hear on our weekly podcast,
found exclusively on firehouse.fm.
Hey, we're firefighters doing radio right.
Tell them, Chef.
What's the matter, children?
Explore us radio.
The motitude's went forth and cast their pods in the direction of all who would listen.
And casting their pods in this manner, they were henceforth known as pod castors.
Yes, you can get in your ear.
I've got your podcast right here.
Alright, that's it for today's show.
I'm going to get it up on the server, see if we can get it all right.
And Christina's home, so I'm going to go make her a little snack.
As always, comments are welcome.
Adam at curie.com.
The place to submit now is submit at podshow.com.
Podsafe and podshow.com for your podsafe music and mash up at podshow.com for your mashups.
If you're looking for the show notes, you can find them on www.curie.com or on dailysourcecode.com where you can find them later.
Show the podcasts feed and the archives.
I'll leave a comment if you can see it or like it.
I definitely want some feedback about this one with a new equipment.
Alright everybody, I'll be back tomorrow and every single day this week.
No travel plans in some plan, Mr. Maw.
Maybe Christina and I will do a podcast on the way to school in the morning or something like that.
Have some fun.
Take care.
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye.