Delta Sierra Charry 2, 6, 3.
They came from every city in Hamlet, from every walk of life, from the shadows of the Golden
Gate Bridge to a Wisconsin farmhouse, from the couple's homespeech of historic Boston and
the windy city, from the affluent suburbs of London, England, to the squalid steamy slums
of sunny Florida.
They came with a burning hunger, a permanent desire, and a single-minded obsession with
taking back the media.
They are the pod people.
Starring Don Maselli and Drew Dumpkin.
Don Andrews are 167.
CC Chapman.
C-Homefras.
Michael Butler.
Delato Rochice.
Big Mike.
C-Homefras.
Mark Hunter.
Father podcasts.
Sleepy Sunday morning.
Steve Gilmour.
Hello and welcome to the Attention Tech Daily Park.
Marcus Couch.
It's the Seen Z.
Magic Weinstein.
My porter, Goss, hurts and smells.
C-W-Fent another addition of radio-free radio's digital supply.
With special guest appearances by Dumb and Jaris.
How not?
Ryan Know.
The editor of the 20th Century.
Which at all, rather fair.
Taylor's eyes.
It's me.
And directed by their fearless leader Adam Curry.
It's the world against us and us against the world.
Raise your head hands and say hi!
Coming to you in Living Super Cinematic Digital 5.1 surround sound manoral.
The pod people.
Now, playing on serious satellite 103 and finding B3 players everywhere.
There are no secrets.
I'm sorry, information you don't get higher.
Adam Curry.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking friends in it.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic.
It's a battle curry.
And it is Thursday.
October 20, 2005.
The power of the door.
Why everybody?
How you doing?
Welcome once again to the show.
I brought to you from the Curry condo.
Another foggy day in San Francisco town.
It is about 5 minutes past 10 Thursday morning.
The 20th of October.
This is your daily source code.
A little bit later than normal today because, well, I got cable now.
So you know what I did last night when I got home?
Yeah, exactly.
Is it a veg out?
My goodness.
Television is so destructive.
It's stolen entire evening.
I don't even remember what I watched.
But it's here.
Not one but two televisions.
One of the bedroom.
One in the main living room area.
Nice little LCD flat screens.
I'll cheap those but they certainly do the job.
You know what?
Comcast is amazing.
It's like a thousand channels on a thing.
I think I'm witnessing my jet lag.
It's starting to finally catch up with me.
Yeah.
See, when I come in, I came in Sunday, right?
Yeah, Sunday.
And then switch my clock immediately and got going on Monday.
So this is what usually happens.
I went to bed around one o'clock, 115.
That's when I switched the TV off.
Of course, my brain was nice and rested, not.
And I was up at like seven o'clock before the alarm clock.
But I had my alarm set for eight.
So I lounge around and rednate on a blackberry.
Yes, probably in food tours as well.
Okay.
Today, some different pot-save music, some different genres.
I've been hunting around trying to get a different kind of fix.
Instead of what we've normally played on the source code.
And good old art, a dub for mashuptown.com, sent me a wonderful mashup.
It's kind of a remix mashup, but it's just, it's like so honky honky.
It's an album, John, but as you've never heard of before,
Adam's honky cat remix brought to you by mashuptown.com.
Enjoy everybody.
Good morning.
Good night.
until the weekend, then I'm going to go to the Apple Store,
I'm going to load up, get me one of the,
do you see that they released a new IMac G5
with a dual processor?
Oh yeah, man, they're just coming one after another.
I hope that, you know, since I'm going to wait
until the weekend to get the IMac,
I hope that all of a sudden new power books will appear.
It's unbelievable, Apple just cranking the shit out.
So as I said yesterday, he probably heard it at the very end
of the show, the cable guy called up, he was downstairs,
activating my service, came upstairs, installed the Motorola
bitch surfer, whatever.
I think it's called bitch surfer, but bitch surfer, sex, sex.
Sorry, Freudian slip.
Six megabits per second download speed and 500 kilobite per second
upload speed.
It's good enough.
I'm really digging it.
It's called curry condo and I'm broadcasted from the 24th floor
across across the south of market area of San Francisco.
So if you can read my signal and you can hop on, let me know.
It's open, obviously.
So I bought a, what is that?
Is that a deal link?
I'm a, I'm a, I'm a dork.
I probably didn't even get a linksis.
It's so stupid.
Oh, man, I can't believe that.
Because linksis has that firmware that we talked about.
Oh, man, okay, well, anyway, so curry condo,
you can get in and use that and curious to see how
far that signal reaches.
Because I've got nothing but glass up here in the condo.
Okay, daily source code for Thursday.
As I said, it's kind of drab and dreary, it's gray, foggy.
The sun is up, but it's having a hard time breaking through and burning
anything off.
It may burn off, but this is kind of like the weather that we had when I was
here with the girls.
And I gotta tell you, I really do miss them.
Oh, dude, that's the one thing where the time zone really sucked.
Oh, we've been through that a million times, but I miss them.
And Christina has vacation next week, and I'm not going to be there.
Oh, by the way, so we decided we're not going to Portugal because Patricia
wasn't feeling well, and she needs, she needs it like a week to recuperate,
just to make sure, not by getting another airplane, she's going to get sick again.
And by the way, she sounds like some sickly woman, but she's not.
This is just unbelievable, series of events that have come down.
So she'd really deserves a break.
So the big break, of course, is not getting up early in the morning for
Christina's routine to get her off to school.
So that just by itself, and of course, not having me around to keep her up late at night.
Second part of the health update is about the cholesterol reading that I gave you yesterday.
I'm a dying man.
I mean, of course, we're all dying every single day, but let me see, where was, oh, of course,
there was a doctor, oh, man, let me see.
I thought I'd cue that one up from the talk about with you.
Let me say, I got a couple of different emails pointing to different sites about cholesterol.
Here we go, Mark Katz, that's the one I wanted to read to you.
Okay, this is from Mark R Katz M. D.
Chief of cardiac surgery, director Virginia Transplant Center,
Henrico Doctors Hospital in Richmond, Virginia, Adam, your ass is in big trouble.
Stop eating all that crap and get your butt off the couch.
A cholesterol of 200 is too high.
Most current think it should be below 180.
Diet is the first line of attack to lower your cholesterol.
HDL was the good cholesterol, so you wanted high.
Exercise is one of the best means to accomplish this.
There's some more sophisticated tests to further delineate the subgroups of cholesterol and lipids.
That's the HDL LDL and VL DL.
And it's always as bad as RSS and OPML.
Sometimes drugs are indicated to help with these, but diet and exercise are first.
Well, first of all, I'm not a big crap eater.
I really am not.
I'm just not.
I'm not a big crap eater.
I don't exercise enough.
That's for sure.
And then I find out that basically I have a moderate risk of a heart attack because,
well, you know, of the main two points.
One is you're over 40.
You get that right off the bat and what's the other one?
You're a guy, I don't know, something weird.
So, uh, so that's really nice.
I'm a little concerned about everything now.
Okay.
So today, track suit, gym, workout, ride the wheels off this motherfucker.
Remember back with alternative rock music really meant something?
If you know what we're talking about, your retro fix is only a click away.
This is your best hot day, you ever had joy.
Chicago's Tarsus Lopez each week at www.tarsus Lopez.com.
But for the alternative classics podcast and for the very best punk,
new wave, college rock and grunge from the 80s and early 90s.
Listen, listen.
You can email your requests to alternative classics at a meritech.net.
Download the alternative classics podcast today.
My mother, my daughter, my friend, my great youth, my mommy,
is living with, lost the fight, one the fight, survive,
breast cancer, breast cancer, breast cancer, breast cancer, breast cancer.
Hi, this is Daria from boutiquefay.com.
For the third straight year, hundreds of eBay boutique designers joined together for a
cause near and dear to our hearts.
The breast cancer awareness auctions or the BCA's.
We hope.
Please give, we bid, we bid, we bid, we bid.
October 17th to 21st, search boutique BCA in your eBay search box to find all of the
beautiful handmade items, who sale will directly benefit the ongoing fight for a cure.
For a cure, for hope, for hope, for love, for my family, for my future.
For more information about the BCA's or to listen to an interview with Angela Goons,
founder and creator of the breast cancer awareness auctions, go to boutiquefay.com
and listen to our most recent podcast.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Do you love movies?
Do you consider film an art form rather than mere popcorn entertainment?
Do you gleefully chuck handfuls of raisinets and morons who leave their cell phones on during
every single screening you attend?
Do you refuse to run away an abject horror at the thought of a subtitle movie?
Then you should check out CinemaSlave, a brand new podcast devoted to the passionate celebration
of all things filmed.
Reviews are the best and worst in cinema and DVD.
Discussions about filmmaking, Frankenstein and the French New Wave, and best of all violent
arguments about movies from people who love them in a way frowned upon by the Bible.
Check out CinemaSlave at www.cinemoslave.com or through the iTunes Music Store.
It's free but not recommended for the faint heartache.
Thanks by the way everyone who sent in a new or great duo or duet names to compare Ron
Bloom and myself too.
Yesterday I said that we were kind of like Kenny Rogers and Dolly Parton when we get to
happen with each other.
The best one came from Julia in LA, my buddy, Jules.
She said, no you guys are more like Donnie and Marie because he's a little country and you're
a little rack and roll on gosh darn.
So yesterday, right after the Comcast guy came and installed everything, Ron and I rolled
off to San Hill Road, famous place in Silicon Valley where all the big venture capital
firms are to have a meeting with Ray Lane who, of course, is anything but the quintessential
venture capital venture capitalist, he's not, you know, that's probably why I'm
like him so much, he used to be the chief operating officer of Oracle.
So he, you know, he's an operator, he knows how companies run and he has a lot of experience,
he's up there for in my mind, he's up there with a lot of the really big guys who run
the really, really big companies.
But he's a guy's guy, you know, went to WVU, and of course I went to West Virginia, not
for long, but I went to West Virginia for some college, so there's some connection there,
but this weekend he's off hunting with his buddies, they're going fescent hunting in South
Dakota.
Oh man, he has some interesting stories.
So we were talking yesterday, just, you know, as I said, whenever I'm out here, we always
want to go and, well, actually, we've tried to hate our investors, at least once a week,
just to keep up to date, we always have some questions they had to go and have some input
on or open the rollo decks on, which, of course, is very, very cool.
And it was a little earlier that he had asked Ron, said, do you know the names of all
your employees in the office now, and, of course, I think both of us do?
And he says, well, good because the diet is cast, you know, from now on, you know, you've
set the mold of the company, and everyone else who comes after that is going to be reflection
of that first team.
And I thought I was a kind of really interesting exercise to go through the names of the
people that we have in the office.
Now there's a ton more people outside, you know, members of the pod squad, of course,
so we have P-D-O, P-W-Fenton in Florida.
We've got, well, as I said, I just outside of the pod squadters, we have, let me just go
through the office for a second.
Let me see if I can name them, tell you a little bit about each person.
And I'm doing it visually, right, because I'm just closing my eyes and seeing all the
heads where they sit.
So we have Sue, I'm going to start with Sue.
Sue has been working with us along with CC Chapman and Chris Bershier, so we'll
get to in a second.
On the Podsake Music Network, so we've actually known Sue for a number of months, and she
kind of worked freelance on that, and then we hired her because, you know, she did a kick-ass
job managing the project, and with the design and with the user interface, I'm not going
to go into too much depth about everyone because I could talk for hours.
Next to her, we have Colleen Colleen's, I mean, with us for like a month, I think, she
comes from tag.com, she's a social network specialist, then we have Marcus Moller, well,
we all know Marcus.
Marcus has been attached to my hip, you know, even though there's been thousands of
miles of distance between us, but ever since we started school blogs.com, so that's
been a couple of years.
Our favorite poopcaster, Chris Rockwell, of course, you know, I bumped into, well, he
interviewed me on the Daily Download, where he was doing his poopcast, and I reciprocated.
It's still a fantastic show to listen to, I love it, and he started out doing a lot of
the database programming for the Podsake Music Network, and he's moved out here, and
Lori is coming, I don't know if Lori's out here yet, but she's coming, that just picked
up and moved.
Let me see, go around, then we have, the prints of the Podcast alley, Chris Mac and
Tyre, we got a lot of Chris's, by the way, all with different spellings, of course, then
we have Kevin, Kevin, we call him the Rockstar, he's a code slinger, and he worked with,
how's the name of that company that does websites for music stars, so he did like the
kiss website or Gene Simmons website and how to deal with him, so you can deal with Gene
Simmons, you can deal with anybody, then we have Aaron Brousel, Aaron, as marketing and
PR, better known as the Pod Pimp, then I'll kind of go to the left there, we have Chris
Jacob, let me go back to Aaron for a second, Eric and Chris know each other from the Web
TV days, and Aaron drives a Prius, okay, then we have Chris and Chris is all over the
place, man, he's in New York, he's in LA, he's, as I said, business development, he's
doing a great job, and I've known Chris a long time as well, from the on-ramp days, man,
I was like 14 years ago, 12 years ago, when the first metaverse dot com server was in
his apartment here in San Francisco, then we have Brian longest, director of operations,
we talked about Brian a lot, he was, with Ron and I as we started up Pod Show, then we
knew guy Phil, I don't know Phil's last name off hand, but he's a freelancer, he's
like a, he's like a gun slinger, he comes in, does PHP and leaves, and he'll be in for I
guess a couple of weeks, then we have Matt, Matt is, he has an interesting job, he's in, I call
it traffic, but that's not, that's not right, but he does all the statistics, all the
add-insertions, understanding the audience, I think he's still developing his job, there's
so much to be done there, we've got Rosie up front who just really runs the office, if
you will, let me think, did I get everybody, I thought I did pretty good on that, yeah, I think
you know what, if I forgot someone, I'll buy you dinner, hello Adam, hello Adam, hello Adam,
do you know who this is, this is PW Frenton, I'm Mike, this is Alex, I do, and that's Adam's,
hello, the announcer guy Kevin here, it's Dave Fox, and I'm here with you on today to bring you
today's hit test, the hit test, the hit test, the hit test with young bullet, hey Adam,
you can hear I've been having some fun with some editing software and a computer, and I've put
together bits and pieces from all the things I've collected in the last 66 hit tests, and now it's
time for hit test number 67, so are you ready, this is number one, I got to be careful not to
blur it out the answers too soon because I want to give everyone a chance, that's got to be
night fever, BG's, and this is number two, this is why she was still a pudgy little teenager,
I met her in this period, when I think of you Joanna Jackson, this is easy young, and the final one is
three as always, he's the greatest dancer, sister sledge, I think, I'm afraid I made it a bit too easy
today, no shit, this is answer number one in today's hit test, it's a song from 1978, it's the BG's,
this is night fever,
answer number one, the BG's, and this is answer number two, it's a song from 19, what is it?
86, and it's a genogection, and the song is called, when I think of you,
I really made it to easy, I think, at least for you Adam, but boy, what did they make good music,
way back like this one from 1979, sister sledge, who's the greatest dancer,
essential number three in today's hit test, one night, and disco on the outskirts of
fiscal, I was cruising with my favorite game, the place was so boring, without a time as touring,
I knew that it wasn't my thing, I loved the one, he's the greatest dancer, I loved the one,
he's the greatest dancer, and that's it, answer number three, sister sledge, he's the greatest dancer,
and that concludes hit test number 67, okay, thank you for playing this one Adam, I hope you enjoyed this
one, and you had all three of them, if not, I am very disappointed in you, just kidding,
okay, well thanks again, see you next time, oh and don't forget to check out the iTunes links
on the website if you're gonna buy some of the tricks, that's you've heard on the hit test,
I leave it to Dave to give you all the other and the other info, so until next time, bye-bye,
okay, I have really and pissed off now, you hear mega-sag, it's gotten out, this has, this is my
Mac, man, let me just see playback, is any options that I messed up here, auto-sag trim, oh well,
how about if we just bring that back, you know, maybe that's the problem, maybe it's cutting out after
seven seconds or something like that, god damn, but so that's the ending problem, but the other
problem is, I think the Mac need to reboot, I'm still running off the fire wire drive, okay,
saving library one moment please, I forgot to tell you one thing about Ray Lane, so we were almost
almost got, he has a, we talk aviation a lot too, he has a G4 golf stream, jet, and he has a
challenger, he has a jet for each foot, and I say, hey, you know, I sold half of the challenger,
the other half is for sale, you know, I second buy half a challenger, oh that's one, yeah, five million
dollars, oh my goodness, no dude, I'm not gonna buy any plane that I can't fly myself, I'm still in the
Charlie 182 Romeo golf mode if you don't mind, it's be kind of flying, I guess I told you about the
flight back from from Redmond City at all, where the pilot came on and told me that if you
looked out the left-hand side of the aircraft, you could see Mars underneath the moon,
well of course, one of the source code listeners, can you just believe the kind of people who
listen to this show, how cool is that? We've got a major cardiologist telling me I'm going to die,
and now we have a space cadet. I had him, this is Russell Hanson, I was listening to Davy's
source code 262, the other morning, and I heard you say this. And say, you know, if you look
out the left-hand side of the aircraft, you'll see, you'll see the moon, okay, duh, saw that,
but underneath that it's a planet, he said that's planet Mars and apparently this is the closest
Mars got to or has been to the moon, and I subsequently, I guess, the Earth in 60 years.
So I thought it'd give you some details of what you actually have in here.
I'm on October 29th, around 11.25 pm, meast in daylight time. Mars and Earth will be the
closest that they've been since August 2003. Now, the August 2003 event was closer than it is this year,
and the August 2003 event was also the closest that Mars had been to Earth in nearly 60,
thousands years, but this year's events still pretty good. And it's the closest that Mars
will be to Earth again until summer of 2019, so we don't get these changes very often.
As Mars gets closer to Earth, it gets brighter. And by the time it said it's closest point,
it'll be not quite as bright as Venus, but it will surpass serious, which is the brightest
star in the sky. So I'm going to give those Halloween kids something to look at while they're
picking up all their treats. Now, the other thing you mentioned was that it's the closest to the
moon that's been. Now, I don't think that's really correct when we're actually talking about
closest distance wise. When you see it in the night sky, how visually close it is to the moon,
as what you're talking about there, I think, which hasn't got anything really to do with
where Mars is in space itself. Just makes it good to look at, which, of course, has
astronomy being such a visual hobby science that it is. It makes it great for those of us
looking here from down below. So I hope that gives you a few more details. I hope that gives you
the answers you're after. You can look forward to more of this kind of information soon,
when I release my astronomy podcast on astronomy.podcast format.com, I'll be covering news
and events and all sorts of astronomy on the internet information in a couple of different
podcast formats. So I hope you found this useful again and keep up the great work with
the highly source code. And I'll hopefully talk to you later. All right, dude. Thank you very much.
Hey, Brams, you guys. I'm going to be playing some different genres of pod save music.
Had a great time this morning now that I could download really fast and skin through all the new
submissions to music.podshow.com. Here's restless for the sun. Jimmy Bratcher on your daily source code.
All right, I'll lay me down to sleep tonight, toss and turn, sleep on car,
restless for the sun.
A dream a dream with you in view. Better times and dreams come true.
As wide open tell me where's the dawn. Restless for the sun.
The view from here. Don't darken. It's shout so clear in my mind.
Don't break in through darkness. Dreams come true. Better times.
So hold me close. Speak to me.
For the dreams we've yet to see. Can't wait to see you when the morning comes.
Restless for the sun.
So hold me close. Speak to me.
For the dreams we've yet to see. Can't wait to see you when the morning comes.
Restless for the sun. Restless for the sun.
Isn't that pretty? It's almost unbelievable. As the sun was playing the sun,
broke through on the eastern side of the day and just started to burn away. Some of those fog and
clouds really, really, really nice. Just wrapping up the aviation part of the show here.
I heard that many airlines are going to allow cell phones to work in the air while you're flying.
What a crazy world we live in. 10 years ago,
even less than that, having your own private airplane meant that you could actually make phone calls from
the air. That was like the hot shit. These days, or in the very near future, you're going to want
to have your own private airplane so you don't have to listen to some dickheads sitting next to you.
I'm against that. I'm way against that. That's not a good idea. Because you really don't notice
the cell phone culture walking around on the street. People don't use their cell phones and
meetings that much, but occasionally, want to ring or you know, it won't be unviberate mode and
they'll start skipping across the table. But otherwise, people use cell phones pretty much everywhere.
You know, in restaurants, in stores and at ball games, in the movie theaters. Oh, man. I don't
know, I'm not for this. This is a bad trend. Good trends are coming out of Los Angeles.
It was intended for mature audiences and may contain some language like pee. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa,
hold on. This, this warning is for real, okay? If you have your kids around, turn the volume down
or stick it in your ear. Kaka, doo-doo, and the occasional fucking do-spag cock sucker.
Holy shit, and hot, damn, Mark. You know, Shemoto and MCOP from Pacific Coast,
Hellway. Hey, Adam, I just want to let you and the daily source code listeners know that after
months of begging and pleading by myself and the listeners here on the highway, we finally got Sarah,
the 21-year-old virgin, to call in to our message line and leave her self-induced orgasm.
Hey, sorry, call me a tease, but that's all he get for now. However, we will be playing her
entire one minute and 43 second long orgasm on Pacific Coast, Hellway, on Thursday show.
So, come with us on Sarah's journey into the realization of her own dormant sexuality.
Hey, I'm telling you, her orgasm is so hot, it made me harder than Chinese arithmetic.
Wait, hold on, let me play that again. Oh, hey, Adam, I know it gets lonely there,
a curry condo away from your beloved, so I especially invite you and the daily source code
listeners to light a few candles and get ready for a virtual visit from our own lovely Sarah,
the 21-year-old virgin. Hey, now what you do during the show is between you,
whatever God you believe in and U.S. Attorney General Alberto Gonzales. We at the Hellway aren't here
to judge, we're just here to provide you with stuff nobody else can. All I'm saying is that after
I post tomorrow's show, I'm buying stock and clean eggs. So, come, check us out of Pacific Coast Hellway.
You can find us on the iTunes Music Store under Pacific Coast Hellway or at Pacific Coast Hellway.com.
Adam, stay groovy, a big lug. This is Martin Yoshimodo, an MCOT signing off. So let's all get home safe
and let's meet at Pacific Coast Hellway and talk about some more shit. I'm out.
Harder than Chinese arithmetic? I know that one, I like it. I'm out. I'm supposed to invite him
up this week. We'll have to do it next week then. Have to see if you can come, I really want to meet
this guy in his Pacific Hell Coast players. They've got something going on down there in Los Angeles.
Very cool. Hey, all-time radio, it really never won away. In fact, it's alive and vibrant at the
small world. Oh, the lone ranger. Oh, the lone ranger. Yes, when you hear that
going to be hard, it's the lone ranger. In those days, you sat back and your imagination took
over and you created your own images of the characters that you listened to. I Adam,
visit your show here from the small world podcast. Like yourself, I'm a big fan of all-time
radio theater. On today's small world podcast, I had the pleasure of talking with Radio Hall of
Famer, Fred Foie. Fred was the voice of such classics as the announcer of the lone ranger,
the green hornet, and the dick-evite show as well as narrating dozens of documentaries. I invite
you and everyone else to listen to Fred as he shares some of the moments from his great career
in radio at smallworldpodcast.com as always. Stay tuned.
And I produce a weekly pod safe music podcast called Robert Smooth Music. If you're tired of radio
and junk food mainstream music, RSM is for you, there are great artists out there. They're just
hard to find. That's the mission of RSM. You'll find a coherent mix of indie rock, folk, pop,
world, and beyond. In addition to great music, you'll appreciate the fact that your host,
that's me, Robert Smooth, is quiet, bland, and inoffensive. Basically, I'm a big bore who loves to
play great tunes without a bunch of a name chatter. Just great music. I invite you to give
the show a listen. Visit my web page at robbysmovemusic.blogspot.com or search for RSM in iTunes.
Enjoy Robert Smooth Music. Ciao.
Right, the exact opposite of me. I have all the in-game chatter. What does that guy say?
All right, time for something that is really American. If you hate country, skip ahead for four
minutes. He has rusty blue and bill Anderson.
Please me, and baby, it's starting to hurt. There's not enough feeling when you kiss me,
not in the fourth and your touch. There seems to be a whole lot of little things,
chipping away and I love. Chipping away, chipping away and I love. One little too little,
three little problems, pretty seeing you and I'm all up. And all the King's horses and all the
King's men, couldn't put us back together again. We got a star, star, star, star,
chipping away, chipping away and I love.
You used to leave me a little of nose, lying all around the house. Then you used to laugh at all of my jokes,
but nothing's worth of fun in that. There's not enough feeling when you kiss me,
not in the fourth and your touch. There seems to be a whole lot of little things,
chipping away and I love. One little too, chipping away and I love.
One little too little, three little problems, pretty seeing you and I'm all up. And all the King's horses and
all the King's men, couldn't put us back together again. We got a star, star, star,
chipping away and I love. Chipping away and I love. Chipping away and I love. One little too little,
three little, four little, pretty seeing you and I'm all up. And all the King's horses and all the
King's men couldn't put us back together again. We got a star, star, star, star,
chipping away and I love. Now there's got to be some source code listening on an interstate
somewhere I say, yeah, finally. It's my dirty little secret. I love country music. I really do.
It's so pure America. It doesn't exist anywhere else really in that it just country. It's
great country and jazz, man. Those are, I mean, country and jazz. Jesus Christ, my headphone is
shot. I think I have to purchase a new one. I've blown this one out by cranking that volume up too
loud. Another thing that's going to kill me, I'm sure. So that was a whole long second. Of course,
I immediately went past a chip chip chip. Rusty blue with Bill Anderson straight off the
pod safe music network, which is great. Just shows that there is more out there than you would
presume from something that's independent, but you heard the problem before that. I mean,
this is what's happening. This is a, oh, man, I sound like a broken record. By the way, you know what you
get when, when you spin country and Western music backwards, right? I wonder if you can do that
with Megasake. Can you reverse it? Let me say if you can reverse. No, no, you can probably do it in
quick time. But do that for yourself. But what happens when you, when you spin country and Western
music backwards is you get your house back and get your wife back, your dog is undead.
DailySourceco.com is where you can find the latest episode of this particular podcast. You can
subscribe to it if you're using iTunes. It's a real easy way to keep track of your podcast. It's a
free download from Mac and for Windows. You don't need an iPod necessarily. If you happen to have
one, gee, that'll work. That's really cool. That makes it all fit together. And of course,
feedback is more than welcome at Atomacurry.com. If you are going to send something, send an audio
feedback. Don't attach it. Please stick it up on a server somewhere and point to it. And I'll be
back tomorrow for the thank God it's Friday edition of the DailySourceco. You have yourself a great
day and we'll be talking tomorrow. Take care, everybody.