Delta Sierra Charlie 277.
No joke, this satellite radio company signed former MTVVJ Adam Curry as it's exclusive
PJ.
Amanda.
What a serious?
Yes.
From the streets of New Jersey to the suburbs of the UK, this is the man who trains media
as we know it.
And now, here is the Delhi source code with Adam Curry, Adam Curry.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
It is Friday.
How are you doing everybody coming to you from the lovely Sheraton in Ontario, California?
It is the podcast exploitation of the Delhi source code kicking off with the guy who
performed last night at the pod save.
Hold down.
Oh, there we go, round again.
Shut up and taste the way it's looking better.
I never want to scun.
It's a part of trip, but I never got out of the bus.
I don't know if you do like I said it's looking better.
I don't know if you do when I'm never reached by your way.
Say what you will, but maybe this is never made.
Say what you will, but maybe this is better.
Left on there.
When I look up, it hits me like it's yesterday's rain.
Say what you will, but maybe this is better than me.
I don't know if you do when I'm not reached by your way.
Believe me, say what you will but this is hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell, hell
Oh yeah, we just have full pleasures that are eleven attacks, whatever they do, they just link them up and they will let them leave.
I'm so true, they're very worthy of, they take shit without the right.
That they hurts if their penetrating stuff will never push you up,
I know this is gonna be the same
Say what you will, but this is better, this is better
So I'm live last night in the acoustic set
At the luxurious Melodout Mariah
Can't say what you will for the pot-safe music network
Oh, hey everybody how you doing if you're listening to us on serious satellite radio
Channel 103 serious stars and you're saying what the hell is going on here
This is the daily source code the beginning of the the pod shows spot spot quad pod squad line up
As heard every single week day after noon
And I am in Ontario, California not to be confused with with Ontario Canada
And this is the place where this weekend the first annual portable media expo is being held
Otherwise known as the podcast expo, although it officially is called the portable media expo
And we're here, the pod people are here and I witnessed that last night
Let me tell you what's oh by the way you're hearing the I'm in the there were no more rooms in the Mariah
So I'm in the Sheraton where you get the sweet sleeper bed by the way
I'm just noticing that and it wasn't too bad
It's early Friday morning and that's the air conditioning in the luxurious hotel
Sweet that I've been provisioned with it kicks in once every ten minutes
It's not much you can do about it just live with it, okay
Got in last night actually yesterday afternoon arrived around four o'clock from London on on virgin
On the upper class got to say love the flight once again
Although it wasn't a 747 this time it was an airbus and you can't fool me
The sweet chairs and it's just they called a sweet what you get your little sweet
They're shorter they're shorter than on the 747
But it was a good flight overall got a couple hours of sleep and was able to watch the movie that we had a lot of conversations about on the source code when it first came out
Willy Wonka's chocolate factory got to say I thought Johnny Depp actually did a fantastic job as as Willy Wonka
But I did miss kind of the evil the back story of the evil guys who were trying to steal the tickets or buy Charlie's ticket
There wasn't enough of that in there, but it was good. It was a fun movie to watch
And I tried to watch that kind of like that dark you drama about Brian Jones gets called stone and I fell asleep halfway through
Anyway, so got in and as you know virgin Atlantic has and this is not a paid endorsement
I just really love virgin Atlantic they give you a car service to and from the airport
And actually called him I said hey, you know, what if I have to go to like Ontario, California from LAX
And I said yeah, no problem. It's wherever you want to go
So Francisco drove me up out of hour and a half at that time a day and got in
And I decided to just stay awake and and wait for the pod save music
I called the pod save music hold down essentially CC Chapman and Craig Patchett
Organized this this little mini acoustic concert in the Marriott
They and of course pod show chiptain and sponsored and there were several other sponsors
For the show and it was it was just unbelievable
And I'm going to try and throughout throughout the show today I'll try and explain why it was so unbelievable and what's so cool about it
You have to understand that I believe at least a thousand maybe two thousand podcasters and not just podcasters
But also listeners have descended upon Ontario for this for this conference
And I kind of walked in expecting maybe a bit of like a nom dex vibe or a blogger con or one of these types of the
But no way this is something completely different
Sure all these people are still introverted
Crazy black jobs like myself who are much more comfortable
You know burping into a microphone than anything else
But it was really a very interesting set of people and the must have been I think by the time Chan's gone on stage
Chan's and brother loved performed last night when Chan's got on stage
It was filling up. It was like 150 people. It was a nice size room
Sorry my eyes. Oh man. I'm going to put my lenses in today
And I don't know if I can be able to make it my eyes are not really participating anyway
And you know so I walk in and it's like everyone wanted to say hi and and of course I met just about all hundred or 150 people who were there last night
And there were, you know, there were names that are recognized. There were shows that are recognized. There were voices that I recognized
But it really looked like
Oh man. How can I explain it?
It was so much more of a revolutionary vibe than any of the other conferences that I've been to
These people are just unbelievably enthusiastic about what they're doing about the change that's happening
About the music that's involved man. A lot of talk about pod safe music and about my recent experiences with the RIA or the European versions of it
And just a really really good crowd
Good to see and you know that I had never met CC Chapman in person so it was good to hook up with CC
Who looks just like his character chair
You know for the logo for a show. It is. It's so CC. It's amazing.
We have a number of other pod squad members who came up for the festivities. I think the mommy casters are in town
I saw Chris Rockwell, daily download Chris McIntyre from podcast Dally and a lot of the music shows
I met Mark from the Tarton podcast Big Mike from the accessible access show
Oh man. I met Trucker Tom who I've been a big fan of and been listening to for a long time
And it was great. There was an actual meeting between Trucker Tom who is this
Well, I hope I can find this picture because we actually took a picture of me in between Trucker Tom and Madge
And Madge of course Madge got a new dress got a new hairdo got new shoes
And it was just it was it was very very different and you know take along with that that I was completely tripping on jet lag and you know and some other
Some other things that seem to be circulating around the conference and it was just it was a big trip
So I got in around midnight and I thought about doing a show last night about so incredibly tired and
I thought that I wouldn't be able to do the show on the mobile setup
You know I have the the baranger mixer and the and the vocal processor
You know the setup that I tested and Brussels last time we actually that is that is that is that's the time before last the show before last
And as I'm unpacking it, you know getting ready to set up
I noticed that the power adapter for the mixer
Stupidest thing in the world is only 240 volts to
What do I need here 12 volts on this board and I'm like oh man because usually goes from like a hundred to 240
And you can plug it in anywhere in the world and it just says right now
Let me see if it's getting warm
It's not even warm. We'll see AC adapter. Yeah, it says PRI 230 volts 50 hertz
No, 50 hertz that's even something else because we have 60 hertz here in the states
I believe and it to outputs to 12 volts one amp and and I plug it in and guess what it works
Although I have to say the lights are kind of you know kind of flickering and dimming
When I'm talking on the on the LED readout and there's a horrible hum somewhere
So hopefully it'll all just kind of hang together
But it is it is basically working
So as I said last night lots of talk about pod safe music and my recent experiences and lots of feedback about that today as well
Adam Bruce Williams from audio to you dot com how I am
I just finished the commute listening to DSC 275 and I've got to say I was pissed off
Listening to talking about these cock suckers in the Netherlands who think that you know
Isn't it great the way an Australian says cock sucker a cock suckers?
No, if we don't hurry up and play ball they're gonna shut down podcasting
Please this how the hell do they think they're gonna do that?
They're gonna suddenly make it against the Lord of being possession of RSS code
Man unbelievable anyway something I wanted to talk about with you was up until last weekend
I had eight different podcast channels running off audio to you.com
Now the reason I put all that in the past tense is because three of those channels were supplied by a mate of mine
Dom Romeo and Dom's just been approached by somebody who wants to buy all of his back catalog of interviews
Basically all of Dom's intellectual property which is great for Dom
It's bad for me and my listeners because it means that pretty soon
I'm gonna have to take all that content down off the audio to you dot com servers
Which is fine? I understand that you know you had to go where there was money. That's fair enough
The three podcasts that he supplied me one of them was called bum notes and that was a weekly music news segment
And I'll be straight up front man. That was not pod safe. He would you know research all the things that happened in the world of music over the pre-seeding week
And you know there would be bits of songs from the artists that were mentioned
The next podcast that he had was called Stan and Deliver which was a series of weekly interviews with comedians
And the last one which is the one I want to discuss was called waxing lyrical and it was a series of interviews on a weekly basis again
with musicians and as you would expect
Those interviews featured the music of the artist who was being promoted
So you know he had an interview with Bodiddly and that podcast featured Bodiddly music
So where exactly does that fall because you're promoting the artist
So you would think that it would be okay to use the music of the artist because you're promoting the artist
But the artist is licensed and therefore you know not pod safe as we would say
So just interested to know what what happens in an instance like that
You know the s-cap BMIs of the world gonna you know jump on podcasts is from a great height
For promoting a licensed act
That's just the biggest case of shooting yourself in the foot of ever heard
Anyway, can you hear your thoughts?
Can you hear more pod safe music because there's some absolutely fantastic stuff on the pod safe music network
The song you played in 275 right at the end Bob Gentry I think his name was was awesome
Anyway, dude, that's it from me. Keep up the good work and we'll talk to you soon. See ya.
Right now I'm buddy and Bob Gentry is gonna be up here by the way. We're gonna try and hook up
I had a little email back and forth with him and he said that you know, he's selling records
Actually brother love said last night. He said dude first time I made rent money because of sales of my music
So let me sorry about the condition of background. Let me try and address this because there's so many questions about it
In essence the way the way the licensing works. I'll just try and run through it again really quickly
There are two pieces and the piece that that should be easily solvable is the broadcast performance part
Which is what ask happened be am I take care of but using that alone won't allow you to actually play any any license music whatsoever
You still have to have the the rights from the owner of the master which typically is the the record company
So if you have those two pieces then yeah you can you can pretty much although the Harry Fox agency may jump in there
At some point and try and grab some money as well and there's C sack and other organizations which is why you know after I've really done the work on
On investigating what the possibilities are I've just I've given up on it. You know and I think that
Although it really is a shame when I hear that you know it's like you know we legally can't do a profile on bow didly you know
Who of course is a legend
I think the only way to play this right now is to just ignore him just ignore all license music
And when we have the numbers and we can prove and substantiate the the kinds of numbers that the
Music industry I think is looking for because I'm not thinking promotion. They're thinking only sales and theory
That's the only way they look at it. Yeah, yeah promotion is great, but we got radio stations. We don't need all that
But you know now you're kind of stealing this to put this on your show
That's all that they're concerned about and I'd really hope that through mashups and hit tests
We could actually create enough
Momentum that
Enough sales momentum because I was you know quite cognizant of what the record industry is really looking for
I hope that we would be able to convince in time by saying hey look you know
This is not stealing music. This is actually promoting music and look at resulting in sales
I have to say was not successful at achieving that that fell on pretty much deaf ears
I think we have to come back when we have you know when we're doing a million spins for pod safe songs
You know and then maybe we can turn the tables and maybe we we ask for we ask for a couple more things
When they come back to us and say hey gee, you know you guys are really kicking ass there
Okay, would you mind playing some of our tunes and that's where I think the tables are turned and where we get to say no
I don't think so because your licensing is all out of whack and maybe you should get that straight home in a second
This is the
The pod pimp Aaron or so
Let me just see what's going on
Hey Aaron
Hello
Did that work?
Oh, okay
Missed the call
Yeah, that's typical
Lots of stuff going on. I guess the
The expo the first keynote starts in about 25 minutes
I don't think I'm going to make the first one
And one of the things being streamed live at all
That's what I enjoy so much about nom decks and blogger con and pop tech and stuff like that
I don't know if this conference has a life streaming feed or not
Because you know that way you can kind of do you can multitask you know you can begin your room getting ready for something
And you can still listen to some of the conference some of the the keynotes that are going on
So I hope that well, I'm sure this is going to be one of the most podcast events in history
So I'm sure I'll be able to get everything I'm looking for after the fact
So
Yeah, so it's I must say the the feedback that I've been getting about about going 100% pod safe
Proud to be pod safe has been just phenomenal and I've been getting more
Yeah, I got you Aaron, I see you boys milk
I've been getting
More offers of pod safe music than ever before the signups at the pod safe music network
And oh by the way, there's just to be very clear it's that's not the only place you can get music that could be Dean pod safe
You can get it from places like Garage Band and Megatoon
But what is taking care of at the pod safe music network is the basically the license that if you sign up as a podcaster
Anything you see on the pod safe music network you can use without having to pay for a license
And the artist has a similar set of rights where they can also if they want to take their
So on right off the pod safe music network no longer have that license in effect
Go ahead, the license is over there and they're there for the reading
And if you have any comments we'd love to hear about them we've changed them in the past
If the community felt that they should be adjusted a little bit
But I think that we're so far we're doing pretty good on
On all that although there is one lingering question which I think is solved, but we're going to get a legal opinion on it
If someone has a song that is registered with AskCapper BMI for the performance rights
And they still put it on the pod safe music network
The opinion I guess is that for that's a separate agreement
It's a separate licensing arrangement the artist at all times is in charge
It's not like BMI and AskCapper all of a sudden are in charge of their work
They're a collection agency so if it's on the pod safe music network then you have a license to play
That without having to play a performance royalty
That's pretty much the answer to that question
Let's see, I think there was a couple more about pod set music
Let's see what we have here
What's up man, I'm Mrs. J Mag from hoodide.com again
I had a quick quick, well actually let me first apologize at the sound quality
This is the guy from hoodide.com which is a rap hip hop R&D podcast of pod safe music
Which is kind of hard to find and this feedback will explain a little bit why I think
Hopefully you can make it through this without getting totally irritated with my voice and the quality of this through the phone
My microphone a home sproke
Anyway, what I'm trying to do is get more artists off of this
You know from the street and onto the internet
The problem is a lot of people don't deal with computers are kind of scared of the internet
So I had an idea was to you know the service taxi if you're not already familiar with it
It's just an ANR service. All they do is they're a conduit between record labels and artists
The record label puts up a class of five listed being the artists and it's their music to taxi taxi
The taxi's ANRs take a look at the music
If it's worthy to be submitted to the label then they turn around and submit it to label otherwise
They send it back to the artists to let them know you know what could be changed or whatever
Anyway, having said that taxi probably has a massive database of unsigned artists
Which these are paying members. They pay like $300 a year to be a part of the service
So my idea is this try to form a relationship with taxi to the point where when they're
Members and on and for their existing members to offer them a membership into the pot safe music network
Now this would allow artists to put in whatever songs into the pot safe music database under that license
So that's the thing that I'm getting at is I'm wondering if we have a way that we can we can tap into that
And I contacted a guy named Chris over at the taxi yesterday
And he said that they only deal with really huge record labels and really big film production companies
Which kind of it was a downer for me, but you know we're talking
I mean if we can go at them with your numbers with your pot, you know for your daily source code and for the
Pot safe music network and say look this is something small this is something that's eventually taking over radio
If we can show them that maybe it will be a valuable asset for them to offer to their to their artists
The thing is they it needs to be something of value because these people are paying paying good money to be a member of the service
So having said that I would really like to hear your feedback on that. I would also like to hear back feedback from any other podcast
Or so if you can email me my email addresses JT Mac JT MCK at Gmail.com
Or you can actually call me and I don't mind if you play it on the air my my cell phone numbers 810 599 0202
I would love to hear what you have to say and I'd really like to see if you have any other resources as far as getting people from
You know from the streets on to into the pot safe music network and ultimately you know into my
Five cast as well as other people
And also I forgot to mention the beauty of this thing was it is it is a service that's online
It's through the internet, but it originated through you know they have catalogs and the people mail their stuff in
So that's the big thing is you know that's that's getting people who aren't necessarily on the internet
So that's a huge thing anyway. Good back with me. Thank you so much Adam have a great day. I love the show.
See yeah right on buddy
Well here's what we've done
We have hired Michael Butler who of course already was a member of the pod squad
Doing the rock and roll geek show and he's also managing the music block on the serious on the on the serious 103
Which airs I think between 9 and 10 and 930 and 10
Oh, before I forget Monday starting Monday on serious 103 right after the daily source code Pacific Coast Hellway
Our new pod squad member to join
If you're listening to serious and even if you're not you know if you're if you can't wait for Howard Stern to show up
Give Pacific Coast Hellway a shot
I think you'll like it
So we've got Michael Butler in and Michael what he's been doing he's been doing this proactive work
So if if you if you if you're confused if you don't have a computer
Or if it's a little bit too daunting give them a call at at pod show
I think
What is the what's our phone number?
Hold on a second. It's like 27704. Oh, oh, I think on let me see
27704 oh, oh, yeah, I think that's it in a 415 area code
Just give Michael Butler call and and he'll definitely help you out and hook you up because that's where all about
Did you hear the the beginning of the show?
Now you know you really made it
When you become a question on jeopardy. Let's see if I can play this thing again
Hot cast for a thousand no joke. This satellite radio company signed former MTV VJ Adam Curry as it's exclusive PJ PJ Amanda
What a serious. Yes, I'll take what's I'm a PJ everybody
I tell you my family got a kick out of that my aunt emailed me that. She's like, oh my god. You were questioning on jeopardy
Oh my goodness. Okay, we got lots more feedback for some reason on today's show not a lot of promo is but a lot of feedback
I think I hope I didn't play this one by my mark. So I've kind of been shuffling stuff around and I don't of course
I've forgot you know half of the stuff I was supposed to be with my really want to whoops get this out
Because again, it's just bugging me. I heard your podcast Monday regarding what the the record companies are doing again
And I'm not in the recording business, but I really am getting frustrated by everything sounding the same looking the same and here it is, you know
There is this great tool we have it's podcasting. I'm one of a hundred million people ready to embrace something different
I mean if an artist can understand that this is a great on ramp to get noticed. I mean I am ready to give you money
I promise I will and there's people out there all they want to they're tired of the radio
They're tired. They want they're looking for juice. They're looking for something that that's exciting
That's real and you can tell the fake stuff from the good stuff and please all I'm saying to anybody out there with talent let it out there
I mean if I had some talent, I don't care about the money so much right now as it is to let your your gift out there for the masses to know what it is
And that's what we've got to stay together on this because podcasts are right on this
This is a correct way of going and this is what's going to make us win in the long end long run. It is because it's right and it's about time
We all stand up to all the BS out there and we say no. This is how it's going to happen because we need it
This is a change that is going on now and if you don't do it this way guess what we get the same old crap day in and day out
I'm tired of it. No way the door has been open just a little bit and that's enough for me
And I hope it's enough for millions of other people out there. Thanks. Alright Mark. I think I did actually play that
But guys so enthusiastic
I just want to play it again for you. Well, it's definitely what's happening here at the podcast expo people are really motivated
They're getting their heart out there and we're having a shitload of fun doing
From the podcast we've got to where now. We've got brain bucket let the book be loose on your daily source code
Spaced us through my eye
Strike a treat off sky looks good to the bone
What a show but I got to get home to the lady
My bro
Says it out yet to it I got no time
Good loving
I work a man like sister and because of no matter what it gets tight
But I still get the town to not get through time
Just say it's the same old shit just a
Given day let the book be loose
Let the book be loose
Let the book be loose today
The man he offers him way
Let the book be loose tonight
In a matter of time he'll feel it alright
Drink up
Put down the seeds
I shed the light on the brand
The day he has stretched my own
To give a sigh
I watched the cross by
Not a hot eyes I hit out
Don't let him
No shame and jamming
Don't let him around
Roll out
Just do the show
All these girls ain't knocking
I find those no worries
Money gets tired
But I still get the town to not get through time
Just say it's the same old shit
Just a different day let the book be loose
Let the book be loose
Let the book be loose today
The day he offers him way
Let the book be loose tonight
In a matter of time he'll feel it alright
Feel it alright
All these girls ain't knocking
No shame and jamming
Don't let him around
Roll out
Just do the show
All these girls ain't knocking
No shame and jamming
Don't let him around
Roll out
Just say it's the same old shit
Yeah so you look quite strong
Everything is all taken care of for your mister lattice
Lets see what this is
This is from Rogers
Hello Adam Roger here
I've just been listening to your show from Monday
And it sounds like you aren't able to do any more hits
for a while
Now don't worry
Slowly be 10 Korean
Until the music industry comes calling
About once you need to give the products and promotions to drink
In the meantime I get you a nice little quick situ
You're a plant on your show
All you have to do is guest the everyday household
and from the noises that they made.
Okay.
Firstly, I don't think it's very fair of jump, flat, to ask you to name the famous songs.
Especially considering your whole career was based on talking over the beginning of them.
Anyway, it's the first sound just getting to help.
I'll give you a clue, Dan. I think it's a bit tricky.
There's a pair of them and you can use them to cut things.
Is this a second one?
Okay, scissors.
Then to these rules, things that you find lying around the living room.
There we go.
That's the thing you have to pay back in that ear and you will just listen to that.
Okay.
Right, here's the last one.
That would be a drill, I guess.
Like this.
A lighter?
Okay, so that's all three noises.
There's this one, there's this one.
And the other one as well, which I won't like,
just take too long.
Okay, give you a minute just to think about the answer.
I'm just a new one.
This is Roger Smalls who is kind of a stalker.
He's written some stuff on my weblog in the past that I found very disturbing.
And I appreciate the effort there, Roger.
We'll check back in with Roger a little bit lately.
I'm Suzanne.
I'm Robin.
We are in siteworks.com.
That's INSYTWORKS.com.
Where we believe in site and really works inside into ourselves.
And into others.
We look at everyday events.
And not so everyday events.
Under the lens of depth psychology.
Some of our past podcasts have included forgiveness, fear, decision making.
A really popular one that we did was body weight issues.
We've talked a lot about grief and some discouraging responses in grief.
Yeah, we've also talked about emotional parasites.
Are you a parasite?
Do you know a parasite or do you host them?
And those are all in the past.
Let's talk about the future.
Some future shows we expect to do are displaced anger.
Expectations in relationship.
And we also are going to feature about dreams.
Perfectionism.
And money, honey.
And somewhere along the way we will do a podcast about the theories of CGO and depth psychology.
The hot one is going to be when we talk about deviant sexual behavior.
How do you define it?
What is it?
And do you do it?
We will also start a series on self-injurious behavior.
Also known as cuttings.
Suzanne is doing her thesis on cutting.
If you're ready to get real and you're ready to get relevant, you are ready to get with us.
Robin and Suzanne at insightworks.com.
So check us out and we'll talk to you soon.
Bye for now.
Thanks for sharing the journey.
Deviant sexual behavior, huh?
All right.
I'm subscribed.
Here's a song that definitely characterizes what is going on here in Ontario with the portable
Media Expo.
Monk, who I'm hoping to hook up with, talks about it.
The pod people.
Yeah.
You seem lovely.
Be in the right to me.
Everything I need.
Better than the old dead frequency.
From underground.
Hold down the sound.
Come set the fire.
Burn the old dial.
The China's now.
You are never alone.
All I know is a ground.
Can't stand the title of all this.
And then you are wasted.
You've been brought to the bomb.
Say, we'll call you and you'll be the same.
You say, we're wasted.
If I need one, take it over.
I need one, take it over.
In visions coming closer.
We're in control.
Everywhere you go.
Once we start the blow.
You're in the know.
Like the BCHL.
Can't stop the bleeding.
Suck away the green.
Break down the beach.
Liberate for free.
Kill the radial crew.
You are never alone.
All I know is a ground.
Can't stand the title of all this.
And then you are wasted.
You've been brought to the bomb.
Say, we'll call you and you'll be the same.
Say, we're wasted.
If I need one, take it over.
I need one, take it over.
In visions coming closer.
If I need one, take it over.
I can ride the holding glasses
and you can do that
And in nature the chemicals are
But dear, this is paperwork
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yeah oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh I can't understand the old let's play
Give yourself some extra boost, nice remote control, and then there's the Bluetooth headphones,
which also work with your iPod.
So check them out at Logitech.
I guess Logitech.com.
If you go to, if you go to daily source code to the show notes, there's probably a link
there, also a podshow.com.
There's websites really coming along.
I'm liking what I'm seeing here.
In fact, we also have a, let me go to it here.
We have a, let me say, hold on.
Podshow.
We have a rundown of what we're doing here at the expo.
Let's see.
So we have the Podset Music concert that was last night.
Then tonight at six o'clock at the Marriott, the Don and Drew Appreciation Party.
We have the Podshow podcast lounge.
Look for Aaron Bursell.
He's a big guy, you can't miss him.
He's a big guy looking like a big podpimp.
Find him if you want to come hang out at the lounge.
He Michael Butler is going to be around.
Actually saw him last night as well.
The Firf, Chris McIntyre is hanging around from the Podcast.
Ali, Steve Gilmore, was he going to be here?
I won't, yes, Gilmore is going to be here, I think.
I think we're doing the Gilmore gang, could do something this morning.
The mommy casters here with their daddies and magic courses running around doing all kinds
of wacky stuff, we're doing video reports.
So if you want to see those go to podshow.com, you can sign up and you'll get the URL for
the feed to subscribe.
Just one more thing I want to mention, slow is still working with Ronald and CC on the
if every day we're Christmas, we're trying to put together, actually, I think now that
what they're going to do is they're going to tag this song as owned by UNICEF with
ASCAP BMI.
So if it does get played outside the Podcast arena, then any money derived from that will
go to UNICEF.
So that's very cool.
They're looking for more soloists to sing along and they're looking for lots of people
to be in the chorus, so I want you to give CC Chapman, drop them a line, drop an email.
And hopefully, by Monday, slow says you might have something for me to listen to, so we
can start kind of previewing the work as it goes along, which I think is very, very cool.
Yeah, I'm a speedy love with Love House radio.
Wanted to tell you something that you're probably already aware of.
And that is that you're a very lucky man.
Yeah.
I'm not talking about your lovely wife or your wonderful family, I'm not talking
about your jet set life going to and from the UK to San Francisco or Pod Show or your
airplane or what are you talking about?
What I'm talking about is PWFN.
PWFN.
He does.
Rob at Pod cast four one one.
You everyone has been just truly helpful.
Um, so my show has kind of evolved into playing a lot of jazz and blues on Friday.
Uh, starting picking up the tunes off the Pod Safe Music Network and some of them were
PWFN in the second ward.
Uh, they just seemed to fit the mood for a Friday afternoon kind of easing to the weekend.
And so I figured, you know, what the heck?
I'll shoot PWMO.
See if you wouldn't mind throwing together a little intro for the Jazzy Friday show.
and a swear five hours later in my mailbox, I had this.
Hi, this is PW Fenton.
Man, Friday is such a great day.
In some ways, it's better than the weekend
because it's the beginning of the weekend.
And whenever I wanna begin my weekend
in a kind of jazzy, bluesy kind of vibe,
I listen to Love House Radio
because, well, that's where the love is.
So now I have to change everything
all of my slogans to read where that's where the love is.
I mean, PW has set the tone now.
But I just thought that was amazing.
Just wanted to share that with you.
You already know what you've got,
but I just wanted to prove to you that, yes.
PW is the man.
And next time you have a spat with him,
I'm gonna have to go on his side.
So anyway, take it easy, keep it real.
Thanks a lot, Adam.
Okay, so I'll probably be doing a show
over the weekend Saturday.
Maybe even Sunday since there's so much going on here.
Stay tuned to the podcast from around the globe
coming to you from Ontario, California.
And we'll meet each other if not Monday.
Maybe over the weekend.
Take care, everybody.
Bye bye now.
Another podcast, stick it in your ear.