Daily source code April 18, 2005.
Your DJ has only just begun.
$16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hey, everybody.
How you doing?
A brand new week.
It's Monday the 18th of April.
We are back at the cottage.
Sheel and out in the big green thing.
I've got the cast blast of Roland.
I've kind of extended all the wires.
So I'm sitting in the reclining green thing.
It's a big ass chair.
With a laptop with a pen and a microphone.
And the infamous words of back what more do you need than two turn tables in a microphone?
Ah, good to be back with you.
Good to have the microphone.
The big setup, which of course is plugged in through the little box.
My father-in-law made to give it the perfect signal into the microphone in.
And I got all kinds of stuff lined up for you.
We've got a mash-up, a young pull-out is sent me another hit test.
And of course a couple of tunes.
As always, I'm going to play for you here on the source code.
So trippy to be using the pen on the screen.
I don't have this tablet.
It basically is a laptop where you can do as you can open up the screen and swivel it.
And then twist it backwards and fold it up over the keyboard.
Which gives it that distinct tablet feel.
But basically I'm just using a combination out of the mouse and the pen.
Because with the pen I can just point to the screen grab the fader and crank it up or crank it down and hit the microphone button.
A beautiful system.
Okay, lots of stuff to talk about today.
Maybe the first observation I have to make is that I am getting a little discouraged with Gmail.
Although I still totally dig what Gmail brings to the party with search-based email.
I really am enjoying using that and you're able to open up your email on a browser anywhere and keep all these browser windows open.
Great way to synchronize of course across multiple machines.
And I have three now that I'm using full time.
I've got the power book which is hooked up to the sound system and to the mixer of course.
That's what I use.
That's what I use my iPod or on.
So I can listen to podcasts and actually schedule them in a different Mac program called Megaseg.
So that can kind of format them.
So I have different shows playing in different.
I kind of arrange the order in which they come in based upon some rules.
I have a lot of fun with that actually creating my own radio station here at home which just runs continuously.
And even if I walk out of the room and come back later, you know, I have it scheduled so certain things repeat after a while.
If it's a real short podcast and if I might not have heard it then it'll just play later on.
And if something comes up that I've heard I hit a key and then it identifies that I've already heard it moves on to the next one.
It's something I'm playing around with something that I think will be effective for home, car and personal walking around uses as we move podcasting into even more convenient ways to listen.
So to Gmail, I don't know but I'm getting a hell of a lot of spam.
And here's the disappointing part.
You know, you have this.
What does it? What do they call it? Reports spam? Let me just see.
I'm just take a quick look at my Gmail here.
If it's spam, they call it.
I'm on pulling it up here.
Yeah, report spam, right?
And I report spam all the time.
And what you'd think is that by hitting the report spam button that essentially, you know, Gmail would know,
okay, this is spam. We won't show that to you anymore, but it just keeps on coming back.
The same forms of spam, the same, you know, from the same spammer, basically.
And then you have the report fishing and fishing spelled with PH is a form of tricking users into thinking that you're getting an email from.
Typically, it's PayPal or Amazon or, you know, one of these big services that you probably actually have an account with.
And they fake it so that it looks like it's real only if you were to click on these links.
And usually it's like, you know, we need to verify your account or, you know, provide us your password.
Of course, you're not supposed to do that anyway.
But, you know, you have this, all these dialogue boxes so you can report this fishing activity.
And I don't know, do these guys do anything with it? I'm just literally, if I look at one full page of Gmail.
So that's 50 emails, what I have it set to, at least 60% is spam.
And it's, and yeah, you can navigate through it pretty quickly, but it's not, it sucks.
And then you have this creative filter.
And that would be another great way to do it.
You know, it's just creative filter based upon this email, but the creative filter still forces you to fill out, you know, the fields,
what you want to be filtered out.
So it's not working for me that well anymore.
And, you know, I like my adamantcurry.com, which forwards to my Gmail account.
I want to keep that, you know, I want to keep my Gmail account.
I don't want to switch accounts. I want to keep it all as it is.
But the spam is just becoming cumbersome and a big burden.
So the question to the guys over at Google is, what the hell are you doing about the spam?
Hi, Adam, this is Greg in New York.
And I want to tell you about my new podcast, celebrityvinylheaven.com.
It's the only podcast devoted to records made by your favorite TV and movie stars.
People like William Schatter, Telly Savolis, Mr. T and more.
Whether you love him or you love to hate him, we always have a good time at celebrityvinylheaven.com.
As another thing I've really been missing out on is playing the promo.
And people, I guess the MP3 feedback at gmail.com isn't working anymore.
I get a whole bunch of reports that email is still getting bounced back.
So the best thing to do is, you know what we should do?
I could set up a filter for this. This would be great.
If you want to send me a promo for your podcast, send it to adamantcurry.com.
And in the subject line, put dsc space promo.
Because I'll filter based upon that and then don't attach the file.
Just put a URL to somewhere where I can pick the file up so that my gmail account doesn't overload.
Even though we have two gigs now, hold on, let me grab my tea.
I'm not drinking a scentsato today. I'm having a nice cup of tea.
I had already like three scentsails this morning.
And I'm buzzing.
So let's do it that way.
And then I'll set up a filter so that it'll be easier for me to manage the incoming promos.
And they're getting really cool.
People are putting some real thought into the promo,
they're sending and I appreciate it.
And I love playing them for you.
I'm here for the gang bang.
Wait, what was that?
I'm here for the gang bang?
Oh, well, listen to that again.
I'm here for the gang bang.
Hey Adam, it's Kevin Crossman from the Frat Pack podcast.
You know the Frat Pack, Ben Stiller Will Ferrell, Owen Wilson, Ben Spawn.
All those guys in this comedy movies,
will we cover it all on the Frat Pack podcast?
Including this little ditty that you might recognize.
So fun, Adam.
This isn't really a hit test, but see if you can recognize this.
I know what it is.
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah.
How could you ever forget David's soul?
Don't give up on his baby.
Don't make them seem right.
If you choose and just get it, Adam.
That's David's soul.
The original Hatch from Strasking Hatch with his version of Don't Give Up on Us Baby.
That was a number one hit in 1977.
You and your listeners will want to check out our recent Strasking Hatch musical special,
including a version of that song from Owen Wilson.
Alright, cool.
Well, we cover all the weird wacky fun with the Frat Pack on our Frat Pack podcast.
Just go to www.capedo.com, K-E-V-D-O, dot com to learn more about the Frat Pack.
Check out the wedding crazier starring Vince Vaughn and Owen Wilson and the summer.
And that's it, thanks Adam.
Yeah, it was a Frat Pack.
Get another podcast.
Let's check in the iPodr.org directory.
Now, well over 5,000 podcasts listed and actively tracked in the directory.
iPodr.org.
We are really kicking some ass with this stuff.
So I'm going to play a song for you.
This is something that I wanted to play on Saturday when I did my last podcast from Central Park.
I think I even mentioned it at the end of the show.
It would have been nice to have had the cast blaster with me to kind of like fade this one in.
While I was sitting there listening to the birds chirping and the kids playing.
A man-son ice cream singing Italian song Chicago Saturday in the park.
I like the night in the morning.
I think it was the fun of July.
People can't see people laughing.
A man selling ice cream singing Italian song.
You can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that they can't even say that.
One other day, you're the heart.
I think it was the fun of July.
People can't really smell it.
I'm happy singing for a song.
Will you help me change the world?
Can you take it?
Yes, I can.
And I've been waiting so long time.
I will take it.
Slow motion riders.
Fly the colors of the beat.
A crowd's man still can't tell stories in some way.
These children all have lost.
All have lost all have lost.
For the day, you're the heart.
I think it was the fun of July.
People can't really smell it.
Chicago Saturday in the park.
I think it was the 4th of July.
Actually, I'll be spending this 4th of July in the United States.
I'll be in Portland, Oregon.
Here's the deal.
I'm doing a keynote at Nomdex.
What is that somewhere around the 23rd, I believe, 24th?
Yeah, 23rd through 25th, the thing is Nomdex 5.
Instead of flying straight back from Seattle, which is where Nomdex is being held,
I'm going to go to Portland, Oregon.
That's where I'm going to hook up on the 27th, I think, with the Wing Commander.
Wing Commander William, my flight instructor.
He will be going to do some training for a couple days.
On the 2nd or 3rd, I'll be getting my fixed wing ticket,
my PPL, my private pilot's license.
Of course, if all goes according to plan.
Lots of training between then and now.
That's actually cranking up tomorrow.
We've got the airport right nearby tomorrow.
The Wing Commander will be showing up.
I guess somewhere between 8 and 9 a.m. he'll be flying over from Antwerp with the Cessna 182 RG.
RG stands for retractable gear.
Then we're going to do some training all day Tuesday and then check this out.
Wednesday, we're also going to do some flight training Wednesday, but first at 11 a.m. on Wednesday.
The Dutch Marines, I think I told you the story when we did a weeklong broadcast from Iraq
from Camp Smitty. I was all live on Dutch radio.
We were there in the compound and also went all over the place with these guys
to different camps, different cities, different towns within South Western Iraq.
What was cool about that broadcast wasn't so much.
Of course, it was great that people back home could hear what we were experiencing
and we were talking to Marines and they were giving shoutouts back home.
I still get parents coming up to me saying thank you so much for building that virtual bridge
between me and my child, which was just that really blew me away.
It still does when people come up to me and say that.
But I had a 100 watt FM transmitter, a professional transmitter that I somehow acquired somewhere along the line
in my broadcast days. I used to use that at the castle so that you could just put a tuner on or a CD
and put one sound source and hear that throughout the entire place just by tuning in the FM radio.
Don't need that so much anymore now that we have streaming iTunes and all that stuff.
But I had taken that over with me and we set it up at the base camp so that the Marines,
at that point, had listened to all of their CD collections at least 15 or 20 times and were pretty bored.
I could actually listen to our broadcasts, not just our broadcasts.
Excuse me, but we also had a satellite dish with a downlink.
So they could also listen 24 hours a day to the radio station radio Veronica is the station that we did that for.
And I remember distinctly walking around through the tents and the prefab units and seeing groups of people
huddled around the radio just listening, listening to the radio, doing nothing else but looking at the wireless.
The way it used to be when back in the day before television you'd sit down.
Martha, Martha, I've got Pittsburgh on the wireless, you know, the green hornet show.
And so we decided right then and there, I wouldn't leave this transmitter, you know,
and Veronica was also kind enough to leave their downlink and their satellite dish.
And so for the god how long have they been there a year and a half now or a little, yeah, but a year and a half I guess.
You know, they were able to follow along with everything going on back home and it really boosted morale, which of course was the whole point in the first place.
And the Dutch marines have now left.
I think the English are pretty much now.
The English and Japanese are now in the camps MIDI, keeping watch.
And the Dutch marines are back.
And so they want to, you know, obviously return my transmitter.
Now, you got to know that, you know, we built up quite a relationship with a number of these guys.
And as does happen when you're in fricking desert, you know, surrounded by potential danger.
Certainly, we were making friends left and right.
And so they decided to do something rather unique.
And I'm supposed to show up on a field in Holland, in Nardin, which is near Hilversum at 11 o'clock.
And I guess they're going to show up with a cougar helicopter.
And four or five marines are going to repel down with the transmitter and give it back to me.
So they're putting on a show.
And I'm really looking forward to that.
And of course, I'll be doing some sound seeing over the next few days.
And I, oh, that's what I wanted to mention.
I picked up when I was last day in New York, Ron and I went to RCS Experience, which is the store on,
it's like, it's across from Sony's building.
So it's like Madison in 55 to 56.
And it's just a store with cool gadgets, all, you know, laptops, hand-held,
satellite radio receivers, and everything you could need to go along with that, you know, like headphones.
In fact, I got a new headset.
I got a a send-hizer headset with built-in microphone, which is built specifically for gaming.
And I'm very happy with the quality of it.
I'm not using it now, obviously, I'm using my regular microphone, I'm sure, through the,
through the, the processor so we get the sound that I want.
But it's really very nice headset, particularly for Skype.
And the main reason is that it doesn't go over your head, but it goes behind your neck.
You know, it's one of those types of headsets, which is great because I wear it.
My glasses almost all the time since I discovered that glasses give you much better vision than contact lenses.
And if you're a spectacle where you'll know that putting the headset on really after about 10,
15 minutes, just want to kill yourself from the pain because, you know, the,
the feet of your glasses start digging into your head because of the pressure from the headphones.
And of course, I could take them off, but then, you know, I'm basically, you know, blind, I can't see anything.
And in the store, there was, I think, oops, sorry, I think I have, I'm going to put it to my back here somewhere.
This, of course, is the drawback of sitting in the big green thing with the laptop.
I'm not very mobile. I can't just hop up and go somewhere here. It's my bag.
It's a brand new belkin. I started in high belkin.
Griffin lapel microphone.
And it's, uh, because the only drawback really is that it's white.
So, you know, you can pretty, you can really see that I'm wearing a microphone.
But it's a stereo mic, and I tried it with the eye river, and I'm really pleased with the sound.
And particularly because this is a stereo mic, you get a whole different vibe than the stuff I've been using.
And the microphone only costs like, yeah, I don't know.
Do I have the, I don't have the receipt, but I think it was maybe like 19 bucks or something.
And, you know what, I recorded a short test, a sound seeing test.
Oh, this is not going to do something dangerous here. I'm going to see if I can open.
Now, this is true integration, ladies and gentlemen, I'm going to open up in the cast blaster on the windows tablet.
I'm going to my network places.
And it should say, let me see, I should be able to open up my, yes.
I can open up, I can access my Mac because it has windows sharing enabled.
I'm going to go to the desktop now, let me see if I can find it.
I think this is it.
Oh, let me just select it.
So, you know, the big benefit here is that it, it's just a microphone.
So it doesn't have a preamp or in the case of the stuff that I have.
It doesn't, that I've been using with my wireless mic set.
I have to carry these two black boxes with me.
And this, well, hold on a second, let's see if this is it.
Yeah.
Okay, this is a, a test of the new setup.
Hold on a second.
Right, so I was in the lobby of the, the Waldorf Hotel,
while I was, while I plugged it in.
So basically all I have is just my eye river.
I've got my, my little iPod headphones plugged into listen to it.
And then I plugged the, the griffin mic in and listened to the quality.
And listen to the, particularly the stereo sound.
With the brand new microphone, stereo microphone.
And I think I'm digging it already, this listening to what's on my headphones.
It's so dynamic, you can hear.
It's really popping out my, my ear buds here.
I put my bag on walking through the lobby of the Waldorf Historian.
It's just completely cool.
Lots of intelligent talk there, curry.
stereo system.
stereo mic.
And you can really hear it's by Norl recording, even.
Not quite sure about sounds a little bit nasal perhaps.
But wow.
Getting a great stereo.
Soundscape.
And I got the headphones on.
And we just, for this, focus a little bit this.
Come on.
Wanted to help.
Well, I think we shouldn't do too often.
Probably like health, style, microphone.
I can already tell that I probably need a.
Probably need a wind screen to make it work in all situations.
I plugged directly into the audio in.
Okay, the idea.
What do you want to say, actually, about my I River, I had a 799.
So there's no windscreen at the package.
Okay, there you go.
So you get the idea, what we've essentially now created is the perfect sound
scene to were set up.
So that's the I River, IFP 799.
And using the Griffin lapel stereo microphone, which I haven't
been able to find it online, actually.
Maybe it's brand new or whatever.
I'm very, very pleased with it.
The sound is, it's good.
It sounded a bit nasal, but also it was just clipped onto my, onto the collar
of my, I was wearing a light sweater.
So it was underneath my mouth and I could have positioned it in a different place
and we'll probably get better audio.
And I do need a windscreen for it, because of course I've already heard this
15 minute test or whatever it is.
And the other minute, the wind hits it.
It really hits it hard and it's a bit much.
So I'm going to try and figure out a way to create a little windscreen or something.
Maybe piece of panty hose that I'll cut from one of Patricia's nylon.
Oh man, you know that could end a marriage right there.
That's a dangerous thing to do.
People who listen to jump cut radio with Devon and Nathan are experiencing a breakthrough.
I'm full!
That's right, they're full.
All of new movie reviews celebrity news and info on overlooked classics in cinema.
Here's just a sampling of what you can expect.
It's become ridiculous.
I was over at Best Buy yesterday.
And the ocean swells the only days out.
Really?
So the DVD's 20 bucks, 20 bucks.
That's a little steep for one desk.
That's almost as ridiculous as guess.
It's copy protected on the back.
It has a big old X or something.
It says this disc will only play on certain players, which usually means it won't do shit on a Mac.
But here's the clincher.
No special features.
That's really getting on my nerves.
Nothing.
For 20 bucks, you get the movie.
Then that's for inch subtitles.
So my advice to everyone out there,
wait until you find a copy of Ocean's 12 and some like bargain bins.
If I'm not getting any special features, damn it.
Why in about it, William?
Yeah, well.
After listening to just one episode of Jump Cut Radio,
you will have lost 10 pounds.
guaranteed for your money back.
More information visit jumpcut.lipsen.com.
Or search for Jump Cut Radio with podcast addict.
And remember, Jump Cut Radio is always fair and balanced towards our listeners,
as long as they're views match our own.
Jump Cut Radio.
Movie banter for people with nothing better to do.
Bloded Lesby and welcome.
So let's talk about two things there.
First, Ocean's 12.
I think I mentioned that that was the movie on the flight back from Denver.
And it was very disappointed by this movie.
It was cool because parts of it were filmed in Amsterdam.
And there was a big, you know,
it was a big to do to have, you know, Brad Pitt and George Clooney and Julia Roberts all
walking around Amsterdam.
So that was cool.
The movie was just, I don't know.
It was like, you know, who cares?
It was a thin plot.
Yeah.
It was just, I don't know.
It wasn't for some reason.
It just didn't work as well for me.
And also I think once you know the location that a movie is shot at,
and if you know it intimately,
then you know, you really,
I don't know.
It loses a lot of the magic for some reason.
And a lot of it was shot at the Pulitzer Hotel,
right across my office on the canal.
I've stayed there a couple of times myself.
It's the hotel with the ceilings that are too low
and the struts, the beams that you keep banging your shoulder into.
So that was, you know,
and then also heard in the Jumpcut promo,
I'll talk about copy protection.
I was planning today.
And I was, you know, I'd done all my homework.
I wanted to play a couple of these CDs that Harvey leads it give me from Sony music to play
or from Epic actually.
And one of the missozi su, which he was crazy about.
So I slipped it into my,
into my Mac, you know, obviously,
to create an MP3 or an AAC or whatever to play on the show.
And guess what?
It's copy protected.
You can't play it.
I tried it on my windows machine copy protected.
You can't play it on either of these machines.
So I'm like, well,
you know, what am I going to do now?
I don't have, I'm going to have a regular CD player anymore.
Yet somewhere downstairs,
but I'm not going to start stringing cables, you know,
so that is clearly,
you know,
that's all the whole copy protection idea works, I guess.
I mean, if I really wanted to copy it,
then I just get a cable and, you know,
put it into the input of my Mac,
and I'm going to be able to record it just fine.
But I'm not going to go through all that trouble.
I just shoot.
I just wanted to listen to CD just to sample it.
I can't even copy it legally into my iTunes.
So such a shame.
And it was funny.
There's this, I have a DVD with like a 10,
10, 12 minute.
Piece of video that we cut to show to different people,
you know, what podcasting's about.
It's really, it's a, I'm pretty proud of it.
It's very well done.
Katya actually edited that Katya,
who did our Adams family reality show.
And we burned it onto a DVD,
you know, so that you can basically play it from laptop,
or, you know,
lots of people have DVD players in their conference room these days.
And at, at Epic,
they have a beautiful conference room,
you know, just like the, you know,
the really nice shiny wood and the leather chairs,
and the huge screen, of course,
all this Sony gear.
And we put it into the DVD player.
And it went,
cannot play wrong region.
So here's something I didn't know.
Even if you burn a CD on your European base laptop,
you will not be able to play that DVD,
even though it's your own content.
You won't be able to play that DVD on a different player
in a different region.
You know how it's split up, right?
That's like if you get a DVD from the state,
so you put it into your laptop,
it'll say,
you know,
this is region one,
I think it is.
And you're currently on region two,
which is for Europe.
I think those are the right codes.
I don't know if it's one or two or whatever.
And you have like five chances to change that.
And you know,
and each time you change it,
it drops down one,
then after those five are up,
I guess you're stuck in the region that you're in,
you know,
and you can't play DVD from any other region,
which is just,
so fucking stupid,
it just,
and but to have your own content
be debunked and denied
because of,
you know,
this this rule for,
for Hollywood,
basically,
is just beyond me.
And it,
well,
quite frankly, it pisses me off.
Hello.
Killer.
Innovations.com.
What's in?
What's out?
What's in all about?
A source of ideas
equipping you to create
the next killer innovation.
Listen to film McKinney
on thekillerinnovations.com.com.
And end your creative vacuum.
All right, time for a mash-up.
This one is titled Zombie Kiss Three.
I'm sure benign can already tell
what it's going to be on your daily source code.
The source code.
mashup done by Ed Hago Pian. I think I hope I pronounce it that right. Here's a
email. He says, you've reached out and converted another soul and you're
quest to smite the shit out of that relic we call classic radio and to
break the ice I bring an offering of a mashup I did an able to live in an
hour and effort to find two unlikely bed fellows that actually might work
together. No one else other than my closest friend of her this so it was the
most intimate gift I could think of for a complete stranger. Thank you very much Ed
and just know that you're amongst friends here and keep them
coming. That's that able to live stuff is good. I actually I learned some
stuff about this program called Reason Have You Ever seen That Man That's an
awesome awesome it's a sequencing program but you can you can do mixes with it
and it's not a really appropriate for recording podcasts but I also saw
someone actually operated and it's just blown away by the stuff that you
can do with these types of programs. Yes my friends it's a whole new world of
audio. Do you think Ann Colter's an idiot Rush Limbaugh's a hypocrite
George Bush's evil and perhaps stupid. Republicans are running a mock. The
rich should not own the government lock stock and barrel. The environments
actually worth protecting in this country should have this thing called the
democracy and not be run by a theocracy of right wing radicals. If so come
on over to lowlife.com that's L-O-L-I-F-E.com. Listen to my podcast, check out my
blog. Let's change this fucker. Good day sir.
Promote and not necessarily reflect the ideas viewpoints of the host of the
Daily Source Go.
Okay this is Murano from Murano's Minute and this is a promo from my show. We are currently
at W-W-W-W-M-R-O-N-O-S-M-I-N-U-T-E.com. That's Murano's Minute and the show
is usually about whatever I want school, stories, music. It's obviously not a
minute. I mean that'd be really boring. If you want to Skype me my Skype
address is the E-R-I-D-K-I-D. Of course if you want to email me you can just
put it at G-M-L at the end of my Skype address and send an email to
me. Well that's all for now people. I choose.
Okay, there you go. And information with all the promos of course can be found in
the show notes for today's podcast which you can find at DailySource Go.com.
And I also posted at www.curry.com.
Ah, you know what? I have missed. I have really missed. I have missed the test.
Yeah.
Hey, y'all, come on in.
Honey, Adam, I haven't got any idea where you're right now.
At the cottage or when you're gonna play to hit this but today.
There's one for you and we're gonna start right away. This is number one.
Alright, kick it.
Uh, don't waste my time.
No. Is it don't waste my time?
Okay, I know you're sitting there yelling at your iPod, and this is number two
That's uh, SOS fan
You are in my system, you're in my system. I like that. You
I'm talking number three
Yeah, I'm kind of recognizing the bass line, but not doing too well today. I'm afraid young and times up and these are the answers
Number one
It's Karen white and the way you love me. Oh, yeah, I was close
All right, number two
Karen white and to number one in today's hit test and this is enter number two
That's the best right loose ends. Oh, and this is hanging on a string. Oh, she's this
I should have got this
Yeah
Yeah, you got me hanging on the street now
I guess I can give myself a boing for sucking
Hang in on a string answer number two
And this is answer number three
It's the right of Michael Walden. This is divine emotions. I never would have guessed that one
I think I've ever heard this before
It
Man this brings back memories
Not for me, but way back when I used to do a dance show on the radio
This was all music. I used to play
Because it was all a UK and US imports
Okay, there's a long time ago
Well, that's it for a hit test number 33 with whose counting
I am as always feedback is welcome and hit test at gmail.com
You can find information about the hit test and hit test podcast at the ampulet.nl
That's J-A-N-B-O-L-E-T-D-T-N-L
All right, yeah, but I don't have a safe trip you and see you next time for the next edition of the hit test
All right, buddy. Thank you very much. I'm glad everybody with the hit test number 33 is already made 33 of those and we've never even met
The live from Rotterdam, the Netherlands. This is electronic entertainment bringing you the best of space music
You know, I'm not really one for house music and
Techno and stuff like that, but I did check out this space music.nl this podcast and it's really cool
It's kind of trippy. It was the kind of thing that you can put on the Sunday morning and a particularly with the like they have soundscapes and
Their version of sound seeing yet. It's not bad. I kind of like it and man. There's just so much
There's so many podcasts so many diverse creative ideas that are out there. I'm just
Lated with everything that's coming in on a daily basis trying to keep up with the the workload on the ipodder.org
Just all of the the new shows that have to be categorized and put into spots and the
The no-dead editors are doing great great work on that and we all should be pretty happy that we've now crossed that
5,000 podcast milestone. It's absolutely awesome
Okay, so that puts us at 42 minutes for today's source code. We're gonna wrap it up. Of course, I'll be back tomorrow
As I said with a sound seeing tour with the new setup
Which now is actually become kind of affordable. You know, I think you can get an i-river 799 for somewhere around
Was it 65 or 70 bucks and then this microphone for under $100?
You could be done and you could be rolling with your very own sound seeing tour setup. I love this stuff
Power
So thanks for checking us out today. Stay subscribed. You can find the podcast via David source code.com
That's where you can find the latest showing all the archives
Feedback adamantcurry.com or I can always leave a comment to my web blog
www.curry.com and if you're gonna send me a promo send it to adamantcurry.com put in the subject line
dsc space promo and then whatever the hell you want to put after that so I know what promo it's about
It's like I'm set up a filter to be a lot easier for me to get to all of them. All right everybody. Thanks for checking us out. I'll talk to you tomorrow. Bye. Bye