The Shira Charley 2, 4, 1
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass, and the next generation radio
content in my ears.
Time for the party on a Friday, it is September 16, 2005.
Hey everybody, how you doing coming to you from the Curry condo that would be in San Francisco,
California IA, 94105 is the zip, how you doing everybody, so sorry I'm late, but gotta
figure out the time schedule, I'm just, I'm too international.
So once again I'm set up here in the open bar kitchen, hey, shoot, two ropes just appeared
in front of my window, I guess they're finally gonna watch the windows, then, oh, maybe
we'll have the guy stop by for a couple of tea.
I think it's gonna be an extra long source code today because I've got lots of promos, lots
of fun stuff that came in, an email, some audio feedback, we even have the origins of the
word fuck, and news about some biodiesel you may be able to use, so we're probably
gonna go the full 40 today, I actually had a big, I had several conversations with
everybody at Pod Show today, as it looked, we got so much business, we have so many things
happen, and I've got to get myself on some kind of schedule because I just can't do
this shit on demand, you know, I can't, I can't say, oh yeah, today I'll do the
the storage code between 130 and 3 o'clock no problem, you know, I got love going to this,
art creativity, and sometimes I get the same kind of feeling back,
what do you need, and we got that for you, starting it off with a mashup, as I said, mashups are
getting a little bit low, but art from mashuptown.com, send me this one, base 2-11 crunches together,
Moby and Jet, to give us rug on, be my honey, something like that, check it out.
Three 10-man, Hannah Come With me, because you look so far that it really want to make you
wear, so far that it really want to make you wear, so far that apart,
I'll find that really won't it make you buy
Five six come on and get your kicks now you don't need money when you look at that through your heart
I know you ain't got muscle say I'll never let you get away
I said are you gonna be my girl
I don't know you ain't got muscle say I'll never let you get away
Two three ten my hand is coming with me because you look so fine that I really won't it make you buy
Five six come on and get your kicks now you don't need money when you look at that through your heart
I don't know you ain't got muscle say I'll never let you get away
You ain't got muscle say I'll never let you get away
I said are you gonna be my girl
I don't know you ain't got muscle say I'll never let you get away
You ain't got muscle say I'll never let you get away
I'll never let you get away
I love playing games