Delta Sierra Charlie one nine or three
A 60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass
The next generation radio content in my ears
Everybody how you doing it is Monday it's June 13, 2005
I know I know you were waiting for a show on Friday
I really apologize, I just I didn't have it in
That's it and that of course is the beauty of podcasting
It's a craft you'll get it when I did it when you got it got it get it
Okay, it's the start of a new week
How many of you from Curry Castle in the lovely affluent suburb built up
That's in Surrey in the UK where the weather is absolutely beautiful today
So little on the it's like called on the nippy side actually
The wind is shifted it's now coming from the
It's from the southwest which means it's blowing right into the studio windows
Which are always open for smoke relief
You know what I mean
It got a pretty cool shine show lined up for you lots of freaky stuff
Also apologies to the Dutch listeners who were perhaps expecting a Patricia Adam podcast
This week and we really just didn't get around to it we slept a lot
We hung out a lot we went shopping in fact right after this show
I'm going shopping again because
I kind of came to the realization that I haven't purchased new clothes in three years
I think it was actually Ron's wife Marta who really got me back on the on the buying trip
She says something very prolific to me
She said hey, you know with the pants you ring it looks like you have no ass
Okay, how many good looking women you need to say that to you before you decided to do something about it
All right, we got some cool stuff to talk about and of course pod save music on the way plenty of promos and
Scorching mashups
Drop it like it's a whole lot you're going to love this party Ben getting stupid with lead's new plan
Let's see
The one that pimps in the crib must drop it like it's how I drop it like it's how I drop it like it's how I drop it like it's how
The extra to get it you pocket like it's how I pocket like it's how I pocket like it's how I
Get it to pop it like it's how I pop it like it's how I pop it like it's how I got to roll you
Only a moment when shot down and I'll go best because I got it when I'm a nice team
I'm a nice kid and see these ice cubes and see these ice creams
No people that you're not a boat that's quite it and what's going on you throw the fan
You should think about it take a second matter of fact you should say for me and think before you full those
Stay for me when the kids in the crib must drop it like it's how I drop it like it's how I drop it like it's how
The extra to get it you pocket like it's how I get like it's how I get like it's how I get like it's how I get
Get it to pop it like it's how I pop it like it's how I pop it like it's how I get like it's how I got to roll you
Only a moment when shot down and I'll go best because I got it when I'm a nice team
I got it when I'm a nice team I got it when I'm a nice team
I got it when I'm a nice team I got it when I'm a nice team I got it when I'm a nice team
I got so much you.
I got it when I'm a nice team
If they get me clear-mon, drop it like this how I get I'm a nice team
Try to get it you keep on getting like this how I get I'm a nice team
Come on, it's like a song, get ahead of two, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song, I've been like a song,
I can't be cool, you can't
Party, Ben, getting stupid indeed
Drop it like it's hard, droffed like it's
Man, as what does that in mix of Snoop Dog and
Well, blah blah, blah blah
that's funny because I was actually thinking about that song
I don't know what it was, over the weekend I was thinking about
Led Zeppelin, I don't know why I just the song was in my head, and then all of a sudden this morning, I'm
the show and that shows up. I love it. And if you thought, oh man, there's this quick time
problem again because it dropped out. No, this show is actually being produced in its entirety
on cast blaster beta number 15. Now the sound of course of the microphone is going to be pretty good
because I did route my regular microphone through it, but I'm just using the little craplet
with the cast blaster right up there. I'm using the combination of the the mouse and the
pen actually to kick stuff off to start to start the bits. We did a lot of testing over the week
and cast blaster mic. Lead developer was working on actually discovering how to create a compressor
limiter and most of the stuff these days you know of course I still use the stereo valve process
which is done with old well old fashioned radio tubes. Most of the stuff is done on chips in
or in software in fact a lot of it's done in software but you can't do that in real time because then
well unless you are not interested in hearing what the mix sounds like which is just not doable
for someone doing a podcast on the fly the way I do them at least I just do them live
because then you'd hear latency and you'd hear your voice back in your headphones at least a
couple of fractions of a second if not more after they come out of your mouth which is very
very difficult to do you should try it sometimes. So what my came up with is a way to create or
simulate a compressor limiter by actually creating that in the hardware by or not by creating
it by talking to the hardware which is just phenomenal because it really really works and the sound
I mean there's no homes no well let's listen for a second no no homes I was able to remove all
of that everything sound and really good so really fantastic you know just a fantastic piece of software
so you probably noticed the size is a little bit smaller today since there's two defaults to
record your podcast and you can also put your show notes right in there currently the version
we have uploads if you want it to you can upload right up to an FTP server all your tags are taking
care of and of course is one step removed from the full blown service which pod show dot
call the offering very soon where you actually get your show blog and your RSS feed and everything
all in one so we're doing real good I'm very very excited about it. I got a list of stuff to talk
about today I see I hit the cast blaster got that oh tomorrow night actually thanks to Aaron from
parking in bitterman's circle who was a tech on the road on the current tour with Weezer has
hooked us up with tickets so I'll be taking Christina and a friend of hers to of all places
Brixton Academy which is pretty much not the nicest part of town I haven't quite figured out
if I want to drive it again because last time it was a first of all it's a reasonably long drive because
I think Brixton is more on the eastern side of London and we kind of coming on the west
through the southwest and I don't have to tell you what that burp is right and it's a bitch to park
and if you can park then you know you kind of wonder if you're going to come back and there's going to be
I don't know cinder blocks underneath this car instead of fuel wheels so we may take the train
in the tube or I may hire a car I'm not quite sure what I want to do yet but looking forward to doing
that of course I mentioned this I think on Thursday's podcast and already I'm getting lots of emails
saying hey you should you should I do a sound seeing towards the Weezer concert let me tell you
Brixton Academy is really pretty strict about cameras and recording devices and they check
out really well so I'm a bit wary of doing that although of course I could take the I river with me
and we could do some stuff in the car maybe and talk about the show afterwards we might do that that could
be kind of fun promos plenty of them lined up for you as usual here on the source code
Hi my name is Joe Burgers and I'm from the rootsmart.com tech podcast I would like to invite you
to listen to me for about 30 minutes every Sunday we cover all of the hot news topics and today's
tech world keep you up on current tech topics they're changing our world right in front of our eyes
we also have how to's and tips and tricks to keep your Linux Mac or Windows computer up and running
efficiently please visit our site at podcast.gootsmart.com and tune in
hot show content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother
oh excuse me
let's see if you're bad
yeah links to those podcasts in the show notes of course today at dailystorescode.com or
www.curry.com a lot going on man shoot Patricia's taken off on Thursday for a couple of days
she's going to go visit family and do some stuff and she'll be back on Tuesday and then Wednesday
next week that is I take off for nomdex which is the 23rd through the 25th I believe
then Sunday morning I hop on the plane and go to Portland and that's where I'm going to hook up
with the fly boys this will be a day before win command to William comes in but I'll be training for
three or yeah probably out three days nonstop just doing training training training touching goes
touching goes touching goes probably in a sesno 172 which is one of the main reasons for it by the way
because you know I have the the sesno 182 retractable gear actually I say to people now I have a 182
RG and they say yeah I know it stands for retractable gear because they do this freaking podcast
I tell you people are listening to this podcast it's unbelievable remember I did the shout out
to Frank Casanova about the quick time issues dude I got an email like the next day from Frank Casanova
and he said hey how you doing um a couple people mentioned to me that you said something on the source code
and he was going to turn that right over to uh to the engineers at Apple and see if anything could
be done if it wasn't detailed something that had just kind of been laying around for a couple of years
and no one really deemed important until now so that's really exciting it's it's really it's quite
amazing it seems like there's a lot of people listening um all over the west coast actually not
just in a kupertino but also in redman and it's quite a pleasure to have you all along for the ride
if you want to know what's going on the podcast community this can be partially the place to find out
about I actually would recommend podcast alley to go to the uh go to the forums there to see what people are
really really saying but there are a couple mail lists one for the iPod or developers and then there's
the podcasters mailing list which is a Yahoo group and a big big discussion that last count 62
messages about the following press release by Madge Weinstein this is Madge Weinstein of yeast
radio dot com with a very important press release who's the hottest thing in podcasting June 11th 2005
Chicago will annoy big mouth fatso rush limbao declares himself the hottest thing in podcasting
but how does that sit with true podcasting innovator Madge Weinstein everyone knows that I'm the
hottest thing in podcasting says the fiery lesbian firebrand rush limbao is a big fat slob if he wants
to post the video clips of him and Madge rush sucking come from Rick Santorum's ass.
I'll gladly hand over my crown Madge spells a smell's a conspiracy he has been copying my
stick for years and he is late to the party as usual prescription drugs hello been there done that
kissing Republican ass Grace I went down on Nancy Reagan podcasting not on my watch after all
I put the broad in broad band but aren't we talking about one of the legends of media yeah
he's like a bad cartoon they should put him in the macy's Thanksgiving day parade as a balloon
he's already pre-inflated and high on oxy content next thing you know he'll be claiming he's a
homosexual and that he's managing a rock band called T and the bags Madge is throwing down the gauntlet
I've a standing offer for Lardass Limbao to appear on yeast radio let's see if he has
man enough for a lesbian like me about Madge Weinstein you're undoubtedly familiar with Madge as
the manager of the popular girl rock band that's girl spell g double r l goddess riot juice her unique
perspectives on everything from lesbian feminists of color to vaginal yeast can be heard in her podcast
and on serious radio channel 148 she is single and lives in Chicago with her dog troncy
young ladies check out her podcast at yeastradio.com Madge is proudly part of the Adam
Curry's pod show dot calm team about Rush Limbao Limbao is a big fat fuck who has his domestic
help school drugs for him a racist sexist homophobic bully this clown managed to get out of going
to Vietnam because he had a cyst on his ass for more information contact loaded lesbian at gmail.com
or call 206888 count you know I really should have mentioned that that was not work safe
promo sorry about that okay Madge Weinstein stern it up loving that fantastic see what we're
talking about last week uh yes yeah I miss out on Friday and then the brain goes kind of dead over
the weekend oh yeah I remember we're talking about accessibility um because there are you know the
the blind community of course is is astronomical over the entire globe and podcasting has been like
you know such an incredible breath of fresh air to to this community being able to
receive all kinds of information now via audio and I uh as if you know what the deal is with
accessibility basically with um with the programs that make computers more usable for the blind
and I got some interesting feedback apparently iTunes has none to almost completely or almost none
to absolutely zero accessibility now I don't know if that's in windows or on the Mac because I do
believe the Mac now has uh integrity at least it has some interesting accessibility options but
I've been getting a lot of comments and one of them from one of my favorite podcasters oh
Adam I'm Shelley Brisbane I'm a writer and a former associate editor at Mac user magazine and I'm
also visually impaired I wanted to share a few thoughts with you about accessibility for blind
people using windows in the Mac windows users don't have screen reading software built in they
either have to purchase jaws or window eyes which are both very expensive third party screen
or applications and Mac OS users didn't even have that option until OS 10.4 tiger was released
Apple now includes a tool called voiceover a screen reader from macOS and it's the first time I'm
aware of a screen reader being included in an operating system and that by itself is really exciting
even though voiceover really isn't quite as good as it needs to be to answer your specific
question it does not work with iTunes they don't communicate with each other at all voiceover does
work with Safari and with mail and even with iChat but iTunes users are out of luck so it's not that
the podcasting component of iTunes needs to be made accessible but that iTunes itself needs to talk
to voiceover and that goes for any other app that Apple ships with tiger I think it voiceover is
going to become more than just an ADA compliance checkbox blind people are going to have to let Apple
know that they'd like to become Mac users and I think once people do the math and realize that you
can get a Mac mini for six or seven hundred bucks which is less than the price of jaws or
window eyes by itself that that provides an accessibility option at a really reasonable price that
didn't exist before so I want to thank you for putting this in a spotlight at them and I really
hope that the next announcement we hear is that cast blaster is fully accessible. Actually I have
I've had discussions with Mike about that so I don't know if it's going to be in the first beta release
it's a lot of work obviously but that is pretty interesting that iTunes doesn't work with voiceover
I wasn't aware of that and Shelley by the way I've listened to a lot of your podcast
I was doing a lot of traveling between San Francisco and London and I somehow had always
seemed to pick up your podcast I haven't heard one in a while I wonder if you're still doing them
or something happened to the feed or something just broke on my end please let me know
now I have a hit test from young pollack he did number 43 43 came believe that 43 podcast
a hit test already but I'm going to say that one for tomorrow because I found this in the mailbox
which I probably should have played on Friday but it's so freaking good it's about the length of a
hit test but it's something completely different
recognize it
good day Adam good day welcome to the special edition of voices from the vault okay
in a few moments I'll be playing you the voices of eight of my favourite podcasters
all doing their best to impersonate you strapping that 60 million dollar airplane
give my ass your job is to identify who they are
cellyson carefully as we play Adam curry okie on voices just on the voice but also be non-work safe
I'm afraid
with sixty million dollars of airplanes strapped to my hands
and the next generation we'll be content in my ears
okay and so one please get me a sense ale okay I know that it that's that's Brian
Abbott from coverville this is a good game the same thing every $60 million
of airplanes strapped to my ass and the next generation radio content right in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future baby
oh man I'm gonna be embarrassed I can't think of them
I recognize the voice with sixty million dollars with a airplane strapped to my ass
transmiters the next generation radio content in my ear we don't need no stake
and transmiters I'd like to think I'm flying into the future
look at the podcast are you kidding me it's an Adam curry
that's uh Kevin the announcer guy from Yomple that's it that's it this is great you guys
have a lot of work do you need dollars for the airplane strapped to my ass
transmiters and the next generation radio content my ears we don't need no stake and
transmiters I like to pick up flying into the future podcaster it's Adam curry
I don't know if that is either she's this is really difficult it's also it's not enough
of the sample $60 million with a airplane strapped to my ass transmiters and the next
generation radio content in my ears we don't need no stake and transmiters I like to think I'm flying
into the future oh come on let's talk let's you know you vocoded that way that's
Yomple that of course I can recognize him through a book holder
sixty million dollars with airplane strapped to my ass
the generation radio content in my ear you don't need no stake and transmiters I just think I'm flying
into the future that would be a PWF infant from Tampa Florida
with a sixteen million dollar strapped on in my
well done that's not right what true it's a sixteen million dollar airplane strapped to my ass
what are you sure that doesn't make any sense yeah like you're sitting in the chair strapped in the
seat belt I you know what I think he said I gave out strapped on the next one is and the next
generation of radio content in my ears all this penetration talk in my ass in my ears it's so
very arousing
I've done that was that darn the diamond drew show all right was that eight yeah
Adam that really blew my reputation for being a family friendly
party yeah mine suit but mind how did you go first of tonight's voices from the vault in
person 18 you briny bit yeah from coverville got that one voice from the vault number two
Dan class from the bitterest pill Dan okay so it's been a vault number three a special appearance
from Kevin the announcer got Kevin the announcer got number four Michael Butler from the
from all geek shot could I not hear but voice from the vault number five the wonderful young
pollette yeah number six PWF infant and digital flots and got him and last but not least
don't endure of course from the dawn and drew show awesome
what again well Adam my hope you enjoyed listening to that as much as I enjoyed putting it together
maybe I should do it again sometimes soon in the meantime don't forget to visit the voices from
the vault.com website to catch more voices from the audio archives of history and I'll see you again
next time we play Adam karaoke on voices from the vault Adam karaoke very nice
I don't think we should play that too often Jerry because I'm going to get in trouble man
I don't recognize how I can't believe on this Dan I can't believe I'm just Michael Butler that was
Elamo to say the least I could very much it's actually you know people
ask all the time if I can read a line for them and but why don't I do one right now because then
let's see who is this the tartan podcast mark from the tartan podcast asked if I could read a line
for for the awards was it awards what awards oh man I get a text message let me just see
that is oh no of course it's from the lawyer oh boy okay well just leave the lawyer stuff for now
okay so the line is hindsight I'm creating a source quote the second nomination for artists of the
month is casino okay I'll just do this now and he can cut it out and that'll be perfect so
kill two birds with one stone here we go hi it's Adam Curry from the daily source code
the second nomination for artists of the month is casino there you go that's how you do it I think
this has something to do with pod safe music that's why I want to roll some out for you right now it's
lady Bianca played her before it says lay me down pod safe on the source code oh man
you know you're driving crazy when you do a thing you do and I'll throw right up to the
sea land anytime you come around I get a good good feeling every time you lay me down
my body starts to sound good I start panicking again every time I think about them that's
me love we'll be making and I'll turn around you say oh I like I like I like to be a sound
yes I do oh you feel me you feel me in every way every time you lay me down
yeah
What you said, my heart will blow, and I'm proud of what's ahead, what are you so known?
Don't worry, I'm my bed, don't hold back one bit.
I won't ever getcha on the sun, just a new moon.
You, you, you, you give me loneliness, be with this baby.
It hurts time you lay me down.
Dad, when you lay me down babe,
on home, I start when you're sick and baby.
Baby, when you lay me down babe.
Oh, I just love it, when you touch me like that babe,
when you lay me down.
I get that good, go, go, go, go, go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll stop, I will stop, I will just stop.
Just let me touch me like that babe,
when you lay and you're down, I'm hey,
don't know those kids are right there, lay and they're there.
Lady Bianca, lay me down, it's pod save on the Daily Source code.
I love the pipes on that girl, of course you can find out all the info about all the songs and everything
played on the source code of the show notes.
Okay, okay, feedback out of recruit.com. Yes, your audio feedback is welcome. If you wish to
attach an MP3 file, but of course there are places to send off your potsafe music, your mashups
and anything else you want to send in. We've got three email addresses, get a pen, get ready to write it down.
And they actually make sense. It's mashup at podshow.com, podsafe at podshow.com or submit at podshow.com for
your promos, your actually for your podcast as well, if you want to get them on the podshow on serious.
And by now I think most of the pod squad has their serious radio receivers and they're all
enjoying it, the big blue boom boxes. And then a good time with that. Something's a mess up with the
show notes though. I still got to figure out what exactly is going on with that because you can't quite
some reason I'm not flowing through to the show notes.podshow.com weblog, but we're working on the
technology.
Now ready. So that's it for today. As I said, lots of stuff coming up this week. A lot of audio
production. I actually a drag for Steena in front of microphone last night. Had a cut a couple of
voice drops. She's sounding very mature. I have to tell you something about the digitizing
of the girl that makes her just 15 going on 27. I need to go above that one. Dailysourceco.com
is where you can find the podcast feed and the archives and of course the latest show.
www.curry.com for comments and the other stuff I'm posting out there.
And we will see each other tomorrow. Same time, kind of, same place. Definitely the source code. Take care.
www.curry.com.
The other pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.