source code February 10th 2005 transmeters we don't need no
stinking transmeters
it's Adam Curry it is Thursday it's the 10th of February
everybody welcome to the daily source code which is almost daily
sorry about yesterday you know what happens sometimes life just gets in the
way of shit and even though I really had planned to put the show together
I just ran out of hours in the day so I'm gonna try and make up for it today
so you probably hear a different acoustic right off the bat I'm wearing
the wireless lovelier microphone and you could probably guess just by
listening to the acoustic search to where I am of course I said that I was a
way I'm business I've been in Amsterdam for two nights now Tuesday night and last
night and right now it's about two o'clock I'm sorry three o'clock in the
afternoon local time and I'm flying in what is it so I'm not flying until 10 o'clock
now 930 tonight so perfect timing to do a bit of hang in here in the bunker
so the TV production crew is moved out they're done they were here for
that's Chris but I think it was like I have the lovelier on both my
headphone wires breaking against it and I think they were here for 10 weeks
and they've moved out the places completely clean whatever's left is just
after our our possessions that we left here that we didn't move to England and
of course Chris was still here and has the office and all the files
and we're kind of winding it all down you know we're still trying to get rid of
this place so trying not to empty out too much so it still looks like a house
and it's still sailable but at the same time yeah you know we're we've moved
we're out of the country so we're just waiting to you know finalize some
stuff here and then actually finalize our our entry into the United Kingdom
so I'm in the kitchen of the bunker you can hear actually a CNN is on there's
big news today in the UK that you'll probably hear about it's oh man they're so
happy they got something to talk about now in the big news media you know forget
about tsunami and Asian tsunami relief now it's Charles and Camilla they're
getting married it has been announced and of course a lot of people have a
lot to say about this and you know I think everyone's pretty much agreed that
it's proper that it will never be queen Camilla but it will be what is she
something of cornwall Duchess of cornwall I think is what her title will be
but wow they're pretty rough in England
Patricia was telling me that you know some of the headlines of the papers
you know he's doing it he's finally marrying the dog I think that's pretty
rough so let me just to unhook the myself from the headphones see let me turn
off this CNN racket of course now that I have the lava layer on it can be
mobile and oh wait there's no batteries in the remote
oh second so hello we're walking into crystal's office high crystal how
are you no one knows you I haven't put you in the podcast yet okay yes
crystals my sexy PA right baby what are you doing oh you call the
Belgium guys here are we still not done with Belgium either okay good I'll come
back later for you crystal crystals I will almost leaving me she's going to go
to Geneva to live with her man she's looking for a job in Geneva y'all yeah I
think our upstairs I think we've done this before one upstairs and listen to
our Russian concerto pianist practicing and I think I just heard a fire up the
keyboard so walk upstairs now on the second floor walking towards the back
which is where I can hear him best this is our bedroom yeah he's playing
oh listen
he's really soft or maybe something here better in the bathroom
I hope you can hear that it's gonna be really soft I'm sure anyway so the place
is pretty much empty I just had a couple things to do here and now I have a
few hours to get through some stuff you can hear me panting that's because I'm
smoking well not tobacco of course but hey this is Amsterdam right so oh the
minute I get in the cab with taxi Eric who's the I've had the same cab driver
for years he already has my first split for the day ready to go okay so let's see
today of course is it's trivia Thursday and I've been keeping all the
trivia stuff standing by for you and for myself of course I actually have no
idea anymore what what you know what all the different trivia bits are about I've
of course I've listened to the intro's each one of them as they came in but I
forgot and completely completely about you know what they are with all
different themes and what was this this is oh yeah Michael Butler rock and
old Vic sent this to me this is he plays this all the time is this this cool
thing these string quartet versions of rock songs and he sent me a little
package of good Charlotte songs that have been done by or because he's the
anthem let's see oh shoot kind of regular like volume there with my like
arrow keys I was put that in the background a little bit there so we can solve
some of this emptiness that you hear in the background of the house kind of
pressing so last time we spoke I was pretty hyper about the ASCAP license and I've
been received well I basically I need a producer this is my problem now because
you start off some stuff right and you start talking about you know just
about something that catches people's attention then there's all these you
know this great feedback and there's emails and there's lots of MP3 files
and just haven't had time to wait through it yeah if I'm at home every single day
and have nothing else to do but you know get up take routine at a school get
the papers start trepping for the show record the show you know do all the
post processing and you know production shit getting it up to the server
doing the show notes and it's that's a it takes a major portion of the day
I have to say so whenever something else happens it's like I just breaks down I'm
sitting here looking at my Gmail inbox which is I mean I love Gmail so much it
is so incredibly easy to work with it's a great combination of you know keeping
your hands on the keyboard and being able to manipulate and your mail just like
you could do with pine or l or you know any other of the Unix mail programs but
has all the convenience of the web built right into it and you don't really
have to use your mouse at all so it's I love that but anyway despite that I still
have 164 messages now waiting for me just haven't gotten to and haven't had time
you know so and a lot of that is pertains to podcasts so hey if I ever
figure out a way to make money with this shit it's going towards that
getting some production help and I can just see how it would work with outlines
and you know it could work from anywhere you don't have to live with me to
produce it but anyway so there's a whole bunch of feedback on this
ascap license and I'm not really sure that we have anything here yet folks to
be honest and I'll know much more probably over the weekend I'll have a chance
to sort through all of the comments but it looks like your minimum payment is
going to be $288 and I'm probably just going to pay that just so we can
fuck around and test and experiment to make sure that you know at least we're
pushing the edges of the envelope and then we come up with some better answers
and find out where the line is I don't think that you know you have to be deemed
a pirate or some kind of degenerate if you if you just try to do it so I'm
definitely signing up for it after I figure out which schedule to a select and
what you know how the payment stuff works I guess without having any
revenue on the show it's it's going to be pretty easy it's just the 288
box I think so we'll take it at that what is this I'm trying to figure out I
have this something that opened in my play I'm not quite sure let me see what
this is what is this okay I know what that is we're going to play that oh yeah
that's what we're going to play let's see if you haven't heard the latest
Jenny and Lee show I go over to Jenny and Lee dot com oh man these kids can't get
a fucking break Lee has a short podcast that you know at Christmas really allowed
let me just she's on the phone so she's doing work and that does have
precedence so let me just close this for a second okay now you know what let me
get everything that I have in the front so now I'm walking from the back of the
house through the this is the what do you call it the chapel part it's a
little little more echoey and now we're into the first front room now the
second front room this is the one all the way to canal side okay my stuff on
the phone here and phone calls now I was supposed to go flying with wing commander
William and looking outside you know it was like I or this morning I knew it
was not actually last night I knew it wasn't going to happen the weather's been
absolutely crap but not that you can't fly in this weather and not that I we
flown in plenty of shit weather but when you're training it just doesn't matter
I mean then you're you're not really going to learn that much because you're
compensating for forces and things that you just don't understand yet you know
in other words you got to learn to walk before you're run so bummer
it means my first you know my next training session won't be until the end of
the month when I come back from the trip on planning to the states
anyway Jenny and Lee and Jenny just had some some medical shit and it's
and it's just fucked up and you know these kids had their you know the they
first they moved to the states and then they had to move back within two
weeks because shit fell apart and then of course the dogs had to go in a
quarantine for six months they couldn't get them over they were sitting at
Atlanta the podcast community came together really helped him out with that
it was beautiful and now Jenny has all these medical problems and I just want
to know that from everybody here the courier house hold as well as Amsterdam
we're all thinking of you guys and if there's anything we can do you just
you know just let us know we want to be there for you and our prayers go out to you
and the last update I saw on your on the weblog was that operation was
success and now we have to you know start to the recovery so anything we can do
but just let me know right lots of feedback about a couple things
first of all the USA today article which I was able to pick up here online as well
but it's always kind of fun to see the print version a huge picture of Don and Drew
and of the farmhouse in the in the European or the international edition
which is just you know so proud so wonderful to see that I'm just like yes here
they are the poster children of podcasting but really you know it makes so much sense
when you I mean Don and Drew if you look at their picture they are kind of you know
two sides of the same coin does that make any sense I love them both my girlfriend and
my other girlfriend is apparently in New York I think there was a picture of me in the article
I'm not quite sure how that works interesting why they would use different different pictures
and different markets I mean I guess they have some kind of market researcher data that would
lead them to make those types of decisions in fact I believe that Madge Weinstein was even
promised the European cover which must have changed into Don and Drew
because I didn't see actually even see some email correspondence about that I don't
maybe you were say today isn't ready for the lesbian anthics of Madge just yet so
that didn't happen but yeah great great article so what happens is you know lots of people
start you know reaching out and contacting and opportunities and it's just it's great it really
is a lot of cool stuff and I got major league feedback on the past two podcasts where I've been
playing pod safe well not really pod safe mash-ups which are commercially
unviable anyway because you can never get the rights to release them commercially and
should my pin daddy is there hook them up again in vain of playing some micro Jackson music
here's the Tokyo Scott Paradise Orchestra's just loose rock mix of ADC
pop a Jackson pop
If you see, if there's one for people, I don't think there will be no reason
If there's one for people, I don't think there will be no reason
If there's one for people, I don't think it's no reason
You see, oh, you gotta do it
ономhi!
으로, ar, echo, echo, echo, echo
You see, oh, you gotta do it
Shake it, shake it, come on! Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake
it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it,
Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, flick it, shake, hands it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it too, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it Shake it, shake it, Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake
One to play, hey, hey, hey, hey
One to play, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, okay, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, I, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
guys done has been pretty amazing. That's the Tokyo Scott Paradise Orchestra as
just the Roots Rock mix of ABC. I was talking about Gmail just a minute ago, I forgot to
tell you that I'm a little worried now because I've switched to Gmail, I totally love it,
the interface, just everything. Forget the gig of storage, which of course is perfect.
So it works for me. It does work the way I think. I'm liking it. In fact, it has a lot of
outline or properties in their way it stacks up conversations as they call them or threads or whatever.
So I totally dig that, but now I've been using it for two or three weeks,
I'm already an 8% of my quota. So what happens when I fill it up to a gig?
You know, then what do I do? Of course, I can send myself 15 more invitations, but you know,
what starts to make sense? Is that when I start to buy more space on the Google grid?
Oh, if you haven't seen that flash movie, if I have time left after the trivia today,
I'm going to play that flash movie movie for you about called Epic 2014. My God,
that's so well done. Even without the visuals, I think it'll be great, it'll be perfect.
Happy Chinese New Year. It's the year of the Rooster.
That started yesterday, actually. So I was, I had it on my notes to wish you a happy New Year.
I don't know what the Rooster will bring us, hopefully the year, the Rooster. I had a lot of interesting
things planned for yesterday on a Chinese New Year. And so far I have to say they've been
pretty favorable in my way. So I'm hoping that this will be a good New Year for all of us here.
But what the heck has gone on with Condolizer Rice? I just wanted to say that
because she's been over in Europe talking to Jim DeHoop Schaffer, which of course is a Dutch politician
who left to join NATO. The way we pronounce this name is Yopde Hoep Schaffer. He's the director
general of NATO. It gets a lot of extra coverage on how I saw it on CNN, but I know how good the
coverage has been or if anyone gives a shit that Condolizer Rice is over here saying, hey, you know,
Iran, but it watched their ass. And lo and behold, I'm seeing, it's like I'm seeing a fucking replay
before Iraq where now I see CNN shows all this, all this armament and all these nuclear
trucks rolling down the street, which of course is Archive File Footage. But, you know, so apparently
that's the Iranian threat. I mean, shit. What the hell is this? I mean, it's exactly the same thing.
You know, what's next? We're going to have Condolizer Rice will be holding up a vial of some
enriched plutonium, who the fuck knows what that is. You know, I would know it if I fell into a
fat of it. And, you know, this much is enough to kill everyone in the United States. I mean, just waiting
for that next broadcast, you know, it's just crazy. But on the other hand, I was just totally
tickled pink. I want to remind you that coming up, but it was at Tuesday or Monday, the 14th of
February, of course, is Valentine's Day. But today is 10, so it's more 11, 12th, it's on Monday,
Monday, over the 14th. And God and Themed podcast is the perfect podcast for Valentine's Day.
She always has a podcast of theme songs. Usually by an hour long, it's 53, 55 minutes. And it's
all Valentine's Day songs. And it's a perfect podcast to just kind of slip on the background.
In, you know, Karen does some introduction of the songs, but she has this great, like, really
mellow kind of voice. And, you know, and, of course, there's obviously no commercial interruptions.
It's just really nice. It's a great vibe. I listened to some of it last night. Like, oh, yeah,
I'm totally going to put this on streaming through the, the eye trip. And I'll be, uh, when I make
my romantic moves on my significant other. If you know what I mean. Hey, everybody, it's Thursday.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, it's Thursday.
Hey, y'all. Y'all believe it with a hit test. Today is his special edition. Oh,
because it says, Sea 100 edition with lots of air checks. Oh, so, hold on, it's like,
let this be the last time we do air checks, y'all. I mean, and I'm getting, you know,
when I listen to myself doing the Sea 100 shit, it's like, oh my God, I'm pukeing,
This is exactly why we have podcasts because, you know, this is like the epitome of pukedist
jockey 80s.
So please, you know, this is where I came from, not where I'm going.
It's probably not that difficult, it would probably be very easy for you.
But that should be fun though.
So if you're ready, here are the three clips.
All right.
This is number one.
Well, yes, we'll be, uh, I want to wait a couple seconds so you can guess at home,
but it's, uh, I read the friend plans respect.
Number two.
I know this one too.
This is, um, Patrick Hernandez.
Born to be alive.
And number three.
That's it.
All right.
Everybody should know this one.
Step and roll.
One.
These are the answers.
This is number one.
C-100.
Right.
If you ever hear podcasts, go ever blow that.
It's something we were talking about months ago that the, that's exactly what I was doing.
That's a body and talk.
I can see one.
I'm honoured.
It's reasonable.
All right.
That's good.
It's all in a respect when you come to me.
So the answer to number one is that we have a friend plan and respect.
We won.
180.
I'm proud of you.
Straight into the weekend.
Hello.
Who's this?
This is Mike.
The boy.
We like you to play bread and be alive.
This is going out.
David and Mike in the round.
We have a great weekend.
Let's get a party.
You got a man.
It's on.
C-100.
The answer to number two.
Born to be alive.
Venture can't handle this.
This is number three.
100 can't get anyone other than right here.
Everybody.
Your name, but I don't know nothing fun.
Okay so!
Let's get the challenge back in there.
Oh my goodness.
This my goodness a lot of energy though, and that actually and you know, it's like there's your there's your MP3 feedback
You know on the radio we call that a telephone, you know, we've got all the elements here
It's just you don't have to have no big stank in transmiters
Born to be wild
You may be answering yourself and boy, did you do that fast?
Yeah, well, this wraps up the Z100 New York
She dish it up the hit test
Please keep sending air checks
Oh no, hit test at gmail.com
That's quite alright
And see you next time, Adam for a new edition of the hit test, bye-bye
All right, y'all thank you very much, excellent
Y'all collect the the originator of the hit test here in the source code, of course
No, not a completely new concept of boy
I just love playing this game with you, but
Let's uh, yeah, we got to stop with the air checks
You know, that's history
I'm glad that there were people like Tom Scuding
I've pointed to him before, you know, who's archiving all that stuff
And that's very important, but you know, let's move on, let's move forward
Let's move to the next hit test and our Thursday trivia day
Hello, Adam
Hello, everybody, this is Craig Maloney
Just wanted to share a quick music test with everyone
Hopefully this is a pretty easy one
These are all songs from the late 80s, possibly early 90s
Countdown started
Let's begin
All right, number one
Number two, they pocket
I don't know until this is number three
I know the song
I don't see something I'm here to share about this
Hard for me though, I know I know clue
And last but not least, number four
It's like power station, a wall of polymer
It's like, I'm just guessing
Maybe I smoked too much dope, I can't get it
No idea
Oh, that's
That's pretty easy
Sure
All right, hit me with some hands with you, buddy
Yeah
You sure?
Yes, hold on a second, my phone
All right, let me go again
I'm phone rings
There's the answers
Electric blue by ice house
Ice house
Shit
I got a pocket
I was singing it, I knew that you stand still
Rush
Should've known that one
My god
This one may or may not have been easy
This one is
Killer
I seal
Ah, no
I wouldn't associate this with seal
But yeah, and now you say
What was I doing?
I was like running a company
I wasn't paying attention to these
There are less but not least
Power stations
See, I knew it was power stations
Boom
Bang a gun
Right
All right, so I didn't completely suck
I had some of it going
Okay
Good one
Definitely
I've created a cassette
Yeah
Thank you, so I got the credit
I said Robert Bomber as well
Boom
Down
Bang
Bye, everybody, thank you very much
Cool
Oh man, that's exhilarating
And we've got a whole bunch of different
Different ones all lined up today
If you want to send something
And we'll just do this for a while, you know
I don't like you know
Falling into anything that is like permanent
And eventually
We may even get tired of doing the hit test all together
But if you want to send some unique type of trivia
You've got to keep it
If it's music, you know
It's got to be 60, 70s, 80s, 90s
You know, whatever
Just trying to stump me
It's cool
I think people kind of like guessing
And listening to me, you know
Fucking it up, right
Is that kind of what it is?
Something like that
A broken glass
This is Frank from Hamburg and Germany
I've recently started listening to your podcast
Quite enjoying it
So I thought it would be a great idea to contribute to that
For a little trivia quiz
I like that very much as well
So we'll see how far you've got
Okay
He's number one, get ready
Yes
Or question when you were in the dark
If you leave
I'm going down
Ah, got it?
Great
He's number two
Oh, what's that in the song?
Is that you, howling somewhat?
On we go to the last one
J
What do you call it?
Ultrawax Vienna
Ooh, the last one was a quickie
But I think you got it
Don't you?
Art
Okay, here we go
Here the answer
The first one was
OMD
Orchestra maneuvers in the dark
If you leave
Yes
Okay, that's OMD
And the next one
I hope you got that right
Very distinctive intro
The cure
The love cats
I never like the cure
Really
Nice guys, but I never really like the music
Christina's now into the cure
Oh, I don't know
How do you pronounce that one?
Is it Max Werner?
Oh, Wayne and me
Oh, shoot
That's right, Max Werner
Good, Larry
Okay, thank you, Max
And thank you Adam for trying this trivia
I hope you got three out of three
So
I got your next time
Keep up the good work
And greetings from Germany
And bye-bye
Okay
Cheers, Grisgot
Thank you very much Frank
Still to come a Beatles bassline trivia quiz
Which is
I listened
I listened to the first clue
In previewing it for
I remember I did this last week or something when it came in
And I didn't know which one it was
So it's going to be a good test
I kind of like this
Let me know
Most people seem to like the Thursday trivia
So we'll just keep this going
As long as we can
The lost in translation trivia
Is the second time we're doing this one
This originated
Let me see
There's a whole email that I put in the show notes for table
Where this concept originated from
Of basically taking something
Putting it into translating it to another language
Then translating it back through
A sort of kind of translation device
In this case I guess Google Translator
Or Autivista
And then that becomes the lyric clue
For the lost in translation trivia question
To be a quad from iLoveRidue.org
And that means it's time for
Cool
This sort of thing ain't my bank baby
This is how this works as usual
I'm going to take an 80 song
Put it into the all of us to translate
And search engine translated to finish this time
And back again to English
You hear the translated version?
You try to figure out what the original song was
Ready?
Yep
Let's play
Here we go
Do not touch me to satisfy me
I can no longer hold the manner by which you seduce
Although you wouldn't be that so much
Yet I love
Now I will collect all and leave
Which corrupted love
Let's hear that again
I was going to lie
Of course we get to replay it
Right?
Do we don't have to take it in real time
Like on the radio
We don't want to get one shot
To satisfy me
I can no longer hold the manner by which you seduce
Although you wouldn't be that so much
Yet I love
Now I will collect all and leave
Which corrupted love
Oh
Tainted love
Of course
Oh
Oh man
I cannot stand
But when you see
I love you though you heard me so
Now I'm gonna let my things and go
So that's it for this week
Here's a hint for next week
Though
Your clue
Think
Biggest hair
Okay
We'll check that out next week
I guess Thursday on Trivia Thursday on your daily stores coast
It's
So
You really?
Hi Adam
I am Rick's
That's our
I ex from Copenhagen
I then use a kiss for you
Hold the reversed hits
And the rules are very simple
You get to hear
Three hit songs
But they have been reversed
Of course
And then you get to hear them one more time
Okay
Then there would be a short
Thinking intimate
So
Cowbell
Fiesta whatever
And then you get
All right
So I hope you are ready
I'm ready ready
I'm ready to go
I know this one
I know
I won't say it until it's not
It's a long clue
Okay that's a B52's
Love shack
Before that was 10cc
I'm not in love
C
Can I see this one
Can I see it
Can I see this this one
Can I see this one
Can lanç this one
Which is letting me know
I think that's David Bohey
One
Nice
Oh
Stop
You
Go
R
B
Oh dude, I'm going to fucking answer this.
I hope it's not a stand.
What do you have is it this way?
Oh well.
I'm committed now.
Yeah, that's a little shock.
Yeah.
I think it's David Bowie.
Okay.
Some of these songs sound the same.
Oh, this is my cowboy intermediator.
All right.
We need to tighten it up a little bit and take it a little bit shorter.
Okay.
So I think we have 10CC and not in love.
B-52's Love Shack.
And then some David Bowie, like Ziggy Star,
start us period, post Ziggy, post Patricia.
Here it is.
There we go.
He is of course.
I'm not in love with 10CC.
Yeah.
You got that one right.
B is Love Shack.
Yeah.
B-52's.
And the C, I don't want to live without your liver.
What's that?
What's your color?
Oh.
Wow.
Let's have you have fun with this music quiz.
Oh, this is Rick's from Copenhagen signing off.
All right.
Thank you very much.
I'm Copenhagen.
All right.
How are we doing time wise?
Okay.
I hope you're still with me.
Now at any point, you can always fast forward through this stuff.
But to make it interesting, there's also a pod-safe music trivia, which is kind of like
McMotion.com.
Yeah.
The listening to all these really cool trivia questions you've been getting.
And I thought I'd do a little twist on it.
Never one knows the 80s and all that music.
But what I want you to do is see if you can guess this pod-safe music.
Now, I don't want to give you total obscure stuff.
All this stuff has been played on at least more than one pod gas.
And it's been played over at accident at Hatch.com.
At least once.
Okay.
See how you're doing what pod-safe music.
Here's track 1.
I don't know, but I like it.
Track 2 is a little bit easier.
Uh-huh.
Much easier.
Track 3.
And here's the last one.
Track 4.
All right.
Well, I hope you can go tell us where we can find all these tracks.
Because I see this as a music sample.
And they're good.
I like all these songs.
All right.
Now, it's no fun without the answers.
I know you're like the answers right afterwards.
So now, let's give them to you.
Okay.
Track 1 was, now is now, with days of self.
Of course.
Okay.
Like small bro.
Sounds cool.
I hope you can tell us where we can find rock from manned in the marbles.
This is rice, like a new music sample.
It's cool.
Track 3 was chance with hip hop high.
Look around.
You're already there.
The next impact takes a long time.
So feel out the question now.
Then drop it to a hip hop high.
And finally, one of my personal favorites, Taxi Doll, with waiting.
You know I can wait in waiting way too long.
So now, I'm waiting alone.
For this I've been waiting much too long.
So long, I'll never waiting as long.
Anyways, Adam, I'm really digging the show.
And I hope you had fun playing a little pod safe music trivia.
So I'm going to buyaxonhash.com now even here more.
Have a good one.
Peace.
Axonhash.com.
Okay.
So as a trivia quiz, it sucks.
Because I don't fucking clue.
I've never heard this before in my life.
But if you're so confident that enough people know about these songs that you can put
into a trivia quiz, you know, Axonhash.com.
I'm over there.
I like a lot of these tunes.
I'll just want to play them.
All right.
So the last one is we come up on the 40-minute mark is the one that I promised you about.
I think it has a lot of promise.
If you're a real beetle freak, and there's a lot of people who are totally into the beetles.
But baseline, now that's really tough.
Hi, I'm this is Mike Stewart of InternetAudioGuide.com.
Podcastgear.com and really my real passion is Beetles Music from BeetlesSing Along.com.
I've been listening to the Daily Source Code for quite some time now and I really enjoy what
you've done.
And I thought you might enjoy this kind of twist on trivia.
Because I'm such a huge beetles fan, I know all the baselines from all the hits.
And I own a 67-hoffner base here in my hand, and I'm going to play baselines from the hit
songs and see if you can guess them.
Here's the first one.
And then here's number two.
I can't hear it.
I know there's musicians who don't know me.
This one's going to be a little harder because it's not in the beginning of the song.
A little harder.
Okay.
Oh yeah, I know this.
But only because it's a solo.
And here is number four.
It's difficult.
No clue.
It plays well though.
There's number five.
No, no, no, no, no.
I feel like I'm standing at Sam Goodie's music store.
But one guy's playing stairway to heaven over on the left and another guy's playing
Beatles bass line.
The answer's right after this.
After what?
The commercial lesson you enjoyed this new twist on trivia.
Well, the first one is all my love.
Oh my god.
Okay.
Oh, that's shocking.
I didn't hear that.
The second one is I dig a pony from the let it be album.
Okay.
Yeah, I wouldn't have been able to name it.
I'll still name it.
I recognize it.
She is.
The third bass line was the bass solo in the middle of.
I want you on a heavy road.
Yeah, I forgot.
Wouldn't have been able to name it either.
Yeah.
I recognize the solo for sure.
The fourth one.
Being for the benefit of Mr. Kite.
I'll start to pepper.
No.
Okay.
The songs are a little too obscure for me, I think.
The first one.
Got it. Got it. Got it. Got it. Yeah.
And the last one was what Paul opens up.
His latest concert that I saw here in Atlanta.
Hello, goodbyes.
I should have known that one.
Man, great songs.
Complicated stuff, though.
Listen to those bass lines.
That's a good shit that Paul McCartney came up with.
That's really.
The music geniuses.
What can I say?
Well, I hope you enjoyed this beatless bass part.
Trivia.
And if you like some more of these, there's 313 songs.
I don't want it.
Well, I hope you enjoyed it.
Yeah.
I certainly didn't enjoy it.
Okay, that wraps up Trivia Thursday on the daily source code.
I hope you enjoyed it.
Oh, man.
Let's see.
I think tomorrow we'll just try and wrap up all the loose ends.
All the stuff you've been talking about.
And leave some room open for some promos.
There's lots of new podcasts that have lined up to be added to the directories.
And then on the weekend, I'm thinking we have some fun.
Maybe we talk to Canada for sure.
What an experiment.
If the weather was any better, then we could actually do another sound scene
to us somewhere.
We'll see.
Both the girls have, like, they have a little mini-flue.
They're all stuffed up.
So I think they'll be into going home soon.
They're kind of sucks, but may just be a stay-in-home day.
Just T.C.
OB.
If you have any comments, send it out on McCurray.com of the audio form,
MP3 feedback at gmail.com, and you can get the latest source code
on the archives and the podcast feed at dailysourcecode.com.
My weblog www.curray.com.
We don't need any more info than that.
Thanks to the lovely crystal for today's show.
Thank you, dear.
Thank you for supporting us.
As always, she's my lifeline.
All right, everybody, take care.
I'll see you tomorrow.