Delta Shira Charley 2-1-2 something remarkable is happening here radio is springing free
of the regulated gatekeepers who managed what you can hear since radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass than the next generation radio
content in my ears.
Hello everybody from San Francisco just in time for the weekend it's a source code.
Okay, I feel really, really bad because I have left y'all in the dark as in completely
radio silence but there's all a good explanation for it.
Most of it has to do with human fatigue.
It's the source code for the 22nd July 2005.
And I'm coming to you from San Francisco last time we spoke was Tuesday when I was in
Curry Cottage.
I'm not going to tell you what hotel I'm in.
I've learned my lesson ever since iTunes launched whenever I tell you what I'm doing on the road
and where I'm staying.
The phone starts ringing like 3 in the morning and I haven't quite got to that point where
I registered the hotel as Mr. Ben Dover.
Anyway, we've got lots of stuff to talk about.
Lots of catching up to do.
We've got pod safe music and young pellets hit test all on the way.
Okay, I'm just trying to think where I have to start.
You know, it's been an amazing almost 72 hours.
Left Tuesday morning dropped Christina off at school and went straight off to the airport.
So I'm going to check my microphone levels.
Of course, I'm coming to you on the cast blaster, which I love to do when I'm on the road because everything
is so self-contained and everything just kind of works and I got all my stuff loaded up.
I love it.
And basically 10 hour flight got in when straight from the airport to some meetings 24 hours of no sleep
which took me out for Thursday and Friday, which was today.
Well, I'll get into all of that.
You know what?
Let's get the weekend cranking.
Hopefully you're still kind of ending up your work mode.
It's Friday wherever you are listening to this.
If not, you know what?
This will work for any day of the weekend, I think.
Check this mashup for mashuptown.com.
It's owner of a lonely butt, which means we've got some yes mixed up with sir mix a lot.
You might want to crank this one up and stick it in your ear.
I hope you guys try to warn me.
But you've got me.
You've got my sweet skin.
You say what?
In my hands?
What you think?
You know, because we've got everything.
We'll be.
I'll see you in a damn city.
To hell with you.
Man, say to see a swim.
We've got to go on like a triple-flat.
I've got to make a scene.
Do you see what's on the plane?
I've got everything left.
She got to pack much back.
So fill it up.
Fill it up.
Shake it, shake it, shake it.
Shake it, shake it.
Fill it up.
All they do is say we ain't leaving
We're not pull out quick to retrieve it
So girls know social fat
We're ain't down with them
Because your wings are slowly getting
And I think I'm sticking
To the big hot things and the magazines
You ain't even mentioning
In this stock and resist stock
We're being embraced in this stock
I'm never going to try to kiss
And this girl's a whole lot less
So ladies and gentlemen
Gonna try to pull it slow down
To a one nine centric mixlock
To kick the middle of the thorns
We learn and learn and learn and learn and learn
We learn and learn and learn and learn
We learn and learn and learn
Oh, you're a lonely butt
You can find that at mashuptown.com
Eight doubles been sending me all kinds of cool stuff
And I'm loaded up for
Certainly for the next couple of weeks
I've got mashups but do not hesitate at all
The send your mashups in mashup at podshow.com
This is the daily source code
I'm gonna try and play catch up with you
See if we can
Woo
Man
I'm in stand-up mode actually today
I figured that's about the only way I could see right now
It's a six thirty p.m. Friday afternoon
Early evening of course in San Francisco
I am so tired
I can't tell you how tired I am
So yeah, so
Plain ride
Let me just do it in chronological order
That's probably the best way that I can keep track of all this stuff
Upper deck
Virgin upper deck
Unlike their mobile phone service
Which interestingly enough
I was reading the financial times
The UK financial times
On the airplane
And there was this article about the virgin mobile
As you know, I've had some
Well, I had some
Not only to have some problems with them
But I dropped them as my carrier for my phone service
And actually I thought about it
You know, there's probably
Anywhere from, you know, like 13 to 15 thousand
Dollars worth of revenue that they lost
Simply by just not being able to deal with me as a customer
And it's a technical problem
You know, there are virtual mobile operator
They ride on top of T-Mobile
And they just couldn't figure out how to un-blacklist my phone
No problem, so I'm a very satisfied T-Mobile customer now
But I was reading that last year they had 150,000 new sign-ups
In this period and this year it's 75,000 sign-ups
So it makes sense if there's any analyst listening
There you go, and now they say they're concentrating on
What is it? The concentrating on the higher
On the upper level of their customers
So people who spend a lot of money
I think if I'm spending $15,000 a year on
On phone calls that I would probably fall in that category
But you know, they got some work to do
Anyway, so their airline virgin airlines
I'm still, or a virgin Atlantic
I'm still very happy with it
It was great actually
Two times in a row, I don't know how it works
But they have a massage service on board
And of course, you know, there's probably about 50 people who all want the massage
And they can only do
There's one masseuse typically
On a flight and they can only do so many people
So I did get my shot this time
Which was great because man, my shoulder
It's much, much better
Thank you so much
I'm still getting so many emails from people who identify
With exactly this problem
We were even saying, oh, you know, I've had this, but never really thought about what it could be
There's no pain actually, there's very little pain involved
But sometimes I can just feel my
You know, the tendons or muscle, whatever it is, my shoulder
Tighten up, going to some kind of like spasm
And then immediately my whole arm
Starts to tingle and starts to go numb
And I have some exercises now that I have to do
Which I think I did them for you
Didn't do them last week, we pushed your chin back
Into your neck like gratins
It's not very attractive when you do that
Because then you get like triple chin
Oh my god, just caught a little glimpse of that in the mirror
Let's see, so I actually did some work on the flight over
Hopefully by now you've had a chance to check out our first shadow cast of Spike Lee
It's listed prominently in iTunes
And you can subscribe to the podcast
There'll be four episodes
And I was editing episode number two
Which will be out this coming Tuesday
You've probably got a good taste of what this Spike Lee podcast of
Inside man is all about with our shadow cast or human Newman
Who just kills me with his narration
I really love listening to that
So give it a listen if you haven't checked it out yet
So I did some editing, which was great, you know
You've got their in-seat power
And you can really get a lot of work done
Very, very comfortable doing that
Very luxurious in their in their seats
Where you kind of you can even recline during takeoff and landing
Which I totally appreciate
Also watch two movies
I finally got the C-Ray
Which I hadn't seen yet
About the life and times of
Of Ray Charles
I was really good
I was a good movie
I understand why it was an award-winning movie
I was nice
Although there was a lot of stuff in there
I felt they focused really heavily on the hero and aspect
And you know those days
Back in the late 50s and 60s
Everybody was screwing everybody on the road
And doing all kinds of drugs
And it wasn't really out of the ordinary
And I thought the movie focused quite heavily on that
But I loved seeing a lot of the
You know the technological improvement in the music scene
Where Ray got his willets
Or the first eight track recordings
And man the guy is just a musical genius
And of course seeing Quincy Jones
Or actor portraying Quincy Jones
And part of how that story all came together
That was very enjoyable
So I watched that and also watched Hitch
Which is the Will Smith movie
That was cute
That was very cute watching that
It actually inspired me to have a dirty vodka
Martini
With all of us when I got to San Francisco
Anyway so I got in around 2 o'clock
Ron picked me up
And we had some very important meetings
Which unfortunately
That we've got the no-dam announcement
Rule still in effect on that
But let me tell you this much
I'll be making a whole bunch of phone calls today
And tomorrow and over the weekend
To a number of people that we've been working with
Over the past months
And I've got great news to report to them
And once everyone's informed
Then we'll start announcing
Some of this great stuff that we have to talk about
So that we have to talk about
So I'm very very excited
It's been great
But by the time I got back in the hotel
It was 11 o'clock
So I've been up for more than 24 hours
I didn't have it in me at all
To create a source code
Then I had to get up early
Because actually I didn't just have to record a source code
I had to create the podcast
Ali Top 10
Which aired today on serious satellite
In fact, it's running as we speak
Very excited about that
A lot of good vibes
And I think it's really for the serious satellite listeners
It's going to be exciting
And what we're working on with the press department
And serious is really publishing this list
And getting it into several publications on a regular basis
So that there can be a wide distribution of the knowledge
Of what the top 10 podcasts are
And what I like about this top 10
Is it truly is a listener-based top 10
Now sure
People are, you know, enticing
And begging almost
Their listeners to go and vote for them
And podcast Ali
But I'm fine with that
You know, by the way
I'm not in the top 10
Dawn and Drew are in there though
So if you have a chance
Look out for that list
And you can always go to podcastali.com
And check it out for yourself
And vote for your favorite podcast for sure
So I did that
I had to do that
And I was just two tired
Two tired
So I got up Thursday morning
Around the 630
I hooked up with PETA
Who had basically pre-produced everything
It was ready to go
And it was weird
Because the first thing he said
When I skyped him as he said
And if you see the news about London
And I'm like, oh, Christ now
So of course, by now
We all know about what's
What's that noise?
Oh, is that my computer?
Yeah
I have the window open
I'm on the 15th floor of the hotel
So you may hear some typical San Francisco sounds
In the background
I'm just
Oh, that's just work outside
I guess
Not hearing someone
Some working crew
Ah
Where was I?
Okay, so that you know, heard about the
The failed bombing attempts in London
And so of course
I immediately hopped on with Patricia
And talked to her about it
And
Man, this is pretty messed up
This is
It's funny, you know
For years
I've been watching television reports
And news reports
And we've seen what's been happening
In Israel
And with the suicide bombings there
And all of a sudden it's like, you know, hey
The world truly has become a smaller place
Because
We've got the same shit here
And
Well, not necessarily here
But in the UK, of course
We had
You know, what happens in September
11th
And the world has definitely changed
You know
And there's lots of
Well, I hope we have some damn good leaders
Who can really help us through these times
And work on these problems
And, you know, it's not going to be
Travilion
It may be a problem that we're stuck with
For the next 50 years
But
You know, I'm no political analyst
But I'll tell you
When it comes down to it
And the only recourse people have
For whatever their frustrations are
Is
Blowing themselves up
You know, then
We've got some serious serious issues
So
That said
Onto the more fun stuff
To did all that stuff
That I had to do
Production-wise
And by the way, I'm really enjoying that
You have no idea how
Incredibly enjoyable it is to me
For someone who's been
Creating radio shows
Since I was 14 years old
To have almost come full circle
You know, I used to do stuff in my bedroom
And I'd be recording it
And then
Have little transmitters
And later became bigger transmitters
And those were illegal
And later it was all legalized
And I was getting paid for it
And now we're kind of, you know, back full circle
And back in the bedroom
Yeah, now it's all digital
I don't have turn tables anymore
But
You know, it's still in the bedroom
And I'm not getting paid for it
So that's how we've come full circle
It's pretty nice
Let's see
We had
Strategy session
With a couple of people
Who were out on the west coast
Operational
That is for
For pod show
Which of course is all based
To part
I was all a part of the
No Dam announcements
News that I'll just stop talking
About since I'll probably only make
Only piss you off that I'm
Teasing it but can't tell you what it is yet
But within the next two weeks
That'll all become very apparent
And one of the important things that
I came out for
Wasn't meeting with Apple
Now
I think I told you
Last time we spoke Tuesday
That, you know,
Mads Weinstein
Among other people
I've said, well, you know,
Look at what Apple's done
How come you're not
You know, yelling at the top of your lungs
About how they've messed this up
Or haven't done this right or haven't done that right
And I'll tell you, you know,
That is a, that I think is a
Need jerk reaction
What I really wanted to do
Which, you know, which I was very happy
I did is I wanted to go talk to the people
At Apple and see what was going on
And coordinate and find out what some of the issues were
I tell you
I was so pleasantly surprised
When I met with
Not all but
Major portion of the iTunes podcasting team
And then the iTunes really
The iTunes music store team
And some of the engineers
And the strategists and people working on the directory
We went through all of the features and services
And processes that the podcast and community
Has been working on for over a year
And some of them Apple just wasn't aware of
Or the team just wasn't aware of
And other ones they actually were quite aware of
And have been working on it and, you know,
You know what the biggest problem is
This is, it's not really a problem
But this is so new for a company like Apple
To actually they have to kind of, you know,
We'll do a couple of interesting things
They have to really be listening to their
To their customers at this point
And of course they listen to their customers
But their customers have a year head start
Which is new for them
They have to be much more forthcoming with
Information
And they don't have a feedback loop
And you know a downstream feedback loop
Traditionally always done through PR and marketing
And advertising in fact
And so, you know, to open up a channel
It may seem very simple to think, you know,
Hey, they should just do a weblog
Or they should do a podcast or, you know,
Where's the Steve Jobs podcast
But it's not in the DNA of companies like Apple
And what I did see though
Is they want to program that into their DNA
You know, you can almost see like
They've got the helix there
And they're trying to insert little molecules
Whatever the heck it is
And I was really encouraged by that
I'll just give you a couple of
A couple of things we talked about
We talked about opml
Import and export or subscription list
We talked about statistics of feeds
We talked about the updating of the feeds
We talked about using some existing infrastructure
And what we've agreed to
Is that
I will
Well, we agreed to so much
I really want to try and help them
Learn how to communicate into the community
And you know, of course I said, well
Steve Jobs should do a podcast
I know if he's going to do a regular podcast
But he should give it a whack, you know
And we should look at how
How you're building the directory
And I have to say
I was extremely encouraged
But, you know, don't forget
There are people inside of Apple, you know
And the human beings
And they're being deluged with all kinds of
Input from all over the place
From phone calls to, you know, to emails
And people who are upset
Worried pissed off
Disappointed
I think there are also many who are extremely happy
In fact, when I entered the country
And I went through customs
The customs officer looked at me and said, dude
I just saw the podcasting tab in my eye
And I'm loving it, you know
So there's a lot of good stuff there as well
In fact, I think there's much more good than that
It's just, you know, we're a very vocal community
And my God, we're actually using our vocal cords
So, you know, I guess all I can tell you
You have to give it a little time, you know
Here's a company that has jumped right into the fray
They recognize and realize that
They didn't get everything right
And they have a lot to learn and they're in learning mode
And I really am very positive about that
And we even talked about content delivery
And we talked about Bitcoin
We talked about a whole bunch of things
And it's not my position to tell you what they're doing
Unless they explicitly tell me that
That I can and they've promised me that as they bring new features online
That they're going to start sending that message out
And I will gladly help them with that communication
So, I'm psyched about it
I really, really am psyched about it
And I was apprehensive, I have to tell you right up front
I was like, oh man, you know
We'll get some of this stuff right
And I really have a good feeling about it
And they're also learning about what makes a good aggregator
And what people use their feeds for
And how important subscription information is
As a feedback mechanism to content producers
But also, you know, it's some technical stuff
But I learned a lot about why feeds weren't updating in a timely manner
And there's some infrastructure stuff there that we talked about
And I pointed them to some infrastructure that we've already created
Within the podcast in community
That they can use right now today to make that better
And I think it was just, it was the right conversation
At the right time
And I'm excited about what is going to be coming in the next couple of weeks
But make no mistake, it's going to take time
Developing software takes time, developing services takes time
They have partners that they work with
That have to change their processes as well
Aquaman, I've talked about Aquaman a lot
And some of the issues that we run up against
And this is all new stuff, you know
Even content delivery networks have never really
I mean, this is when podcasting
You know, I'm going to put this podcasting has a
Band with them request curve that is almost the severe as when a new
Windows update comes out, you know, and all these
Hundreds of millions of machines around the world
Start updating their Windows software
This is big, big stuff and even I'm surprised
By what this is taking resource-wise
And you know what?
We have a lot of stuff to fix
We have a lot of our damn announcements
We'll communicate how we hope to fix a lot of the issues
One of them being bandwidth
Because, you know, if the case is
If we have a situation where an independent podcast
Can't be listed or promoted through for instance
iTunes or some other big avenue
Because then they run out of bandwidth
And they basically take it off the air
Then podcasting is going to fail
It's going to be, well, it's not going to fail
But it's not the way it should work
You know, that should not be an issue
And I think we have some ways to really help the community
To make sure that everybody has a fair shot
And that everybody can be pointed to by iTunes
And not go off the air
And everybody can enjoy a global audience
Jumping on board with them
Oh, that's one thing I want to mention
I'm going to skip water here
This is Fiji water
Five blocks of bottle, my goodness
Something that I didn't, I wasn't aware
But something that I'm happy to pass on
The top 10 list on the top 10 podcast list and iTunes
First of all, there's, you know, there's
I think there's 15 different countries
So there's 15 different
versions of iTunes, not just the music store
But also podcasting and localized top 10 list
So in the Netherlands, you'll see a different top 10
Then in the UK, which will be a different top 10
Then in the US
And that is a top 10, which is, and here it comes
Just so you know how that works
Because I don't think that was explained very well
It's a top 10 of new subscriptions
To podcasts within roughly the last 24 hours
So that's why you can see things shooting up the charts
And it also is really, and I have to agree with this
It's a pretty fair way of doing it
I'm no statistician, but it's a pretty fair way of doing things
So that, you know, when a new podcast comes online
Or, you know, it catches on
And people start subscribing to it
It really will
Start to
Propagate into the top 10
And by the way, that data also
I believe is going to start to flow out of Apple
So again, new stuff for them, new stuff for us
And I'm looking on looking very much forward to continue
Work with Apple on doing this
So we also released, as you know, pod finder
2 pod finder 3 will be up on Tuesday
And it's funny
I got a wonderful email from
I think it's Clark Boyd
Who works in public radio
And also works for the BBC
And he said
And he said, hey, you know, how come you're not promoting
Any of the public radio stuff?
Oh my goodness, you know, now
We've been promoting the indie podcasters so much
Now everyone, sorry, I don't know what to do
I just want everyone to hear as many podcasts as possible
Much out there as as humanly possible
And it's, you know, on serious satellite
We get four hours a day
On the pod finder, it's, you know, an hour a week
Or whatever we can make it
And it's about 10 to 15 different podcasts
We're just going to keep on tracking, keep on promoting
Keep on pushing it out there
Any suggestions, we'll be more than welcome
Okay
I want to play some music for you
I was searching through the pod safe music network
And came across
Let's see
From a California
It's a dream of thought
I believe is the way you pronounce it
Our debut album is titled Elusive
Let me see
Her influences
This is kind of some interesting info we've got here
Sarah McLaughlin, McLaughlin, McLaughlin, how do I pronounce that?
Toriamos, Coldplay
You kind of get the picture when you start to listen to the tune
And I think you like it
Nightfly, fly
Andryna Thorpe, pod safe
On your daddy's source code
And I'm blue, that'll sky
Rolls, it's days, it's been in sight of my mind
And as I float through the midst
Or I'll balloon me, it seems to far behind
Like I can fly
Fly, fly, I love these seems to matter
Let you hear beside me
If you're here for a new year
Would you feel like you?
And all the cars wouldn't bite
And motion the same light
They could be parallel
And the light inside me
Feels so bright, it's hot for me
And tonight
Like I can do fly
Fly, fly, fly
Fly, I love these seems to matter
Let you hear beside me
If you're here for a new year
Would you feel like you?
And all the cars wouldn't bite
And as I float through the midst
Or I'll balloon me, it seems to far behind
Like I can do fly
I love these seems to matter
Let you hear beside me
If you're here for a new year
Would you feel like you?
And all the cars wouldn't bite
And as I float through the midst
Or I'll balloon me, it seems to far behind
Like I can do fly
Fly, fly, fly, fly
Fly, fly, fly
Fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, no
Than seems to better
You're here for scenting me
Fly, fly, fly, fly
When I'm here with you I'd feel like
Fly, fly, fly, pad, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing
on the daily source code, definitely go over and check out the Podsafe music network. I was looking at the, let me go in there, let me see with the, I don't get the most pod play. I was very interesting, because I really see the system. Let's see.
Top of the list here, brother love summertime, we've played that bill, sound scientist, transfer how hazardous we are, brother love with push, I played that a while while ago, Rob Costlow still, whoops, second my, oh man, I want to do that, my browser just kind of freak out. Here we go, two era with filled, another Rob Costlow song in the top 10, the most pod play, which is family, haven't actually played that one before.
This one, Adrina Thorpe, Fly Fly Fly Fly, Chan, say what you will and another Rob Costlow, man, three Rob Costlow's in the most played on Podcast. Let me just see who's playing, so Adrina Thorpe, I think, can I, I should be able to go check out and see who else has played Adrina, home on a second, let me just check, oh wait, that's, boy, I'm missing this all up, aren't I?
There's still a couple of things that I'd like to work differently, not everywhere within the pod safe music network, is it possible to immediately go to that band's page?
I don't think so, I haven't figured out how to do it, so hold on, let me see, who's playing, who else is playing Adrina? Oh, it's interesting while I'm searching for this, hold on a second, so I would have to play Fly Fly Fly, let's see.
Oh man, connectivity here is sucking. Well, while that's loading, I got a note, it was actually, wasn't a very polite note, it kind of said, you know, dear Adam, very disappointed that, you know, you haven't taken the blind casters, the blind listeners into account on the pod safe music network,
because the registration process is not accessible for the blind. Hey, you know what, we messed up, but guess what, we fixed it, or at least we put a fix in that is workable and did that almost immediately.
What we got to do is just ask, you know, not to be too nasty about it, so hopefully that's better, and it's, you know, it's amazing, we all kind of like hit our forehead, it's going, oh my God, you know, how, how could we mess that up, such a sense for such advocates and, and dude, this is audio, we should know a lot better than that.
So that is fixed, got a nice email from Andrew Sylvester, and it was, it's just a little thing, but I thought that I'd pass it on to you because he, he said I was, he was listening to daily source code and heard me struggle with the Celsius or centigrade to Fahrenheit temperature conversion and he has an easy trick on how to do that conversion.
I just want to give it to you because it's one of those things, it's real handy, once you know it, then, you know, then you can kind of use it forever.
So if you want to go from centigrade to Fahrenheit, you double it and add 30, so if it's 25 degrees centigrade, you double it, which would mean it would be 50 and you add 30, which mean it would be 80 degrees.
If you want to go the reverse, all you do is you subtract 30 and then divide it in half, and then you obviously come up with the centigrade number.
Now, it's not completely accurate, but it does put you within, you know, like plus or minus 34 degrees, but it's just something really handy when just, you know, you need to know real quick, and hopefully we'll get one of those simple ones for gallons to leaders, one of these days,
because man, I'm lost on that as well, what else did I have?
Oh, Christine, the finished school, her year is up, so vacations officially started, our plans are to go to the states that I told you the first week of August.
August, first actually, Patricia and I have been invited to a party, the Playboy UK party in London, and I've actually been asked to do a sound seeing tour of it.
So, beyond the lookout for that, I'm pretty excited, but Christine, I had a great report card, very excited.
Here's a kid who came into a new environment, a new country, a new school, halfway through the school year, hadn't even had Spanish ever in her life, which is one of, you know, which is language she had to take this year, and she got her SATs back, which are very comparable to the SATs in the US, and she did fantastic job.
I'm so incredibly proud of her, I'm just so proud of her. She's been great. What a trooper and a half, she is, really is. Okay, let's go.
You're so disgusting with Adam, you're bringing John, it's time for the hip-tooth with y'all, Poles.
Hey, John.
Hello?
Hey Adam, they take this number 49.
And the clips and answers are edited by Richard.
Okay.
So that means there are a few 70 songs in there as well.
Yeah.
And it gets your guys to the intro.
Number 1.
All right.
Oh, come on.
This is one of my favorites.
This is a very easy one.
That's the motel's suddenly last summer.
Suddenly one summer.
Suddenly last summer, I think it is.
And this is number two.
It's a steely Dan.
Do it again.
Oh, this is going to be a fun one.
Can't wait to hear the answers.
And the final one is number three.
Oh, yes.
Of course.
You can use a congenius.
We all should know this one.
That's the Stevie Wonder.
Superstition.
I've got my Boeing ready.
Oops.
Time's up. This is answer number one.
Okay.
From 1983, the motel.
Yeah.
And he does number 49.
Suddenly, last summer.
For a short time.
Oh.
One summer, never ends.
It takes all my wings and so many.
Last summer.
Okay. Number two.
And so number one.
The motel.
And this is answer number two.
And hit this number 49.
It's a song from 1972.
And it's from Steely Dan.
This is doing it again.
Yeah. Two for two.
We're going to learn.
Back.
Yeah.
Down.
Now we're going to see.
Steely Dan.
And number three.
And this is answer number three.
From 1973, there's a superstition.
Steely Wonder.
Yep.
We create.
What a classic!
Awesome!
Steve you wonder and superstition well that's it for hit this number 49 and that means that next time is
the match is right magic number still don't know what I'm gonna do with that hit test but
we'll just have to wait and see I've got to drink a beer I've got to go get some your
idol on the road now are gonna be in a few days well have some fun in the United States
I hope you had fun with this hit test so thank you for playing it thank you for listening see you next
time have a safe trip until next time bye bye all right thank you very much Yana thank you a
Richard and of course Kevin the announcer guy and he didn't say at this time but make sure you
check out the hit test podcast young pullets very onsite at youngpullet.com let me see I think
we've handled just about everything well it's the magic 40 minutes I'd say it's time to
to leave it at that for today's source code now I'd like to do another source code over the
weekend just to catch up after I've had a little more time to sort everything out of my Gmail by
the way has gone from 6,000 on red to over 7,000 I'm trying to cherry pick the best out I really
apologize resend if you have to that is source code gonna be found at dailysourcecode.com
still haven't moved those sites so we're but you might have noticed a little bit of
performance increase in curry.com and I potter.org so we are definitely working on some stuff
and we've I've been working with Marcus and we really worked out a whole bunch of strategies for the
server move trying to keep service interruptions to a minimum and we're on a good track I told
you we'd invest in it and we really are doing it we're putting people in money behind it
and by the way the idea of moving to indiepotter.org you bet you we're gonna do it so look for that
so that's also when you upgrade just upgrade the whole damn thing I tell you we got a lot of work
to do but damn is it gonna be a lot of fun doing it um so you can leave a comment at my web
blog www.curry.com audio comments are welcome now the Gmail is on the infinity plus one tip
that's adam at curry.com send it off to me please look to hear from you
and if you want to send anything in for this show or for pod show and serious or for the pod
finder send it to submit at podshow.com thanks for listening everybody have a great weekend and stay
subscribed okay