Delta share Charlie one nine or six hey Adam this is Ben from the Fusion podcast at Fusion
podcast.blogspot.com me and my friend Captain AJ wrote a little song for you and maybe
you should play this as your new intro. I hope you like it. Here you go. His name is Adam
current. His balls are very very furry. He likes to sit on the John boy gets it on he can
steal jobs as well he'll be smoking grass. He rub his dick with man while he's drinking
and say it. He always plays with his wife Rackley smoking a pack North West gets him furious
while the retard makes him curious. He registered MTV 100 years ago but now five centuries later
he's got his own show. So check it out Adam Curry's show is insane he'll bite your balls off just
for spare train. $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass than the next generation radio
content in my ears. I like to think I'm flying into the future.
It's Friday June 17th. Welcome to the Danny source code coming to you from Curry College and
go further to the United Kingdom back from from my visit to the city this morning. I've been
back for a couple hours you know that a slow email day actually seems like I don't know what's
going on but it's been really quiet which is good so time for the source code.
Oh, it's going to sound really weird but before I start I actually thought to myself yeah this
is one of those days when I'd really like to you know put a source code together I really love to
hear how it turned out but the energy to actually do it. It's been a long week let's put it
up. So I had a great morning I met with Don Kats the CEO of audible.com we'll talk about that
got let's see we'll talk about a couple podcasts got some promos coming up and we're going to hear
from an old voice we haven't heard from in a while as well as podcasts tunes.
All right so I suppose that a lot of you are going to be hearing this in the morning some of you
may be hearing it at the end of your day it is Quentin everybody it's Friday which means we're going
to get you weekend started with some movie tunes. Wait till you hear the odd save tunes that
I come out. From the mashup been Qtip versus Michael Jackson breathe don't stop on the daily source code.
Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out
Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Got out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Got out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out. Step out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, pretty much, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah,
And so yesterday it was actually perfect, everything worked fine until it hit an AAC file that I'd purchased from iTunes music store
and it hung on that and for some reason this is totally hanging on this one which is just a regular MP3, I don't know what's going on.
I still think it's my Mac, you know what?
I have to say that being a Mac user, and to see although it wasn't mine, it was my dad's, we had a Mac, an Apple 2,
we had, we had that, I didn't do much on that. My first real Mac was the Mac Plus, although I did learn how to use a Mac on the 512.
Is that the 512K or something like that? It was basically the operating system you had to boot from a floppy disk.
And my philosophy is, once and a while I just got a, you know, buying a new one.
And then they'd you, you know, repurpose the other one for something else to rip off the entire OS and, you know, reinstall it.
And then usually it all the problems clear up. I did that recently when I upgraded both my machines to tiger, the power book which I'm running now was fine.
The other power book which the screen broke on that power book, oh man, a year ago.
And I thought, well, instead of sending it off, I'll just plug it into my cinema display and use it that way.
I really should have it fixed, but, you know, there you go. It's just like, oh well, just get a new one.
Because it's fun. It's like going to the, it's like buying shoes, I guess.
For Patricia, it would be like, oh, I guess I do. Let's see.
Let me see who this is right now inside. Hello. Hello.
Yes. Hey, Lee, I'm writing the middle of the source code. Can I call you back? Okay, bye.
That's fun. Let's leave Wilkins. Remember, man, was that probably half a year ago? Yeah, more than half a year ago.
Lee Wilkins and his, is lovely girlfriend, wait. Is it, are they married now, Jenny?
I've to look that up. They're, they moved to the States and then they moved back almost two weeks later.
And because of the circumstances, the way the dogs were exported, they've two lovely little dogs.
What they jack Russells, I believe, they couldn't be imported back again. So they had to go into quarantine for six months.
And I think we raised like $700, which is what they needed to get all that done. And I think the dogs came home yesterday.
So I'll, I'll make sure I put a link in the show notes today to, to Lee's weblog and podcast. Those guys are pretty happy. I'm sure. Okay.
So I'm going to be talking about my chat with Don Katz this morning. Oh, yesterday, I played, was that yesterday? I think it was, yes, I played Rob Coslo.
Maybe it was the day before yesterday.
The instrumental piece of pod safe music. Wow, I got a lot of response to that. And it's not just from Rob. I mean, he sent a whole bunch of emails through to me. People just go nuts about his stuff.
So I'll put another link to his website in today.
Because it looks like, you know, there's, I don't know, it's just the, it's struck a chord with a whole bunch of people and everyone really liked it.
I think it, for me, even it was a bit off, you know, off color like that. It's not the typical piece of pod safe music I play. And actually, it's P. W. Fenton, who picks all this stuff out.
He's producing the, the pod show on serious. And essentially, we have a whole, we have a pretty cool system set up. It could still be better. And we're, we're actually using Megaseg,
to schedule these four hours a day of, of podcasts and promos and pod safe music and mashups. And of course, my, my, my, my, my, what would just call them voice drops or tracks or wraparounds, you know, whatever.
And so it's a, it's a very cool system. But what does have to be done is, you know, there's all the stuff that's incoming. And so that's put in, in a shared drive and, you know, we can look at stuff and I can drop stuff in.
Hey, it's, uh, it's, uh, it's really cool. And he's finding some amazing things really is not, so that, that was one of his picks. Okay, it's your daily source code. It's Friday and, uh, got lots of promos. Let's get to it.
And now, I'm going to let you fly from D to D with a part of the system that I like on the point of it. It's the future podcast.
You can post it in this picture. Listen now, if there's ransom rates, if there's personal mobiles to deal on, they work.
No topic is left on spirit. This is now at www.minkview.com.
Hey, Adam, it's Bill Powers from the Fantasy Focus podcast. Every week, Chris Adams and I will take a look at the world of fantasy baseball.
Well, tour the major leagues. Take a peek at the injury reports and how it may affect your fantasy squad.
And, of course, the fantasy stugs and duds from the week before. So give us a try. Download us at fantasyfocuspodcast.com.
Thanks, Adam.
Yeah.
Love that completely non-podsafe, Metallica in the background, man. I wonder if the guys give us shit about that. Technically, that's illegal, by the way.
People ask me that all the time. Yes, if you put together promos and sweepers with non-podsafe music, that's really not supposed to be done.
Okay. So this morning, actually had a great experience going to London. I hadn't done a half day trip or planned one in the past.
We just kind of, you know, go in and have a meeting and come back.
It was really good because I dropped Christina off at school at 830 and then I went to the station. It's only two minutes from her school.
Literally, you know, like within walking distance.
And there's a train almost every 10 minutes, which is it's almost an express train that goes from Guilford to London.
It stops only at walking, I think, and I forget the other one.
And while the lady at the ticket office was nice enough to give me this little mini booklet just, you know, it's so cool. It's exactly what someone is doing business once.
You know, so you can put in your shirt pocket, you know, it's just that particular line. It really gives you the information about the direct lines, the direct trains and not the ones that stop a million times, which I've taken before, believe me. You don't want to make that mistake.
So it was a 35 minutes into Waterloo, hop in the cab from the cab. Although this was kind of interesting. We agreed to meet Don Katzenai at
But we'll cover in Garden Hotel. And so here's a cab drive who didn't know the Coven Garden Hotel, which was I didn't quite that that was weird to me because I thought these guys had the knowledge and I suppose to know everything.
So that was the first, but I have myself on with me and I went over to Google local.
Not even sure how I got there, but it just kind of worked on my cell phones pre installed Virgin Mobile does that.
And there was, you know, had the address and I could look in a little map. I could literally walk to it. That was a very nice experience.
Don was there and I hadn't Googled him before going.
Normally I do that just to say, oh, this is what he looks like. I can't remember. I don't know what Don looks like. Actually, I do.
He was a journalist for Rolling Stone Magazine and a accomplished writer himself.
And he co founded audible.com years ago. I think it was 95, 96.
And we had a really good chat. And let me tell you, here's a guy who.
First of all, he is feeling some of the pressure of running a public company and Ron and I, our previous company was public.
And it's really tough because you get distracted by a lot of crap that is.
Yeah, I mean, you at a certain point you're really going to have to evaluate if you, if you should be a public company or not.
But of course, this is a company that went public in 1999, which is just about the worst time you could do that.
But wrote it out. And that's, that's the impressive part.
I wrote the storm out. And they're still around and they're doing very well. They're growing.
And now Don and I have a similar agreement that that I have with Steve Jobs, you know, no damage announcements.
And we can, you know, we don't have to sign anything. We'll just agree that we keep the parts of our conversation and be a confidential confidential.
And of course, we talked about working together. So, whoops.
Man, it's busy today. The OK around. What's this? Oh, there's a text from my daughter. Okay. All right. She's hanging out with friends after school. Got, you know, moms not here. Remember, so I got to do it all on myself.
Oh, boy. I can hear moms everywhere going shut up. I can hear the mommy cast groaning as we speak.
He has a strategy for podcasting, primarily for podcasting, what he calls premium content. And I think it's a good strategy. And I think it makes sense.
And I think there's definitely a place for that. And he has, yes, some damn announcement coming up, which will, I think, show the way of how we're thinking, how the company's thinking.
And what's nice about it is that we pretty much agree that we can work together because, you know, when I talk about our pod show definitely has a different model, but, you know, they could cross over. They could, there's intersection. So it could be interesting.
So it was a nice chat. And we had a nice breakfast. And I hopped back in the cab, went back to Waterloo Station, trains running every 15 minutes. Actually, it's fast on the way back 30 minutes. I was back home by, you know, I won 130. So that was really good. That was a enjoyable. So hopefully, hopefully, don will make some damn announcements at Nomedex.
Hey, Adam, I'd like to ask all of your listeners to give listening to AirFurga try. Each week at AirFurga, me and my wife Shelley Piccatopic, and we give it the AirFurga spin.
Anything from music to movies, TV, politics. And in fact, our most recent episode actually centered around poetry. And here's an example of a bit that we did on that episode.
Let's call the lost pages of Dr. Sus. Hello, and welcome once again to the lost pages of Dr. Sus.
I am your host, Neville Furf and Burger. This week's installment comes from a lost manuscript that many thought never existed in the first place.
It's called the Fields Freshness Fix. And it deals with the problem that many people have in society today, and it tells you how to overcome it, how to rise above, and come together as a family.
Please enjoy the Fields Freshness Fix.
Here in this house where the Fields Family grew, a problem arose, and that problem grew too.
Behind a closed door that was shut and locked tight, Jim Fields and Jan Fields did what they did at night. In the midst of the doings, the grouping and tickles.
Jim smelled what he thought was a four-year-old pickle, with resolve and great courage Jim did not slow down. He took care of the business that he had downtown.
Jim was very determined and not very fickle, but this task became daunting even for a lover of pickles.
And it was not just poor Jim who breathed pickled air, the children and neighbors they all breathed their share.
So finally when you mean Jim sat down with Jan, he opened and spilled the beans out of the can.
Oh my, I must do something Jan then exclaim, then Jim and Jan fields sat with the storm of their brains.
I'll scrub it said Jan and she reached for a brush that was made to do scrubbing and harsh to the touch, so scrub she did Jan until she was swollen and sore, but there was little less odor when she'd finished the job.
Some perfume said Jim, the finest money can buy, so he coded her business in Chanel number five.
But after some time perhaps maybe an hour, the smell came back only mixed with some flowers.
said Jan, is it time I give Douching a try? This condition is embarrassing and burns the kids eyes.
How could you? Why should you? It's just vinegar and water. I wouldn't wish that on my worst enemy's daughter.
We need something stronger, something stronger for sure, so he went to his workbench and he opened the drawer.
Jan watched with great wonder as Jim sat there mixing.
Wondering what mixed Mr. Jim fields was fixing. A breath of fresh air, a hummingbird's beak, a rose and a lilac, a snow capped mountain peak.
A cup of stream water he pulled from a stream, a shiny star's twinkle, a full moon's moon being.
He pulled out his stir and stirred it quite good, then dipped his balls in it as any good stir or wood.
This is our last chance, said Jim fields to his wife, our last chance to remove the sped smell from our life.
So without hesitation he then poured the mixture from the beaker in two Jan fields warmly fixture.
Within seconds or moments sometime very soon the sweet smell of roses encircled the room.
At last it had happened and freshness abounds. There will be no more tears and p-u-ing sounds.
So remember, if freshness is something you lack, a Zeus doosh is the thing that will bring it right back.
Oh my, what a wonderful tale with a happy ending and a good message to boot.
Well, that's all for this time. Join us next time for the Lost Pages of Dr. Zeus.
Goodbye!
Well, hopefully that gives everybody an idea what airferg is all about.
If you liked it, please check us out at stearferg.com and remember airferg.
It's not just a podcast, it's like a doosh for your mind.
Alright, I'll take it.
Foughts a music now on the source code. Here's Brother Loves Push!
What?
Let me stay, what a way you wanna be with you.
To walk away, let me stay, let me be with you.
I search me so slowly, I hear years,
Oh yeah, I'm thinking no, no, no, no, no.
I'm lagging in the fogging out, and you make it so hard.
Yet, tell me no, no, no.
You're having to go here, you push my hands down and run
And say, can't take control, you're so afraid.
Afraid I'm laying you, I'm not that true
You always messin' with your heads and now
Let me stay, you wanna play, you wanna be with you
Let me be with you baby, we have a push
Don't walk away, let me stay, let me be with you
Don't let it end this way
Everybody, breathe for the girl
I will live, I will live, I will live
What about the band of girls?
I love the band of girls, I love the band of girls
I used to go right now, I know, yeah
We got so sexy when we make it dancing so far
I'm going to stay, yeah, I'm not playing here
We're just not used to guys, not messing with your heads and now
Everybody, stay, you wanna play, you wanna be with you
Let me be with you baby, don't let it end this way
Don't walk away, let me stay, let me be with you
Don't let it end this way
I think you wish I was a different person
All together, I do believe I am the right one
You're from town, if you don't know why I put up with
We're so crazy, yeah, yeah
We can't be happy overnight, yeah
We're just not used to standing, yeah
Everybody, stay, you wanna play, wanna be with you
Let me be with you baby, don't let it end this way
You wanna play, wanna be with you
Yeah, understand you, welcome somebody
ass
I love you, understand you, yeah
We're just not used to juego
I just wanted to share it with you one more time. So another hiccup there. This is very frustrating.
I'm going to ask a Ron Bloom question right now. This is my partner's thinking and this is how
fresh that I am that I'm the now, you know, this is where I'd say Ron now you need to help me out
with a technology and he usually gets it fixed because he'd say, well, let's see, the firewire
cable you're using between your firewire drive where the MP3's are located and the Mac.
I'm actually using the firewire cord that came with my eyesight. Now, as I was sitting here listening
to that hiccup and then jamming out of course with the song, I was noticing this wire is very thin
compared to any other firewire cable that I have. Do you Abby could this have something to do
with the hiccup is it maybe that I'm getting less of a transfer rate because of this shitty cable
or do I not know what I'm talking about? Okay. Hey, I told you I was a little tired and I just remembered
why last night before I went to bed, it was around midnight and I was all set to go to bed
and then the Gilmore gang showed up the virtual Gilmore gang. Now, over the weekend, actually
before the week and I'm Friday I spoke to Steve Gilmore and he said, well, I don't think that's
going to be a Gilmore gang this weekend because I'm I'm going to Singapore, he's attending a conference,
he's speaking in a conference and I was going to be on the plane with Steve Wozniak and it was going
to be, you know, all kinds of cool stuff and he was going to do stuff from there. I said, but you
do, you know, skipping one weekend this like, you know, you can't just stick the needle in and pull
it out again, that just doesn't work. So he called two of the gang members who are also
spread out all over the world, Doc Seroles himself was in God. Well, he's in Denmark, I think
Steve Wozniak, I'm pretty funny when you hear it, that you can hear Doc of, you know, when you
call someone up and or when someone calls you and you know, wake you up and then the first thing
you say is, did I wake you and the first thing you always say? No, not at all. I was I was awake.
Why do we do that? When I, yeah, Cox Zucker, you woke me up. I refused to have a phone in the
bedroom for that very reason. I don't care. Whatever it is, if it was the middle of the night, I can't
help you anyway. I need to sleep. So, but it was, it was a long Gilmour gang and I guess Steve
did the, the calls via Skype from Singapore and then edited on his, on his Mac and then uploaded it
to the servers and got everything up and rolling and it was great. But it was now in half, so it was
like 130 before I realized that here I was just listened to the show. Give it a, give it a go though.
If you're into, in fact, the topic was about Intel and Apple and I know it's kind of been
been beat to death by the trade press, but I want to hear the gang members. I want to hear what they
have to say about it. And you know, I love hearing that balance of ideas and what it means and
not even though I have nothing really to do with that industry and that regard, it's kind of cool.
Gilmour gang. What was it? Gilmour gang.podshow.com. A hearty blend of reality TV, celebrity gossip,
police blotter and Dawson's Creek re-run. Time for the Delta Park Project. On this week's show
was a suspicious frying pan. It's a David Hasselhoff couple of rhinestone cows shooting cats from
canons. I like squishing peas in my mouth. I dislike my cat's wookie breath. Did you hear
about Willie Nelson and Nora Jones looking up? Okay, but what is the monster on loss? Make Delta
Park Project part of your weekly ritual on the inner web at DeltaParkProject.com.
So I ran through my iPod or this morning and I'm subscribed to OpenPodcast.org's OpenPodcast
feed and low on behold, what showed up actually was like a day or two late. Our friend
Sandra Lowell and those of you who've been listening to the source code for a longer time were
to episode 196 now. Your call, she is our very own tap dancing newscaster.
We have other countries in seeing Michael Ballforday. Thank you here in Gallard just to do this
was how it would be. And other news, a planet was discovered that could be like the planet
Earth. It was around the nearby store that had hovered. But far enough, we'll maybe get
Michael's career remorse. Even on our planet there could be success where he's head. But
what will become a sister-determined top step made a mess of this case gone wrong. It won't be long.
Till his career's gone unless Michael writes him into another song. Stay tuned for late
ranking hope days. That's the tap dancing podcast news.
Oh man, I had that all set up. It was supposed to be fucking seamless. Oh dude. Okay.
Give me a second. Wow, I'm back. That was whoa. That was pretty awesome.
I had a kill mega-sag and I got all kinds of errors. I took screenshots. I'll send it off to
the developers. Of course it's beta, but I said okay let's try it again everybody. See this works.
There are bomb casting. So go check us out at www.vom.cast.com so it's bombcast.com.
Write us a mail at my email which is email at stuffmc.com.
S-d-u-l-b-l-f-m-c.com and come to listen to us. My name is Stefan C. I'm with a bunch of friends.
I'm with H-B-troll, my t-u-p-r-shout, my son and some others. And we speak all about the things
they do with a pertino. So hope to hear a son. See you soon. Read you soon.
To the Rocky Horrors Show.
Look got fixed and bailed by us with just a bunch of new drill fangs.
But now you took your virgin dragon.
I found you lying in the snow.
Cougars and blow. Cougars and blow.
I am now home. So proud of their holy sun. They come to see if you would have been fun.
I said that I'll ask you if I ever saw you again. You're still being at a clock all day.
I found you lying in the snow. Cougars and blow.
Cougars and blow. Cougars and blow. Cougars and blow.
Cougars and blow. Cougars and blow.
Cougars and blow.
Cougars and blow. What more does a growing boy really need?
I have a conference call coming up. Let's end the show. Now I've messed around long enough with all the bits and nights.
Have you ever suffered a week and a week?
Next week, Patricia comes back early in the week. I think she comes back Tuesday. Then Wednesday,
I'm off, which is I believe the 22nd. And then the 23rd to the 25th is Dome Dex and Seattle.
That's what I'm going to be. So I'm looking forward to that. And of course we'll be podcasting the source code from there as well.
Feedback is very welcome. Adam at curie.com. You can send along MP3, audio feedback and feel like it.
DailySourceCode.com is where you can find the podcast feed to subscribe to the show. You can check out the archives, the latest addition of the source code.
And just to confuse you with more URLs, www.curie.com or comments on the web blog.
I post the show notes up there as well. So anything you hear in the DailySource Code, you can probably find a link to it right there.
I need some more tea.
All right, forget. Craig Maloney, thank you very much for the pod father Photoshop job you did. I freaking love it.
I think that's, I should start embedding that into my M3 files.
Maybe the press will finally use a picture that I pick out for them. I'll send them while the ugly ones.
See that's exactly the problem. Nothing left to say. I'm just going to shut up.
I'll talk you on Monday.
Unless of course something happens over the weekend that would make sense to chat about.
Take care everybody. Have a great weekend. Bye bye.
Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.