daily source code for Tuesday, January 18th, 2005.
Transmeters, we don't need no stinkin' transmitters.
Oh, I'm drowsing casting with Adam Curry.
You coming to hear from the cottage?
The power of the door, the door, the door, the door, the door.
Hey, everyone.
How you doing?
Welcome to the daily source code, as I said today is January 18th, it's Tuesday, 2005.
That's the new thing we're doing now, it's help everyone queue up the new, uh, oops.
That was interesting.
You have the new, uh, source code just by the day to do a little tag at the beginning of the show.
Anyway, it's the power of pure intellect to work.
Although that intellect is not to be found at British Telecom, or easy nap today.
Currently, the time is 11 a.m. here at Curry Cottage in the,
affluent Surrey Suburb of Gilford in the UK, and, um,
I've been on the phone again this morning trying to get that last 15 meters of cable connected to the house here,
and boy, have a lot of fun not getting it done, right?
I'm pissed off about a lot of things today, so this should be a good show.
Look forward to sharing with you the next 40 minutes is your daily source code.
You know, last night, um, I called, uh, I called a couple people in the states, uh,
a couple podcasters, actually I spoke to, uh, to Drew from, uh, Don and Drew show,
and he and I have been actually been exchanging emails with him with his lovely wife, Don,
threatening to call, and of course, they're so nice and so polite, they never call me, right?
Um, and here's the problem that I run into. I don't know if anyone who lives over in Europe
and deals with, um, communicating with the states in real time from time to time.
Uh, probably has this, uh, the same issue is that by the time it's, you know,
you're going to call someone, like Drew gets off work at five o'clock, um,
mountain time, I guess there's a central, whatever, uh, which means that's 11 p.m. here in the UK.
Well, it used to be midnight in, uh, in Belgium when, uh, when we're living in the castle.
And for, well, I mean, so the 11 p.m. is one thing, right, because it's kind of like the end of my day.
I'm getting ready to go to bed. Um, yes, old and boring at 40, go to bed at 11. He leaven.
He leaven, dammit. Um, but in my case, there's an extra handicap, because I'm usually pretty much
baked around 9 p.m. And then what happens is like, oh, man, I should call it.
So I can should call Don Drew. I should, I want to talk to him, but then I'm just, oh, man,
I'm not going to be coherent. I don't want to be saying, um, and actually a cop to that,
uh, to Drew yesterday and he said, oh, dude, I totally know what you talk about.
But you're talking about, so that's good. So I, so I feel like, uh, like,
people understand my pain. Um, but it really is, it truly is an issue. Um, the time difference,
even though it's only five hours, it's still it's more than you think. Anyway,
uh, lots of talk about today. I got a lot of feedback from yesterday's show.
The first thing is a glaring error that I made. Of course, it is not Jamie Far, uh,
who played Ray Charles in, uh, in the movie Ray, but Jamie Foxx. I did have in
living color correct. Uh, that's the show that he became, uh,
most famous, uh, or that he really broke through on, I guess. Um, and we watched the Golden Globes
last night, uh, it was a tape delay. And, uh, so it was like, was a three and a half
out. No, it nine to let that two and a half hour show. We watched it here on, uh,
I guess was on ITV, uh, boring. God, man, that's gotten so predictable and just
boring. Hmm. It's no wonder in the States, the show, uh,
the show got kicked in the in the ratings by Desperate Housewives. Come on,
don't you know, does you tell of his an executives? No, what people want?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
um, there was some real sincerity, though, I like the way Jamie Foxx, uh,
accepted his award, uh, because apparently it wasn't independent film, uh,
some independent finance year pulled $35 million out of his pocket and said,
hey, let's go make this movie. And then it got picked up. I mean,
very much the way I see a lot of podcasts, uh, the way they will go,
at least for the foreseeable future because radio and television is not dead by a
long shot, my friends. But I do see that we'll have some podcasts,
casters who will break into the mainstream, more importantly probably is that we'll see some
music breaking into mainstream and getting a, quote, real recording contract. I'm looking
forward to helping a lot of people getting there. That's one of the missions that I'm taking
upon myself for the, for the next foreseeable future, which would probably be a part of any
commercial venture that, that I take part in, which would get in close to figuring someone
that stuff out. Although before any of that can be figured out, I have to get my freaking
broadband, okay? And yesterday, not a peep out of easy net or British telecom, no one called
me. I figured it give him one day after the weekend after I was, you know, doing the rounds
on Friday and easy net, Lee from easy net. I'm not going to use last names, but I'll certainly
use first names. Lee promised me, oh yeah, we'll keep you up the speed. Let you know what's going
on, fucking bullshit. Bullshit, okay? So today, I called up at 9 o'clock Lee who has been my
contact. There's no longer answering his phone. I figured that's because I have my caller ID on
and he just doesn't want to be bothered and he's there for, it's not going to voice Miller anything
it's just ringing and ringing and ringing. So I called the guy who sold me this wonderful service,
his name is Philip. Philip wasn't in, but I did get through to somebody and I've decided that I'm
going to record every single phone call with British telecom and with easy net and replay them here
for you so you can hear just how excellent and how helpful the friendly fucking services. Let's see
what this part is. This is, all right, I was just put on hold for a second with this guy was trying
to find Philip, the sales guy that originally sold me the easy net package. I'm not getting any
luck on his phone. I'm sending him an email that you called and came to get back in touch with you.
Well, maybe you can help me. I'm just really looking for anyone with an easy net to help me at this
point. My line was installed on January. Listen to the guy, he's going like, okay, he knows that
this is the shit call, right? He's going like, oh fuck, what if the pick of the goddamn phone,
I get the gas holes? Hey, I saw the like match for a second, didn't I? You know what? That's it.
Yeah, I got a real threat for you in mind. Hold on, let's listen to the rest of this call.
May the fourth. Yeah. And apparently British telecom neglected to connect the curb to the new wiring
in the house. And I've literally been trying for two weeks to get anyone to complete this job and I'm
not getting a lot of love from using it. That's for sure. Yeah. And I need someone to escalate
this somewhere to get this going because it's now been two weeks that the line is literally
disconnected by 15 meters of wire. Yeah. Okay. Well, what's your company name there? I don't know.
Okay. So, you know, now it's like, he should have asked me what my company name was. The minute
before you even try to get the sales guy. But okay, I'll let him slide on this. So, of course,
I have a great company name, right? I look on Polder. Okay. Seven minutes.
Silicon Polder, you ask? Polder, POL, DER. Okay. Now listen to this.
Right. He's looking at the file now. He's going, oh fuck. This is the, this is the trouble case.
I want to bounce this one away from you as soon as possible.
I can give you the number of the provisioning department.
Oh, that's not going to do it for me today. I've been through all the provisioning departments.
They're all saying it's British telecoms fault. So, I think it'll come right back to sales.
The people who sold it to me. I've been around this loop multiple times. He's with me through
the provisioning now. Oh, no. Not going to work. Because I would assume that would be the best
assessment that does that. I want to respond to people for it. I don't know what they're saying
is they're not responsible. British telecom is responsible and they hope it'll happen soon.
But at this point, my business is severely suffering. Now, you see, I'm sliding in a little
something here, which is true, right? Because remember, I am an asshole American. We love to
litigate the fuck out of people. Oh, I'm really getting, I'm, you know, how about emotional distress?
My marriage is under actual strain here. BT, eating net fuckers. And it's past all promise dates.
And there were a lot of promises when I signed up. And, you know, what needs to happen is
eating that needs to talk to BT, which as far as I understand is a commercial company. And tell
them that they are out of line and need to get this done today. I mean, literally out of line,
15 meters of line. All these, I've had three guys here, but all the wrong guys who can't dig a
fucking trench. Oh, boy, I tried a little bit of humor, but I slipped. I didn't mean to say
fucking, but now it's getting a little frustrated, as you can understand. What I'm going to do
then, because when you become an agent at customer, you get an account manager and we're really
through to, I'm going to put you through to that gentleman. Who is that? But you haven't got
one to signed yet, but I'm going to try and put you through to my colleague, Mark, if he's free.
Okay. And, and each of you, I'm just going to say, Tony, she put this for you, and then help you
with your business in the future. That will be good. Okay, so be patient with me. I don't want to see
a fucking piece. Okay, thank you. Okay, so far, so far, this guy's saying all the right things,
right? I definitely want to have an account manager. It's interesting. I didn't have an account
manager up until today, and he's going to help me with my business, so he's saying all the right things
there. You know, this is stuff that's making me feel really good. However, this whole music
didn't make me feel so good.
We're sorry to keep you racing. Your call will be handled shortly.
Creative, huh?
So this again was nine 15 this morning. After I'd already called the league guy, who said he would
keep me posted of anything and would call me on Monday and didn't. So I'm figuring this guy's running
around and going like, god, terrible. I got this dickhead on the phone. Thank you for holding. Your call will be
dealt with as soon as possible. I don't like being dealt with, man. I don't like being dealt with,
I like being helped. I like being serviced. So you only wonder what the guy was doing. You know,
did he get this guy in the phone? Did he explain who I was? Did he explain that I'm a customer?
That I don't have a customer representative yet? No one is helping with me with my business.
Sorry to keep you racing. Your call will be handled shortly.
Hmm, now I'm going to be handled instead of dealt with. All right. My call was being handled.
I could have edited this out, but it was too much fun to put you guys to the same pain I went through this
morning. So I'm literally just waiting just waiting. Hello Adam. Yes. So it's keeping you an old
end. Um, I had a discussion with the, yeah, kind of element thing. And they said that it's still kind of
skills, skills issues. I've just spoken to Phil. And he's going to call you back in a minute if that's okay.
Okay, you promise me he's going to come back a minute. Yeah, what's your number though?
Oh, okay. So I should fast forward through that shit night.
And then he doesn't get my number right because he, this is all, I'm not a zero, whatever.
I'm on zero. Yeah. Yeah, I'm on one. Yeah.
The two main numbers in the mobile swipe. No, I don't know the zero in there somewhere.
Okay, that's fine. I'll get to call you back at him. Okay. Okay. Thank you.
Anyway, no problem, cheers. No problem, cheers.
Suck my knob. That was two hours ago. One minute is very long and easy net term. So we're still
waiting. And I have the phone right here actually hoping that someone will call back during this
podcast at which time, of course, I will, I will put the, the phone call through and take it, right?
And Patricia just walked in here earlier. And she said that fairer faucet of Charlie's Angel's
fame. And of course, she lived with the, then she, what was she married to? What's she married to?
Shoot. I don't know. She's a little bit wacky, but I kind of like her because she's, because she's a little bit wacky.
Now she's more than wacky. I'd have to say she's extremely wacky. She is suing.
I didn't get the full details, but she's suing a or, or multiple cosmetics companies because
she's so sick and tired of the lies they tell, of the fake commercials. And this is exactly what
Patricia says. Every single time she sees like the remote mascara commercial come on and just say,
it's God, the fucking fake fake eyelashes. They're pretending that this mascara gives you these
beautiful long eyelashes. And they're fake. They're fake put on eyelashes. They're not even real
eyelashes. And of course, you know, I said, well, but, you know, dear, look at Vogue. You know,
every single pictures photo shop. It's models don't have to lose weight or, or keep their weight
down or throw up or smoke cigarettes at all for their weight. I mean, they do it because they're
hooked on this shit, right? No, they, they just let it, you know, everything's photoshopped away.
It's like everything is like the fake radio voices that have turned us all on to podcasting and
getting into some real real stuff on on the radio or on your iPod or MP3 player, just audio sound,
you know. And so fair fuss that is pissed off about this and she wants to sue the entire
cosmetics industry or something like that. But I'm going to get Patricia on that. Maybe tomorrow
and we'll do a podcast. Well, I'll have her on as a special guest that talk about everything
fake in the cosmetics business, which she can know about because she has a cosmetics company.
So that's for tomorrow. Let's see, brief update on some of the stuff that happened yesterday on the
Daily Source Code. We had the trivia, which was sent to me by Stuart Hunter. And he, of course,
as promised, came back to me today, says Adam, that was fun. Fun playing it for you. Anyway,
here are the answers that I didn't get yesterday. I'm not going to play all the sound clips again
for you. But I really hope that people do this. I mean, let's keep it to a top three or top five.
But let's definitely try and stump me. And let's try and keep it 80s and 90s. You can do 60s,
70s and 80s. Okay. The 90s, I was over the hill and I don't know shit anymore. Maybe some,
but I missed a whole bunch. And I lived in, you know, in different countries. So, you know,
different hits. Very hard for me to track. But 60s, 70s and 80s. And I'm from 1964 and I bet
I bet you I could get a lot of 50s tunes, even. That's right. Here's the challenge. 50s, 60s, 70s and 80s.
Because I'm a disco jockey and I have all the Lawrence Welk albums. So, the first song that I
missed actually was Morrissey, every day is like Sunday. I'd never been into Morrissey. So,
that's probably why I didn't even catch it. Wet, wet, wet, love is all around. I had wet, wet, wet,
wet, wet, but at a wrong spot. Visage, fade, degree, I had right.
Live it up. I had the title right, but mental is anything. I didn't have the band, John Farne
the voice I had. Ice house. Shit, a little girl. I should have known that one. The
Connell 74, 74, 75, I think I got half of that title right. And then wonderful life. I got right,
but not black who did it. So, I'd basically pretty much sucked. But would like a rematch. So,
if anyone wants to send in a stump, the podcaster, stumped the prince of pod. Then feel free.
Because that's fun to do. I really do like it. Ken Gantt sent me an email. And all these, of course,
are linked from the show notes, which I'm contemplating today putting in the actual web post itself,
just to make it that much simpler, so that you can get right to it and don't have to go through
OPML or another, I'll still post it as OPML, obviously, because I'm hoping that applications are being
made everywhere. And people are trying to figure out ways to put show notes into their iPodder software.
But he was sent a listening diary by Arbitron. These are the guys that do the ratings for radio in
America. And he says, hopefully I'll go down in podcasting. History is the first person to
document a podcast that's shown my Arbitron radio diary. So, this is how the radio ratings are actually
maintained. Sure, they have some, some meters that people carry with them, but I think the majority
fill out a diary. And your station even gets points if they can name the DJ that's on the show
or on a show or on a station even. And so he had hoped to list the daily source code in the
diary, but couldn't get it around the fact that one of the pieces of data they require for each
entry is whether the show was on AM or FM. And you was afraid that listening that daily source
code might invalidate the diary. So, he did kind of an end around. He said, my favorite show is actually
and he did fill out podcast done by Leo LePort on KFI 640 AM in Los Angeles. Now, of course,
this is great because he lives in Louisville, Kentucky, Ken does. So, there's no way in hell,
he could have, he could have, have listened to this show in Los Angeles. So, let's see,
let's see if if that actually makes a difference. And maybe we should get podcasts on the
Arbitron diary. I mean, if it's a frickin' diary, right? It's, I don't know, it's just a thought.
Lots about the sound seeing tour. I'm going to second open up these outline here.
Lots of people sending in ideas about how to connect GPS data with sound files. And I think
fill up to Ron of in gadget has been working on some of this as well. I guess what we really need is
an iPod or an MP3 player that when you record something, records the GPS data of where the recording
was made. I don't think this is a device that does that. There will actually there are some devices,
but they're usually video. And of course, we need it both ways, right? It's one thing to actually
create a database. And for me to do a sound seeing tour. Oh, by the way, sound seeing.com was already
taken. I got sound seeing tour and sound seeing tours.com. Kind of the same, I guess. Not really
wanted one. But, and some other people registered pod sound seeing and some other things for
which was totally nice to them to do. And what was it? Oh, this was an email from Ryan
who says, hi from Snowy Road Island. Was rather intrigued to hear the Edward R. Moro clip posted
from another listener in the source code yesterday. I said, don't know if you know about CBS
history or the structure of radio at that time in the 1940s. It says that before Edward R. Moro came
to CBS, radio was very much scripted and edited down with little or no live broadcasts at all.
And really, Edward R. Moro was a pioneer in the sound seeing space. And actually wrote a book,
there was a book that came out called Edward R. Moro and the birth of broadcast journalism,
which is something that you might want to read if you're interested in, and really how
the first sound seeing tours got started and that blitz creek over in England. So that email
and others, including some great suggestions for something called geofencing, which Adam Bloom sent to
me. How twisted is that? Adam Bloom. It's like Ron Bloom and Adam Curry had an ugly love child.
Although Adam Bloom isn't ugly and he actually is related to Ron. But he sent me a whole bunch of
cool links which I've also posted in the show notes today that lead to geotracking because
what of course what we need is the reverse. When you're walking down the street and you hit a spot
or let's say you're within 10 meters proximity of a spot where I recorded something. That's when
you know, I want you to be able to access that file or even better it should probably already be
downloaded onto your device and we'll only play when you hit that spot. I mean that of course makes
the most sense. And I think some cell phone people are looking at ways of doing that
where you're cell phone actually then either sends you a message or alternatively I guess could
play some kind of file for you. So just a quote just thinking about it would be cool if we can get
some of that going. But just who got caught? Well I'm going to have myself a real good sound because
I feel alive man. I feel alive. Like I can take the world. I'm just turning inside out baby and floated
around in ecstasy. So don't stop me now. Don't stop me because I'm having a good sound.
Hello Adam. It's Paul here from podcastpool.com. I'd like to thank you for helping me not to sleep.
I came across an article of yours about a month ago on podcasting and for about a month
I've tried to work out of the heck to make a podcast and now I can't stop making them.
My book shows just called Totally Eighties. It's all about the 1980s. Actually I didn't want to do
just about the 1980s. It had such brilliant response. There's been 6,000 hits in the last week.
So thanks very much mate and love the daily source code listen to it every day.
Apart from when you're not doing it. I hope you brought band connections okay. And the
track that you heard was from my friend Dan at dinemosrhythmases.com. They're not yet signed and
that's why podcast is so good to promote super bands like that. All the best mate and as I say
check this out. Totally eighties it's podcastpool.com. It shows you're only about 10 minutes or so.
So you can check it when you go to work or the band cool whatever you do. All the best. Bye
by now. Okay okay so podcastpool.com and actually went to the site of the artist that he mentioned
because I heard a really cool like lounge version of of Queens don't stop me now. And the band
has all these great cover songs that I really really would like to check out and play for in the
source code. Unfortunately no MP3 downloads which you know if you've got an independent band
make sure you can sell your CDs online. But please make some MP3 available. MP3 is available
for podcasts because we really want to help out and you know it's a podcast and good way to get
your stuff heard you know it's a good way to get stuff out there. And there was oh shoot I don't know
if I still have that article here I was keeping it for the longest time and I probably tossed it out.
Elvis Presley is the top of the charts again here in the UK and I was trying to dissect why. Usually
it's because some great you know back in the 80s you know you'd have like some fabulous
Levi's 501 jeans commercial and they'd add like wonderful world or don't remember it don't know
much about history. Oh I should see if I have that song for you actually. And these songs of course
immediately became hits because you know they were they were exposed to a whole new audience
basically the blue jeans buying audience and these songs stand by themselves right the great great
songs. But I didn't think there was any Elvis commercial that I'd seen out and Elvis has a
top of the charts now and then I figured it out. There's all kinds of let me just see what was I
trying to get. Don't know much about history. Wonderful world. Wonderful world this would be
wonderful world yeah I think I have at home let's just listen to that for one second and I've got to
route my iTunes through okay yeah I think this is it. Come on oh yeah now that's not one
I that's that's not what I was thinking now. Guess I don't have it. I thought I had that one.
Oh no I'm not stupid. Who was that? Was it wasn't Louis Armstrong was it?
Shoot okay don't have it sorry to disappoint you there. Anyway and in the paper the other day I
figured it out why you know all these Elvis tunes being re-released of course you know it was
his birthday recently etc. But in the United Kingdom as with the same as with I guess most countries
in the EU copyrights expire after 50 years. Now you'll remember a few years ago Sonny Bono before
he died. Potition to extend that amount of time in the United States to 95 years and actually
Sir Cliff Richard is here with the shadows is is petitioning around now saying you know oh my god
you know all these songs that were big hits for me that I still make money from are about to the
copyrights are about to expire and I'm still alive and you know and I'm going to stop making money on them
and of course you feel bad for Sir Cliff kind of right but on the other hand you know hey this is
what it's about you know now anyone can or should be able to record this song royalty free
or should be able to record it on disc royalty free I did say of course if it's performed
there's still all kinds of rights very confusing the way that works but there is a substantial amount
of income that's about to be lost from from Elvis Presley so first of all podcasts are out there
then now's a great time to you know record some Elvis tunes and get them released over here in the
UK if you record an Elvis tune you know I will gladly help you out and if it's good all
certainly play it on the daily source code but it's not interesting that that can happen here
the copyrights expire after 50 years and that it's 95 years in the States so all kinds of weird stuff
going on with the with music business and of course yesterday I promised you that since I
didn't have time today I would play that song as was promoted by what was it's webcrumbs breadcrumbs
web droppings it's here anyway here's the song it's Robert Burke Warren this is from the CD
Lazy I it's all right pod save music it's called junk man listen to it right here on the daily
source code for January the 18 Tuesday 2005 got no bandwidth see them pretty low
I'm going down I'm going down I'm going down I'm going down I'm going down I'm going down
I'm going down I'm going down I'm going down I'm going down I'm going down
I want the sound, I want the sound, I want the sound I want the sound, can be
I'm going down, I'm going down, I'm going down
I'm going down, I'm going down
I'm going down
Thank you
Oh
I absence me of важ me milking snug
I'll be bowls of shit moments and coffee crown
When post-ieked instarments to control the heat
Ey
Shoes on a trash and the treasure that is found
Go in town, I'm going down
To the jungle, more in cabbage town
Go in town, go in town
To the jungle, the jungle, the jungle
I owe you
Laying in a clean white man
I gotta help you remember
Yeah, when we ran like wild dogs
Around your head
I gotta help you recall
Got a couple old little little monkey red dog
We back to the living lady
Baby, baby, baby, baby
A couple old little monkey red dog
We back to the living lady
Jump in, jump in, jump in
Robert Bergwarren, he's junk man
Everybody
Your daily source code for Tuesday, January 18th
2000 and five
Something I didn't mention over the weekend
We took Jesse our big dog
Which is a cross between a German shepherd and a golden retriever
We took her to the vet and have a great vet nearby here
Because she hadn't been eating very well or at all for the past week
My dog is dying
She's 12 and a half years old, she's almost 13
She's always been extremely healthy
We got out of the pound when she was
As with all of our animals, we all get them out of the shelter
She was about one or one and a half
Perfect dog
It's just been the best dog you can imagine ever
And her liver is basically failing her
There's nothing you can do really
Except we put it on a different type of diet
She's eating great now
The doctor gave her a couple of antibiotics
It could be a minor infection in her liver
But basically the doctor said very clearly
You know, your dog is at the end of its life
And if she doesn't start eating then it's going to be
It's going to end pretty soon
So we're really happy that she's eating and she's full of life
As long as she's full of life and eating then I'm considering her
Good to go
But yeah, you know, it happens all dogs
And so then we'll have God
We've had so many animals go in the past couple of years
We had Dickie or Dick Ed actually
My cat who I had from my bachelor days in Amsterdam
He was 23 we had Gina, Pinkie
We had to put her down about four years ago
She had a few line aides
Then we had Chrissy, our multi-stog
You've heard her on the podcast, right?
She had to put her down, she was blind and deaf pretty much
She had no quality of life left
She was way old, she was almost
She was also 13, 14 years old
And then we basically will have two cats
And we have shrubber, our little yorky
He's still going strong, he's a crazy mut
Anyway, so that's just a bit of personal biz
Something else a lot of people have been sending the emails about
Which I was aware of since I was talking about easy jet
And I've booked another easy jet flight by the way
Thursday going to Amsterdam couple meetings
Going to finalize the television show that I've been talking about
We basically sold it, now we have to get down to the details
What did I sell, how many episodes did I sell
And you know, what is the budget going to be, etc
So that's kind of fun
And then I have another meeting at Graham Masterview
Which I'm taking on Friday
And what everyone, what every, oops, hold on, there's that drunken thing again
There we go
What everyone's been emailing me about is the introduction of the new airbus
I'm sure by now you've heard about it, it happened yesterday
The new airbus A380
What mother load this is, huh?
It's a double decker
Can carry up to 800 passengers
Which is twice to 747
If configured in all economy, class mode
Virgin airs ordered six of them I think
And in all they have already have like 120 orders or something
But these things looks just awesome, you're so big
And I'm wondering, you know, I have a call into Wing Commander William
I'm going to try and hook up with them Thursday
And get some fixed wind flying and he has a assess number 182
That he's been patching up and I can't wait to try and fly it with him
And I'll ask him, what kind of runway these fuckers need
It's like damn
This thing is so big, it must be so heavy
I mean it can't land everywhere, I have no idea
And as I sit here looking at my screen
I see that there's new software available for my computer
It's the new version of iTunes
Let's not install that on this slow link, shall we?
It's only 8.66 megabytes now
So anyway, I'll get some details on the airbus 380 man
These things are interesting
And I've already heard that some configurations may include a jacuzzi
I thought the sleeper seats were cool
Hey Adam, I'm PW Fenton
Create a radio-free radios digital flatsum
I don't know, maybe you've heard it, I hope you have
But I'm looking for a favor from you
My podcast
Oh, I don't know, I'd call it like the podcast version of the Ed Sullivan show
Well, no longer second
There could only be one Ed Sullivan of podcast thing
In that I try to be just a little bit of everything
There's no guiding light
You might hear some sort of a jazz performance
Followed by a comedy routine
Followed by some kind of a rant
Followed by whatever
The idea is that it's kind of a stream of consciousness
Kind of show, even though it's put together
Fairly slickly
What I'm hoping that I can get from you Adam is just a plug
On your show, everybody listens to your show, I listen to your show, I listen to your show
Every day
I only have time to create my show once a week
But I listen to your show every single day
I figure out some way to work it in
What I'm looking for is just some kind of a little plug that you could give me
And more than that, just a suggestion for people who are listening
And I know people are listening because people download the thing
To give me some kind of feedback
They can find me at PWFenton
At digitalflotsom.org
And, you know, just to send me an email
Let me know what it is you think about what I'm doing
Right on, so it's digitalflotsom.org
And I just couldn't resist playing that promo because he was so polite and so nice
PWFenton, and he has a very intriguing voice
And you know what, when I get some fucking bandwidth today
By the way, 1134, still no word from my account manager
It's easynet.co.uk
But he has an interesting voice, so I'll definitely check out the podcast
Hey, if someone's doing an Ed Sullivan podcast, I definitely want to know about it
Hey, Adam, this is Eric over at developmentc.org
I know you don't like Skype right now, and for good reason
But I want to let you know that it might be getting better
I just got an email from Skype, inviting me to a three free month trial of voice messaging
I guess it's their version of voice mail
So, anyway, that calls for him another call now
No ringing in the air, goes right to voice mail
When I don't want to talk to you, reject, I didn't hang up, they go to voice mail
And if I'm not around, they also go to voice mail
I just tried it out, you can leave a 60 second message
And it's cool, I can tell someone I can check these messages from many computer
So, I don't know how we got one of these cool beta voice mail accounts, but I definitely love to have one
And I really, I don't, it's not like a hate Skype right now
It's just that I've seen that they're missing such a tremendous opportunity
Here's a product that almost every single podcast or uses in one form of the other
It wouldn't take much to make it just a little bit better and make it perfect for it
Hey, I'd even pay extra for some services that's, you know, to get Skype to do certain things
Like recording, Skype could be perfect for recording an entire podcast
You don't necessarily have to be talking to someone, you know
If, if it has the capability to record MP3, then for God's sake, let's try and get that working
So thank you very much, Eric, and I'm wondering if these voice mail accounts are this like a Gmail account, you know
Send me one of those, I can get some Skype voice mail
And here we go, we have some actual paper, yesterday as I was waiting in vain
For someone to show up at the door, like, you know, British telecom
There was a ring, and it wasn't BT, there was a van outside, so first I thought, oh, goody, you know, he's here
The man to dig the trenches here
It wasn't, it was federal express
And they delivered a small package and in the package, a letter
From Chris Anderson, editor in chief of wired magazine dated January 13, 2005, dear Adam
I'm delighted to let you know that you've been nominated in the tech innovator category for wired magazines
2005 wired rave awards
I forgot the pumpkin, the tympany pumpkin
The wired rave awards is an annual magazine featuring
Feature celebrating the people changing your mind
The rave awards are selected by wired editors, honor innovators and 14 categories
Ranging from business to design to entertainment to science
Please keep your nomination under wraps as we will formally announce the nominees January 18, 2005
And this year's winners will be unveiled at the six annual rave awards celebration
At the legendary film Warren San Francisco February 22, 2005
And published in wired smarts 2005 issue
Excellent, hey, goddamn
Let's see, it's still, let me see, is it still pretty early in
On the west coast in the states, let's see if wired has released it yet
See who the other nominees are
I wonder how that works if it's
I just don't know
So in the tech, what is it tech innovator category, first of all, I'm honored
And I presume it's for podcasting
Let's see if I can find out who, because you know, I'd love to go to this show on February 22
But as usual, you know, you kind of only want to go when you know you want to win
Right?
But seeing as, I guess who chooses this, is this the wired editors choose this?
So it's not like a public prize then, no, I don't see anything I'm looking at wired.com
I don't see any, I see cell phone, shushing, push button, wine tasting
Oh, wired, it's got some good stuff, doesn't it?
Okay, so, no, not out yet, but it will, so you have, there you go
There's a premiere, everybody, a premiere news event on the source code
All right, cool, so maybe I will go out for that, we'll have to see one thing for sure
One thing for sure
It's good, everyone!
If you're not, all making me laugh
If you're not
Morning, doing a night
That's it for today's source code, thank y'all for the subscribers
And that is what we have to say, right?
Don't say stay tuned, but keep subscribed
Your comments, questions, trivia, and of course, if you have a leading to British telecom
Or if you have a shovel, I know how to hook up the wires from the curb to the house
It's atamacurry.com, we'll leave a comment on my weblog
www.curry.com, and of course, catch all the source code at dailysourcecode.com
All right, today is a big day, because I'm going to get my haircut
Take me down to Tony and Guy, or Chuchin Shisha
Whatever, it's going to stand there and make sure they do everything just right
Don't mess it up
So who knows how happy I'll be tomorrow, right?
And have yourself a great day, great evening, right after noon, whenever you may be checking out the source code
Talk to you tomorrow, everybody, for the hum day edition of your daily source code
Bye bye
Peace out