Well, good morning everybody. Welcome to the daily source code. Right now it is 5 minutes past 8.
It is Wednesday, today is March 2nd, 2005. Got to remind myself, my sister's birthday is coming
up in three days. I always have that I have like every month. When I say the month, I got
these little bookmarks in there. So, March is, is Willow's birthday. So, it's five past
day and as usual, I'm waiting for my daughter. We are supposed to leave at 10 past 8 for
me to take her to school and she's not done yet with whatever she's doing, probably doing
her hair. And as we discussed yesterday on the show, I was going to ask her for was okay
if we had a podcast together this morning and she agreed. That of course was yesterday,
last night when she agreed. So, she may have a different view of that right now. And
I'm going to do it. Every parent probably doesn't the morning, trying to prod the children
all along. Christina, it's 5 past 8, huh? Sound familiar?
Oh, I see. So, just for the technical part of the show, I'm recording this on the
I River, the ISP 799, direct to the line in. I'm using my wireless microphone set. And
what's nice about the I River is when you are recording directly from the line input,
which of course the receiving part of my wireless mic is hooked up to. You can stick
the headphones in and you'll actually, it passes the sound through exactly the way it's
being recorded. So, you've got a real good idea of what's getting captured on, it's not
you're on the disk in the flash memory in this case. And that I have the one gigabyte version.
So, we could continue for, oh, 17 hours. And I'm recording at 128 kilobits per second,
KVPS and 44 kilohurred sample rate. So, that's a pretty high quality recording, which
actually I'll have to down sample a little bit before I put it up because usually I make the
source code 64 KVPS. So, it's not as cold as yesterday, it's probably just going to guess
it's probably about 3 or 4 degrees centigrade. And it's now 7 past 8. Also, I've got her breakfast
ready. I did another thing that you probably probably recognize if you got kids. I burnt
the bagel a little bit, so I just kind of scraped off the burnt part. Here she comes, don't tell her.
Hey baby, we're going to do our show today, right? Yeah. The podcast of camera recording now,
just so you know. Okay, it's a bit of your high-local down. Yeah, it's different. It's perfect.
Yeah, it's poofy. Come on, get you. Oh, I'm sorry. Well, I'm poofy.
Dude, dude, you have like 3 minutes before we should be going.
Let me see. Let me see. Let me see. All right. What can I do?
I'm going to start the movie. Now I'm playing with the Christina. Why not?
What? Just no one who knows she'd only had it. She was listening to it. She was giving it back.
Who? Ellie. You gave your iPod to somebody else?
Sure. She was listening to it and she chapped it. She chapped it. What does that mean?
She barks. It's it on an eat. Sit on an eat.
It's not. She doesn't really have that. She doesn't really have that. She doesn't really have that.
Well, let me tell you something. That's a bad idea because she could lose it. She could drop it.
She could break it and then watch. She's going to replace it. I doubt it.
It's not going to lose it. Drop it. I don't think that's a good idea. You shouldn't do that.
Then why did you do it?
You forgot. You forgot. I'm going to get it back. I'm going to get it back. She also has my
name as you want. She gave it back. Okay. Today, right?
Okay. Here's what I'll tell you what's going to happen. You're going to say,
oh, can I have my iPod back? Oh, I forgot. I left it at home. How much you want a bet?
How much you want a bet? That's the way it always goes.
Nothing. Just for the honor. Eat. Come on, Hunts. 10 past eight. We should be in the car now.
What can I do to make this process go faster? Okay. It's not good for you to eat fast like that.
Wow. I hope that this is the same with you and your kids. Or if you don't have them,
I hope it turns out like this for you when you do have them. Make me feel much better.
No, I was telling the listeners. I said, I hope you recognize this. I hope your kids are like this.
And if not, I hope when you have kids, I hope you they're like this.
So can enjoy this pain. Hey, ginger. Come on, girl. Boy, thing, cat wants to drink from the
boss. Our cat's drink from the faucet. It's up with that.
I can't wait until he's drinking normally. What? He tried to jump in the shower. The cat. Really?
Why didn't you let it go? Why didn't you let it go? Why didn't you let it go?
Because I need to freak out what's in there. Oh, they're funny.
Okay, good.
Well.
I'm going to put my coat on, okay? Yeah.
Right. I'm going to have to move the microphone a bit.
In fact, I definitely have to move the microphone.
See, contemplating putting the mic. Hold on a second. Bear with me. That's rustle.
I'm sorry about that. It's definitely extremely unpositioned.
Well, I'm not going to find a good place to clip this sucker on. Okay. Now, I'm not quite sure if I
want to, well, I have to see how the acoustics are in the car. I can pick both of us up equally as
well on mic as it is on my right lapel now on which probably will work or it'll probably be just
this crappy listening to me. This isn't a Christina. So I'm sitting on a left-hand side of the car
at least for the next two years. Next four years, three and a half years.
Yeah, and she'll be sitting on the right-hand. So that's kind of like those.
What's that? Right, because we have a European car with the steering wheel on the left-hand side
and it was like, wow, she's awfully young to be driving. We should get you like a little steering wheel.
Well, you please hurry up, my dear. You're so late today.
Dang Navit. Child. Dang Navit. Okay, let me get my stuff set up here. Put the recorder on the
lock so I can't accidentally stop the recording. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Uh, putting the, yeah, I put in these, uh, the ones, they're, yeah, they're in there. Not
salt and vinegar. You got the good ones. Yeah, well, you have these now. Salt and vinegar is not good
for you because it contains salt and vinegar. Of course not. If you don't take time, okay?
Not good. It's the most important meal of the day. Okay. Okay.
Did, and please take your vitamin C pill?
Oh wow. The hell is that? That's not good.
Why does it make, shouldn't make such a difference when I, uh, check one two.
Oh, that was all about one. Oh, so didn't get louder.
Okay. This is not very interesting. I was planning on being in the car talking with you.
Take your vitamin C pill, please. Okay. Come on, babe.
Okay. Well, so, what is this? Is this what you wipe your face with?
My face with that wash my hands and I do this. Okay.
Didn't get to play the theme tune. I had everything all cut up. I had the eye trip ready to play your songs.
I'm sorry. I screwed it up.
Yeah. Somewhat.
I see it's the cable going into the eye river that's a little cruddy shoot.
That stays okay then.
So, yesterday we had, uh, you continue all just tell everyone what's going on. We had a minor crisis
because Christina's uniform needed to wash it.
Oh, I just wanted to check it out. I left it for five minutes in your room and it still smells like
moldy ass and cigars. What do you mean moldy ass?
Like moldy ass. I washed it in the sink, but it smells. Well, maybe I smoke the cigar, but I don't have
a moldy ass. Let me smell. Let me smell. It's this morning.
I sprayed perfume on it. Well, the moldy ass part might be from someone who was wearing it.
There on the ground, on the ground behind the chair, behind the chair, right where you hung it up.
Give Jim anything. Okay.
I have religious education today.
Ari, yeah, I learned about that at the teacher conference last night.
Oh, yeah, I forgot because I'm the cab driver. You're right.
On the cook, the cab driver. I saw him like mom.
Oh, well, I got to get you done. Do you want to? Do you phone charged?
I guess I'll tell you something. Okay, coat, you don't want to wear a coat?
No, I don't wear a coat. Oh, it's fine.
So, let's go. Okay, it is now eight.
Eighteen.
Let's put the scarf on. Put the scarf on before you go. It's worth the extra 10 seconds.
You're going to tuck your shirt in here. You don't do that either.
Oh, no. No. Christina.
There you go. Ladies and gentlemen, the influences match Weinstein on the youth of America.
It's all mages, false. Ready?
You got your lunch isn't there? Yeah, just open your bag. I think I did.
That's what you should have a song. You know, I can self-reflect blame Canada. You need blame now.
Blame mag.
What close your bag, I kind of still, it's open.
Okay.
It's like a sound seeing tour now, all of a sudden.
Watch out.
So we are here, only everything through the headphones.
Kind of funky.
Let's turn that down for a second.
Yeah, it's cold. What's the temperature? Hold on.
Let me just set up the sound system. Make sure that works.
Blame.
Two degrees.
There you go.
So now we officially begin.
Let me just stop that. We should have done the tune hours ago.
Okay, backing out of the driveway.
There we go.
So if you didn't read it on the weblog,
even though it's impossible to get Christina out of the door this morning,
I am very proud of her because yesterday last night
I went to the very first parent teacher conference at school
and I actually, I had, what's the, who's the chemistry teacher, Christina?
No, he's a nice guy.
Well, I don't know if he's nice guy.
He's scary. He's thought he was scary.
Well, hold on a second.
But so you set me up for that, right?
No, like, oh man.
So I actually regretted setting it up because I thought he was going to be really mean.
No, he's like, well,
Christina has the highest marks of the class.
She's at the best grades.
I'm like, huh?
I'm like, huh? I'm so, I see, curry.
See, you are wide.
Yeah, yeah, and she's really good.
And you need to get your revision guide or whatever that is.
You have to buy that.
What is that?
Oh, it's just a sort of thing that everyone has to buy.
And let's see if no one bothers us with that one to discuss.
What is it, but what is it?
I don't, I think it's something to study out.
Just a little bit.
Okay.
So, now we're traveling down good old Epsom Road, which is the later we leave the
busier at Gets.
And I think we're so late that we've missed a water boy and big bun.
Water boy big butt and how about bicycle chick, haven't seen her, dude.
All our friends.
We should pick up a water boy or just say, hey, you want to ride?
Oh, that's okay.
Okay.
So, but anyway, all of your teachers, at least the ones that I had appointments
with, were like, Christina's settling in, beautifully.
She seems to be making lots of friends, which I think was really nice, because that was the first thing they all said.
It wasn't like, wasn't about grades, it was about, they were very aware that, you know, you would move in.
Oh, shoot, what's the, oh, that's the, they were very aware that, you know, you came in halfway through the year.
And that's what they were all concerned with, not really made me feel good about, good about the school.
Uh, although, oh, shoot, I'm sorry, lady.
I didn't even see you do that.
See if I can back up a bit and let her in.
Come on, baby.
Go, go honey.
You!
Oh, go ahead, fucking Mark.
Oh man, it's so fucked up.
Back up a bit.
Yeah, and they're all angry at you because they think you're driving Christina.
Okay, well, if you're not going to go, but I'm going to go.
People are actually quite nice in, uh, in the UK in, uh, in traffic.
They're really courteous. Is that water? No, that's.
They're really courteous.
They wave you on all the time, and, you know, and especially me, because they, you can't tell by the,
I just, they can't tell by the license plates that were, obviously,
foreigners, um, and so I've done some really stupid shit because, of course, I'm driving
on the left-hand side, and sometimes I get confused.
Not that much anymore, um, and then the, uh, they're no kind of wave like,
oh, hi, you're bleeding idiot, but that's okay.
Yeah, you had people sitting in the car and laughing at you.
I had that too, right?
Right, that too, yeah.
Um, audio.
So anyway, Christina, I could not be prouder, really, and you had good grades.
Except, um, who's the inmissive Alan?
Oh, well, what, what, what, what does she teach, uh, biology?
Yeah, you said, well, little bit chatty with Beth.
Not actually, I had to drag it out of her.
A bit chatty with one of the other students, I said, uh, let me guess, uh, Beth.
He said, yes, who was there? Beth was there.
I can't believe that you didn't come with me.
Did you talk to Beth?
Uh, she can love to me, she said, hi, Adam.
Which is nice because, you, at least she didn't say, Mr. Curry,
Oh.
That makes me feel old.
She's tall too. She's about as she taught of the new, Beth.
Yeah, she's pretty big.
She's so cool. She feels old, because she fancy you.
That's, that's, that's a very cute.
uh okay see well you don't have any uh any tunes
Christine and that's too bad
so when you get some legal stuff or like we played my music
I found a really cool podcast
yeah I want to hear it
listen to this you're like
Hi there folks and welcome to the inaugural podcast of what is
tentatively being called don't be afraid of opera
it's called that because as I hope you'll learn over the next little bit
you already know a lot of opera
I'm going to attempt to mix a little bit of opera you know
with some pieces that you don't
um the piece that I just inferred with a little bit there
that you'll hear more of a little bit later
is from the barbers of ill by recini
it's a fun little opera and the piece there is called Lago Elfactotum
it's used in all sorts of different things
from commercials on to movies
or you just may have heard it on the radio
it's a very famous piece because it's a lot of fun
it's figures and reductions the world
talking about how he is in fact
you know the man about town he's everything
he's talking hard in the morning
no I think he's uh I think on the compression
it's mp3 started skipping
but this the podcast is called don't be afraid of opera
I like that
the barbers of it
some opera guys probably have eaten some children
that's uh poplarotti's eaten several kids
oh
so if you want to learn about opera
don't be afraid of it
don't be afraid of opera podcast
see I was I was thinking you were going to have all these cool bands
can't go ahead baby
it's people from the train station
okay honey
oh I did
I have a great love filled
I know I wanted to listen to all the tunes
that you had but you know
someone whose name I've never heard before
you've seen Ellie the little short kid at Beth's house
okay
oh she's nice
but will she take care of it?
of course
then she have her own iPod
oh clearly she does
she does
we will listen to my iPod
during math
you're allowed to listen to iPod during classes
really?
yeah they like you
you're kidding me
oh really
wow
so
do you ever listen to the radio Christina?
I listen to the eagle
okay what's the eagle
explain the eagle
the eagle is this little station
high street
and you can walk in their way
but people want to record
the little glass
tiny glass box
and you can even get
requests if you hold up a sign
in front of the window
and if you say they're logging up
and they're really nice actually
okay
but the station
they play the music you like
um
they play green day
okay
oh I was listening to Michael Butler
rock and roll geek
and he had his daughter
Martina on his show
uh
she definitely doesn't like
she doesn't like
good Charlotte
and those guys
yeah
I think it'd be upset
here that
we need to convert her
I think that's a pretty hard
chord dude
when your dad's in a band
Paul American Heartbreak
and he's touring around Europe
and you should see Michael Butler
he is totally
he looks like a rock and roll
mutt of fucker
so when he's famous
he's famous
even famous
you have a perpetual backstage
pass
I'm sure that's not a problem
yeah no he gave you the CD
with um
yeah I didn't even know he was in that band
I remember you were talking about
and what band
yeah yeah I remember that
yeah I like American Heartbreak
pretty good
do you want to hear us on?
yes please
check it see how they are
oh my I think I have it on my iPod here
uh
I would hope
let me see
I have to go to browse
oh this is stupid
the iPod is like anything
but handy
if you're looking for something
oops
don't want to crash
I'm sure I have it here
American Heartbreak yes
yes
let's see
I'll play my favorite
last of the superheroes
that's my favorite
okay
this is American Heartbreak
every body
well that was
oh
here we go
it's really commercial
I like this
we've seen the amount
to be our life
to the friends
of the world
and to the lives of the life
I can be a candy
or a nasty
or a record
or a bonus piece
there's those
in the hood
and dogs
and cops have an old face
think I like
oh
boom, boom, boom
you like that kind of stuff
don't you?
that's kind of
that's kind of called
that hard core
well
I said he's hard core
they've got other shit
to hold on
second
try some mouths
and that's just a really
one of the
you know me I'm a commercial guy
I like that stuff
sick and tired
very easy
feel
pretty good
I'm in my chemical romance
except
I'm probably back before
I'm going to remember on that
show the guy to my swing
his face
oh
it was so funny
what we watching
that was a top of the pops
no top of the pops
it was top of the pops
and the base player
yeah
it was freaking out
and he tried to do like
the base
the base flew off the
strap and he looked like
a big dark
that was pretty funny
every bat has a
now
so
green day on the tonight show
I mean
try to cool he was
drumming and he finished
he threw his drumsticks back
he tried to step off stage
I think he might have heard
himself because he fell
like
yeah
dude I look like
shit
but I need it
dude
I'm okay
oh man
hey you want to go
riding today
since yesterday was a bust
are you going to
yeah
you sure
okay
well then you have to
text the
the stables that
okay
so they don't
feed
freed
so
well two things
that
princess back in her
inner stable
and they don't feed her
so we're now
the
the busiest part of town
which is kind of this
inner section
junction
roundabout thing
which leads up
to
the street
the school is on
for almost there
well I hope you'll come back
on the show again
Christina and bring your iPod
sorry
no that's okay
so
we really
we're really late
well actually
traffic is not bad
we're not late
tutorial is in the
start
what doesn't start
tutorial
what's tutorial
I think that
do the register
and annoy you as
notices
why they call it tutorial
interesting
is that a general assembly thing
y'all have to
we have an assembly
we might have one this morning
I hate this
but it's so boring
what do you do with a
assembly
sin
kumbaya
oh he listened to the boys
while last time
but that's cool
Christina goes to
like a
music specialist school
which means there's a lot of
bands who play green day all day long
but no they don't
let them play back
or so they've seen the line
came
no
the line
they didn't have a little
dance
to the left
no way
that's so lame
everyone must really
happy doing that
we're all
see that
haha
yeah
most of the
we have Mr. Lewis
yelling
what's the
I don't know
he's really cranky
okay
well you have uniform
check
uniform check
you're
sure but I've a really high
start that's like
past my ribs
I've to tuck it in there
let's really
okay we're
we are at
lecol
everybody
now
be careful getting
out baby
okay hey by the way
I promise
love you
careful careful careful
look out
be careful
okay yeah
love you
love you too baby
have a good day
bye baby
there she goes
and
it's got
my legs
and her mom's looks
that's the combination you want
believe me
of course now you know when I
when I honk in the
other kids around you won't even
acknowledge that I'm
even closely related to her
oh guys go ahead you cross the road
okay
well
so that was
uh...
turn out
go ahead
turn out a little
different than I expected
but that's okay
because
yeah
it's
it's the surprise
now
here comes the worst part of the
of the commute today
or the commute
the drive
is
turning around
so
I want to
be going the other way on this road
so I have to pull in
it's
somehow
funky man when you're writing
a dirty on the left hand side
through like
you turn
just feels really weird
and
so it's particularly busy today
we just get a
time check
it's like
uh...
it's 30 minutes
okay good
good
we're still going to
come in at 40
let me uh
position the mic
so I have a little more
this truck driver let me
not be very cool if he did
sorry about that
okay
uh
looks like he's going to let me in
you know
dude
totally appreciate it bro
okay
oh yeah I wanted to say
something
I've been following
Dave Weiner
and his
his discussions about
the Google toolbar
and I just want to say
even though I've never used the toolbar
nor can I use the toolbar
because I'm a Macintosh user
I can totally see how
Christina would install something like that
in fact
the computer that I bought
or the windows computer
came pre-installed
with some form of toolbar
which may have been a Yahoo
toolbar
maybe even
what is that thing
the packet bell or an HP
I don't know what brand
it is
there is some form of toolbar
already installed
and I can totally see
where she would install something like that
for some benefit
and
and not know
what else would be in the toolbar
so the idea of
of opting in
is
the toolbar
will be pretty prevalent
there's going to be two bars for all kinds of things
and we two bars
with the already art tool bars
but two bars
you know functionality within two bars for tracking
for
tracking is a big one actually
tracking
what some might call your attention
and
so
up in the air is whether you care about it or not
as a consumer
or as a
producer of content
personally
I don't want people
or companies
necessarily
downstream
changing
something that I've done
and granted right now
it's
pretty benign
and
it's showing
ISBN numbers for books
but
Dave's point
that companies
you know
where do they draw the line
we may have our disagreements
Dave and I
but
I'm a commercial mother
fucker
and let me tell you
if I were Google
I'd certainly be doing that
or I'd be contemplating it
and I've been thinking about it
and I certainly would find ways to make money
off of this wonderful toolbar
and I am
therefore very sure
that Google is going to do the same
so
I'm with you
on that one
okay
you know what we'll do
I actually
prepared for this
there's
two things I
had loaded up
hold on
I got to go back to my playlists
just so convenient
I'll set up
playlists here
for today's show
I mentioned it right today
it's March 2
okay
first of all
let me play this
now we'll go out with that
what I'll do now
is
something that you could have expected
one
casting
with
three
two
one
it's time for the head
with your
right
there you test
this one is a bit different
answer number three
it's going to be played
all the way
so the whole song
the whole track
if you want to stop it
you may
but
I think you're like it
and you will
let it play
okay here we go
this is number one
one
okay
I'm over one
I've no idea what that was
also sounds a little weird
through the speakers
and this is number two
okay
I know that one
that is
Spendal Ballet
and true
which is a great song
classic Evergreen
and the final one
this is number three
oh
I know what it is
oh John
you listen
oh dude
I'm so happy
thank you
of course
it's Dan Hartman
oh that's so cool
John and really appreciate
okay
these are the answers
this is number one
I didn't get the first one
the leap up the goal
refers
I would never
yes
just play
yeah
you got me on that one buddy
and so number one
we've got the goal
refers
and we did out
and this is answer
number two
Spendal Ballet
this is true
man those guys were
closed up when I met them
on my show back in Holland
nice guys
but
all these men
so true
but now
it seems
always in time
but never
life
yeah
I know this
my cheese
I'm a sucker
for like a star
I'm a ballet and through
his answer
number two
in today's hit test
and before we get to number three
we'll show you that feedback is welcome
hit test at gmail.com
and if you can find all information about the hit test
and the hit test podcast
at www.jumpleets.nl
www.jn
p-o-l-e-t.nl
well I don't see you next time
for number 19
this is then argument
and so number three
I can dream about you
You know you guys are bound
What's the free moving sound of voice
After to your number
I'm the main of front
And in my heart is it's you
You know you guys are bound
What's the free moving sound of voice
After to your number
You know you guys are bound
What's the free move sound of voice
After to your number
You know you guys are bound
What's the free move sound of voice
After to your number
After your number
You know you guys are bound
What's the free move sound of voice
After to your number
You know you guys are bound
Thank you very much
that was a great way to start off the day. Dan Hartman, I can dream about you on the daily
source code for March 2nd 2005. Well this was interesting, definitely a different type of show,
but had fun, hope the audio quality wasn't too crappy on the Dan Hartman and hope you enjoyed
us hanging out. Hey man, who needs a mixer when you've got a stereo system in the car?
Oh my gosh. All right, as usual, comments to Adamacore.com. All the latest shows, archives,
and the podcast feed at dailysourcecode.com. And of course you can always leave a comment or
check out my weblog www.curry.com. Well that's it for the Mr. Mom episode. Patricia is arriving back
expect to around 3 o'clock because the afternoon should be back at the cottage and I'll be very happy to see
okay take care everybody have yourself a wonderful
two days and one day with a hell day to Wednesday take care everybody I'll talk to you tomorrow bye bye
bye