Delta Shara Charlie 213. Hello everybody. Welcome to the daily source code coming to you from San Francisco, California.
The time now is 17. Actually, I watched a little fast. It was about 15 a.m.
And I am at the, I can actually, I can tell you where I'm at. I'm at the Pan Pacific Hotel, which is right near Union Square in San Francisco.
And I can tell you that now because by the time you hear this, it's Sunday night and it'll be Monday morning when you probably hear this or Monday afternoon. I've been checked out. So no sense,
It makes no sense to call the, to call the hotel in the middle of the night and wake up, which has happened the last couple of times, I've actually mentioned where I was staying.
Today's been a production day for me.
Been very busy working on a number of projects.
One is the Spike Lee inside man podcast, which is this concept that we have of a shadow cast. We have a shadow cast or follow someone around in this case. It's Spike Lee.
On the set of his new movie inside man.
So I had some production to do on that as you know, I produced a lot of that on the plane actually on the way over from from London.
And excuse me. Oh, a sense of a moment.
I just finished up cutting all the tracks and doing the pre-production or the secondary part of pre-production,
because the pre-production of course is the selecting of the shows and the clips.
Man, it's actually quite a lot of work goes into the, into the pod finder podcast.
I'll tell you about that as I take you on a trip of, I don't know, just to walk around the neighborhood here near my hotel,
which as I said is right near Union Square, famous for its shopping extravaganza.
You kind of get everything all in one spot here in San Francisco.
You can walk one block and be in a neighborhood you might not want to be in around 130 in the morning.
And I don't know really. I've never walked around at 130 in the morning, so let's go.
I'll tell you about everything that I've been doing.
That's a really shitty door.
Okay.
So I'm on the 15th floor. This is a great hotel. It has an atrium.
So all the rooms are, it's kind of like the, you know, that's the watered 15 floors.
We're actually 12 floors below because the reception is on the third floor and the entrance to the hotel is on the first.
There was an atrium where all the rooms are kind of surrounding a central spot.
And we're going to take the elevator down and go out. It's chilly.
So I have a sweater on. I didn't bring a coat. So I borrowed Ron Bloom's jacket.
I have a sweater on, but still it's, no, it's going to be pretty chilly.
I think it was Mark Twain who said the coldest winter I ever witnessed was Summer in San Francisco.
Everything is going like cloth work. It's almost like gets smart here.
So these are beautiful glass elevators. And as we whisk down, I can actually see the floors flying by.
And it's really funky and we hit that third floor because it's a solid floor.
And you actually go right through the floor, kind of like a fireman on a pole.
There we go, pass reception, hello reception. Good bye reception.
And we're down at the ground level.
Okay, we're going to walk out the front door here.
Evening.
Okay, here we go.
Anyway, the pod finder podcast. I just want to tell you what kind of production goes into that.
Because it's pretty cool. Particularly, that we can actually do these kinds of productions now.
It used to be unthinkable. Maybe even five years ago, mainly held back by bandwidth constraints.
You see, I'm walking right now on, what is this?
I think this is this power. I believe. Maybe it's post road on.
It's post no bills. That's where I am right now.
Walking through some construction here.
Wow. It's a real funky.
I'm walking us. You can tell I'm working on board.
I'm going on very much like a scaffolding. You might see in New York City that you walk underneath.
Actually, I think I want to be going the other way towards Union Square.
I'm going to walk up to the corner here.
Or is it Taylor? I'm going to cross over.
So we've got a good idea of the sounds of San Francisco.
I'm the streets of San Francisco.
So the pod finder, the way it works is we have an editorial team.
The first looks at different podcasts. I put in some suggestions.
We kind of have a little ad hoc group meeting about what we want to feature on the show.
New shows, exciting new things that have happened.
Then we have to pull some clips from each show.
And we always look at the description field in the RSS feed.
So we know how people want to describe their own podcast.
Oh, what a bunch of noise here.
We're holding that.
Man, big 18 meter.
So once we have that, then I basically put it into an outline.
And, you know, come up with an order.
A run down of what I want to be in what spot.
And then I write little intros and altros to each piece.
Sometimes it's, you know, it's real copy that I'll stick to.
Sometimes it's just bullet points kind of depends on the podcast and what I feel about doing.
Then I cut all the tracks.
And then I upload that, including the outline to a central server.
We're our production engineer.
Then grabs everything and puts it all together.
Now, as I said, there's just no way that this could have been done.
A couple of years ago, mainly because of the bandwidth constraints,
forget processor speed and great microphones and ways to record stuff on location
without slipping along entire studios.
I may basically just have my Mac and my microphone combo.
The same one I'm using right now for the sound seeing tour of the streets of San Francisco.
And then Dave will put it all together.
And then he'll upload, you know, almost kind of like a final mix and we'll listen to it.
Then, of course, we still have to put the images in for the enhanced version of the podcast.
From the corner now of Mason and Post.
So I cut the corner into the hotel.
I'm walking towards the Union Square.
Oops, a little wind here.
Come on.
And then the enhanced podcast is made.
And then we shoot it all up to the server, create the RSS feed,
and notify Apple so that they can feature it in iTunes.
So as I said, kind of chilly.
What's interesting about San Francisco and I guess California in general
is that homeless people are everywhere.
It's not like New York City where homeless people are in certain areas.
Here you can find homeless people anywhere, which areas for areas.
Anyway, you can imagine.
And what's kind of weird and really takes them getting used to.
And I'm still getting used to it.
It's how people just step over them.
You know, just pass them by as if they don't exist.
And they really are everywhere.
In this time of night.
Especially.
Like here at the corner.
He's got a cup. You probably want some cash. He looks hammered.
What's up?
I'm your last hope.
Yeah, yeah.
He's treating so good.
I'm so glad I met a nice guy named.
What's your name?
My name is Will.
Will.
What's up, Will?
Can I help you out there, brother?
Yeah.
There you go, man.
One more for the stop there.
All right, buddy.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you.
So I was smart enough to come out and bring some singles.
Now, I could do this all night long.
You could be giving money to people that's really outrageous.
Every single street corner.
There's someone asking for cash.
So, I don't have any policy about that.
It's probably not even a good thing to be handing it out.
But, you know, if someone has a nice approach
and someone says, I'm the last hope.
Well, what can you say is a good scenario?
You know, you just got to do it.
I know walking has the same Francis,
famous hotel.
Right across from Union Square,
which is packed.
Well, there's some guys playing guitar over there.
Maybe I'll, uh, maybe I'll head over.
Let's see what they're doing.
Hey, listen to what they're playing.
Let me go check.
That could be fun, all night.
I'm trying to sell these things. I can't find anything cash.
I need $10 if you know anybody.
Is one.
That's the start.
One is all I got for now.
Oh yeah.
Can I have a listen?
Can I have a listen in?
No, no problem.
What are you guys from?
Rush it.
I'm recording this. Is that okay?
No, no, no.
Okay.
Let's see what they're playing.
Let's play.
Calm down.
Don't feel the same.
Done.
The sound sounded a little.
Bony,
It's not a long still morning, it's a long day
It's a long day, it's a long day
I'm sorry, I hope it falls today
I'm sorry, I hope it's so good
I hope it falls today
I'm sorry, I hope it falls today
I'm not listening.
I'm the one pleading Thank you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you know, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, STOP, well, I'm gonna show you, what up so catch you? So play well. And ever through the shorts, you can also see it, yeah. What up baseball and tune, here right, yeah. How it's played! fertilizerador and silver I hope it's so play, yeah. I hope it's played, yeah, mate.vale
We will be sure to say,
That's great. What's it about?
What are the words about?
All songs, of course, are about love.
Are you guys on vacation or?
Yeah, students.
Are you going to school here?
No, I'm not. I'm just working here for a couple of days and I live in London.
You can tell from my accent.
And do you like them?
Yeah, very much.
Yeah, it's great.
It's beautiful.
Yeah, definitely.
What do you mean?
Where have I?
Cold.
At night.
It's very cold.
Yeah.
Where are you from in Russia?
I'm from Europe.
Where are you from?
It's between the European nation and something.
Okay.
Sorry.
Moscow?
Yeah.
I've been to Moscow.
In 1989,
Was the Moscow Music Peace Festival.
Remember at the Lenin Stadium?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I've been to Moscow.
I was the Osbourne,
and Motley Crew,
and I see Gorky Park.
Those guys still around.
Gorky Park?
Yeah.
Do they still play the band?
It's just...
Yeah.
Cool.
You guys just...
You put out records or you make your own CDs or anything?
No.
Just for fun.
Everybody in Russia can play like this.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't love you.
Well, it's only three chords.
Four.
Four chords.
That is beautiful.
It's beautiful.
All right, guys.
We'll have a good summer.
Thank you.
All right.
Take it easy.
Bye-bye.
All right.
I guess that's a pod save, then.
I didn't even ask him if it was there, so I guess it's there, I'm so.
So walking past Union Square,
only just do a little time check here.
Okay.
We've been at it for about 20 minutes.
Good.
That actually filled up some time.
I didn't even expect it.
And it was sound a pretty good.
It was guys, you know, all young.
I'd say they were in their early 20s.
leather jackets.
Banged up guitars, pretty cool.
Man, and while I was standing there, like three homeless people came up and
begging for money.
It really ruins your walk.
But then again, if you're homeless, you have no house.
That could fucking ruin your whole vibe, too.
It's just, it seems like something could be done, you know.
Weird.
Oh, looking at the signs here.
Plenty of billboards.
Big sex if they have a new store.
Nike town.
Sky, vodka.
Please.
No comparison to absolute.
You know, the pod save music network is flavored by absolute all summer long.
Came in across over here.
This is Stockton.
So I'll go from Stockton over to Gary.
I'm sure I don't get run over.
Let's see.
Or does that a fire truck or police?
I can't sell.
I got a green light, so I'm growing.
Okay.
This is the corner of Gary and Stockton.
I'll walk down and then we'll do a big circle back up to the hotel and see what else
we encounter on our.
Sound seeing two of the streets of San Francisco.
You know, I was talking to Brian.
He's our director of operations on the show.
And you said, you know, it's, you feel so safe in San Francisco.
And I said, have you ever watched the streets of San Francisco?
And he's 32, I think.
And I realized, yeah, I'm an old-fucker.
That was a series that had the.
Michael Douglas starred in that.
It was a cop series called the streets of San Francisco.
Solving crimes.
Hainest crimes.
I'm at Macy's now.
I'm going to.
Turn right here.
The corner of Macy's.
On the side of the corner is Creighton Barrel.
I'm wondering if I should.
I walked down one more.
Big 18 wheeler.
Hey, I'm going to.
It says don't walk or it has the red hand, but.
I think it's pretty safe to cross.
And walk down towards if you know San Francisco, the kind of know where I am.
So I'm still on the Stockton.
I'm going to walk down to, I think, that's market.
Yeah.
The market.
My goodness.
I already know my way around.
Hey, it looks like I might have found an apartment here.
For.
For when I'm staying.
Isn't we spending a lot of time in San Francisco.
And really excited.
We put an offer in.
Hopefully it'll be accepted.
Um.
Actually, I posted a picture of the view from the living room on my weblog.
And people thought it was a hotel.
It's an apartment that I really hope I could.
I can get.
Hi, is the apple store here?
It's a guy in the apple store.
I'm sitting there reading the book.
Okay.
Now we're going to.
What do we do?
This is Ellis.
So what I'll do is I'll.
One more.
Go to market.
The sidewalk is being sprayed clean here.
It's one of California's savings.
I don't want to get wet.
So I'll cross over past market.
Across the trolley tracks.
Right in front of the good old Navy store.
It's deserted.
Completely fricking deserted.
No one on the street, but.
Almost people.
Me.
And you guys along for the ride.
Maybe we'll find some more interesting people to talk to.
You notice how I asked those Russian kids.
It was okay that I was recording.
Kind of learned my lesson from the yeah.
Elevator sound seeing tour in the wall to restore it.
Oh, I got so much flag.
True.
I guess I should.
Related.
Maybe we still need some kind of.
I'm podcasting.
Blinking light.
Next to the lapel microphone.
Oh, man.
Had a late dinner.
So this walking is.
Reminding me that I had that.
Give me many sense.
Let's see.
Shall we do?
Shall we go?
There's a walking past a bus stop.
Person sleeping in there with a shopping cart.
It really is sad.
And it's something to do with the policy of California that this.
Isn't dealt with.
It's also the policy of the United States I guess.
You don't see many homeless people in.
What even in London?
Just don't see it that much.
Let me see.
I'm going to cross back over here.
I'm going to cross market again going back towards the hotel general direction.
Can you hear 21?
No.
Oh, this is the place where the cable cars turn around.
And they don't really turn around, but they hit a plateau.
And it's kind of like a lazy Susan.
And it twists around and spins them back in the direction they came from.
I'm sorry to say there's just not a lot going on right now.
This would be power, I guess.
So we'll walk up power.
And see.
What else are we talking about?
What else is going on?
Well, I'll be going back Tuesday afternoon.
So it'll have been exactly a week, which I think is pretty much going to be my schedule
for the foreseeable future.
It'll be kind of like a working on an oil rig.
You know, one week on three weeks off.
Although, of course, it won't really be off.
It'll be, you know, source codes and all kinds of stuff.
Lots of production and we're ramping up with even more.
Okay.
Where am I now?
Power.
So if this is power, then post is going to...
No, power is what my hotel is on.
I think.
I think that's what it is.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hope my battery holds out.
I did so much recording today that the transmitter battery
Counted out on me.
I think I was another guy.
How you doing?
Oh, my goodness.
Just doesn't stop.
People going through garbage cans.
Unbelievable.
It's not that you don't feel safe for anything.
It's just like weird.
Okay.
Coming up to...
Oh, yeah.
People screaming up here.
Always find the check that out.
Let me see.
Oh, you don't want to go that way.
Doing a total J walk.
Okay.
We'll continue up.
Power.
Man, everyone's closed down.
All kinds of cultures.
All kinds of people out on the street at night.
It's trash night.
That's for sure.
Well, maybe this is just your regular trash.
Man, he wouldn't kind produces a load of crap.
Bags and bags piled high here.
Okay.
Let's see what we are.
This is Gary.
Okay.
I got my bearings now.
So...
Oh, what am I getting here?
My MBA is talking to me.
That's something pretty interesting.
I've noticed.
Let me see.
What should I do?
Go up one.
Something I noticed is that San Francisco is without a doubt.
One of the most wired cities.
Got the MBA, which has Wi-Fi built right into it.
A little pocket PC, phone, combo.
It has GPRS.
But you walk around the streets here and has an auto discovery mode for Wi-Fi.
And you just turn it on.
And it just...
You know, I'll do it now.
The networks just start appearing.
It's outrageous.
It's going to turn on to...
Wireless manager.
Okay.
Let's see.
Scanning the network.
Now it should just start popping up with all different kinds of access points.
I hope at least.
Sometimes you have to...
Like all good pocket PCs.
Sometimes you have to reset it.
But it actually works properly.
Don't see.
Don't see anything coming through, which immediately makes me think that I have to reset it.
So let me do that now.
Okay.
Okay, it's reset.
There's the theater.
Two big 18 wheelers up there.
One for Lemis.
Lemis are ably.
They're unloading.
I'll walk over there for a sec.
And listen to some of the unloading going on.
It might be something interesting.
We continue to scan for Wi-Fi.
Oh, they're loading in.
What are they loading in?
Looks like they're loading in.
Ringing.
Yeah.
Okay, I'm scanning for Wi-Fi again.
Big pieces of set are going into the trucks.
I wonder if the run is over on the pack and it is.
Okay, let me check my wireless manager here.
If you in the pocket PC boots up,
takes a while for it to figure out what it has to do
and what it has to display.
It's not a very rewarding process.
Okay, so I've got the Wi-Fi manager running.
It's scanning for networks.
See if we can find something.
Okay, nothing going on with a loaded.
There we go.
Airpath, Union Square Wireless, Wayport Access.
And I'm sure I can connect to at least one of those three.
A lot of free Wi-Fi here in San Francisco, which is extremely cool.
So I'm going to keep watching the MBA.
Now I can hear the phone park clicking.
That's pretty dead out here.
It's a nice folks.
I'm actually not that cold.
It was cold or a couple of nights ago.
It's quite nice.
A little bit of wind just puts the chill in the air.
There you get something here.
Still waiting to see if we can get a hit on the Wi-Fi.
Probably if I go to Union Square that Union Square Wireless will pop up again.
But it works, you know.
I have been using it quite successfully.
Just about everywhere you go.
Within a 50 foot radius.
You're able to find an access point that is very usable.
We are now passing B.C.A.B.J.
A high-fession.
Rounding the corner back on Powell.
Moving back up past St. Francis.
I'm going to put the MBA back in my pocket.
Wait, Google Wi-Fi?
It just doesn't stop.
I wonder if there's a Google office here somewhere.
One of these days.
We'll do a full sound scene tour where we stop at each Wi-Fi access point.
See if we can get a little bit of war walking instead of war driving.
Up to the corner.
Now bum no fucking cigarette off we do.
Okay, Disney store here at the corner.
And we're going to go back towards the hotel.
Which I can see up in the distance.
Another quick Wi-Fi check.
Just for the heck of it.
That's beeping at me, which means you've found something.
But it's cool how it'll show you a list of sometimes five access points just sitting there,
waiting to be used.
And I've noticed there's a lot of access points named net gear and linksis.
Which is just the standard names.
That's why they're all on secure.
Your heart always leaps of joy when you see some access point called linksis or net gear.
It's guaranteed I'm on.
Okay.
Right there may not be anything to receive here.
Okay, back in the pocket.
The MDA goes through back at the corner of Mason and Post at the Pam Pacific hotel.
And we've been at it for probably about, what is it?
About 30 minutes now? 40 minutes.
So.
Perfect time.
I'll take you back up to my room.
Hey, baby.
Want to come up to my room.
Take you back to my room.
And then we'll turn it off.
Compress this sucker into an MP3 and get it up.
I'm cleaning off the signage here at the Pam Pacific.
Here we go.
We're back.
Unstave.
No harm.
And a nice little evening walk.
Which is good.
It's really good to get out.
After sitting in the room for so long.
Come on.
Here we go.
Back up to the 15th floor.
You can hear the acoustics change immediately.
Up we go.
Count the floors with me now.
Here the beats.
Not very audible, actually.
Okay.
And we'll have my stuff.
The hotel is officially asleep.
Nothing going on.
Two AM.
And we're almost done.
Get my key card.
Someone has a nice little cup of decaf.
While I check the show for any errors.
Well, it's compressing.
We've got to open up the window.
A little stuffy.
Air condition is not a big thing here.
There's some kind of cooling unit here on the wall.
Let me see if I can, yeah, 71.
You want to be a little bit cooler than that.
Okay.
Well, once again, thank you very much for joining me on the sound seeing tour on the streets
of San Francisco.
Tuesday.
We'll be tomorrow.
We'll bring you yet another daily source code.
And feedback.
Always appreciated.
Adam at curie.com.
DailySourceCode.com is the website.
We can pick up the podcast feed, the archives, the new show.
And of course, you can also subscribe through iTunes to get to this show.
42 minutes.
Almost on the nose.
I'll talk to you tomorrow, everybody.
Bye-bye.