Delta Sierra Charlie 2-5-6
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It is October 7, 2005.
Time once again for the Daily Source Code.
Late today, 225 p.m. coming to you from Gilford from Curry Cottage.
That's right, it's the thank god it's Friday edition of the show.
And we've got a lot of stuff to talk about regarding my power book.
And it's replacement and what I'm doing.
In fact, it's put the sucker on ice.
I'll explain all that in today's show.
Well, because everything is changed significantly because I've basically had to resort to
buying a new Mac and installing all of my pertinent applications.
Nothing is working properly.
I'm learning a whole bunch of things.
And I guess there's only one thing we can do since we can't do a fully-formatted show.
Gmail Friday!
Yeah!
That's right, Gmail Friday.
Since I didn't have any opportunity to line anything up all of my licenses and expired,
everything is expired.
I have to be reinstalled.
It's not a very good day.
For those of you listening to this on a serious radio,
a serious satellite radio channel 103 and you're thinking of what that.
That was this kind of talking about.
Well, welcome to the party.
We've been dealing with this crap for about two hundred and fifty-five episodes.
All right, let's get the Friday party started,
shall we?
Ada from mashuptown.com, sent in something.
I actually think we've played on the show before,
if not, I definitely have heard this one.
But it is the kind of mashup that really gets you going on a Friday.
You know, you've got to combine the Scissor Sisters,
sneakle back,
and then what do you get this?
We've been dealing with this crap for about two hundred and fifty-five episodes.
We've been dealing with this crap for about two hundred and forty percent episodes.
We've been dealing with this crap for about two hundred and eighty-five episodes of Reviews.
We've been dealing with this crap for about two hundred and ninety-five episodes.
We've been dealing with this crap for about two hundred and fifty-five episodes.
to mashuptown.com.
Whoa, oh, that gets me in the mood.
I'm in a pretty good mood, actually.
I must say, because at the end of the day, my friends,
opening up a brand new computer,
I'm gonna tell you all about the story is,
it's like porn, you know?
It's like, it's just so wonderful to open the box
and smell that plastic and case equipment.
Mmm, I love it.
This morning, got up bright and early.
Christina was up at 6.30.
I don't know what she felt she needed more time
to do her hair and makeup.
Yes, this is what 15-year-old are into.
Oh my goodness.
I've had seven o'clock after a relatively short night
and I didn't get to bed until about 230
almost quarter to three.
I spent most of the evening, well,
actually, it's been a lot of time
talking to Pod Show HQ and SF
because we have a couple of team meetings.
And we use all kinds of stuff.
We use Skype, we use telephones.
We use I-Shat.
That's pretty cool, actually, the I-Shat.
That works reasonably well.
And I also really spend a lot of time
with my pot or book.
You know the continuing saga by now
that I think the disk is basically what's fried.
It may not be the disk, actually.
I think the disk got so defragmented
that it can't really find its boot sectors
or whatever and so it's kind of hate or miss.
And last night, I finally got it up
and running a couple of times late in the evening.
And it would run okay, but if you did any finder actions,
opening your hard disk, it would slow down
and of course iTunes and there's something
with iTunes, I'm sure, would just pop up once in a while
just to start downloading Podcast
and I try and force quitted as soon as possible
because once iTunes starts running,
then or any even a browser have to say,
the drive would start spinning and spinning and spinning
and then everything would get slower.
And so I was able to rescue a lot of data
that I knew I would want.
One is a couple of these OPML applications.
Unfortunately, I lost, well lost.
I'm the outliner is actually,
let me see if I lost I'm the outliner.
Because I got all the way to,
let me just check on the second if we go to,
and we go to applications,
we'll be able to save on the outliner.
Oh yes, oh save it, wonderful.
Okay, although I don't know if the license will work
or not, that's not a big deal.
Okay, so I finally got it up and running.
Then I was able to shut down restart
and it would start up again,
but still really all these slow problems.
So I was pretty confident with start
and so I turned it off.
And that was, as I said, around two, 15, the morning.
And then I went to bed, got up, took our scene at a school,
and came back, let me see what was, yeah,
because the PC store doesn't open until nine.
So I came back and I tried to boot up the power book
and it wouldn't boot up.
And so I figured right, I'd already kind of planned in my calendar.
I was supposed to go to the eagle this morning
and meet with Rob Harris, who was the news director there
and the news guy.
Chat and just to say, I don't, I think you wanted to interview me
about a couple of things.
I'm not quite sure.
So I sent him a note at night saying, dude,
I'm not gonna be able to make this
because I gotta go to the computer store.
And this was my plan.
My plan was to boot the power book up,
get a Mac Mini or something comparable,
and then boot the sick power book up in Firewire mode
and then basically transfer everything over.
I figured that I could probably get away with that.
It would probably do the transfer.
It might take longer than normal,
but I thought I could get that done.
And so I said, I'd already dumped a bunch of stuff
onto my Firewire drive, not everything, unfortunately,
but the application's directory
and partial part of my preference is not all.
So I went to a PC world with this one in Guilford here
on that Woodbridge Road and really good, actually.
It's quite, they've changed the store
in the past couple months since I was last there.
And I like it, it's, yeah, it looks good.
And I got a small but complete Mac section.
They had a Mac Mini and then I saw a G5 iMac,
1.8 gigahertz, do you can't get it?
Anything bigger than I think, 500 megs of memory.
It's got a hundred and...
It's like some humongous hard drive.
Let me just see what the hard drive says is.
I remember being quite large.
Yeah, it's a big one.
That's poor, man.
It's not that box.
Ah, light.
Let me see, what does it have?
160 gigabyte hard drive.
Yeah, nice, nice, nice.
So I thought, you know what, I'll just take that one
and I'll just keep that one in home.
And then, of course, the idea was,
was to get everything onto this iMac
and then do a complete, what is it?
Low level format of my hard drive on my power book
and completely clean that up, do a fresh install.
And then, my great, everything back over.
So I basically have a copy of what was originally
on my power book.
So that was the plan and I spent,
oh, a good two hours trying to reboot the power book.
It would not reboot, not from the drive at least.
It will from the CD and then the CD,
you get disc utilities and it doesn't see the drive.
So there's something very wrong there.
I've gone through all the FAQs
and there's been lots of great emails
and lots of helpful comments.
The only thing that really may work at this point,
and I know because I've had this before with the Mac
as you put it in the freezer for a little bit
and then it really gets cold and then sometimes it will boot up
if you're having boot troubles.
So as we speak, it's in the freezer
and I'll deal with it later
because now all I want to is at least be able to access the drive
and just erase it and clean it
and if there's no physical errors,
then I'll be able to rebuild my book.
So I got the FireWard drive hooked it up to the IMac
and I was able to salvage the most important part
of my radio user land install,
which is how I'm still using show notes.
I'm going to change that by the way, boy,
did I learn something about proprietary protocols
and formats with that exercise, man?
Because you cannot update anything
on the radio user land servers without using radio user land
and it's a proprietary, it's probably published
but it's an upstreaming protocol that it's not like FTP.
So which is kind of lame, I guess.
Now that I always thought upstreaming was pretty cool
but it's not because you can't use any other tool
but radio user land to do anything with your file.
So because of course I could upload a text file
from my RSS feed, I could do a number of ways,
I could hand code it if I wanted to.
So unfortunately, that wasn't possible
but I was able to download a fresh copy of radio user land
futs around with a little bit as always.
I luckily had the copy of my web blogs data base
so all of my postings for the past five years
were in there so I was able to say that I have backup
but this was really a most recent copy.
And my daily source code folder,
for those of you who use radio user land,
you know what I'm talking about.
So it took a little bit of fiddling around
to get that up and running
and it actually runs much better than it ever did
with this fresh, clean install.
I got my my OPML application
which has all the indie potter.org scripts
for updating the home page and then mega-seg.
This is the program that I use to schedule everything
that I'm gonna do in the show.
And the way mega-seg does their licensing,
you can download a demo copy.
And of course I also saved that application
but for some reason I guess you have to install it
from an installer.
If I recall properly when you purchased the app,
then they take you to a special download page
and that download page I think has an installer
and then you install it and there's no serial code
or anything to enter
because that app was basically just for you.
So reinstalling as I looked at their website
does require that you send them an email
with your purchase information,
your serial number or whatever you get.
And then they'll send you back a key.
But of course there are sleep right now.
They're probably, they may be California.
They must be in California.
So, excuse me, oh yes, you know what it is, right?
Don't have to say it, send sale.
So the limitation they put on the demo version,
which of course I could use
and I had to re-emport up there it goes.
Demo version, buy online for an instant download.
What it does is every 15 minutes it stops.
So I knew that that would never work.
I'd never be able to line everything up
and then kind of time around this 15 minute time out.
So we'll just have to wait until the new code comes back.
And basically I'm gonna rebuild,
well, I was able to, all my songs are on my firewire drive.
So I was able, and you know, all the imaging
and all the sweepers and the bumpers and the promos.
So I could re, I was able to re-emport that.
Of course, none of the in and out points
that I set were saved.
So bottom line, I am rebuilding my digital life.
And I'm gonna do it on this IMAC G5,
which I thought was just a fantastic machine.
Big fucking surprise coming, check this out.
I actually added a noise gate to it.
I want you to listen to the output of the,
because I just use the audio jack.
And now I'm gonna have to go, you know,
get a firewire, what do you call it, interface?
Because, oh man, that's gonna build up latency
probably to fuck, sorry about that.
I'm just going through all kinds of stuff
going through my mind here.
I'm gonna turn off the noise gate,
let me see if I can do this.
So channel five, here we go.
I'm gonna turn off, because I have a noise gate,
I want you to listen to the sound
that comes out of this audio out jack on this,
you know, not cheap machine,
which for everything I can see is pretty professional,
but now listen to this.
Hold on, we'll do that.
I really want you to hear this.
Oh, that's not it, I guess I have to bypass it.
All right, here we go, I'll bypass it,
hold on one second.
Off, there you go, listen to this.
Now that's obviously just the left channel.
Let me do the same for the right channel.
And just listen to the garbage that's coming out
of this audio card.
And if I touch the plug in the back, listen to this.
You can actually hear it.
So that's what we call shit.
That's really, really, really poor quality stuff in there.
So that's a bummer, and so what I did is I put a noise gate
on both of those channels.
So basically when there's no signal coming out,
it cuts off the audio.
And since we weren't able to queue anything up,
it's gonna be Gmail Friday, which means we just started
the top of the Gmail box and work our way down
finding anything to play, basically.
So right off the bat, Peter says Adam Digital Station,
BBC Six music played a snippet from Cruise Box
on a podcast today around 9.45 a.m. UK time,
promoting podcasts from the BBC, interesting.
So it wasn't like in a documentary format.
They were promoting podcasts made by the BBC using Cruise Box.
And he says, I hope your pro organization is getting on
to that.
Yeah, well, you know what?
I think that we'll obviously let this one slide
because we're kind of experimenting
with what we can and can't do ourselves.
So, and it could also be deemed fair use.
So we're gonna let that slide, but when it comes to pro,
which if those you've been listening for the past two days,
is the forthcoming, pod safe music,
writes organization.
And boy, am I getting a lot of feedback?
Wow, I really, really appreciate everything
that everyone's sending in.
And I've got lawyers who are giving opinions
in financial people who are thinking of ways
that, you know, this whole thing can be set up
and how can we make it just much, much better
than what ASCAP or BMI are.
And again, they have all of these splits
and percentages and special bonuses, really because,
you know, their world is finite.
There can only be so many radio stations
that they can collect from, but with podcasting,
which of course has to be completely global,
you can, yeah, you can, it's infinite.
In finite, today we have 9,000 podcast,
a few years, maybe 90,000.
And today we have 10 million listeners,
so in a few years, exactly 100 million listeners.
Email here from, oh, this is from Raymond Port.
Raymond, oh, he says, today one year ago, check it out.
Oh, this is gonna be cool.
I don't know if I have to set it up
and say, I haven't heard this again, it's Gmail Friday.
Maybe Raymond will have explained that if not,
then I'll cut it off, let me just see,
I've opened it up here, it's contacting RaymondPort.nl.
And the call letter, it was, okay, so he didn't set it up.
One year ago today, I was driving home
from the Netherlands to the Curry Castle.
And so this was really in the beginning of podcasting
in the very early stages.
And I'm in the car in the Studio A8,
doing the podcast, recording it as I'm sitting in traffic.
And someone is honking next to my car.
And I'm gonna play this bit for you
since it is our one year anniversary Raymond,
it was of course Raymond, this is what happened.
One year ago today, when I was recording in Studio A8.
What's in the call letter, it was, oh yeah,
W-I-W-I-T-B, which, depending on what,
if you're on the day air shift or the night air shift,
the day shift meant we're in the basement,
which is where the studios were originally located.
On the night shift, of course, it's we're into bombheads.
That was my college radio days.
I still have my, you know, the varsity jacket
from the radio station, W-I-T-B, air personality
and curry involvement.
So, but it was cool and college radio was cool.
And he's podcasting.
Hey, someone, someone's holding up his iPod.
Hold on, hold on, you window.
Exit the net, don't you open the name.
Here, come here.
Come on.
Hey Jeff.
Hey, little boards.
Raymond, boards.
Still no.
Okay, dude.
Yeah, right, dude, we checked out a guy just drove up next to me.
And he's honking his horn and he's holding his iPod off.
And he's saying, I'm listening to the podcast.
Yeah, damn, and I said, I'm recording one right now.
So Raymond, buddy.
Oh, that's very cool.
See, this is what I mean.
This is what it's all about.
Oh, that gives me a boost of energy.
That's fucking great.
Okay, so this is what it's like.
It's college radio only.
We're clearly, we're mobile in more ways than one.
So, American Heartbreak, I really liked that.
All right, so that was one year ago today.
Well, happy anniversary Raymond.
It was certainly a pinnacle moment in those early days of podcasting.
That was the moment when I said myself, oh my God, something's going on here.
He was listening to the Daily Source Code, a previous edition, in the same traffic I was,
as I was recording the next day's show in that same traffic jam.
Fantastic.
Next email on Gmail Friday on the Daily Source Code from, oh, this is from Mark Hunter of
the Tarton Podcast and we had a little back and forth email just talking about stuff
and, you know, talking about good vibes and he said, hey, and if you've never heard the
Tarton podcast, then you have not heard Scottish music, my friends.
So he made a recommendation, Amplifico from Edinburgh.
They contacted him a couple of weeks ago and he just switched them on to the podcast
and he said, music network, they have four or five songs up now and, of course, they magically
a link to that will appear in the wiki show notes.
He says, I put a track up on my server.
I think it would be great on the Daily Source Code, if you want to play it, I'm putting
myself and the Tarton Podcasts 100% behind these guys.
They should be signed up.
The singer probably has the best voice I've heard in a long time.
Okay, so let's hit that.
The track is called 10p mix, Amplifico, pod save music on the Daily Source Code.
Over this, over this, should don't do it when you have got such a bright, such
a breath.
Taken's how to hit them with them, feel the sick, feel the sick, but it flies in my
gut life thing on and out, on and out, on and out, all things you'll just don't
break, it's not hard to believe it that she's got a new name out to you.
There in her sleep, why is this my head feels no wonder more she's trying to hold
the key.
I'm ready.
I know you're letting yourself down, but even one opportunity like this won't come your
way, so you've got to do it through your mama handle, you lost your sense of
the face that I needed, the threatening lotting and insisted something.
Anyway, when it's both good I didn't know I thought it was you, wasn't lucky, like
just when Marco did a racing understood through your Mama ehh, look at my fellow
When you're squashed and let this in the spiders
The goodness you can nest up
How you now lay me down to rest like a town like a town
That's makes not much to go around
But when you do, when you do, stand for me how things are
For more, to believe it that she's calling the name
Out to you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you
Is it my head to show what the mushrooms got to hold
The long rest, I'm going to bed in the sun
I'm going to be one of the two empty lights
This one from the way, something from the truth
Through your far-right hair, go through the sun
Let's say, let me play that everything you're feeling
It's just a perfect sense anyway
Like a joke, like a drug, never feel you've had enough had enough
And when I'm standing, it's covered down
Yeah, because you take it over, you think you can
Like a joke, like a drug, never feel you've had enough had enough
Such a bright, such a breath, deep, but to hear from with it the way
Though you're ready, no sound, I'm going to be the one
Not the tune of the light, this one from the way
She got a joke, like a drug, never feel you've had enough had enough
And when I'm standing, it's covered down
Yeah, because you're ready, no sound, I'm going to be one of the two
Like a joke, like a drug, never feel you've had enough had enough had enough
And when I'm standing, it's covered down
It's just a nothing light, just taking hold
You're going to find yourself later I won't
You're going to find yourself now
Yeah, alrighty, some Scottish music on the source code
Oh, it was alright actually, I kind of thought it dug that
10p mix. It was the title of that. Let me just go back to the G-Mails here. By the way,
in the meantime, I checked out how radio user land was doing. It actually worked.
Everything's back up. I don't think I have to do is repost yesterday's source
coding yesterday's job cast and then we're back up to speed. And actually the app is
it's nice. It's really fast. And of course, all you got to compact databases and all
this stuff to really make a work. But it's working. It's working. I'm rebuilding my life.
It's good to reboot once in a while. You know, it makes you powerful.
Adam, this is James B from JamesB.com. I just wanted to send you some audio feedback to
tell you how podcasting is changing my life. I don't think I'm alone. I'm sure that podcasting
is changing a lot of lives and I have a feeling it's only going to grow. One way that podcasting
is changing my life is that it has reignited my love for music. Several years back, I became
disillusioned with new music. I figured that I was just getting too old and out of touch with
the younger generation. I find now that I relate to a lot of music that is being produced.
It's just a matter of finding it. I can't find it on the radio or on TV. But it's out there.
I found it and it's all because of the internet and podcasting. Let me give you an example.
I learned about accident hash from your podcast. From the accident hash podcast,
I listened to the first episode of the podcast music rewind, which featured the Tartan podcast.
I started to listen to the Tartan podcast and heard an episode about Finiston.
Then I went to thefiniston.com website in order their CD and I just received the CD today.
Wow, now here's a brother and sister band from the UK shipping a CD that they only pressed
a hundred of and they sent one to me here in Utah. How cool is that? What other medium could
have that kind of distribution? Podcasting is truly global radio and much more. Another way
that podcasting is changing my life is that it has given me a creative outlet that I've needed
for a long time. I'm producing a podcast named Navalcast. It's what I call an entertaining
introspective podcast. It's just for fun and I don't expect to ever have a big audience.
Granted, I'd like a few more listeners than I have now. In my podcast, I just tell the stories
that I've always ended up telling to my friends, play some music and have fun doing it.
I figured the very least my children and my children's children will know a little bit more about
me because of the MP3 files I've left behind. I just wanted to finish by telling you and all the
other great podcasts that are out there to keep up the good work. Sometimes when I'm feeling a little
down or tired or wondering if I can really produce a podcast that a few people will enjoy.
I listen to the daily source code or podcasts for one one or Jimmy Jad or Dave's lounge
or the many others I listen to and I feel energized again. It gives me the motivation to be creative
to figure out how to get a podcast out there in the first place and then to do the next one
and the next one. Well, that's all I have to say. Now for a shameless plug, you can find my podcast at
JamesB.com. Thanks Adam. Talk to you later. Yeah, fantastic. Well, you pointed something out there that's
really quite interesting and rather important to just a stance still out for just a second. That is,
you know, when you're listening to one show and then you hear about another show and you hear a
snippet from that show and you pop around, that is, well, first of all, that's a social networking
is what they call that in Silicon Valley. But it's also the hyperlink. It's the, you know, that's
what people talk about when they say, well, the podcasts should have a way to, you know, or in fact,
some detractors of podcasting say, you know, it's no good because you can't, there's no
permalinking because you can't link directly into a certain spot within a file. But that's not
really what this is about, you know, but you see how the networks are built up and how you go
from one to the other. So the next part that we have to solve, which, well, of course, pod shows,
I'm going to do her damnedest. The next part we need to solve is, how do you share subscriptions?
Now, of course, we have the OPML format, that's being, sorry. Let me just, uh, quit out of mega
set here for a second. The OPML format is used to share a list of subscriptions, but really just
one subscription. You know, how cool would it be if, um, if I'm on an instant messenger with you
and I can say, dude, you've got to check out this podcast. I just click a button then you're subscribed
after you accept, obviously. Or, you know, I could, uh, could SMS or I could text the subscription
to someone and it would automatically, you know, whenever they sync up or however it would work,
it would, it would add that subscription or, you know, just all kinds of things like that. And of
course, as we move, uh, well, and actually iTunes has a kind of a version of that,
where, uh, with the enhanced podcast, but, uh, it'd be nice to have some, you know, mobile
concept as you're listening. You say, oh, yeah, I definitely want to subscribe to that,
then there should probably be a way to do it. Okay, moving along in, uh, the Gmail box, as you
can tell, I'm talking and reading at the same time. Uh, see if there's anything, uh, okay, lots of
feedback on their arbitrons, stuff that we've been talking about, some more biodiesel,
here we go. Uh, Adam says Chris, heard your call for promo is this week. Want to let you know that
I've submitted my promo to you five different times in the last six months. You never,
and never heard anything about it. I'm not bitter. Just was wondering if there were others
like me, it would submitted them. And for some other reason or another, you just never got to them.
Well, Chris, yeah, let me see, what's the current count? 11,796 unread emails. Yeah, well, you know,
it might be somewhere in the middle of that, you know, I sometimes I do just kind of miss stuff.
Oh, you know what happened there? Uh, didn't come, uh, no, it's not another drive that
are broken. It didn't come in fast enough. Oh, that kind of sucks. Hmm, what should we do about that?
That's basically, uh, well, is that, oh, that's probably his server. It's a little bit slow. Okay,
we'll just let that load. I'll play that in a second. Let me just see what else we got here.
That's going to open up iTunes. What the hell? Let's see what happens. Uh, it's an, uh, an M4A file.
Remember, this is Gmail Friday. Are your feedback for the daily source code 254 from October the 5th?
And I just want to say a big thank you for other things that you've done so far. The daily source
code, it's their pod finders and all the things on pod show, uh, the pod save music network and so on and so forth.
And, um, I think it's a really nice what has happened so far. The chances that we actually
don't have to listen to the conventional mainstream radio stations anymore has really benefited.
And, um, I think most of us 10 million listeners so far, I think you said, um, I really appreciate
things and don't feel like flaming you or people really working hard for the success of this thing
and basically for the good of all of us. So, um, as I said, a bit big thank you and don't
let this upcoming stress get too close to you and your guys at Pocho and I wish you all the best
for your ventures and things to come. So, uh, looking forward for more stuff to come and listening
to the daily source code to see what's coming up. So, take care. Bye. Thank you very much,
young, young Pacill, who that was. And that actually didn't open up an iTunes that
uh, opened up by default in Safari in a quick time plugin. Okay, let's play that promo again because
guys, give you this imagine, you know, poor guys sitting at home, I finally play this promo. It cuts
out and they don't play the whole thing.
The car cast with your host, Grins Cocker.
I wanna blame it on the night. I wanna blame it on the last good night. I wanna blame it on
the other thing when they're drying out for knowledge and money. Hi Adam, Chris Cocker in here,
wanted to let you know about my show, the car cast. So, what would happen if you took a guy
with way too much time on his hands and gave him the ability to record a podcast while driving
around Seattle? Well, not entirely, but that's the premise of the car cast. On the car cast,
we cover news news items tonight. A couple of things we want to talk about. First of all,
we're gonna do a fat band update. We're gonna talk about bouncing hills back in the news
against an item. Finally, uh, fill her up with wood. Do a little Samsung. Holy cow!
Look at that truck. Okay, Ren front of me is a four-explore, a big SUV, and uh, the tire,
the back left tire on it is literally ripping apart. It's got like hunks of tire hanging off of it.
These are the phone calls. Peter, how you doing?
Peter, you're right now on the car cast.
And all of that is done while driving around Seattle. If you'd like to check out the car cast,
we're listed in the iTunes music store, or you could just go to thecarcast.com. That's thecarcast.com.
Be listening, because I might be the one tailgating you.
You know, car manufacturers of the world pay attention. What's fantastic opportunities here
that you're just letting pass by? Not to mention that you should be giving me diesel vehicles.
It's not to be a new one. Give me the, give me like the executive one that's been driven for
3,000 miles, and the executive gives it back and gets a new car. Give me that one.
I'll podcast from it, and we'll be throwing vegetable oil and stuff like that in the tank.
Let's see, uh, flight humor from, uh, who's this from? Who is this from?
It doesn't even say. Well, that sucks. Uh, our carver. Okay.
This is funny. This is like, uh, the wife fly through the valley of death. I shall fear no evil.
For I am at 80,000 feet in climbing. That's real pilot humor. Yeah, you've never been lost until
you've been lost at Mach 3. Test pilot said that. U.S. Marine Corp Gunner, U.S. Marine Corp Gunner,
he's sergeant says, you, you, you panic. The rest of you come with me. Okay. Yeah, that is definitely
flight humor. All right. Let me roll out another one of these feedback things. Oh, my goodness. That's
cool. Now I clicked on that M4A file and it brought up a whole page of code. That was really nice.
Okay. I'll just skip that one. You know, maybe we should, uh, uh, maybe we should look at
ending the show. Oh, I'm going to download this. This one last bit of feedback. Remember it is
Gmail Friday, which, of course, is the reason why it's, uh, it's all over the place. I want to go to
the pod safe music network and, uh, we'll get out of here with a song. That will be that'll be fun.
Hold on. Let's, uh, oh, it's M4A text. Oh, well, that's not going to work.
Oh, incompatible systems and file formats and everything. Okay. Let's see if this works.
Use M4A. And now I can just open that with quick time. I hope. Let's give it a try.
Hi, Adam. Um, here is stuff. MC in the place to be live, uh, from Antwerp and with the sheriff in the house.
And, uh, I have kind of a comment about two things you said. The first thing is about the, um,
the radios. Um, if radios are good in the country, podcast is working. Let's go.
Actually, I think it's pretty, um, exact. I have my view on the things is that I'm, um,
I'm originally a bad guy living in Germany. And, uh, when I'm in Belgium, I use to listen to a
really cool radio, which is, I think, my opinion, city of Warsaw. Also, on a French-speaking
Belgian, uh, we still have no, uh, corresponding to the coolness of city of Warsaw.
It's all for the country. And when I'm in Germany, I use to listen to Einstein's life.
These are two only radios for which I'm not turning on my iPod on when I'm doing the
radio. Normally, I use, I'm used to listen to the source code or whatever else.
Other podcasts in the radio. And I have a really cool thing in my auto radio, which is a check-in
to put directly the iPod in. But, uh, I still, I listen sometimes now and then to radio,
because like I said, these are the two only radios that I know that are not playing the normal
music and just doing the, you know, typical 70s, 80s, 90s, and the best of today. So, uh,
that's the only reason. The second thing I wanted to react is about beard, here's it.
Wait a minute, did you hear that? Did you hear that? They do the same damn thing over in Germany?
There's seven, the best of the 70s, 80s, 90s, and today, everybody, uh, interesting.
Crap crosses all borders. You speak a lot about beard, here's a lot of Volkswagen Golf,
which is a lot of beginning, but you can put also by a diesel in it. It's written in the manual.
So, I asked a few people around me because I'm a, I'm an ecologist. So, I ask and the conclusion
was that first of all, it's more expensive, most of the time, which is weird. And second of all,
you will consume more fuel. But the second, the third thing is I heard and speaking to the guys
directly at Volkswagen at the mechanics, they told me that it could actually not be so good to mix both.
So, if you started, and for years and years, use diesel, it's not a good idea to mix both.
So, either you start from beginning only with biodiesel, or you stay with diesel. So,
until now, I said with diesel, I hope it's going to change, and I hope that we can
make the things happening, like you say, like put all the crabs in your tank. It would be the best
thing, but I'm not going to do this. Dude, I want, there's like another three minutes on that.
I've got to listen to the rest of that, but I just want to, you know, get out of here with the song.
I just logged in the pod save music network. I'm just looking at all the new submissions.
And what I usually do is I look at the listener ratings and, you know, the genre, whatever I'm
into, what do I feel like, let's see, pop rock, let's see what this is. John McCloy, if it's,
if it vibes, then we'll leave it on. And, uh, sounds a bit like Mr. Mr.
This is called, uh, just believe it.
So far so good. How about the vote?
It should be, you're in a compass, knows what's best for you.
To find out where you're going, where you wake up, where you're to.
In these big surprise, when I let go of the who, the what, the where the when's and why,
surprises us there, let it go, and then all of them come together,
we're alone, let it be, just that you'll find it when you need it.
So believe, believe it, just believe, just believe it.
I lost my innocence and somehow ended here, for you, I'm dumped up, time and fire,
I'm still safe, it's just not in the mirror, still fine, time and fire.
If you hope, if you wish, do you live as if heaven somehow owes you,
that you help, that you reach, that you stretch, that you can't, and I'm not, and hell, we're all here.
Let it be, just that you'll find it when you need it.
So believe, believe it, just believe, just believe it.
If you go, and then all of them come together, let it be, just believe it, just believe it,
just believe it, just believe it, just believe it.
So believe, believe it, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe
just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, sure, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe, just believe
Just believe it.
Cool.
John McCloy, just believe it.
We were lucky.
We just hit whatever came up on the podcast and music network.
Recent submissions.
And I was pretty damn good actually.
I had also had a kind of like a YouTube vibe in there.
Dig that.
Very, very cool.
John McCloy.
I never heard of him.
I guess he's new to the network.
Okay.
So that just about wraps it up for the daily source code for today.
And thank you all of you by the way who were inquired about Patricia and the medicine getting
to Paris on time and arrived this morning.
That was that was very enjoyable.
The whole experience of tracking the package online and seeing that it was delivered to the
hotel at 7.40 a.m.
I was cool.
And you know, thanks to my buddies and other guys who offered private planes and all kinds
of other alternative ways to get it there.
It all worked out very cool.
So maybe we'll do some more over the weekend.
Patricia comes back Sunday and otherwise I'll be talking to you Monday for sure on the
source code.
Take care now and bye bye.