Sunday night, May 23rd, 2005, daily source code, it's 104 degrees outside at
quarter to 11, and according to 11, according to 11, quarter to 11, we're in Phoenix.
courtesy of America worst airline.
So we had a, oh, look here it is.
That's what I'm going to point.
I told you our friend would hook us up.
Who would back us up?
Oh, excuse me.
So we had a flight to get from San Diego to San Francisco.
We had to go via Phoenix, but that was good news because of our meeting.
Well, now I'll talk about that in a second, which we can't talk about.
Yeah, we made it run later, so we had to take the stock to get them a jump flight.
And here's my bag. That's cool.
Thank you. And yours? Yes.
Okay. Oh, boy.
This bag is about had it though.
See, starting to rip. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, no.
Well, here. Yeah, I know.
It's time for another $49 bag.
Okay, well, so I did you already call the shuttle.
So basically, America West, we had a connection in Phoenix
to take a flight to San Francisco and our flight left late.
And when we arrived, we sat at the gate for 15 minutes
because America West had no more people to bring the jet weight to the plane.
Both of their employees were busy.
You sound bitter, Ron. Is it worth that, just?
You. The nature of the machine. We call it the airline engine.
Right, so.
So, of course, we knew we were going to miss our connecting flight.
And it was, you left out the port. It wasn't even listed.
It couldn't find the gate for it. I'm getting there. Come on.
Well, no, it's starting to work on the plane.
And we're waiting for 15 minutes and then the, what do you call them?
Flight attendant, the person says, hey, if anyone wants to ride a letter to
our company, go ahead. Sorry about your bad idea. If you want to ride a letter to somebody.
Yeah. Feel free. So,
oh, check this out. Now, we're going to go out the door. I do 104 degrees at 11 o'clock at night.
Yeah, that's rough. So, there was no one to eat us. No one telling us where to go.
All the screens show the morning flights.
So, while Ron tried to get us free boat for the morning, I went to try and get our bags
for three from the tarmac because they actually hadn't even been brought in yet.
And so, let's see, it's been about two hours that we've been hanging out here.
The thing is, it's fine to get everything square in the way. Now, we should be having our bags with us.
And with any luck, we're going to shovel them.
Who, uh, I think it was Coach Elbach, which was very nice.
And the next flight out is 7 a.m.
From our morning.
So, we'll still be able to make our
That was just going to eat us with some reasonable time for it.
I think what I'll do is, uh, they will continue this when we're in a little bit quieter environment.
We do some kind of cool stuff we've talked about.
wand
They're opening up.
It's really noisy out here.
I think I'm part of the old travelers, yeah, I'm really concerned about my bag now.
But you know the next guy that picks this up is gonna rip open.
Yeah, that's a ticket.
I don't know, I'll shove this down.
It's classic.
We'll just take it.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, I'll stop this and we'll continue with where to buy our environment.
Don't go anywhere, y'all.
Okay.
We are not waiting for them.
Don't know, don't grab it by that.
Get this one in.
You're not drinking with those, isn't it?
No, I'm a van coming right here.
Coming.
Okay.
So, we've opted for the cat.
Oh, that's too much wind.
Okay.
All righty.
How are you doing?
Good.
Feels nice.
Airport Hills.
I know it's close.
I'm gonna hook you up.
Put your money away for the van.
Don't worry.
Don't even turn on your meter.
I'll hook you up.
Fair enough?
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
I know it's right near here, right?
Watch it be 20 feet.
Okay.
So, uh, I actually had a pretty good day.
Which is the humorous day in 4-E-7.
4-E-7.
Right?
It's the one that's closest to the airport.
Yeah.
We, uh, caught up this morning.
I had a nice, really nice sleep.
I like 8-4 hours.
I hate to clock my eyes.
I just went bleeding and opened.
And, uh, had some breakfast.
Had a guy come up to a breakfast.
That's right.
To hell with my weight here last night.
I heard your pocket.
Oh, there was at this morning.
I heard your backpack.
Yeah.
That was kind of cool.
It was interesting guy here.
It was in the automotive industry.
He ended up in engineering team.
Yeah.
He's trying to get, uh, iPod and M.D.3 player hookups in cars.
He says 2007.
It's crazy.
And, uh, then we hang out for a little bit.
So tired.
I'll tell you what.
What is that over there?
You see all those red lights?
Or is that just 50 end of runway?
The end of Area 52.
I don't know what it is.
I haven't been to Phoenix on in years.
I came here to, uh,
go to the Bob Bondoron School of Racing.
With, uh,
Yeah, those two.
That was one MTV still that cool shit.
We, uh, we got the celebrity racing Denver.
And all of us had to be qualified.
So it's like,
the guys from Motley Crew,
White Lion.
And, uh,
Johnny Gill.
Some reason I remember him.
And we spent like four days here getting our license to race.
And, uh,
And, I already live in Dijk, Dutch sky.
It lives out here.
Which is Dijk?
I already live in Dijk.
He, uh,
1 Indy, uh,
3 times I think now.
Or 2 times.
2 or 3 times.
Hey, gentleman.
Splub.
Triple X of Delta Action.
Can't believe we passed that.
and find a planning neighborhood, it's located next to the collisions and not sure what
it looks like. I'm sorry I didn't start recording when I went to the Bagged Resolution
Center. That was pretty cool. Okay. So the highlight of the day was without a doubt
about an hour and a half that we had with Steve Jobs, which was really fun. You know,
just a private conversation. And that was great. And of course I can't tell you everything
but only for us about now. Of course we need to turn this off. But I will say that I was
able to provide a lot of input. The number one great piece of input that I was able
to feedback was, hey, I want to record on my iPod. And I can guarantee you that's going
to happen sometime in the near future. Okay. So we're going to find our hotel sleep and
then tomorrow sometime in the afternoon. Hopefully I'll be able to bring you a longer
daily source code with all the usual stuff. Because we're just about ready to pull
up to the what do we at the waffle house? The awful house. We should know that if you're
certain. Well, I'm not. I'm Easter. Okay. South Worst Airlines. That was America Wars, not
South America Wars Airlines. You see, go to the awful house. I'm telling you. Okay,
put me sweet. Well, yeah, that's a good point. All righty. That may be the shuttle right
deal with no driver. That would happen. All right. So we're talking to you all
tomorrow. Everybody perfect 12 minute podcast. Take care. Bye.