Daily Source Code, Monday, February 14th, 2005, transmitters, we don't need no stinking transmittance.
Happy Valentine's, everybody. It's the 14th of February.
And welcome once again to the Daily Source Code.
Start of a brand new week, a big week for me, because I'm going to be traveling all over the globe.
That's right. Starting off with the Netherlands, leaving in just a couple hours.
It's 1-21 in the afternoon. This is the source code coming to you from Curry Cottage.
Once again, I've got my perfectly brewed cup of Senseo coffee right here.
When we talk about that later on, I've been trying to sell these Senseo coffee machines now that I haven't Amazon-associated.
And guess what? I'll tell you all about the sales later on.
In the show, we've got lots of stuff, news on some iPod or clients.
We've got some pod-safe music, some pod-safe music cromos.
We've got all kinds of interesting cromos.
Of course, young pull-ups hit test and a mashup or two, because y'all love them so much.
So, I apologize if you're waiting for something over the weekend.
There's some form of extended ketchup podcast, which I didn't get around to doing.
Actually, I was waiting on Skype to see if Ken Clark would come online.
And he didn't, well, there was lots of TV to watch over the weekend.
We had the Brit Awards, that was Friday. I got home, I just missed it.
Luckily, my Skype digital box, of course, records almost everything you're watching.
See, then there was the BAFTA Awards on Saturday night.
BAFTAs are the British Academy, I wasn't British Academy film awards.
And it was pretty boring, really.
It was just like a fucking awards.
Well, I don't know, no glitz, no glamour.
Nothing compared to the Brits Awards, which I guess is the British version of the Grammys.
It was really, and the BAFTAs, it was interesting.
There was lots of American movie stars that showed up.
I think all of them were really surprised.
None of them expected the Red Carpet to be very much the Pandemonium that you would see in Hollywood.
She gives me a lot of sense.
I was kind of fun to see the American actors and how different they respond to the press overseas,
and just how different they respond to the fans.
I don't know, it was, well, maybe just wasn't as Hollywood as you'd expected to be.
So it was kind of fun to watch that.
So it was plenty of TV.
Otherwise, you know, TV boars me to fucking tears.
You know, flip, flip, flopping back and forth between the internet.
I'm sorry, the internet.
And TV news, Dresden was in the news.
German town that housed a very important communication center for the Nazis.
And you're the end of the second world war, as well as an important train communication.
Sorry, connection.
And only a couple of months before the war ended, the Allied forces bombed Dresden to shit,
killing what the record says is 30 to 35,000 people.
And so, you know, that's always, every year there's a remembrance there in Dresden,
not just of Dresden and the people that Paris there,
just about ending violence in the war in general.
And it's funny because I was watching the press reports on sky news, ITV news.
I think you even see it as CNN.
And it was, you know, the re-flaying and all that.
But online I was reading about 5,000 protesters who were,
I think most of them were fascist, right wing neo-Nazis.
But I don't know, because I never saw any pictures.
So it goes to show, you know, what's happening?
What was really happening?
There were no pictures on weblogs either.
So just kind of interesting to see this disconnect in the news there.
So we got a brand new week, a lot going on.
Wednesday I'm going to New York.
Wednesday is a very important day.
February 16th, the Bitties cast kicks off in Nueva York.
So I'm going to be there for the big show.
I can't wait to meet all the girls in person.
And, oh man, we're going to be talking every single night about what's going on,
because there's lots of exciting stuff happening.
Lots of opportunities, lots of podcasts, stuff to be done.
And it's all happening this week.
Although today I leave for the Netherlands,
there's a narrow casting conference tomorrow.
Graham has to view the company that I'm a shareholder in.
Flat screen company is one of the founding partners of this conference.
Is anything but a blogger con, right?
It's like the reverse of a blogger con where everyone who is a founder,
or paid to get the conference together,
gets to do their little commercial on stage.
So I'll be doing part of it for Graham has to view.
But also, I will be talking about podcasting.
And I'm really looking forward to it.
I've been working hard with the good friends of mine on a video presentation
of podcasting, which is always fun to present.
Podcasting, which is predominantly audio, right?
In a video context.
So it should be fun.
And today on the show to celebrate the continuing jury selection
of my cool Jackson and his trial.
And remember, I'm supporting Michael Jackson.
I don't know what the fuck the evidence is.
There may be 40,000 pages of testimony,
but I still have a real hard time believing all the allegations.
Clearly, Michael Jackson is under some severe pressure.
It needs a little bit of help there.
Just a little bit of support, you know?
The face known to millions is a superstar pop singer.
Now, we've also used as a mugshot at the Santa Barbara Sheriff's Department.
And we've also used as a mugshot at the Santa Barbara Sheriff's Department.
And we've used as a mugshot at the Santa Barbara Sheriff's Department.
And we've used CRRGs.
And when the blue's dead and gone
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
You know that love's a vibe
So he can run, run, run, run
Um, hey, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Um, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Uh, uh, yeah, yeah Yeah, yeah-yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Come on, come on
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
We don't write the line, baby
We don't tell each other, you know
Why don't you worry?
And I'll tell each other, you two care for
But if you belong to me, and you're the night
And I'll tell each other, to tell each other
Everything about ourselves, this is from us dance
This is our last dance, this is our song
I'm going on like this
Ooh, baby
This music career is on hold, this next record
I want to record the record
To be a criminal
Wow
Most excellent mashup really really enjoyed that one
Clearly it came from the UK
And a lot of people asked me to post these mashups online
Of course, I can't do that as you know, because
I mean, probably playing them as even
Very iffy when it comes to RIA and Ask Cap
And BMI
Of course, these types of records would probably never see the light of day
And in an official release because
Oh, it's just so much hassle to go through
To get all the rights to release them together
And, you know, it's a pain, so it's good that we can enjoy them
But I can't post them online
Although I do hope in the future
And we'll be able to do this with the OPML and show notes
And we'll have some type of system
Which have been thinking about quite a lot
And actually Drew's been working on it as well
From Dawn and Drew
To come up with the way where
Once it's in my show notes
Then you can also retrieve it automatically
If you want to grab it
So really just trying to cut out steps on the
Production side and also on the
You know, on the receiving side
So that if you like something that you hear in a show
That you should be able to, you know, get it
Fairly simply
Oh, man, excuse me, this sincerely
Or it's just really hit me today
Speaking of RIA
He's an email
Matthew, he says Adam thought you're going to kick out of this email
I'm
The guy from Muse
That's been harassing Bob Lefsits to get into podcast
And now Lefsits writes a very very influential newsletter
To all the top RIA industry types
So he
There's apparently this mailing list
That the RIA folks are all on
And I just wanted to read this
This too because it's it's pretty interesting
If this was the RIA
RIA folks
Are reading
Oh, man
How inconvenient to receive a phone call
This moment
Okay, let's switch that off
Okay
Let's see
Here we go, I'm hooked
I might have to download the software to pull all 70 shows on my iPod
But Dawn and Drew are just that riveting
Did you ever know anybody in love?
God, are you reading blank?
Freaks me right out
The part where they talk about where their marriage is going to last
The key element is
Contempt
Oh, it's very hard to read the signals
Oh, second
I just lost my place
Here we go
You've got to be a pro
But once you're glued in
You know that slight role of the eyeball
The slight brow lift that evidence
Evidence is contempt and the marriage is doomed
My marriage was doomed by contempt
My x-y was just too untogether
We'd get frustrated
Couldn't you please lock the door when you leave the house
I've got tens of thousands of dollars worth of shit in here
But as many times I mentioned
She always continued to leave the door unlocked
So then it goes in this whole thing about
Respect about marriage
And then finally we get to the meat of all this
It appears Dawn and Drew are in love
Or maybe it's just that I'm infatuated with Dawn
Maybe she really wears the pants
Maybe Drew is kind of passes
But Dawn is a dream, first and foremost
She's verbal
I hate the silent babes
Well silence drives me nuts
I want to be with someone who's got something to say
And I don't feel like an idiot when I come into
On the minutiae of my life
When I spin my theories, make my observations
Dawn can keep up her end of the conversation
But she's not the tactics
She's not overbearing she's kind of like
You know the kind of girlfriend you can't stop
Bumping into on the couch
They say stuff to bug you
The tiniest little bit to get under your skin
Just a little because you know that's why they're doing it
I want to slide your hip over and bumpers
An evidence of intimacy
As evidence of connection
You got to read this whole thing
I'm not going to go through all of it
But if this is indeed what they're reading about podcasting
They'll be all over it
And there's a lot of love
Dawn in this one
I just got to kick out the fact that the R-I-A-A is reading all these wonderful words
About the love between Dawn and Drew
Hey Adam
I thought it was Daily Source Corio
Dude
But I also know a lot of podcasts you ought to listen to
It's called the B-K-L-A podcast
So we're at B-K-L-A
That likes bad that can
I'm telling you right now
Listen to this show
Or hit you so high I'll kill your old family
Don't say it
I'll listen to it
If you notice
W-W-W dot curry dot com
There's now a Senseo coffee machine on the right hand side
I got a lot of email from people
After I was talking about wouldn't be great
If you had some easy way to set up a store
So when you talk about stuff on your podcast
People actually go and purchase that
And a number of people have purchased a number of different items
And if told me about it after listening to the source code
iPods, I-Rivers
Breakout boxes
Music
And Senseo machines
I granted not many
But I've certainly sold two or three
You know I got all these pointers
You know to Amazon the associate program with Amazon
And well it works
I signed up
You know got the code put it right there on my web log
So if you're hearing me slurping down this wonderful Senseo coffee
And wondering wow
Wouldn't be great if for like 50 or 60 bucks I could buy one of those for myself
Well now you can and so far I've sold
Zero Senseo's
I don't think even
Clicked on the link yet
Some more news in the show notes
Which of course a company the source code every single episode
There's also a way to make your own coffee pods
There are third party pod sites for different flavored coffee
For tea pods
And even to put other stuff in
In case you didn't just want to have coffee in there
Again all of that in the show notes
And if you're thinking of buying a Senseo
Let's see if we can prove the model
Let's see if you can click on the logo on my site
And actually purchase it through Amazon
Wouldn't that be grand
Daddy
This got real
Hey Adam this is David from the debate guide podcast
I've got a piece of trivia for you
Back in the 1930s both
Sigmund Freud and atheist
And CS Lewis a Christian
Resided in the London area
But most people don't know
Is that they used to get together
To drink beer and debate about the existence of God
They secretly met at a place down in Gilford
Which is known today as curry cottage
Here's a little advice
Neither of them like cheap trick
Oh
That's the cheap trick
I'll be falling off my wall
So Adam
You might think about storing your precious platinum album in a safe place
Anyway check out my podcast
That's debate god dot com
Debate god dot com
Okay
You know I got a lot of promo sent to me
MP3 feedback a gmail dot com
If you're wondering how I make the choices
Well, you know it's the creativity
And there are people that send in four or five minute promos
You know this like no way
I'm ever going to be able to get that on the air
No time to cut it down the size either
So the shorter the better
I do love promoting as many podcasts as possible
Because you know
Well, we got to promote them somewhere
And I let all the cross-pollumization actually is great
I was on the skinny on sports this weekend
On there you know the the fastest ten minutes on your iPod
That was great to be interviewed by the guys
They talked to me about
Stairroids and other forms of doping and about you know
What sports I used to play
I
You know even you should listen to the interview
The skinny on sports dot com
TSOS
You can find in the iPod dot org directory under the sports
No, of course
I'll tell you though that I did actually play a sport
When I was
Or participate in a sport
And a sport I should say when I was oh man
I'm thinking I was probably 1514
1314 at the time
And I was pretty damn good at it
The sport
Fencing
Adam this is Kevin C. Total KCT's digital world
And we got a serious problem
While I really appreciate the problem
When you play for my commute cast on your February first daily source code
I've taken a look at my feed burner stats
And there are people downloading this podcast
On iPod or SP
Yep, you know what that means
We've got folks that are listening to the commute cast
While driving on their smartphones
We can't have that
I don't know about you
But I certainly don't want to be
One of these folks wrapped themselves around a tree
While listening to the commute cast
So whatever you do
Please don't mention KCT
They do a world dot com
Or the commute cast ever again
In fact
Please tell me we're not to go to KCT's digital world dot com
Every Friday because that's why I upload the commute cast
We don't want that Adam
Can you help me out
Thanks
Yep, yep
Mum's the word dude
I totally promise
That is cool though
That I've seen a couple of those as well
Podcasts SP
So the handhelds are out there
And what's this is Microsoft coming out with the new phone that I saw
The call it was some I don't like the name P buddy
Why though is have these weird code names for everything
The P buddy phone
Of course it only conjures up images of cartoon characters
It doesn't really
And why P buddy he's a cartoon character right?
Yeah, I guess so
It's like okay
But I could get pretty exciting
I'm seeing more and more mobile
Mobile devices picking up the podcast
And more and more iPodders for mobile devices
Which is very cool
You can find those all at iPod.org by the way
Just look for the link on the left hand side
That's his download iPod
And people who are looking to get started in podcasting
Either receiving or transmitting
We have a documentation place
It's iPod.org slash docs
It's pretty much where I send everybody to
When they ask me how they get started
So iPod.org slash DOCS
And while we're on the topic of iPodders
To we're talking about Doppler
First of all the developers of Doppler
Doppler radio dot net
Two Dutch developers Cindy and Irwin
I was questioning their relationship on the show last Friday
Guess what they are a couple
They were even a couple before I mentioned it
So that's nice and I put a link to their little couple
Shot there of them scuba diving
And we've still had some problems with
Well not necessarily with Doppler radio
But with dot mac hosting
So if you're placing your MP3s
For your podcast on the dot mac infrastructure
Basically you're putting them on your eyed disk
We're still having problems
In fact let me just do the
I do a daily check a couple times a day
To see if they figured out they're caching
They're using these net cache
Boxes that essentially I guess kind of
What what they do they distribute the load
The problem is is hill and here it is
Let me just see if we're
Now still getting a invalid method
The problem is that they have
That probably about 20 of these boxes on their network
And most of them are I'm just going to call it
Misconfigured because they're not allowing a head request
Whenever you ask for head you want to get it immediately
The head request
Essentially feeds back a number of things
One of them is the size of the file that is about to be downloaded
And Doppler radio is actually very smart
Because it's asking for this size
So that it will know if it's downloaded the entire file
Which helps a lot with the resume will download
So if you break somewhere
If you're computer crashes or if you quit the program
The next time you turn it on it will say
Download it x amount of this file
It's this big so let me resume the download
So that is not working even worse
Since it can't get the size and this is maybe
I'm going to hate fucking hacking around this stuff
But you know that's one thing that we could do is we could say
Well if you can't get the size just download
No matter what that's one way around it
But essentially
Dot max stuff is kind of breaking the way the internet works
I mean these are protocols that are tried and tried and
True and relied upon by lots of applications
Not just podcasting
And in my particular case
Since I can't get used the head statement
I can't even attach it automatically
To my RSS feeds with the software I'm using
So it's definitely messing up a whole bunch of stuff
There are people aware at netcash
They know about it
But somewhere we're just not connecting
And so if you know anybody who has anything to do with dot mac
Or with their netcash
It is let them know on curie dot com
Of posted lots of information
It's basically one little option that has to be turned on
To turn off and maybe this is by choice
You know that's cool too but just let us know
So we're not waiting around because I'm already ordering
Ben with from somewhere else and lots of other people
Will be as well and it's just kind of a shame
Because it works so nicely with the mac and tosh
And I tested nimic
Another fact man there's a lot of Dutch iPotter development
I tested nimic and iM iQ
You can find that in the iPotter.org software directory as well
It's for windows only
Did that downstairs on that Christina's windows box under my own account
Of course
And I noticed something interesting there
It has an opml browser built right in
Which is although very cool
It doesn't follow the links
And if you look at the opml file
For the iPotter.org directory
40 to 50% of it
Is links to other opml files that are being handled by other people
It's a distributed directory
And it doesn't follow those
So even worse the links don't show up
So maybe the nimic guys could take it
I think it's ed by the way
I think ed does nimic
So we could take a look and see if we could figure out how to
Be able to follow the opml links
And we'll actually have the whole directory in there
Because what's happening now is
As more people are maintaining
Nodes of the directory
What you're seeing in nimic is getting smaller
And smaller looks like there's nothing left over
Because today and I just posted a announcement about that
We passed the 3000 podcast mark on iPotter.org
357 podcasts
In less than a year
What in less than nine months
Congratulations y'all
Hey Adam
This is Rina Marie from the band tracks podcast
Where we focus on independent pod safe music
And help artists sell their stuff in our online store at
Bantracks.net
Just wanted to thank you for playing the pod safe music
Trivia on last Thursday's show
And yes, I did know all the answers
Because I listened to the accident
Hasht pod cast every time it comes out
That's because accident hash and band tracks
Are part of the association of music podcasting
Or amp
Which we joined along with five other shows
Including in somnior radio
In over your head
Indy feed
And the 250 million dollar radio show
We thought it would be a great way to pool our resources
And get the word out for the thousands of great bands
You've probably never heard
Anyway, the trivia was a bit tough for you
And you asked for the songs to play
Instead of having to guess them
So here's a great unsigned artist out of New York City
Named Andrew Vladik with you can't kill time
courtesy of the band tracks podcast
We were going down living in old canoe
And when we had the rocks broken to you
Pull me out as I was tossed by
Lay my clothes on the banks to dry
But before I could thank you
I fell in again over the falls
And over hand woke up
And I pulled my own sweat
Another dream about regret
I did not foresee
You can't kill time
And feel
And sanity
Time to live
Only
Your vanity
We were driving through the desert
When the whole world the engines was melting
When we were two
All I could find was a dried oak creek
But you found a water bottle under the back scene
But before I could thank you
I liked it out of your hands
You watched it spilled out into the sand
Another rise bounced from view
Another dream about regret
I did not foresee
You can't kill time
And feel
And sanity
No, no
Time to live
Only
Your vanity
No
You're talking so to that
I'm north bare at somewhere inside
I try to uncover but I made a mouse
You listen to a crazy man, guess
Because I never could understand my gut
Wish I could have my trap shut
So many things I never did mention
Only have the best intentions
I did not foresee
Because you can't kill time
And feel
And sanity
No
Time to live
Only
Your vanity
No
Thanks again Adam
And you can find Andrew Vladik's self titled CD
In our online store at bandtracks.net
And check out our associations
Other great music podcasts at musicpodcasting.org
Wow, the association of music podcasts
I've seen that around
I think I read it on the podcast
I've seen it on the podcast
And I remember, I got to remember
I got to play some birdies this week
Together we're almost at the end of today Show
We've got to play some birdies
Getting ready for the big bitty cast
They've been recording all kinds of stuff
I'm really curious to see what they come up with
And then you know Leon is been in touch with me all over the past few weeks
And I said, actually. Sir, don't say
You guys are away
Let me see, still come
The head test
That's right, Moorth grows on you, and it's really growing this month with great savings
on our multi-TV food processor and our Tano Cycle System for only 99,99,99.
Plus visit our Megastar section and join our flavour flavour of the month club, Britney Swag,
Christina Agony, poop froggy frog, and dozens more of all your favourite brand new flavors.
Conveniently picked, categorized, homogenized, and whipped into a consumer-friendly, oops, what
was that?
Chin that's low-carbon, IQ-modulated, to make you look and feel like a teenager forever.
And you don't want to die to you, Moorth, it grows on you.
Moorth, it grows on you, go now at area51show.com.
Yeah, that's a kind of weird podcast.
Just listen to that.
It's production values are pretty good as you could tell from the promo.
It's pretty wacky.
I was turned on to it by Caleb from Florida, I think, Caleb, by the way, has an interesting
podcast.
He has the ex-drunk-alog, ex-drunk-alog.
He's a fabulous painter, and just has a lot of stories about being a former drunk.
Next week on the Creepy Sleepy Show, an interview with quite possibly the most controversial
figure in the last 7,000 years.
That's right, next week on the Creepy Sleepy Show, we have an interview with the Almighty
Herself.
We're going to be asking, the important point in question, such as, does the religious
write really represent him on earth?
It's George Stubby, a really predestined to be president.
Why did it send that crappy band creed to earth to do its work?
If marijuana is so horrible, why did you plant it everywhere?
Why are the secret 11 herbs and spices in Kentucky fried chicken?
Seriously, who's right?
These rallies were the Palestinians.
And most importantly, will old dirty bastards spend eternity in heaven?
These questions and more.
Next week on the Creepy Sleepy interview with...
Sunday night, Sunday night, Sunday night, Sunday night, Sunday night, that's when I got
a tune in.
I do.
It's podcasting.
I get to choose my own time that I listen to God.
Oh man, this is turning out to be a silly show.
So I kind of agreed with a lot of people who sent in email about trivia Thursday that
it was complete overkill.
Although, lots of people like different bits, it was like, okay, you know, no, let's not
do that.
Malcolm, Malcolm Owen sent me this email says, so trivia Thursday is now starting to
strain at the seams.
This means only one thing.
It's completely unpredictable.
Now, I'm a star.
For instance, karaoke Tuesday, mash up Friday, ski Sunday, knitting Wednesday, to
we Maguire Monday, Hustler Magazine Saturday, sponsored by Penthouse, and make Adam
eat bagels whilst doing the cha cha with a blow up doll Thursday.
Yes.
Oh, great ideas.
That kind of agreed.
That's our old school.
That's so, uh, so broadcast, you know, to have those kind of days.
I'm sorry.
Once the while I slip into old habits, which dive very, very hard, and of course, there's
new habits, which you just don't want to have die.
Oh, I'm casting with Adam Curry, my mama always said, the hit test was like a box
or chocolate.
You never know what you're going to get.
But I'm for Adam Curry to take the opportunity with y'all, hold it.
Hey, Adam.
Hey, buddy.
Here's the thin edition of the hit test.
Wait, it's a lustrum.
We must celebrate.
And if you're ready, we're going to start right away.
So here we go.
This is number one.
All right.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, it's magic.
There you go.
Pilot.
And this is number two.
Oh, well.
Yeah.
But this would be Patricia, when she was with a pet shop boys.
And number three.
Man, young, I can't wait to hear the answers.
Of course, it's Tony Katayn's ex-boyfriend David Copperdog with white snow.
And these are the answers.
Good luck, John.
Like it.
And so number one in today's hit test.
This is violence.
Yeah, magic.
Oh, oh, it's magic.
Big one hit wonder band from the 70s.
Played that one in ladies on one.
And the second answer, the pet shop boy, this is West End Girls.
Hey, two for two.
And the third and final answer, white snake.
Here I go again.
And we're going Tony Katayn was crawling all over the jar.
Boom!
Any round of music.
So walk, oh!
Weird, and yeah all on my own.
To conclude, the tenth edition of the hit test, feedback is welcome at hittest at gmail.com
and you can find them all through download at www.helpetense.nl slash hit test.
While I done that's it for today, see you next time for the next edition of the hit test.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate all the work as always.
Maybe we should do a little bit differently next time.
What if we did shorter clues?
But repeat the clue a couple times.
So maybe it's just a little snippet of the intro.
Because now it's like, I'm actually, I can hum along and sing along until I get it.
Just to make it harder for me and maybe even more fun for the audience interaction is play a snippet.
Play three times, maybe in a row.
So I could stop it and think about it and think about it with the audience.
And then obviously we'll go with the answers the same way you've done it.
But I love these hit tests, y'all.
Thank you very much.
Once again, hit test number 10 on your daily source code.
Wow.
That's almost 40 minutes for you.
I've got to pack my bags, get all my stuff together.
It's just a short overnight, but it still requires hair products.
By the way, not a lot of comments about the hair and the USA today picture.
I guess it wasn't all that bad.
Actually, I thought it was pretty hot, so.
Hey, comments.
Adam and Craig are comments.
You want to send an audio comment or some other promo or thoughts a music or whatever.
You can send it to MP3feedback at gmail.com.
For the latest source code and the archive and the podcast piece,
daily source code.com.
My weblog www.curry.com.
That's it.
I'm off on easy jet.
Remember, not just a passenger.
Also a vishareholder.
Have a great day.
I'll talk to you tomorrow from Holland.
Bye-bye everybody.