Good evening, ladies and gentlemen, this is the Saturday Night Special coming to you from
the Curry Condol.
It's San Francisco, California, tell us you're a Charlie, two, four, five.
Let's talk, talk, talk until you talk to yourself and to the ground with what, what, what,
until you've taken me and danced around this love love the one you never knew could be
found that stuck, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk,
we are walking on my tightrope of words and crossroads, and I hope that the words I
choose will come back to haunt you, I wish wish that you would listen the first time
time time because it would save us all of this, it's a crime crime crime that we're wasting
all this precious time time time time, we have talk, talk, talk, talk, you say I'm never
Sta pod, look at it this way, all of their say it's a good thing, babe that, let
That I started in the first place
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
But I thought I'd better, better, better, better, better
Let's talk, talk, talk, can tell you talk yourself into the ground that's walk walk walk
Until you've taken me around this town, skirting the issues, you knew it would come round soon
I wish you'd listen the first time through
I heard you said that twice before, yeah, I already said that twice before
I heard you said that twice before
I already said that twice before
Straight from the Podsafe music network, Cheryl B. Engelhardt
And talk, talk, talk, talk on the daily source code
It's not often that we meet each other on Saturday night
And I realized that if I were doing this over in the cottage
The cottage, then you probably would hear it Saturday night
Because I'd be eight hours ahead of the ball
So this may be Sunday for you, we hear this show
I'm back at the condo, I was in Vegas last night
And we didn't have a chance to speak on Friday, no show
I just got way too busy with people over visiting
Our office from out of town
And we had some stuff we were talking about with them
And I just took up time and didn't really have all the necessary time to do the show
And I find it sometimes very difficult to put a show together
If you have to fit it into a certain slot
It's like a go-paying to picture and do it between 130 and 3
It still is kind of a creative process, I think
But there's a lot to talk about
Because I really wanted to get it out while I was still fresh
And I was sitting here on the couch in the condo
I still haven't received the shipment from J.C. pennies
And don't even get me started on that crap
So I have candles burning everywhere
To basically keep the place kind of lit
But it's been beautiful night, I can see all of the city
I can see the marina, it's really quite a sight
And I find myself more and more in the situation
Where I'm thinking to myself and I'm talking kind of with my inner voice
I think and man, I should be podcasting almost all the time
That would be much more convenient than trying to remember all this cool stuff
Every second is like, oh yeah, I should talk about that
Oh, maybe I should talk about that
So I thought maybe what we do is we'd catch up on some email
Because there are two topics really that just prevail
And there's not a day that doesn't go by
They don't get 15 to 20 different comments on both the biodiesel
And biodiesel and that other thing
Oh yeah, the hate podcasts, but we've kind of closed that chapter, I think
Let's see, there was also, well, those have been some other interesting little tidbits in there
Oh, the sound advertising, of course
And it's interesting how many people have been anchored to different objects
Some of them are pretty interesting
So to make this show completely different
I was going to play just a couple of tunes
To mellow stuff or mellow stuff that I pulled off of the Podsake music network
Just kind of scouting around and there's an amazing array and variety of music
You kind of expect me to think independent, you think, well, there's going to be a lot of alternative rock and punk
See, what up? Well, I mean, and that's in there too, and actually a lot of it is very, very good
But if you're looking for jazz or hip hop or R&B, it's in there as well, it's definitely cool
And I've played, what I'll do is, I'll get all my thoughts together to tell you about the adventures and vagas
Which actually this morning, or what was it, it was around noon when I finally got up
And walked down to get some breakfast in downstairs in the casino eatery part of the wonderful Venetian hotel
I actually started doing a sound scene tour
And I got all the way, you know, I was playing some slots and it just didn't work for some reason
I think there was too much noise, there really was too much noise
I have to listen to the stuff that I did record and see if any of it is worthwhile and I'll play it for you
But right now, let's see, oh, yeah, this was a mashup that arts and make mark for mashuptown.com
It's called All Rocks Down, done by Unknown
So if you want more information on this, I'll let you guys know that I would have mashuptown.com
Saturday night, just chilling, catching up with y'all
I'm getting all the way, I'm getting all the way
i'm getting all the way, I'm getting all the way
I'm getting all the way
I'm getting all the way, I'm getting all the way
And I can't even go to the grocery store without someone's that clean, and I start with a clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean,
clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean
, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean,
clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, Clean, clean,welcome, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, fast, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean,ices, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean, clean,
Hey, look, it was a reason to go to Vegas, right?
The reason why is because Jamane Dupree was celebrating his 33rd birthday and was throwing
a, I would say, a medium to large scale party, I think 700 people were on the guest list.
And I was invited to go meet with these folks and then after that go to the party.
The meaning was, of course, about potsafe music and the version people, by the way, are very,
very cognizant of what podcasting is, but damn if anyone was listening to it, podcasting
that.
It's unbelievable.
So also, you know, I always say, what's your favorite podcast?
And, you know, usually it's, you know, if I were to ask, have you ever listened to a podcast
and say, oh, yeah, sure, you know, it's much easier to kind of play it off.
But if you say, what's your favorite podcast, then, you know, the person has to think for a second
before being able to answer and, you know, by then they probably realize that just
might as well be honest and say, I've never listened to one.
So there was one guy who he was pretty turned on.
He was switched on.
He, a younger guy who works for the label, but he, he's a junior guy.
And when it comes to, so that was really about, you know, what kind of broader distribution
can we get for some of our podsafe artists?
I mean, we're creating stars and there's hits here.
You know, this is, this is amazing.
There must be more avenues and more ways to distribute.
And of course, there are.
You know, that's basically what hip hop is these days.
It's all distribution deals.
It's really small record labels, which, of course, do grow big, some of them.
But they have distribution deals with the majors.
And that's a, it's a, it's a pretty fair way of doing things I have to say.
And it's a very successful part of the music business, probably one of the most successful.
So the other part of the topic of conversation was the reverse, you know, can we play some
of your music on our shows?
And I was interesting, everyone's like, yeah, that's great.
You know, fantastic.
Of course, we should do that.
So it'd be good to realize that there's a, there's probably an issue about that.
And you know, the lawyers may take may, may not agree.
And all of them assured me that didn't seem like that would be too much of a problem.
So we'll see.
And then the party was held in the Venetian hotel where I was staying as well.
And, uh, yeah, there was a dress code.
It was a 50s and 60s rat pack.
And I didn't have my rat pack outfit with me, unfortunately.
So mad dashed to go find a black jacket and a bow tie and a hat, yeah, I have a picture
somewhere.
I'll get around to putting that up eventually.
And yeah, so the party started out in like 10 or 11 or something like that, but really
didn't start it until around midnight when people really started coming in.
And I felt like it was in a music video.
It was, it was unreal.
It was a very classy, beautiful, you know, separate room of this, you know, really for
private functions of this club in the Venetian hotel, T-A-O, I think it is yet tau.
And it was an R&B video.
I'm telling you, that's exactly what it was.
You know, the way the tables were said beautifully.
They were nice couches.
There was a great DJ, man, I don't, I didn't get his name, but he was awesome.
It was loud, you know, so conversation was still kind of possible.
You could drink anything open bar, just tons and tons of orders and stuff.
And, you know, it's like some real major people from the music industry, some of them
who, who I knew a lot, I didn't.
And just all kinds of types of people.
And I was just like, whoa, I'm just going to sit here and observe.
And actually I wrote down a couple of the names I wouldn't forget.
Usher, usher, very, very laid back guy, he and his wife were there, Nelly, let's see, who
else was there.
Oh, no, what's interesting is, everyone's smoking cigars.
Every single one of these guys is smoking cigars.
In fact, the thing now is you have to walk around with either a box, so, you know, just
like the one you buy in the cigar store, a box of Cubans.
So there's, you know, some people walking around with a box of Cohibas, or you have your
ostrich skin, ostrich skin leather, portable humidor box with your cigars in it, with
your selection of cigars.
And man, you got a puff on those suckers, a lot of cigars smoking going on.
I was one of 10 white people there.
I should, I should point out, which makes no difference, but it was, just totally, totally,
totally different world.
I've not been in the R&B and hip hop world at all.
Shug Night walked in, I'm telling you, I was in a video clip, I'm like, you know, what's
next to Poc and Biggie come walking in?
Oh, yeah, one point, so it may be like 10 of us sitting in one of these tables and kind
of the booth and, you know, two huge body guards or guard, like security guards, I should
say, come over and say, hey, can we ask you to clear out this space because Michael Jordan's
coming?
I'm like, well, that's a cool party.
I said, yeah, I'll bow down to Mike, he never showed up, by the way, that corner was
cleared out for the entire night and Michael Jordan never showed.
And nor did Jermaine debris actually, he didn't come in until, like, 1-15 or 1-30 and
I was not, not too early before I left, but that Paris Hilton came in with her hiltonets
that's like five or six girls, all little Paris, you know, kind of looking girlies.
And I have to say that she's, it's kind of sad when you see what she's doing.
I mean, no one's paying attention to her, I'm really no one, or more than, oh, there's,
you know, there's that Paris Hilton woman, and she came in, she immediately walked around
the entire joint with her cell phone to her left ear, which clearly she was not really
talking to anyone.
It's almost like her shield, or, you know, whatever she has, or just something, like
it's almost like sucking your thumb, I guess, maybe it's her security blanket.
And then she and the, and the Hiltonets got up on, on a couch, you know, and danced, and of
course, there were photographers there and a couple of TV crews.
And it was kind of, you know, just like, I don't know, the thing was, no one was really
paying attention to her, and, you know, wherever the cameras were, she'd kind of move in
and then she'd just start dancing in front of the cameras, it's the weirdest thing.
It really is.
She smells great, though.
Yeah.
She was walking by and she stopped kind of near me and I'm like, I love sniffing women.
You can only do that when you're talking, like me.
Okay.
I'll tell you about some of the other guests who showed up, play a song first.
It's another one for the, off of the podcast music network, Carmen Tyler, I played a cover
version that she did.
I don't know, this may be a cover as well, I'm not too sure, but it showed up on the
podcast music network.
I'm like, okay, I do like the way she sounds.
She was a saturday night special, the daily source code, just chilling.
This is make believe.
Only make believe.
I love you.
Only make believe that you're lovely.
Others find peace of mind and pre-tending.
Couldn't you?
Couldn't I?
Maybe my lips are blending in a fancy kiss or two or three might as well make believe
I love you, for to tell the truth how to, though the cold and brutal fact is, you and
I have never met.
We need not mind each other's peace and cues.
If we put our thoughts in practice, we could banish our regret.
Imagine we most, anything we choose, we could make believe, I love you.
Only make believe that you're lovely.
Others find peace of mind and pre-tending.
Couldn't you?
Couldn't I?
Wouldn't you?
Couldn't you?
to
H
Carmen Tyler make believe on daily source code 2 4 5 the date is September 24th Saturday
Just
Getting back to the germane to pre-party who did eventually show up and a janitor as well. He's a he and janjax and lived together for I don't know
Five six years maybe
Samuel L. Jackson was there men. He's a party animal that guy is damn oh man
Sam gets down and he shaved off all the facial hair and he looks really good after say
It was really really good
And
Let me see L. A read
Was there these just all the people I recognized. Oh yeah, and then
So you know, fashionably late, but perfect timing is always Mariah Carey comes in
And she has a some kind of massive bling watch that she that she gave to germane
And so of course immediately cameras going off and everyone huddling around that and
But it was completely just a music video. It was awesome
And there was me you know six foot four white guy with a freaking black hat on with a white band and a black bow tie
So anyway, I left around one thirty quarter two
That and it went on until like five like now
Man, I'm just way too old for that and besides I want to go I want to go back home
I want to go back to my girls
It's it's not so much being away from each other
It's the time difference that is just such a killer eight hour time difference so
You know, we're on the exact opposite ends of
The body clock you know when I'm just getting up she's winding down and vice versa
And you know, so some I mean it's like I could wait until midnight
And then you know that's 8 a.m. and she's getting Christina off and so then after
Wait until 1 a.m. you know that it's 9 for her and
And then I'd be like dead tired. It's just very weird
So I'm going to go home at the end of the week and I'm very much looking forward to that
I'm wondering what I should do with all this email
And I maybe I should just put a stop behind all of the topics that we've been discussing
Because I read it all I love all these comments on on this on the sound
Vertizing on the bio diesel
I mean I have so many different
You know sources now to go to I'm really going to do that by the way
I am getting a diesel and I am going to run it on you know vegetable oil or
Whatever
I
Totally believe that's the way to go
We've just been marketed away from from the obvious the obvious other natural resource that we have
I think we can grow it
What what a concept we've got farmers in this country they can grow our fuel
But I don't know if you can grow enough of it fast enough
You know we seem to need
Was it 20 million barrels a day or something like that maybe it would be more unbelievable
Oh
God this I really did want you to hear this you know that jet blue plane
Um
That landed at LAX
Oh my my iTunes here so it might what's that oh yeah
I have the window open to give us some sometimes a fire truck goes by it's perfect San Francisco sounds
Um
So there was a jet blue aircraft and this was earlier in the week that
How did it made an emergency landing at Los Angeles International Airport
And the reason why is because although all his gear was down his nose wheel was down
Um but the wheels were turned 90 degrees
So you know that's probably the worst uh
They don't roll very well if they turn 90 degrees
And uh there was a lot more behind this entire story
Uh of what you know what went on because this was clearly a maintenance issue and you know
Well there was there was some pilots up there who were uh doing a damn good job of uh getting
Information figuring out um you know what they were going to do
And uh
Recorded some of the air traffic control
Conversation between ATC and the pilots of the jet blue flight and he put it out
Um on Friday
And it's uh I don't have a queue to up hold on a second let me just uh
I love their cheer
That's so cool
That actually fits. Yeah, let him explain
Come on in the next episode eight and a half of fly with me
I'm Joe Dion and I'm a short addition to episode eight for you
I usually wait to have a whole show put together before I put something up
But something happened yesterday that I was able to catch at least partially on tape
And I thought you'd like to hear it
It actually relates better to an upcoming episode I'm planning
About the responsibilities of being captain
And I've spoken to a number of experienced captains about their philosophies
What it takes to be a good captain and one piece of advice that keeps coming up
Is don't let people talk you into a decision that is not your own
I've been told that the people around you who are offering you suggestions and information
Are always acting in good faith
But they're not necessarily onboard the aircraft with you and they don't necessarily have to live with the decision you make
As captain you have to live with the decision
Listen to this event as it unfolds and hear how this captain keeps on top of the situation
And how he tries to get the best information possible before he goes and makes up his mind
Off a fair bag
We expand the landing to the air shock absorber's pulse
It shows maximum speed 280.67 the landing gear is currently down. I have three grades
I'm also showing the wheel, nose wheel, steering pulse
I have reference to the up top
It tells me not to retract the gear
It also tells me that there's a possibility that the nose gear is candid 90 degrees
Ball off center
This is the same anomaly that occurred with 5.03
Do you copy so far?
Over
Standby is like a weekend figure out a close-up action for you
Okay, thank you so much
The aircraft is pretty similar to the FCA
It was written up and it was signed off
Do you want to look back at that
So anyway, what do you just said there by the way that the aircraft has experienced that yesterday
And it's been signed off that means that the mechanic signed off that the problem was fixed
And someone's getting their ass fired over that
I probably worse worse than that you get in the trouble with the FAA
So definitely go listen to the fly with me episode 8.5
That's just phenomenal stuff
And no one has that audio I haven't seen or heard any news media talking about it
And it's great stuff
And just when you listen to the captain of the airplane, he's really got a shit together
And he's really really smart
And you have to listen to it
So well worth it
Let me see
What else did I have
It was cool
Oh
If there was anything
I had the wiki stuff
For the show notes for the daily source code
I requested that we all kind of look at the idea for a wiki for show notes
So everyone could contribute
And part of the reason is all this email
If we could have people putting stuff on up on a wiki then
You know, you would basically have all of that
That info as well
It's funny stuff too
It's really really cool
They write to me, you know, they would write it on the wiki
Maybe because it's not just like comments on a on a web log
But it's more of a
Collaborate into in the notes as we go along
Good point about not having the show notes
In the RSS feed because they would basically be posted later
I have an idea for that
But you know, we'll we'll get to that bridge
Eventually first let's see if we can figure just get the show notes going
Alrighty, let's play another song
Ah yes, of course
This is
Hmm
It's my baby
It's my baby Patricia
One of my favorite soundtrack
Come on baby
I've got you
Under my skin
Deep in the heart of me
So deep in my heart
That you're really a part of me
I've got you
Under my skin
I've tried so
And not to give in
I sat to myself as a fan
Never will go so well
But why should I try to resist
Baby, I know so well
I've got you
Under my skin
I sacrificed everything
Come on my foot is sick
I've had an unirienced battle
The war in the world
The calm's in the night
The repeats and repeats in my head
Don't you know
No little fool
You never can win
You're your mentality
Wake up your reality
Let's go
I sacrificed anything
Come with my foot is sick
I've had an unirienced battle
We're inspired to warn and voice
It comes in the night every piece I want
You can't see my ears
Don't you know it all for
You never can win
You show mentality
Wake up to reality
But each time that I do just the thought of you
I'll make me stop before I begin
Because I've got you
Under my skin
And I feel you
And please stay there
Under my skin
Where is your baby?
Patricia Pai
That's her dad's band by the way
His big band
Her dad is 80
And so are most of the guys in the band
In fact when they were recording
They were doing like a mini CD
Four tracks
This is maybe like four years ago
You know it would say
Hey, where's Pete?
And on that piece having Andrew done today
He'll be here next week
That's amazing
Well, this was kind of fun
And it's funny because
It's only been 33 minutes
I thought it would be much longer
Even with the songs in there
Wow, cool
Then why don't I play
See if I can play just one last
Let's do a non-pod safe
Let's break the rules
Yeah
Stick it to the man
Oh man
Something I've been going around
Am I head all day?
I think I have it here
I don't know ready
So this actually might work for you
On a Sunday morning
If you're
That's because that of course is when you're going to be listening to this podcast
Okay, here we go
Yeah, and I won't come back after this
I'll just play this song
So if you don't like it then
Then you can just go to the next track
Go to the next podcast
Hey, I'll talk to you in Monday
Everybody have a great Sunday
And God bless
I see us in the park
Throwing the summer days
Of imagination in my head
And words from my heart
I don't need to do the winds
Baby, I don't need say
I don't wanna go
You wear my travel
But there's so much love
Then next week
And the sea of life
Yes, I'm about to love
The night is about to die
On a wall
We lay beneath stars
One day I love a street
That's seen through the eyes of my mind
And I reach out for the far
Of me that lives in you
And only your two hearts can find
But I don't wanna go
You wear my travel
But there's so much love
Then next week
And the sea of life
But there's so much love
Then next week
And the sea of life
Yes, I'm about to love
You wear my travel
But there's so much love
Then next week
And the sea of life
Now I know I said I wouldn't come back
But
So those who shut all the head
Won't hear this now
Will they?
It'll be our dirty little secret
I was just gonna say
As an afterthought
Those exact from the record company
You know what really turned them on about podcasting
It wasn't the freedom of it all
Yeah, that was all right
That was kind of interesting
What was the number one thing that turned them on
Is the numbers of listeners
And they're just like, what?
How many people?
They could not believe it
All right, I'm out
Another pod show pod guest
Stick it in your ear