10. Delta Shiaracharli, 2. 6. 4.
Hey, you a date is now. Friday!
1. Hit, free, no, it's Friday.
3. No, it's all right.
There are no secrets.
Only information you don't get out of it.
Adam Curry.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
October 21st, the year of our Lord is 2005. Good morning.
How you doing? We made it Friday.
Almost did a show every single day this week.
I am so proud of us.
Once again from a foggy northern California morning.
I'm sure the sun will start to burn it off soon enough.
It is your daily source code and it is Friday.
Happy birthday to my niece, Roxy.
She turns 23 years old today.
I know she and her mom listened to the show almost religiously.
So although, of course, by the time she's hearing this,
the day is almost over with the frickin' time difference.
Oh, man. Hey, guess what? I have a bed.
We actually had little Chinese food bed assembly party here last night.
Ron and his lovely wife Martha came over and I haven't slept this well in ages.
I can tell you though, man.
There's a lot of work that goes in the putting a bed together.
But once you've got the frame kind of down and understand where the cross pieces go
and you've kind of out, you know, all your little bolts and wing nuts
and slick and lock in the new hikies.
I'm good with motorized things, like engines.
But when it comes to putting pieces of steel together, no, no, not all I do.
So of course, forget pictures.
I got to do a video cast from here.
So seeing as the new power works are out, that means shopping this weekend.
I'm going to get me a G5.
I'm back, one of those dual processor jobs and a brand new power book.
And then we'll do a video podcast from the Curry Kondo.
Kick it off though with a wonderful mashup.
Check this out.
That's it.
We're going hard.
And you know, we don't give up.
There's a lot of work there.
Go find me in the club.
Find it for the book.
My mouth.
I want you to need it.
You can fill the balls.
I'm gonna have the same sign.
And make it love.
So come give me a hug.
You can give me a hug.
You can find me in the club.
Find it for the book.
My mouth.
I want you to need it.
You can fill the balls.
I'm gonna have the same sign.
You can make it love.
So come give me a hug.
You can give me a hug.
I'm gonna draw my mama punch.
So come give me a hug.
Actually it came from a new source. I should mention who that came from home on a second. Let me just see if I can find it
Naina oops, Naina
Naina should be enough in Gmail to pick it up, right? Let's see if it gets it. Oh, here we go
Dice Van Tinnon. Let me just see what his email says here. I made a mashup of Naina's 99
Loved balloons of 50 cents in the club a friend of mine suggested I send it to you as an idea for your podcast. Yeah, fantastic
Thanks, thank you very much. So he's he's from the Netherlands
Where a lot of the new music has always come from at least as it comes to stuff that's done with technology and remixed and comes out of keyboards
A lot of the house scene really grew up in the Netherlands. Hey, man, look at all the DJs we got from there. Huh DJ Tiesto
Man, I used to work with
Roland Molendack back in the day. He's big now in the club scene
So let me tell you right up front
First like have different headphones on so I got to kind of get used to the sound
I think yesterday the one of these these white ones these Mac alley headphones, which are nice because they're
They're also noise reducing headsets. I think I blew out the left and the left earpiece all it all you hear in your left ear
Like
And how blown out yours
So gotta get used to this sound. This is a this is actually a very nice one. These are
JVCs also noise cancelling, but I don't put the noise cancelling on because that is very distracting today's source code
It's Friday
Lots of sex in today's show so if you're easily offended or if they're young children around keep them away from the show today
And not just you know not porn well, maybe a little bit of porn, but really
I guess I made a prediction
When the video iPod came out, you know the first thing I thought was uh-huh JOP and
That's a
A term I coined oh five years ago the JOP that's what the internet needs JOP stands for jerk off platform
I should try building that believe it or not
But it seems that the video iPod just may become the JOP and I predict that actually
It was interesting because I said that on the source code was picked up on a whole different
Told bunch of different new sources like AP picked it up, you know the the pod father predicts the new video iPod will be great for porn
Well, maybe I should have re-specified maybe I should have said
Relationships that would have been better because this is totally going to make it for
Dating anyway you want to get in touch with someone
But also I can totally see RSS feeds of
Products coming off of eBay, I mean you can go on and on and people are really experimenting with this
So it's extremely cool to see what's going on and oh yeah
Within not just a week of of the release of the or two weeks of the release of the video iPod we have POV pod dot com
POV stand. It's a that's a a cinemat cinemat cinemat cinemat cinemat cinemat
That's a term they're using the moving making business call POV
Point of view
So if you're thinking of actually I should look at this website because they have instructions
Well, you're supposed to do as you're supposed to
Subscribe when you bring it up here POV pod dot com you're supposed to subscribe to their feed
Actually, they here it is
Okay, yes, I agree sexual content. Okay
POV pod dot com step one
And this is really funny they have like little iTunes character, you know
It's always a silhouette of someone and you see the white headphones and the white iPod
So there's a guy sitting on a on a an office chair
As a step one download our videos to your iPod through iTunes six you can subscribe actually two hold iPod at crotch level
Three watch our point of view video and feel like you're there
So I thought we'd now mega sag is great. It should play the the video there we go
Huh
This is amazing so what I'm looking at is and actually I think the French I don't know where these movies are coming from but I don't think they were made specifically for POV pod dot com
Which is kind of disappointing because what you what you kind of want is
You know you'd want to hear some dialogue or something's very specific to this fabulous new invention of point of view
Poenography and so they're all they're all French
French actors and
You can kind of hear what's going on. Okay, now let me see if I can stop this
There we go
So you might want to check that out. It's clearly where things and once you get video, you know that's
When we got pictures what was the first thing that happened on the internet you know well the first thing that happened is
People told Mark Andreason that he was going to kill the net because pictures were going to pollute everything
And of course that may be true, but I think it's a much richer experience now
Yesterday I played a promo for you from Pacific Coast Hellway. They were so excited
Mark and the Pacific Hell Coast players that they had finally I mean it's listening
He's got like 13 years old finally they had gotten Sarah the 21-year-old virgin to call into their comment line
And to produce say what do you call it a self in he can't even say masturbation a self-induced orgasm and I must say the promo was great
The whole you know the whole build up to this one and a half minute piece of audio was fantastic
Well, it was a little bit disappointing about it though is they went straight into I don't know if if there was any pre-amble to the call
I would have liked to have here
Hey Chris
Yeah, because you're on the show. Yeah, yeah
What
Yeah, can I can I call you back in like half an hour and we can talk about that?
Okay
Okay, bye
I'm a such high demand
But you see we do break for we do break for work
Okay, so a little bit disappointing that
We didn't have
The kind of like pre-amble to when she first called into the voice mail system or the neo left her her voice message
So that was a bit of a bummer
But of course the whole it sounded pretty realistic and that was cool so that was a and of course
You never want to see what she looks like we never want we don't want to know anything more
It's so cool just to hear some audio and kind of let your fantasy go about you know
What Sarah the 21-year-old virgin looks like so anyway
They built this up as the first orgasm on a podcast and I promptly received some audio feedback
From Melissa and Melissa is from San Francisco and I it's amazing that I never found her podcast before
She also never sent into promo and said this is the first time she's ever
Don't eat any type of audio promotional stuff for her podcast called the horror cast
I don't be thrown off immediately by the title because
Melissa is
Well, let me just play the feedback for you and then we'll talk about it. Hold on. Here comes
Hello Adam. This is Melissa Sharif. I'm San Francisco
of the podcast or cast at sacredhor.org
And tonight I was waiting for MUNI probably not too far from curry condo itself
And I was listening of course to daily source code for October 20, 2005 in which
Of course, I'm one of your promos you promised the orgasm of a 21-year-old virgin
So now I know Adam something about you
Oh podcast with orgasms. Well, I have just the thing in February of 2005
I believe I became responsible for the first orgasm to be delivered by RSS
In the form of a podcast of course, I'm gonna start sleeping in the bed here and just let it fade out for all of you
Only rejoign only without for waiting
for the scenario you saw in the study
or in the last we moved the pages of Herodis
Sebastian you
dreams and to build3% in
You want to hear the rest, you can visit SacredHorror.org, thank you Adam, I've been
a much warmer night.
So, obviously I didn't go and check that out, I'm not going to go to any website to
listen to that.
So, I did check out Melissa's website, she's a podcast, interesting, she does one podcast
a month, and she really is exploring sexuality, this is not about porn, although it is, of
course, in a way, also about porn, which is a part of sexuality, but very, very interesting,
interesting podcast, interesting experiments, participatory experiments that she's getting
her listeners into.
So, I'm going to keep my eye on this one.
This is someone doing something completely new, and it really works because she's focusing
on the audio of it.
I don't think at all that she's interested in all about the video, she's probably done
enough video in her life, that this is something new, and I got to tell you, the more I see
video of podcasters, the less I like it, and it's purely because you build up some kind
of visual, you build up an image of what someone looks like, what their surroundings are,
for instance, well, let's take the Pacific Coast Hellwife, for example, so Mark always talks
about being in the studio three series or three series studio, so I guess he has a BMW
three series, so I immediately have a car in my imagination, and I can kind of visualize what
he may or may not look like, where he has his microphone and where he's driving, you know,
if he really, he may not even be driving, I don't know, it certainly sounds realistic
enough, but then sometimes I think, maybe that's just done in the studio, but it
doesn't matter, it's all my imagination, it's like reading a book, you know, it really
makes my mind work, and the minute you add video to it, although the initial excitement
just about, hey, wait a minute, someone created a video and now I can watch it and it
comes in automatically, and all that's extremely cool, but it does take away all of
those elements of, yeah, have imagination, so I'm kind of torn between all this stuff,
for instance, he'll all get, here's an experiment, this is what we're going to do, this
is a good one, since this is Friday, I want you all to think about what the Curry condo looks
like, where I am, what I'm doing the show, what I'm wearing, what the view is like, just,
you know, all the things that you've heard in the past couple of shows when we've been
talking, we're doing this from the condo, and then on Monday, if not over the weekend, but
maybe I will do it over the weekend, anyway, once I want to get the new machines in here,
let's just say, I got to get those guys to pay me to do that. So either over the weekend, depending
on the time in the setup, or certainly on Monday's daily source code, I'll do a companion video
podcast, because I'll have enough machines to be able to record it properly, and then, you
have to kind of think, how could you, it'd be nice if you could draw a schematic, maybe that's
an interesting way to do a draw a schematic of the living room in the kitchen, because I'm podcasting
from kind of both, so I think I've discussed many times what the setup is here, so maybe you just
draw a schematic, and then compare that to what you actually see, and then I want to know if
you were disappointed or not, or if the mistake is thing, I think the mistake actually goes away,
that's what it is. You know, many times I've been asked my magazines, you know, can they
or television shows, you know, we want to, we want to be there when you're doing the podcast,
want to take pictures, want to take a video, and I'm like, no, you know, you take away all the magic,
you know, the sound that I'm creating, that's the visual that I want you to have.
So I'm just being a little careful on the video stuff, but I do want to experiment with it,
I really do, so I hope you'll join me for that. Hi Adam, it's Andy here driving around in the
mojo crash mobile unit on a beautiful UK autumn day, listening to the daily source code on the
iPod. It just occurred to me that today is my one year anniversary of first hearing the daily source code,
and I haven't missed the day, and I have to say when I first heard you, I thought,
ooh, that Adam is a bit of a cheese monkey, he's a bit of a medallion man, you know what I mean?
I'm telling on me, to the extent that now if you miss a show, I mean a medallion man,
what the hell is that? A medallion man, it doesn't sound very good, feel a sense of loss,
a profound sense of loss, and if somebody burps, I think of senseo, so thanks a bunch for that.
I use it, I'm demotivating it, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah. Yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Thank you very much for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next
video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see
you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the last video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video, I'll see you in the next video,
Dope sound system, album, music.podshow.com is where you can find all kinds of music, not
just indie rock or alternative.
There's even classical music showing up now, which, and I'm not, it has to be synthesized
or orchestration that I'm hearing, but it's, it's pretty damn good, it's just a humane.
Well, you know, I can go on and on about all the great music that's coming out of the
podsake music network.
Some good news that is starting to reach me about my quest for a new car to run on biodiesel.
So it seems like a lot, you know, Volkswagen who do have an interesting diesel automobiles.
And it's not the new facade, I've been looking at that, because you know, I've got the Audi A8,
but that's way overqualified for the mission.
So I want to get rid of that at the end of the year.
And I was, and I looked at the facade, it's interesting, they have, they've really, they're
really taking a whole different tag on, you know, what a car should have, and they have
all these, you know, little special lights and little places to put stuff and, and is it
the facade that has the, the chilled glove box, so you can put your fresh sushi in there
and chill it on the way before you consume it.
So that looks kind of cool.
That looks like a nice car.
D on something smaller, I'm looking definitely looking for something a bit smaller.
And of course Volkswagen and Audi, virtually the same company or automobiles, I presume.
So if, of course, it won't have the, the quattro, the all-wheel drive, which I like
so much, particularly for the, for the winter months.
And then I was watching a commercial that came by yesterday on the new TV for the Ford Motor
Company.
And man, they're doing a lot, in fact, they're whole push now, as you saw the, the chairman,
the CEO and chairman, Mr Ford himself, who, of course, is a, I guess, grandson of Greg
Ransson of, that must be Greg Ransson of, of the original Henry Ford.
And he was really saying that, you know, we're pushing towards less dependency on foreign
oil.
And they're talking about their hybrid engines, their ethanol.
And in fact, they were coming out with an SUV that runs on ethanol, diesel or biodiesel.
Like, wow, you know, they're, that, now that's an American company who just doesn't
take any shit when someone tries to put the squeeze on us for oil, I'm loving that.
Of course, it's going to be interesting to see, you know, how that, how that moves along
with the interest of big oil, because big oil and big automobile companies do kind of
go hand in hand.
So, um, but that's a very positive, very positive change.
I'm excited about that.
So, still looking forward to seeing if we can get some kind of deal together, where under
supervision of the manufacturer, obviously, I mean, this would be one huge promotion.
And of course, it would be a lot of fun for me because, you know, I love doing shit from,
you know, from cars.
No problem.
We've done plenty of podcasts from the car, but now I want to learn how to do this biodiesel
thing.
You know, I want to learn, and I want to pass this information along so that we indeed
will not be dependent upon foreign oil.
So, all righty, uh, what else do we have to, oh, we got so much stuff to talk about.
Let's, let's open the door and let our friend Jan in for a second.
Come on, Jan.
Hello.
Oh, no, here I come.
Oh, I'm proud of you casting with Adam Curry.
Hey, Adam, are you ready to be stumps?
Oh, yeah.
Cause he used that little test with the iPhone X.
Hey, Adam, this is a new hit test, it's number 68, and I guess it's a bit more difficult
because they are a bit shorter than usual.
So, here we go.
This is number one.
Uh, oh, I know that one.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, it's Alan Parsons project.
I don't know.
And number two.
Easy.
Okay.
And he's self-respecting DJ from the 80s would recognize foreigners called as eyes.
Number three.
That's either, it could be, he's so shy, no, that's just, uh, I want to talk about it.
And this is the first answer in today's hit test.
The song from 1982, this is the Ellen Parsons project, this is old and wise.
And I love it as far as my eyes can see.
There are shadows surrounding me.
When I move the wise, when they ask you, if you knew it, remember that you were a friend of mine.
As the fire of the earth on the floor, with all my eyes, oh, when I move the wise.
Answer number one, the Ellen Parsons project, and this is answer number two, foreigner.
This is cold in size.
You're as cold as ice.
You're willing to sacrifice our love.
You never take advice.
Someday you'll pay the price I know.
I've seen it before, it happened all the time.
You're lonely, but no, you leave the world behind.
You're thinking of a goal.
You're going away.
From 1977, foreigners answered number two.
And this is a certain final answer for today's hit test.
From 1979, chic, I want your love.
Can you tell I'm going through relationship crisis?
No, you don't say it.
Okay, that's it for today.
Don't forget to check out the iTunes links on the website if you want to buy some of the tracks.
And I hope you did well and had them all at them.
So, thanks for playing this one. See you next time.
For number 69. So until then, bye-bye.
With your relationship problems, I'm expecting episode 69 to be something incredibly special, my friend.
Part-time music.
And to round someone else.
Don't know, you don't show the way.
Don't know, someone like me.
It is the way you live in your chest.
I'll say I will not keep you wrong.
But you've been wasting all your time.
I'm poor as you don't say that.
You should know that it's the way.
One leg and one leg and one leg.
You're the first of them all.
It's a baby don't be so tight.
Don't know, you don't show the way.
Don't know, someone like me.
Someone like me.
It's the way you live in your chest.
Don't know, someone like me.
Someone like me.
You're the first of them all.
It's the way you live in your chest.
Don't know, you don't show the way.
You're the first of them all.
That's the way we're in your chest.
San Francisco, Grittle, the Ferris of the Mall,
Pot's Same, from the Pot's Same Music Network
on the Friday edition of the Daily Source Code.
Hey, I got great news to report.
Yesterday, we had a couple of meetings
at the Pot Show HQ and the radio professionals
are now here.
They're showing up at our door of these are people
who are very, very excited about the opportunities
in podcasting.
We're talking all about the content side, OK?
Because remember, Pot Show is still about listeners.
So we're about getting great stuff to listeners
and great stuff comes from passionate and talented people.
And there are just thousands of them
in the radio industry.
Many of them without work.
Many of them who've given up on the radio industry
and who are now coming back and they're starting
to show up at our door.
And I can't, man, I could not be happier.
Because here it is.
We've pissed everyone off, at least clear channel has
and other large conglomerates, not just the listeners,
but also the people who've been doing the work all these years,
who you've commoditized down to card pushers.
They're ready.
They're coming in and they're showing up at our door
because in order to do this, you got to be able to eat.
So I think we're going to see some restart of some careers
and not just people who are behind the microphone,
but engineers, producers, writers,
it's, I think it's going to be fantastic.
So I just want to let you know that that's what happened yesterday.
Today, see what do we have?
Well, today we have the second, is it the second
Fubar Friday, this is a cultural phenomenon
that has started within the Podgeo offices, Friday afternoon,
Fubar Friday, we get together, we hang out,
we have drinks, we present what we're working on,
what we're thinking of, and just generally have a good time.
And I've joined via IChat previously,
which of course puts the Fubar Friday well into Saturday morning
for me with the time difference.
So I'm looking forward to celebrating
with the boys and girls this afternoon.
And there's something wrong here with Nengaseg.
It's being a little shitty on that.
Oh, my God, it says it's there.
Hello, almighty and most omnipotent part of it.
There's my song.
We approach you with a most unworthy request.
We ask you to bless us with your wonderful powers of promotion
and play this promo of a podcast,
free by and intended for those of us
who can never hope to raise to your levels of greatness.
We ask you to play this for the ordinary average guy.
Hi, this is Bob Bickler from the ordinary average guy podcast.
Our podcast is all about how the average joes,
so in this case, the Fphops live their lives.
Sports, work, TV, tech, watching kids.
Just about 80 else in ordinary average guy deals with
on a day-to-day basis.
Throw in some pot-safe music, a few mash-up,
and lots of new Jersey humor.
And you have podcasts.
Find out more, visit www.oagkask.com.
Thanks, Adam.
Hot show, content that will make you squeeze the dog
and burp your mother.
In a world where everything is nothing as it seems.
In your stock, with a network engineer,
it a hard-tricking generator, and it's Halloween.
Join us as we present the server room of horrors.
What secrets lurk in your server room?
This is a friends-in-tech production.
www.friends-in-tech.com.
I like that as a new network of podcasts.
There's fit.
The friends-in-tech sounds like they got something cool going on there.
And indeed, Halloween's coming up.
One of the things, if you go anywhere near an old record store,
that has vinyl, and you look around in the sound effects section,
I'm guaranteeing you will find full length LPs.
Of course, you can get them on CD, but it's much more fun to get the LPs,
because that's when you get the crackles and the scratches in there.
You'll get sound effect LPs.
Albums that have haling rules and all kind of scary things,
because that's, I think it probably originated,
well, it did originate with the old radio drama days,
and I have made so many little plays and things,
you know, acted out bits based upon those scary Halloween albums.
You know, I'm looking forward to seeing if we'll get more,
you know, more creative production on the podcast around Halloween,
and also around Christmas time.
You know, that's also coming up.
And here's something that struck me that is really messed up.
When we get closer to Christmas,
we won't be able to play Christmas music on podcasts.
How weird is that?
Because you can't, you literally, I mean, well, you can do whatever you want,
but legally, you can't play white Christmas or jingle bells
or hark those herald, angel things.
Maybe there's some classical music and classical pieces that you can use,
but all of that stuff is copyrighted and someone owns that.
Just like happy birthday.
I cannot legally sing happy birthday on the podcast,
because it would be a performance of that song.
Isn't that weird?
Isn't that weird that we can't share the joy that Christmas carols and songs
bring, you know, to a human being, to an individual.
It's kind of embedded and grained in our DNA.
We can't do anything with it.
I find that almost grotesque.
I'm looking for Christmas music from the Podsake music network.
Please, I hope so.
By the way, isn't it time we came up with a couple of new damn Christmas songs?
I think so.
Call out there to all the artists listening.
Now check this out.
Podcast ball is going on a little safari.
Swazilang is a tiny kingdom situated between Mozambique and South African.
With just over a million people, Swazilang has one terrible boast.
It's now the world's most highly infected place with AIDS and HIV.
One in two people are infected with HIV and AIDS.
Visit my progress at the Swazilang AIDS orphanage from 31st October
for a pair of about two weeks on podcastpool.com.
From my progress, I'll be podcasting.
I'm blogging from Swazilang.
See you then.
I wonder what it's going to use for connectivity.
Do they have cable there?
Hey, Adam Mark Peacock from the Travel Comments podcast.
Hey, thanks for playing my promo on last Friday's Daily Source Code.
And your recollection is correct.
The Travel Comments podcast is recorded from hotel bathrooms around the world.
From the bathroom of the Marriott Courtyard in Olds, Mar Florida,
coming to you from the bathroom of the Budapest, Marriott of Twelet,
of the Nova Tell and downtown Geneva, Switzerland.
The orchard hotel in San Francisco, coming to you from the bathroom of the camel back in
and Scottsdale, Arizona.
If I can sneak in another promo for this week's Travel Comments podcast,
a bit of an odds and ends podcast, but some of the odds and ends,
we're talking about trouble with chain saws, kind of the TSA coming around
being a little bit more civilized.
We're talking about that fourth quarter dash for program status.
And finally, we've got an update on our Travel Comments web poll on
favorite US Airlines.
So, again, thanks for the promo and I hope everybody will join us at
www.travelcomments.trav.lc.au.
Double M-O-N-Hash.com.
Thanks and take care.
Hey gang, my name is Zen and I am a host of the Zen Show.
I'm coming to you from Newcastle, Washington on the east side of the
Greater Seattle area.
And if I've got a show for you, three times a week I take you through
things I find of interest, maybe some sound scenes or interviews
recorded from my trail.
And of course, hits and favorites from the pod safe music network
music.podshow.com.
Every Monday, Wednesday and Friday, my half hour show is available for
download.
You never know what will be involved in each episode.
Sometimes it's local news or comedy or just a rant.
If you want to leave some feedback you can send in an email at
X-E-N dot show at gmail.com.
We also have an audio comment line at 206-3501337.
So, subscribe to my feed by visiting my website
triple-w dot X-E-N show dot net.
And add my feed to your aggregator.
Or just direct download from the link at the bottom of each episode's
show notes.
Until next time, if you can't be good, be careful or at least
don't get caught.
We'll see you next episode.
Yeah.
And I don't get caught.
That's a good one.
All right.
Just wind them down the show for today.
Looking through the gmail box, a couple things.
David sent me an email.
The US Army has started a singing competition.
And it's called Military Idol MilitaryItal.com.
And they're streaming it.
So you might want to check that out.
Let's see what else came in.
There was a story on New York News Day about
using podcasts for lectures in college.
And they start off with, do you think this is good?
Do you think that this will only incentivize people to skip class
and only listen to the podcast?
I'm like, why isn't anyone thinking of the obvious here?
The obvious is, of course, you go to the lecture.
And of course, it's easy and convenient if the lecture is podcasts.
So if you miss the lecture, but how about if you go to the lecture,
then there's actually some follow-up information
that the professor, whoever is giving the lecture,
can actually give as an additional piece.
You know, and that you could actually,
and it wouldn't have to be a lecture hall.
They could sit at home and maybe create a much more personal environment
for what they're trying to communicate.
And oh, here's one.
You know, there's a lot, a lot of talk about trademarks,
always on the internet.
In fact, I heard, I read somewhere,
that Apple is now sending a cease and desist letters
to anyone, but primarily, I guess, podcasters,
who are using the word iPod in their show name,
or in their URL name, or if they're actually using artwork
of an iPod on their show blog,
the receiving cease and desist letters.
Which, of course, is, you know, if you don't really understand
how trademark works and how important it is to protect your trademarks,
it comes across as being pretty fucking rude
from a big company like that.
But here's what can happen.
This is apparently Google in the United Kingdom
is embroiled in a lawsuit over the use of the name Gmail.
There's a company that had been using Gmail for its clients.
I think there's a financial services company
and there's some kind of special email application called Gmail,
and they've been using that for two years.
And Google has actually, at least temporarily,
stopped using Gmail.
You sign up to Gmail now in the United Kingdom.
You don't get a Gmail.com address, but you get GoogleMail.com.
So, you know, just goes to show that this trademarking stuff
is pretty powerful.
And if you have a trademark and you've defended it properly,
you can even, you know,
you have the right, essentially, as a much smaller company,
to keep Google at bay.
Now, if I were Google, I just paid the $48 million
and move on.
You know, just licensed that shit immediately,
but that, of course, is, you know,
that's their DNA.
And I'm not quite sure.
It's funny.
You know, when something,
you see this happen over and over again.
When you've got to kind of like the run
and the underdog and the underdog grows and gets big.
And then even if it's, you know,
not even true, people start to build up some kind of
anti-feelings about the big guy.
And so then, and this happens everywhere.
I see it, it's just happening podcasting.
How many people hate me?
Because, well, who knows?
Why?
I got some ideas.
Okay, that's it for today's show.
DailySourceCode.com is where you can find
the latest episode.
And, of course, the podcast feed feedback.
More than welcome, particularly,
well, just tell me some feedback.
Adamadcurry.com.
If you can at all, please do not attach your file
to the email, just put it up on a server somewhere,
with the ID3 tags in there, and we're off and rolling.
Now, I shoot, man.
I got, all right, I got to keep all this stuff from Monday.
We have a lot of stuff to do.
And, of course, as promised, I'll come up with the
video podcast of the DailySourceCode from the condo.
Have a great weekend, everybody.
If we don't speak over the weekend,
it'll definitely be Monday.
Bye-bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.