Delta CR at Charlie 218. Good afternoon everybody from Curry Cottage. Today is a Monday,
no promo, no pod save music, no mashup podcast. Just a quick little update about some stuff
and some thoughts over the weekend and I just let you know what's going on because it is now
335 and I have to hurry up because it's 5 o'clock Patricia and I are leaving for London.
Tonight is by the way it's such a hardship. Tonight is the Playboy UK launch party.
I believe actually that Playboy UK launched once previously but I think this is a relaunch of
of the magazine probably on the heels of the success of their television channels. I'm kind of
doing stuff here at the same time and that will be a sound scene tour which of course I hope to
deliver to you tomorrow for tomorrow's daily source code. Patricia and I are staying overnight
in a lovely hotel overlooking the park not far from where the party is which is at a secret
undisclosed location. So needless to say I don't think there will be a lot of editing going on the
evening since yay we're alone. And yeah it's just been crazy busy today I just had a visit from
a producer from BBC Radio 1 hadn't been interviewed by Radio 1 yet so I was keen to do that
and because Radio 1 is kind of like the top 40 pop station really the popular radio station here
that the BBC operates and so she came over for a chat we talked for about an hour and a half
and it was hours love it when you know she's using a mini disc to record and I always love the
the kit they give these these producers when they go on the road you know the big old fashion
stick microphone with a big windscreen and the big radio one might cube that looks so professional
so we had a nice chat about podcast and that's for something in an air pretty soon and I'll be
sure to you know point you towards that because apparently the BBC really is getting into podcasting
and it's interesting she said that just last week they finally gave her a computer that actually
wasn't able to do sound so you know it's not like they've been working on this for a long time
but they're getting into it and the mission that has come down as I understood from Alice
this producer is that the BBC really wants to you know bring the interactive departments and the
the current program creation departments closer together so that's good news and they're also
supposed to suppose to think out of the box and start thinking about programming that may not
make it on the air that should only be for podcast and that's beautiful because that is exactly
what I think the BBC should be doing and they have that's almost in their charter statement that
they have to use any means of distribution available to them and Lord knows it's enough people who
work there so I'm sure they can come up with some great podcasts in the near future I'm looking
forward to it and not just you know re broadcasting radio shows as podcasts you can hear the
con ver in the background that have it on setting one flaps one on the con ver which reminds me of
this this past weekend so the wind command was on vacation but one of his his good buddies yapp
who was a we're flown with before he picked up the 1802 RG and Antwerp and then flew to
Rotterdam picked up the in-laws who are going to be staying here during our vacation but since
Patricia and I had this night out when you know we said I want you come over and then you can keep an
eye on things what we're gone and Christina of course will be here and we still don't really feel
comfortable leaving a almost 15 year old alone in the house overnight so he brought him over and
they it was their first flight in a small aircraft and he did him just this you know
took him up above the clouds no turbulence did a nice little sightseeing tour over London down the
tabs and then over to to pharaohs which is our airport about 15 minutes from the house from the cottage
and I met them there and then they went back in a cab and then I basically spent the rest of the day
flying and it was f***ing fantastic I'm sorry got a lot of email about use of the word f***ing
I have to say it's a it's a it's a fun word to use you know I don't use it to
for any other reason it just sounds good and it's a it's a way of expressing myself and it's just a
word is not going to cut you and make you bleed okay but it was a really good time we did a lot of
navigation flying which means flying on instruments and not on the GPS and I went to Rochester airport
which is about I say about 30 miles probably from from pharaohs and just did lots of touching
goes and and you know had coffee at these different airports and that was really cool and
at the pilot shop because yeah but come over with only one pair of headsets and I didn't want to
you know look around to borrow a pair I needed my own pair anyway so I bought a great
Dave Clark I think it's a David Clark the David Clark headset it's Clark headset you know the
typical green green earpieces you know robust and I also bought in the pilot shop a Bluetooth
GPS receiver and I'd been playing around a little bit with some pocket PC applications that you
can download from around the internet without a GPS receiver connected because this is one thing
called pocket FMS which stands for flight management system it's an open source project where everything
is open source the program is open source all the the nav data the maps it's just everyone
contributes to this huge database and it's amazingly accurate and for GPS certainly and it's it's just
it's got everything you would really want as a pilot in your flight management system and the way you
set it up with with your your flight plan your waypoints you know all the frequencies are there
it has a moving map you can zoom in you can select what you do or don't want to see it shows
all the symbols that you want as a pilot highly configurable and then I just start hunting around
for stuff online of course now I hooked it up right and so I was able to kind of see me walking
down the street is a little plain moving just a couple of centimeters on the moving map but there's
a huge rush right now with the introduction of the Google Maps API and of course my
sound seeing tour San Francisco already introduced me to this got lots of feedback and email from
people talking about this Google Maps API where if you have the the navigational data which comes
in these formats called M E N M E A or November Mike echo alpha then there's G S X where's the
or G P X the G P X data exchange format there's all these different formats of course it's a little
convoluted but once you kind of figure your way through it there are ways to actually take data
from a GPS and hooked that into a Google Maps so that you can see the entire route that you travel
and you can do that with the satellite pictures as well if you want and you can even put in way
points that can include a picture of of something that you took at that particular spot
and I'm just learning now how to do all this I thought it was going to be really complicated
and you had to connect your camera to your GPS but it's much simpler than that because the GPS
basically records the longitude and latitude but also the time of day based on UTC time
when you were there so if you take a camera and your camera is kind of set to the same time as your
GPS that data in just about every single digital camera these days of course not in the
built-in camera on the XDA which was quite a disappointment but I have a different digital
camera and E X and more whatever it is and it has all that data right there in it it has the time
of day data stamped into the file so it'll automatically sync up and you can create these automatic
waypoints and there's a lot of learning to do still and actually I found that Koso he's the
the guy known as pod bad or blog he of course you know I looked for you know GPS data and google
maps API is a Google search and he popped up with something called jeepster as in golf echo
papa siera tango echo romio so GPS based site and he's done exactly this he's got like these
google maps that he's hacked together with this thing called what is it the GPS tuner which is a
piece of software and so he's taken the output from that loading it into the google maps API
you can also load into google earth and you can do flybys of of the routes that you did it's just
I mean it's it's mind boggling this stuff I showed it to Patricia last night and she kind of went
oh okay so it may not be for a very big audience I'm not quite sure if it's going to be that
compelling but it's certainly a major geek thing to do and I'm really loving it so I'm just
going to look out for all kinds of programs that that can tile this stuff together and I'll be
uploading some experiments very soon there's also a site called magna log dot com or magna locks I
think magna log or magna locks dot com and they have it that's a pretty cool project you can upload
your NMEA data and your picture is although you know it's very limited it's to kind of like an
attest and you can't upload high resolution pictures and you only can upload up to 200k worth
of data so I mean I gladly pay the guides to use as tools because the tools are great they're really
rock so I spent a lot of time geeking out hooking up this this Bluetooth and man Bluetooth has come
a long way it's really working I have Route 66 on my Mac and I connected the Bluetooth receiver to
that and so when you know I've gotten the car drove around and you could actually see myself moving
on the map and it's kind of exciting you know there's something about these especially the Google
Maps API that's really what's going to blow this wide open I think and there's a lot of hacking
going on I'm just trying to jump into this community now and I can really see that once again I'm
very happy I have the MDA3 because it it allows me to to do all this cool stuff in a very compact
format and just take it with me so look for me to be data logging all kinds of stuff in fact
what I'll do is I'll log the route to London that we take and then I'll also log the route
from our hotel to the party at its secret location okay so what is the time that's about 10 minutes
this was just an update I just didn't have time to do all the normal preparation so I figured I just
give you a load on what's going on so it's going to be a fun night tonight again sound
seeing tour will be recorded and we'll be editing that sometime tomorrow and uploading that
the new pod finder just want to let you know we're skipping one week because we want to
go on a different production schedule which means we'll we'll basically close production by Friday
Saturday morning at the latest and then Tuesday is when the new shows come out so we're not going
to have one tomorrow but there will be a new one in a week from tomorrow and we also have a new
spike lead podcast coming out that will come out tomorrow so that's episode number three in the
shadow cast of the indie man movie podcast that we've been doing with Spike Lee so look out for that
and I will be back tomorrow with your daddy source code thank you very much for subscribing sorry
this was so short I'm sorry I had to ruin your commute maybe should go find another great podcast
to listen to I'm sure you've got something on your iPod or your MP3 player don't you
talk to you tomorrow