Oh, yes, the daily source code for March 29th, 2005.
Yo, DJ!
Are you done, Netflix?
Your DJ has only just begun.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Do the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need not sticking grids in.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I'm just kidding.
It's Adam Curry.
Hey everybody.
Welcome to the daily source code from Southfield.
I'm going to go away.
Let's stand there looking at me, naked.
The daily source code coming to you from the balcony of our wonderful
Rent and condo here in South Beach.
Close to Miami Beach, Florida.
Oh man, this is definitely going to be a vacation cast.
You don't mind.
Probably underprepared, but how many comments do I have to read?
And how many emails do I have to receive it?
I just got to do some kind of something, right?
Got to get some kind of podcast out there.
Oh, shoot.
I just just turned off all the lights.
I'm out on the balcony.
This is one of those, you know, kind of like the Miami Rice condos that you see,
the high rise is run the 19th floor right now and have that peasant out here.
Time now is 5 a.m. UK time, which makes it 11 p.m. here in Miami.
And we just got back from dinner, which is always much,
vacation time is always later by, by definition, but it seems like light here in general
is just much later.
And I'm on messed up.
We're all jet lagging, crazy.
So I really just wanted to talk about a couple things about our stay so far as you can tell.
I'm pretty out of it.
It's wow.
We had a long plane ride, Sunday.
We left.
We left the cottage.
And we're able to get a direct flight to Miami on British airways.
The flight was pretty much unabentful.
It was nice, you know, it was, yeah, it was just, you know, a typical 10 hour flight,
which, oh man, it's like, you think you're going to New York and then a little bit,
but you really are going like 10 hours.
That's with the headwinds.
On the way back, it would be a little bit shorter, about eight and a half hours.
We just make sure I've got enough volume here.
I'm basically just, we just got back from dinner and I said, you know what?
I just got to do a little, oh, okay, I see what's going on.
I have my volume turned down on the, I'm back to old school now.
Of course, I didn't bring my 19 inch rack.
Don't have no valve or tube processors.
And I think like that, it's just me the laptop and the microphone.
You hear that?
So this is, I mean, the view is, I'm going to take a picture.
I tried to buy a camera the other day.
The one I wanted, they didn't have in stock.
So I decided just to wait until I can get that one.
But 19 floor, overlooking part of the marina.
And let's see, you've got a straight shot of the downtown Miami.
And of course, on the other side, you can see the beach.
It is just absolutely phenomenal.
You've got these, the balcony itself, I think of this.
This is a two bedroom condo that we're renting for, for 10 days.
The balcony is probably like 800 square feet.
It's just unbelievable.
And the first, we were here Sunday.
So we got in Sunday, Sunday night.
You know, we went to bed like, I don't know, 10 o'clock or something like that.
We got in late five or six p.m.
And it was like the Wizard of Oz, man, all of a sudden.
It's just, there was so much wind.
And we knew it was going to be a windy day Sunday and Monday.
And it was just like, you know, plans were flying by and pillows were flying by.
Excuse me.
A little bit dusty up here.
So even though it's vacation, just a quick update.
And actually, it hasn't been 100% vacation.
Ron is in the same building.
Oh, that's what you're just turning the lights on again.
He lives in this building.
That's how we were able to get a hold of this condo that we could rent for the time while we're here.
So of course, we've been doing a little bit of just a teensy little bit of work.
I mean, we've closed, I think, six contracts in the past two weeks.
So we've really, really been working in very hard.
It's kind of convenient, but I am officially on vacation.
Haven't even checked out the pool yet.
I've been going through infrastructure stuff.
Had to get a wireless, you know, a little d-link for the,
because there was, there was internet here in the, in the apartment.
But it basically, you know, a cable motor with a Ethernet wire coming out of it.
So I went to the Apple store at the Aventura Mall.
I think giving shit away now at the Apple store unbelievable.
There must have been 20 to 25 people in line to pay continuously.
And all I really wanted was an airport express.
You know, one of those Wi-Fi deals that you just, you know,
it's a self-contained unit kind of looks like the power adapter that comes with the,
with the power booking is plug it in.
And you've got your Wi-Fi and you can also stream your iTunes over it.
I'm not going to make sure what it costs, actually.
It's got to be over $100, actually.
Let me take a look at, see, now I'm on the balcony.
I got my Wi-Fi, which of course is not going to be an Apple Wi-Fi,
but you kind of guessed that already.
Oh yeah, no, now that I'm recording on the,
now that I'm recording on the power book,
it's kind of hard to use firefox.
Come on, now forget about it.
So it's definitely more than the 49 box I paid for this little mini d-link.
Which is the 56 megabit per second version, the 802.11G.
And it's small, it's got, that's probably got a better range,
and you know, little antenna on it.
So it's perfectly happy with that.
Still looking for the perfect windows machine to buy,
to tote around both as my Skype phone and my podcasting recording set up.
Haven't found that yet.
And we just been, you know, trying to chill a little bit.
It's been getting used to the time difference.
You know, I've been traveling a little bit more recently,
so for me is, I don't know where my ass is.
I'm completely, completely confused when it comes to all time zones.
Yeah, there's a night flight coming in from somewhere.
Flying almost overhead the marina.
So the girls are just a little bit jet lag,
but they're getting better.
As I said, this is just going to be a short little update podcast,
just to let you know that I'm still alive.
Oh, and by the way, something that was troubling me for a couple of days
was what really happened to Billy Ocean.
I don't remember where we played.
The numberally hurts without you.
And a whole bunch of people sent me basically the same story
that Tom sent me.
And of course, I put this on the show notes on curry.com.
But after his 1994 smash at Caribbean Queen,
and over the next five years,
Billy Ocean topped US and international charts with suddenly lover boy.
They'll be sad songs when the going gets tough,
get out of my dreams.
Well, Billy Ocean, after that sadly, apparently fell into drugs,
went to prison and obscurity in the 1990s.
But after recovery and spiritual renewal,
Billy returned to his native Trinidad in 2002
as earned notable respect,
and adulation from schools of fine and performing arts.
He's now a grain, bearded, dreadlocked elder in his 50s.
He enjoys gardening, playing pan,
and occasionally touring Europe.
At least he's alive, man.
There's so many people who didn't make it through all of that.
It's pretty tough to hear about Billy.
Let's take a little quick walk up and down the balcony here.
Hold on, let me take off the headphones.
So I'm now kind of like at the corner, which means,
I guess this is the, what is that?
That would be the eastern corner, I think?
No, that would be east.
So the northern corner, that's it, right?
Looking over the marina.
Maybe you can hear the traffic down below on the causeway.
This is actually the wind's picked up a little bit.
You probably hear some of that rustling through.
So I'm walking back again.
Nice corner shroud here.
This is dining room table.
All kind of normal stuff.
You know, it's crazy though.
So this place is basically glass, right?
It's glass on two sides, big sliding doors.
And the three of us, Christina Patricia and myself,
have at least once, but I've actually done a twice.
I've walked into the glass, even though the doors have been slid open,
so you can walk through.
I just, I don't know what it is.
You know, it's like, probably just mindlessness.
Just kind of walking around.
Oh, I'm going to walk outside and bunk.
I bumped into it, Christina bumped into it.
Patricia was the best.
She had a sandwich.
She bumped into into the glass sliding door,
and there's like sandwich all over the door.
Oh, my goodness.
Okay.
Let me get the headphones back on here.
So, let me see.
What have we gotten?
Like, a 10 minutes is almost nothing.
A couple of things, just a little bit of business.
I got a take care of here.
A couple of promos that I promised I'd play,
otherwise I'd get into trouble.
So check these off.
Hey, Adam, how's it going?
It's reges here and I got a little trivia question for you.
What do you get when you take a guy like me
who could his job in the public schools to be self-employed?
I mean, I don't work, but I'm not unemployed.
A dad who's a domestic engineer by day,
karaoke DJ by night.
I mean, I make money, but I don't work.
And finally, a guy that's unlucky in love and careers,
did you know that you can file for an appointment on line now?
Mix them all together, and what do you got?
Not sure.
Well, here's a little audio clue for you.
Let's put them on me to have a career.
Hello, a career.
And there's your answer.
A show called The Unemployment Line.
For you guys podcasting at a Tuesday morning because
we have no jobs.
Find us on the web at unemploymentcho.com.
And now, back to you, Adam, in the studio.
In the studio, out on the balcony here in the lovely South Beach, Florida.
On the vacation, I've been looking forward to this for a while.
We really needed some sun and sunshine.
We will get it.
It's been 80 degrees.
Except for the first.
Excuse me, the first day, as I said, Monday, Sunday through Monday was just
a little windy.
And it's just going to be great tomorrow again.
I don't know what we're going to do.
We're just going to chill out.
We know we're going to vote over here.
One thing that I do know for 100% for sure is in this week,
Ron and I are going to do a podcast together.
I'm going to interview him.
Let's find out what he's been working on.
And you guys know what?
I've been working on.
Let's find out what he's been working on.
Maybe we can make some damage announcements already, you know?
Hello, Adam, just a brief promo to invite you and all your listeners to
check out the latest edition of digital flats.
This is our show number 11, the one pound edition.
And it promises to be the most explosive edition ever.
We can be found at the directory at ipodder.org.
Come give us a listen.
Thanks a lot, Adam.
Peace out.
PW Fender.
I'd like to tell you, it's one of my favorite podcasts, digital
flats.
I look forward to it.
Every single weekend when it comes out.
It's usually out Friday or Saturday, depending on when my ipodder
picks it up.
It is.
It's always a theme based show and just some great music.
PW's got a great voice.
And I just, you know, the themes are good.
I really, really, really enjoy it.
I know that the one pound edition is a great story.
So make sure you check that out.
You know, I'm going to save all the stuff that I had for tomorrow.
I got a mash up with the, so you got a Kylie Britney mash up.
I got a Joan Jett Queen mash up.
Got a couple of pod save tunes.
I might even just run to iTunes and buy something because of the weather is just so inspiring.
So I'm going to cut it reasonably short for tonight.
And we'll be back tomorrow.
Sometimes in the afternoon with a longer edition.
So I'll post this as I guess Tuesday's show.
If I could still get it compressed and get it up to the server on time.
And tomorrow I'll be back with more.
I'll be a little more coherent.
Still just a little bit jet lag, but one let you know.
I'm alive.
We're having a good time.
Stuff is moving ahead.
And it's all happening in South Beach, baby.
On the balcony.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
All right.
Should have any questions about this.
Rather under-performing show, short as it is.
Atamercurry.com or through the problem at www.curry.com.
DailySourceco.com for the pod show, pod cast feed, and for the latest, and the archive.
So how are all the people in charge?
I'm off to bed, man.
I've had it.
I'll see you all tomorrow.
I'll take care.