There's no place like home, there's no place like home, there's no place like home.
There's no place like home, there's no place like home.
You know the weird guy in the corner of the office who always has his headphones on?
That's you!
Hot chill.
There are no secrets.
Only information you don't get out of.
Adam Curry.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding.
It is the 28th of October, 2005.
You a lady?
Why?
Come on!
The sun is coming up over the yard arm and sunny Northern California.
For the last time they're in this trip from the Curry condo.
It is the daily source code.
All man, I hope you're listening to this on your drive home as you're getting ready for the weekend.
I got some really special for you.
You know the golden airing, of course, are a bunch of Dutch guys.
No one will know the owners of the copyrights.
Everything belongs to the song.
Although not pot safe.
Although they couldn't give me a free license.
They said they wouldn't sue me.
That's good enough for me.
Crank this one up and stick it in you.
You're gonna love the radar love.
It's the golden airing on the daily source code.
For Friday!
I'm in driving on at my hands went on the wheel.
There's a voice on my head that drives my heel.
It's my baby condons that need you here.
Let's have fast forward, I'm shifting here.
When she is lonely and longing yet too much,
She sets a cable coming in from above.
Don't need a bottle.
We're gonna stay, but I suppose we're gonna love.
We're gonna wave in the air.
We're gonna love.
The road has got me every time.
And I'm spinning into a new sunrise.
When I get lonely and I'm but sure I'll have enough.
She sets a cable coming in from above.
We're gonna wave in the air.
When I get lonely and I wish all I've had enough
She sets the comfort coming in from above
We don't need to let her go
We can say, let's go, we don't need to let her go
We can say, let's go
We can say, let's go, we can say
Let's go, we can say, let's go
Rida love
Damn, good morning
Good afternoon, good evening everybody, wherever you are
Man, is that a way to kick off a show or what?
Golden airing, radar love, thanks to a couple of people
For being able to play that on the show
For this one exception
Actually, what I had to do is I had to ask Patricia
To call in to her old record company boss,
Villain from Co to who owns
He owned just about everything, including I think 5% of waste management ink
And, you know, industry from an industry standard perspective
There's no way he could say, yeah, go ahead, do whatever you want
Because that would set a bad precedent in the business
But I don't think we're going to run any trouble for that
One little violation, at least I'm hoping
And please, if you like the Golden airing, go buy their tracks on iTunes
It's where I got this one from, 99 cents
And I had all the memories flowing back to me
Whew, so this is it, the last day in the condo
For this trip out, then I'm back to back home
Unfortunately, I can't fly today
As you know, everything was filled up so I'll be flying tomorrow
Time to wash the sheets and clean up
Vacuum and basically have the condo ready for the next time out
Which will be pretty soon
Although it'll be short one because we got some holidays coming up
We have Thanksgiving on the way
And then before you know, it will be in the Christmas
And I don't know what happens in Silicon Valley
Does everybody like go off?
New York, it's dead, you know, there's no business
Between Thanksgiving and New Year's
There's no business being done
I wonder what happens in Silicon Valley
It was funny, well, I had that the Golden airing
I took off the headphones and plugged in the
Logitech MM50 and it was just
It was, it was, okay, I was dancing
Let's be happy there wasn't a video podcast of that
Actually it's funny because I know that
Hasbro, I dog that we talked about earlier this week
So I have it right next to the Logitech MM50
Check this out, two sponsors and one mention
This is fucking amazing
And I guess I'm last night when I was listening through a couple of podcasts
Because I got home
She got home at seven
I did a Skype call with the Canon Squip show
They're celebrating their first anniversary
I think that'll be probably
I don't know if it'll be out over the weekend
But certainly by next week
And they're putting together a huge extra
Against it with lots of guests
So around eight, you know, I was done
And I figured
I was, you know, we had a huge, huge lunch
We sat with a guy who we're interested in working with
Who comes from the radio business
And it was actually pretty interesting
We're trying to deprogram a little bit
And he's still a bit in the radio
In the radio world vibe
But anyway, so I, and then it was my time to listen to podcasts
You know, so the iTunes on the G5I Mac
Had done its job, had been sitting there
Relentlessly downloading all day
I just got back and, you know, lean back with my ten-foot interface
With that little remote control that comes with the iMac
And skim through stuff
Somehow I must have activated the iDog
Because I noticed and it was sitting right next to the speaker
So it wasn't even plugged in to anything
It has a built-in microphone
And so it's sitting right next to the
Logitech M50 and stuff is pumping out
And then on comes the new Steve Gilmore show
If you haven't heard this, if you're in business
And any type of business whatsoever
This is a program you must listen to
I mean, it's, yes, it's about technology
But man, yes, they were talking about
What was it?
Multi-core processing in the workplace
And how much power
Consumption that's going to save
And, you know, so besides being able to run
Fantastic applications with blazing speed
Particularly what comes to huge ones like Photoshop
And obviously all kinds of server stuff
But also just saving energy within, within an organization
I was like man, this any business person
Should be listening to attention tech
Attention tech.potcho.com
You can find a link of course from today's show notes
But anyway, so the iDog was sitting right next to the Logitech
And it came alive, right?
It started, it's light started blinking
And it was unbelievable. Attention tech
Is Steve Gilmore does the show
And does it with an industry analyst, Mike Vazard
And I swear to God
That every single time Mike was talking
The iDog was like, you know, little green
And yellow lights in his head
And his ears would go up
And every single time Gilmore
Come on, I don't have like a line of red lights
I don't know, you know, I'm just saying
Maybe red head
You know, was trying to portray some kind of emotion
Of course, you know, it's a toy, right?
It's a device, it doesn't have emotion
But it was, it is, maybe it's an interesting thing
To check podcasts with
So I started experimenting
And it does give off different vibes
For different voices
And so you could associate something with it, I guess
I'm not sure what, but it was, it was really phenomenal
Anyway, so, and I wrote down
That I wanted to, you know, of course
The guys and gals that Apple listened to
Or the Daily Source code, we know that
And I only know a few people over there
But I know that there's enough of an internal network
That people do talk to each other
And it definitely gets done
I've been playing with the ten-foot interface
If you haven't seen this, you must check out
The presentation that Steve Jobs did
Of the video iPod
Because what I think was just as exciting
And I have both products now
Is the G5 iMac
Now, when I went to the Apple store in San Francisco
They didn't have the one I wanted
I mean, they had the 20 inch, you know
What I wanted was of course
The 20-inch dual processor
Mega Hong car, they didn't have that one
But that wasn't the power and speed
That delivers wasn't necessarily what I needed
It's always happy to take away
A new one with the built-in eyesight
It has a 1.9 gigahertz processor
They didn't have the extra memory
So I'll have to go back and have that upgraded
For me at the genius bar
But one of the, let me just grab the remote here
One of the cool things about this iMac
Is that it has what the industry
I guess calls is the 10-foot interface
So it has a little remote control
That is I've mentioned this before
It's probably the same housing that they use for the iPod shuffle
It looks basically the same
In fact, I think it's exactly the same
With the addition of a menu button
That's how you activate
I found out if you do applekey escape
It also activates that menu bar on the iMac
And what it basically does
It gives you a way to
It has a top menu so you can choose between movies, DVD
Or the CD player, basic CD, DVD player
And what am I thinking at the hell is it?
What's the last one?
Photos of course, there you go
Doll
So that's basically all you need
And you could even hook up a
A tuner card or like one of those ITV things
You could watch television on it
But who cares? That's not interesting
Because the video podcast come in
The audio podcast come in
You can access your i photo library
And you can play DVD on it
Now what's interesting about this interface
Is it looks very much like the iPod interface
And that really works for me
I'm familiar with this interface
And you kind of go through the menus the same way
But team out there
In a cup of tea
You missed a couple of really important things
Particularly in the podcast area
Whereas in iTunes there's a little blue ball
Next to a podcast if it's
If you haven't heard it yet
I really miss that
Please bring that back
And then also when I go into the library
For songs
That's where I don't want to see podcasts
Because then I put it on shuffle
It's going to come back to podcast
And you guys already solved that
And iTunes
And on the iPod
I think you just need to connect somewhere
And carry that over into this interface
But I think you really onto something here
This is the first time of really
You know really enjoyed this type of
Interactivity with media
And it has nothing to do with television
It's completely unimportant
I can get anything I want
Through this
And you know I sat
Oh man I had a
Just crack in my ass off
Last night
Watching a Tiki bar
That girl in there
She's hot
And she seems like she's really that way
Funny and a little bit ditsy
But yeah
Tiki bar
It's cool
You know
Rolled through
And see Pacific Coast
Hellway had had their first video
Promo on there
I watched the second episode of
Father Roderick's Catholic Insider
The Catholic Minute
It's just
The entertainment is there
And with this little remote control
It works
Very, very enthusiastic about it
Let's do another release of the
Interface
Just carry a couple of those things over
You already have
Across the board
Into this
And what do you call it?
Please
It must have a name
I'm calling it the ten foot
Interface
But it must have some
Anyway
See
I'll do it
When I get paid and I do it
When I don't get paid
Doesn't matter to me
I'm just passionate about the stuff
We're talking about
Yesterday
I talked about
The
The Spat
I had
With PWM
And offered my apologies
And there were some words
I was looking for
And I couldn't quite complete
A min of course
You know
Of course you guys are always there to help me
Hey Adam
This is Andrew in Santa Rosa
California
Just wanted to help you out with your vocabulary
I think the word you were looking for
Yesterday when you were talking about
Bitching and moaning through email
And you said
Leathergic
The word is actually
Therapeutic
So that's all
I hope that helps you
I love the show
Take care
It's just thinking
Couldn't it have been cathartic
Maybe that was the word I was thinking
Oh no, let me just go to
My favorite
Dictionary
Calm the mic is in the way
The keyboard
I don't usually type that slow
Okay
I hear you screaming
Your iPod already
Don't you know what cathartic means?
Let's see
Let's just do it together
Did you mean cathartic with a T?
Yeah, I think that's what I meant
Okay cathartic
An agent for purging the bowels
Especially a laxative
Well that was it
That was exactly it
Oh man
New Bittycast came out last night
LeCivius Bitties
You know my girlfriends from New York
Who I met
More than a year ago
They were the first people I emailed saying
Would you mind if I played
Some of your songs on my podcast
And that actually resulted in sales
And their audience grew
And we've been flirting with each other ever since
It's been just wonderful
And they have a podcast called the Bittycast
And they were
What they do is they basically record
For the past
Oh there's an eye dog
For the past couple of episodes
They're on the road in the van
And also some live recordings
And then I came across a bit
From the most recent Bittycast
I want to play for you
Because not only is it a great pod save tune
Well the whole the whole thought behind it is fantastic
And especially now
When people aren't talking about voting
Maybe now it's the time to think about it
And start ramping up our thoughts on voting
So that we get something that we're all a bit happier with
We, the least serious Bitty's always tried to do
A little bit of like subtle activism
For a while after
We're not, you know, just supporting our fellow human being
So a little while after the Hurricane Katrina
We did some donations of CD sales
And stuff like that
And one of the things that we've been committed to
For the past few years is something that we've called
Swing the vote
Where we encourage people to register to vote
And get out and vote
And we try not to make it super lame
Because we know the topic
Can some pines be a little repetitive
Vote, vote, vote, vote
So Amanda
I know that
But Amanda wrote this song
That we hope you find it entertaining
To say the least
Not annoying
If the deficit's got you feeling blue
Take a stroll to the pole
And here's what you do
You've had a cast that ballot
Cast that ballot
And let your voice be heard
So you say your party is not too blame
And the difference in dog is not the same
You better cast that ballot
Cast that ballot
And pick your favorite name
Think slips layoffs
Unemployment gives me the blue
As you please, our hybrid
Our nose, now's the time to choose
Better care the N-R-A
So much to think about every day
You better cast that ballot
Cast that ballot
And chase your fears away
Right wing left wing everybody's swing
You better cast that ballot
You better cast that ballots
If you're a sock, come on, I'm already as poor, never ever went to college once you wish you had
You bought a cast on ballot, cast on ballot, cast on ballot, you got a cast on ballot if you don't you just be sad
Some folks say the market's gonna take it maybe true
Losing all of our social security, it could happen to me to you, you're right
Wing up who's for the war, if you're slaving hippie who's feeling so
Or you better cast that ballot, cast that ballot, cast that ballot
You better cast that ballot and give your fees to chance
I told you once, I told you twice, being patriotic is so nice
You better cast that ballot, it's the only true American way
I love you, girls
Vitties
Fantastic, perfect for my, that's the eye dog again
Perfect for my Friday show, I'm tired, I woke up the, you know, I did something different last night
I went to bed with the window with the shades up because I have window in my bedroom
And the bed is elevated just about the same, the same height as the window
Actually, and then you just see all the lights of the hills
And it's a beautiful, beautiful view
And I was like, I want to fall asleep like this
And I was just hoping that the sun wouldn't wake me up in the morning
But it's on the west side
So my alarm goes off, well, you know the blackberry starts tingling around seven
And it was still dark outside, and with, oh man, it was beautiful
And I don't even know why I mentioned that
Oh, just because it was good, and life is good, that's what it was
And now on the sun is up to day, it's fantastic
So I'm in good spirits, but you know, just tired from
For everything we've been doing, it's been a lot of running around
But very, very productive and excited to be able to, yeah, start telling you stuff
Very, very soon
Oh my god, another tease
Let's see, what we're going to talk about
Oh well, yesterday we had the hum test
John Paulette is working on building the podcast and curriculum over there
And the lowlands and the Netherlands
It Holland
But the call was out, and the call was heard
Yes, once again, it's a backtracks podcast
Backtracks podcast
So you think you know your hits backwards and forwards
Come on, it's Friday, do me baby
Yeah, right
You're listening to the backtracks podcast
Exclusively on the daily source code with Adam Curry
Hey, Adam, hey buddy, how you doing?
Lamb, I'm going to get right into this week's quiz
Okay, okay, I'm ready, go!
Number one
I think you've done this one
This is hitting you with your best shot
I've been as hard
Pimes out
Number two
I don't remember the name of the song, but it's definitely the Thompson Twins
You can hear that backwards forward
Pimes out
Number three
Okay, here are the answers, number one
Oh, I think I got it right
This is me with your best shot
I think you did that on the first one actually
And here's number two
Maybe it's late your hands on me or something
Hold me now
Okay, I got that one
Now what was that third one man?
Number three
Oh
It's upside down
So how did you do Adam?
Well, like one and a half out of three
Thanks for joining us on this week's Backtracks podcast quiz
You can visit Backtracks podcast on the web at
Backtrackspodcast.com
Catch you next time
Backtracks podcast
Just thinking about the lyrics again to that bitty song
Right wing left wing everybody swing
I'm there's a campaign poster for you
I got a note from the podpimp
Aaron Brousel he does our PR and marketing
So yeah, I didn't come up with the name
But he is affectionately known around the offices of the podpimp
He drives a Prius
The podpimp and Prius driving
No anyway
And he alerted me to a rock and roll geek episode that I
I guess I know I missed it and I know why because I've iTunes configured
It's unfortunate you can't do it by channel
I have a configured to only keep the last, you know, the most recent episode
Just because I'm subscribed to so much stuff that
You know it it fills up the drive and my power book starts to die
And so I had to go back like three episodes
I think it's let me see I have it up here
Let me see which one it was
It was the rock and roll geek show for
I love this new little mouse nipple
Now you now we finally have a mouse wheelet on the Mac
It was the geek show for the 16th okay
And he had constant teen from American Idol on the show in an interview
He knew someone who knew his brother or something like that
You know Michael Butler's reach goes far, man
He knows everybody in the business
and
It was actually was
It was a great conversation
It was fun to listen to it
And what was great about is Michael was kind of
spewing his opinion about some of the other candidates
who were voted off later than Constantine
And
Constantine you know I was like laughing and agreeing with some stuff
And it was just a nice chat
You got to know how this you know people get really really really passionate about
Contest like American Idol you know and
The message boards over rock and roll geek.com
I just just exploding and everyone's pissed off
And and everyone's yelling at each other
It's unbelievable to see what's going on
And this is all it's like subculture
You know this is the TV show
Or that series is you know that particular episode of series of episodes is over
This guy's been voted off
Um
And and the culture continues
It's just fascinating fascinating to see that unfold
And once once again all due to the one is a podcast in here
Adam my name's close hello close
And I'm the one who subscribed to your podcast the one you requested some feedback is
You seem to be hardworking
Yeah
To bring me to unsubscribe from your podcast
Octuliba with this worst sound I've ever heard in episode 2-5-9
You've ruined everything
And then in episode 2-6-2
You simply forgot your sign out
You kept me in a loop for at least 24 hours
I wasn't able to work
Because you
You Adam's curry
Forget to sign out
And you are the one who is lamenting
On cell phones used in airplanes
Oh yes
You are the one
With the cell phone
During your daily source code
Ruin and everything
You are really trying hard to bring me to unsubscribe
But Adam's curry
I won't
So Adam's curry
Go on try hard
But I'm harder
By then
You know
Without guys like class
We'd still have a Berlin wall
Adam
Hey, you didn't think I forgot your mashup did you?
Uh-huh, divide and create
Don't see them
Don't you?
I need some time to get right
You're not so soon to prove
I can't tell them don't know
I never let them know
No, no, no
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey
I'll turn around, wanna hurt down, knock your steps on the floor
There he walks here, now I know it's true
I'm dead when you walk at the same time, don't you?
Now now, don't know, I never let go of the road
I'm so happy this is not a video podcast
You're gonna be laughing when you saw my hair get torn
That's not all about my Alasamoye impression, it's pretty gnarly too
Oh yeah
I think this is gonna be one of those shows I'm gonna want to keep in the archives
This is a great mix of shit we got going on
And thanks by the way everyone who sent in ideas and suggestions etc
And of course this weekend is Halloween
It's strangely enough, we have really only one true tradition
My daughter and I, and that is the carving of the Halloween pumpkin
No matter, every age, every single year
For some reason it's just something that we've always done
And I've always had a lot of fun doing together
I don't know why, I think a lot of it is the goop stuff
We do kind of, you know, we play a lot of freak out games with the goop
You know, I of course have to force Christina as I stick her hand in there
And grab some goop
A bigger than Christmas really if you think about it
Yeah, I think this more tradition at Halloween
So I'm so happy that I'm gonna be home just in time
Cause I leave Saturday, so I'm home Sunday
So just in time to, you know, do some quick, quick goop scooping
Happy Halloween
Other goop stuff
All right, nevermind
It's Derek Miller again, hey Adam
I'm from the Penn Machine podcast
And I had some comments on your Delta
The Sierra Charlie October 27th edition
Where you were talking about the pod show
And your top spins lists
Maybe you're thinking about this already
But how about top pod spins for different genres
Jazz, country, metal, electronic instrumentals
That's what I'm interested in because that's what I'm doing
And how about why just the top few
Or top 100 one at the top 1000
Why not all of them?
Why not the bottom 100 because maybe somebody wants to make a podcast
Of really bad music
And they should be able to find it
Shouldn't they?
Or how about geographically, I don't know if people report this
But top spins from Europe, top spins from Australia
Top spins from the greater Lake County area in Illinois
Or wherever that is, I don't know
Anyway, just an idea
And I hope you managed to get yourself away from San Francisco
Beautiful as it is, back to where you want to be soon enough
I'm at podcast.penmachine.com
And I'll see you later
Happy Halloween
All right Derek, yeah, right on
I hadn't actually thought of it that way
I was still kind of stuck in old world radio mode there
Because the top spins, I've drawn the analogy between what we have
On the Podship Music Network
As it pertains to top spins
And again, we're coming out with the top spins of the day
The week, the month, and of all time
And that is analogous to radio and records
Which is this publication
You can pick it up at new stands in New York
Certainly, I'm not sure about around the country
You pick up radio and records and in there
It's got all those types of charge
Everything is broken down segmented exactly as you said
Not even that good
And I was listening to what you were saying
I was like, dude, that makes so much sense
We should just provide an interface on the back end for the podcasters
To go in and sort and do those queries themselves
It's easy, everything's in the database
So, wow, great idea, thank you
Give us a little time
Because I've got Chris Rockwell
Our resident poopcaster
I've got him working on some other stuff
Oh dude, we're going to have some fun
I'm sorry, I'm not, I'm not a lot of talked about
I'm not a lot to do it
I've been sworn to secrecy about what's happening in a very short amount of time
Did you take French in school?
Are you about my age?
If you are, then probably your French was
Audio tapes
Do you remember those?
Does anyone have an audio tape of the lessons
That always started like this?
Bonjour, Lean
Bonjour, Monsieur le professeur
Sabah?
Sabah, bien
Hello Adam, my name is Pierre
And I am the host for the PCC
The podcast of the Cabernet Canada
It is a podcast in French
Where I do a sound thing to offer
The mantra, a real and often outside of it
Thanks a lot for uploading my promo
Adam, and don't worry, I won't say anything to not in French
Or maybe I should
In the last week, the PCC
You are going to see the ball in the hall
Make sure to read it on your family
And listen to the franco-foli de Montral
And learn other things
So watch out for the address
Cabernet Canada
In a single word
Or via blog.com
To subscribe to the PCC
So see you soon
So see you
Lean
See you, Monsieur le professeur
Eline?
Yes, Monsieur le professeur
Papa, Fumun Pip
Emma Mont Pip Papa
Hey, audition update
I can only give you clues
But it's all a part of my secret messaging to you
What is it that every podcaster wants?
Every single podcaster
Even people who aren't podcasters
But want to become podcasters
If only
You fill in the rest
Hey, this is Dave Grossman
The fighters in the energy into the strange brews
Hi, this is Kevin
And I'm the sidekick Doug
In case you've missed us, this is what's been happening on the strange brewed
A side from celebrity Collins
We still talk about entertainment news
Political gaffs
And my favorite segment
Dr. Phil's ass shabbers
And I get to school
And apparently the raise my still there
And I teach my first hour studying all
And nobody told me about it
By the time I see
The raise and I'm my shirt
And I look down in the middle of second hour
This has been there for two to three hours now
It's baked in my shirt
And I've got this big grease spot
Sadly
There's been an end to one popular segment on the show
Kevin's e-harmony updates
But the good news is I'm no longer searching
Because I found a new love
Conversation and everything
It was very easy everything that happened
It was just easy
No, I say easy
I don't mean
I don't mean easy
I don't mean easy like that
I do not mean easy like that
Oh my goodness
We have loads of new material to keep the occupied
Like the brief but hilarious
karaoke recap
Like a case of her peering of fire
Writing of fire
Be contrast
There's no time right
Oh
I see a hit to see the whets that live a man
Scottled wood, scottled wood
We do the fun
And of course
We've got ill advised Trombone duets
Up the Wazir
So be sure to visit us at
TheStrangeBrewdBROT.com
And expect the unexpected
Unless you expect funny
Because you'll get a crapload of that
Kick it
Partio should only be enjoyed under the supervision of a podcasting professional
Warning
Do not attempt this at home
She's the only female conservative
That gets right to the issue
But our losses
That's the backbone of our politicians
Now cut our losses
What we need is more ammo
It's just getting ready to see
That damn straight-talk express
Carging up your local diner
Where the only straight-talk getting served
Is that to the press
Who will take any Republican
It looks like a Democrat
Is shelling the Republican
Hypocrates
Do you know what a hypocrite is Cindy?
The fact that you use
The crosses of soldiers who have fallen
When their parents do not want any
Part of your liberal movement
That defames their names
Or the value of their life
You know what is hypocritical
The fact that you enjoy the luxuries
Of the American life
But are not willing to defend it when it's tough
Log on
To shelling the Republican.blogspot.com
To hear her latest show
Shelling the Republican
Bringing the Game of Politics
To a whole new level
Holy moly that is a first
Oh my goodness
I have to check that out
Alright, here's one for my girls
I love you both
I'll see you in a couple days
The way they do
What's a melancholy
Maybe they don't really care
They be moving
I've never been there
It's not the fun
And things in life
Maybe they don't really care
It's not the fun
But it's not the fun
It's not the time to bomb that makes us who we are.
Beyond the world, the things you know they are, they will suffer.
We don't have the most of it.
We have the lucky ones reaching ways that can't be seen.
The affection they are all the inside, the finest things that you can't buy.
Oh, it's simply the love you can't deny.
Oh, it's all about love.
It's all about love.
It's all about it's all about love.
Lisa Bell.
It's all about love.
Found that on the Podsafe Music Network.
Music.podshow.com.
Here's how it worked.
I surfed over there this morning and upop.
What I find it through Lynn Parsons.
Lynn Parsons.
Remember we played that promo by Lynn Parsons, who's the radio personality in the 9 Kingdom,
who also is doing a podcast from her little tea house in the garden.
I've been invited over by the way, which I'm certainly going to do.
And she had played Lisa Bell.
If Lynn played it, then that's whoops.
That means something to me.
I like this stuff she plays.
And so I immediately added it to my playlist.
And of course when I'm done, I'm going to go and report that I've played it.
That is the requirement.
Really, you have to do as a podcast.
And I'll link in the show notes.
That's right.
There you go.
Okay.
Man, it's been a great sharing this time with you today.
And I hope you have a really, really good weekend.
Well, of course we'll speak to each other.
Well, maybe not before.
Depending on where you are in the world.
So if I don't talk to you, you have a great Halloween.
And let's see.
I think that's it.
We've covered everything in its entirety.
The only thing we didn't do today is the rock money and off theme, which is good.
It's got a little tired of that.
And change it for once.
Adamaccurry.com.
If you want to send me feedback, it's more than welcome.
I talk a lot about the ID3 tags and I realize that you may be new to listen to the show
or MP3s or shut up, I don't.
What's best is to find it well.
If you're on Windows, then go get castblastartcastblastart.com because you'll just fill
out the description and the information.
And you'll actually be creating a little mini podcast, except you're then going to
send that to me.
Now here's the final trick is I really prefer if you don't attach it to your email.
Because even though I have a special four gig allotment on the Gmail due to my
30-ness factor, please put it up on the server somewhere.
And just send me the link to the server.
That was much, much more convenient.
Maybe we should just have a server for you guys.
I'm going to set it up so you can, so you don't have to waste your own bandwidth on
that shit.
We got $9 million.
We can do that.
Alrighty.
DailySourceCode.com is where you can always find the latest episode.
And now I'd like you to close your eyes.
Okay.
Envision everything in black and white.
And now it colorizes.
But anyway, total, we're home.
Oh.
And this is my room.
And you're all here.
And I'm not going to leave here ever, ever again.
Because I love you all.
And oh, and I am.
There's no place like home.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.