Daily source code for Thursday, March 24th, 2005.
Yo DJ!
I you don't make any more!
Your DJ has only just begun.
Transmators?
We don't need no stinking transmitters.
Autistic.
It's Adam Curry.
Yeah.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's sunny and beautiful.
Welcome to the Daily Source code.
Coming to you from Curry Cottage once again.
It is a podcast.
That's right.
With no commercial interruption.
Now it's all sneaked in there.
Product placement.
So you'd never even know it was there.
Right?
Source code for March 24th.
Oh man, I feel so much better than when I recorded yesterday's podcast.
Oh, I was completely right.
This morning, it's about, I was at the 715 Patricia Chemical Stairs with a cup of tea.
As she all is done in the morning.
Because usually she kicks me out of bed.
You know, get the day going and I'll take Christina to school.
But this morning, she brought up the tea and she said, let me guess.
You'd really love to sleep a little bit longer when she has.
I think I said something like, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Okay, so my back is completely messed up.
We're not messed up.
That's right.
I mean, it was almost a year ago that I had my motorcycle accident,
where I did really mess up my back.
And it really only acts up when I've been, let's see,
doing all the fun things.
Flying, having sex, lazying around the house.
It's completely bite.
But all the flying yesterday, you know, that's,
that's a lot more physical than I anticipated it to be.
All right, got a great podcast lined up for you today.
We've got a couple of promos.
We're going to check in on the skinny and sports, the skinny awards.
And I, I got a fever.
You know, the only thing that can cure is a little bit of cowbell.
With some cowbell goes some guitar. Oh, yeah.
Just purchased this one on iTunes paid 99 cents.
So enjoy it. Here's mountain.
Oh, yeah.
Let's see if it's me
Come and help me
We'll make it easy and easy
If I want to be a man
Hold it, I don't know
I'll do what I can
To keep a longer bread
I'll touch your neck
I'll do what I can do
To know what I can do
To make it easy and easy
I'll do what I can do
Oh man
Yeah, now that's so much better
There's nothing like pumping some Mississippi queen through your stereo valve processor
Anyone who's a radio or audio geek will know it
I'm really a radio geek will know it
I'm talking about
You know that song is that's the type of song that you would listen to
I'm like radio caroline
The AM-only pirate broadcast ships in the North Sea
In the 70s and would sound just like that
You know that pumping and the pumping of the music
Love it and it's such a beautiful day for something like that as well
I mean I can see
Oh man, I could probably see all the way to London
If that's actually what London is way there
And the distance beautiful day here in Guilford, the Curry Cottage
With the daily source code
Oh man, I was actually yelling along to that
And as the first time I've ever bought a song off of iTunes
I mean I had an account with iTunes for a long long time
But you couldn't buy music purchased music in Europe
And they finally got it done for the EU and the UK as well
There's some controversy actually over the pricing in the UK
Because the pound is so high that 99 cents of course
Is almost you can almost get two songs to that if you're paying 99 dollar cents for it
But whatever
But it was a very enjoyable experience
You know to just go to iTunes, Music Store and iTunes
Search for Mississippi Queen and my SSI SSI PPI
And then to have that return to sample it
Yeah, that's what I want
Purchase you want to buy, yes, one other confirmation
And it was downloaded
I almost made a very bad mistake of course
I have two setups here in my studio, two screens
One is my laptop, the other one is an old laptop that is connected to the cinema display
And I almost downloaded on that machine
Which is not my production machine for the source code
And I probably would have run into trouble there
Not being able to copy to the other machine
Maybe I could have maybe there's like a way to run it on five of your personal machines
But I didn't want to take any risk
I just want download the song and play it
So the experience was so beautiful
I was just like, oh man, wouldn't it be nice to those one little extra button there
And iTunes has said, Download this to play on your podcast
So maybe you pay two bucks
I don't know, I don't care
I think 99 cents should probably cover it
I've got a lot of listeners by podcast standards
But not by broadcast standards
So hopefully the 99 cents will do for this time then
That I shared it with my friends
I promise I promise I won't do it again
Need 20 minutes of entertainment?
Listen to one man revolution
The show that looks at daily news and events
From central Florida to around the world
One man revolution
Tilts at the windmills of daily directory
tune in at feeds.feedburner.com slash the revolution
Very interesting, thank you by the way
Nice short promo, I love those for 15 second ones
Beautiful
People who are just starting to subscribe to the daily source code
Or saying things like
Dude, what's with all the commercialism
You know, what's with all those advertisements you play
So what's with all the pro modes?
You shouldn't do that, that's like commercial
I'm not talking about
This is what I've been doing with the
You know, with the show from day one
It's been talking about podcasts in the community
Other podcasts you name it, you know
It's like, and stop with the plugging the eye river
Are you getting paid by those guys?
No, no, no, no, no
The whole point is that anybody can make money that way
There was this totally, oh man, people are like
Skype in me, hold on a second
Let me, yeah
So I quit it, I'll leave it on if someone
Interesting Skype's then we'll bring them in
Okay, I'll just hide it though
So yeah, I'd started with a
Cinco coffee machine, believe me, I had the
Cinco coffee machine a long time before
I can't forget if selling anything
Through an Amazon associate account
No, it's really just to prove the concept
It works, you can tell someone something on a podcast
And drive them to your website
Drive that traffic baby
And they actually will purchase it through you
And the Cinco coffee machine really got me excited
I think the eye river is pretty logical
I really just putting it there because people ask me
Time and time and time again, what's your setup?
So I've been thinking now to put together a whole page with
Everything that is in my, in my kit
Of course, not everything is available through Amazon
Which is kind of helping me back
I don't want to just put in some replacements
People keep asking me about what kind of microphones I use
And you know, I can answer the question
A thousand times
And then a thousand times more basically
I see I forgot one thing as a part of my show prep today
I was going to
I've in Gmail I've set up a label for things
I want to talk about on the source code
Let me just skimmed through them and see if there's anything interesting here
Yeah, this is something pretty cool
This is from Michael Ridley
Now, of course, I have to remember to put this into the show notes
He's talking about mashups and he listens a couple of sites
Again, I'll put this in the
I'm going to start this and then we go
I'll put this in the show notes at
Create.com or daily source code.com
Show notes of
Mashups are obviously infringement
Although I'm hearing a lot of noise from the creative community that
Artists really don't mind if you mash up their stuff
Or a lot of them don't and people seem to be kind of behind that
But believe me
The RIA and record companies will disagree strongly
And he sent me this email about something
It's been talked about on the
Folus, that's Ph.O.
So that's folus.org
Papa Hotel, Oscar Lima, India, shareatango.org
The idea of a client side mixing of mashups
So I'll just read this.
The general idea is instead of the producer
Releasing the actual finished product of the remix
You know, MP3 or CD4, whatever
They would use a tool
Which would apparently be similar to Sony's acid
I've never used acid, but I think, well,
I've never used the Sony tool acid
And then basically that would do the mix
So what would be distributed is just the control files
Like in video would call that the EDL, the edit
Decision list, you might call it
It's basically a control file
So you have to have the originals yourself
And then you get the control data
And then it mixes the mashup on your end
Which is a fantastic way of kind of
Routing around the whole problem of distributing this
And I thought it was an excellent idea
So it's almost definitely, you know,
Think about, you know, what we can do with that
In mashup land
I would love to see if we could do that
And if anyone knows anything about Sony acid
Let me know what that is
Or any other cool remixing tools
I've been hearing some things about this
So I guess it's obviously
Something that people are digging
Let me just go here
Interesting story
Says Wayne Pittenger
About the state of airport security
My wife's friend visited us in Pennsylvania
From Florida before she flew up there
She packed their duffle bag with 80 plastic easter eggs
Packed with various prizes for an easter egg hunter
Husband had warned her that it might not get through security
With a duffle full of easter eggs
Despite of that she went through air support
Airport security and the flight north
Without as much as a search through the duffle
She still had to have her shoes checked though
I love that
I know there's another one I want to talk about
Hold on, let's go back to the source code
Oh my second
I'm going to read this one
After here we go
Okay
First I want you to hear this
This is a
A podcast
This is the way
Any podcast that I'm just going to
Listen to and subscribe to immediately
It's definitely going to start off like this one
Check this out
It's Saturday, January
22, 2005
Welcome to Mike's Lifecast
Hello
There
I love it
Welcome to Mike's Lifecast
Clear
Basically he's in his airplane
And he does a whole sound seeing tour of touching goes
It's awesome
It was like
And the sound is so phenomenal
Let me just
Check this out
Listen to a little bit of him do it
Don't go to my little bit
And he can do it
First we're at
30,000 feet
Well you should listen to that
Mike's Lifecast
Check it out from
From the show notes or to ipotter.org
Really really really enjoyed that
Thank you very much for making my day
But from deep inside the underbelly of Chicago
Comes a show with more belly
Than Tony Suprano
Not a big pussy
But sort of a slight cat
This tool on the podcast is your buddy
Fat Matt
The events of the day
A mash of or two
Fat Matt chats with Scott
And they sometimes were blue
The Fat Matt show
Podcast to the world
Mattonair.com is the source of the code
That might make you hurt
If you liked on and drew
And you like a good chuckle
Here's a podcast
That's new
With a very loose buckle
The Fat Matt show
Visit matonair.com for the source code
Are you driving around?
Then he goes into a whole bunch of examples
Sounds like a pretty good show
Haven't subscribed to it yet
But I certainly will on the next
On the next scan
He has going back to the aviation cell
I got a great email from Christopher Stork
Excuse me
Oh man
I won't tell you what I'm doing
Bob, Bob, I'm here
Hey Adam, you were my sitter in the 80s
When I told the folks I was too sick for school
Bummer though is my 24 year old wife
Listening to the data source code
He says Adam, who?
Alright buddy
Thanks
Did you want to do Rob the cradle here?
Then anyway, since it sounds like an aviation buff
Thought you'd like this
I'm a captain on an ERJ145
For US Regional Airlines
I plug my iPod into the observer audio panel
panel and listen to the daily source code on long flights at 37,000 feet. You come in through
our headphones and keep us entertained like the lone ranger did for our folks. Man, thank
you as a big compliment. With $16 million worth of airplanes strapped to my ass at next generation
radio content in my ears, I like to think I'm flying into the future. My god, let me know that,
you know, we should do that differently. We should do that differently. We should do that line again.
That was going on. Okay, I guess it was a good idea. We're not going to do it. I'll do one more time now.
With $16 million worth of airplanes strapped to my ass and the next generation radio content in my
ears, I like to think I'm flying into the future. As the sun set last night, we were on top of thin layer of
clouds around flight level 350 when the last whisp of light fell under the deck and the stars popped out
above. It was if we were on the edge of the atmosphere. For a second, we were major Tom and you
ground control. Unfortunately, as I enjoyed that moment, my flight attendant called up to say some
dude was Yakkan in the aisle. Man, that's very cool. Chris, thank you very much. That's a wonderful
email and it just tickles me to think that you guys are checking this stuff out at 30s. It's flight
level 35. That's great. Excellent. Really appreciate the email. All right, let me see. What's
going to talk about? Oh, yeah, no, we're doing all this bokeh stuff. You know, it's a, you know,
run a nice set of company in 1990. Actually, he joined me in 1995 with the company that we then
folded into the company we eventually took public in 96. And I paid less attention than, as I
did now, to this, this magical thing that people call the business model. And you have many business
models and, and, you know, in this bare essence, it sounds like, okay, it's, you know, it's a,
it's a, you know, it's a way to make money. It's something comes in and you keep some as a whole
bunch goes out. But in the five years that Ron and I have been, you know, in contact with
having been doing anything, man, he's really gotten good at this spreadsheet stuff. And when it comes
to what we're in the process of developing for podshow.com and some other properties is,
I mean, it's great to see how this is really going to work. I mean, it's, it's for real. We finally
come up with, you know, a way to do things that have numbers there that really work for everybody. And
I think that this, yeah, this is going to be a new form of, I mean, the only word for it is commercialism.
I realize that. But it seems so, so clear and so clean. It's, it's just, it's pretty transparent.
I like it very much. And, and I like the fact that everybody can participate and that we're not
locking anyone in or out by any locks, like distribution locks or anything proprietary. It's just,
you know, how hard you're willing to work, the quality of the work you're going to bring,
what's your product going to be, you know, how good is your product going to be or your service
or combination. I think combination is probably best. And I'm really pumped about,
about moving this forward and getting stuff going pretty soon. One thing that that I've been
concentrating a lot on behind the scenes is I potted out org. This, of course, is not really a
directory in the, in the, in the, in the sense of the word that you may know it. We may think about it.
But more as a resource, I think the main resource is that at the back end of that server comes
an OPML file that anyone can use for their iPod or applications or podcasting applications.
And in fact, you can use it to start your own directory, which is great. And, and there are many
people who do that. But I haven't thinking about how we can make iPod.org a lot more functional.
And that's, that's obviously, you know, it's very clear what needs to be done there. I've already
spoken about what we'll be doing with the, with the category node editors that they'll have
many more tools to, to work on their space and to, you know, really be able to do good categorization
and and build a community around the node. With that come, of course, some community tools,
which would be an obvious one is a forum for a, I guess I should say, a community voting.
That's a big one. And I would definitely say search is going to be extremely important, which is always,
you know, the thought that I've had behind show notes in OPML. And maybe I'm wrong about this,
maybe it's not necessary at all. But I feel that for somehow an extension of show notes outside of,
you know, just a description tag that you put into your blog post was going to be something
we would be desirable because in an OPML file, basically, let's use an outliner to create a
document, a text document, but it formats it on, on the back end as an XML file. So that's very
easy to parse and to, I guess, to index. So I think there's two, two kinds of search. One is,
you know, I'm looking for a show, you know, that I'm looking for dawn and drew, for instance,
or I'm looking for a show about, you know, a risk-a podcast. And then specifically in the show notes,
and that should draw all the way down into the ID3 tags of the file itself. And there should be
some consistency there. So these are things that will really make a great resource, you know,
a good resource to a great resource to have these, these pieces put in there. And I'll tell you,
right off the bat, we're not going to be building that. What was that? No, I'd say we'd probably
be doing some interesting, some interesting deals with people who already have that.
That I'm curious, and the listeners of the Daily Source Code, I need your help. That sound,
that was the sound of my wife running away screaming. You see, the fact is, I'm boring her to
death lately. I'm a geek, and she's not. She gets tired of hearing me go on and on and on and on
about tech and tech news. So you can help me out. Give me an outlet, listen to my podcast, give me
somebody to talk to, talk tech with, let's build a community. I just got one question for you.
Are you a geek? If you can answer yes to that question, you might like my podcast. So check it out at
www.areogeek.com. Oh, man. Well, you know, where's the hot or not podcast? You know, that's,
that's what we need. Where's the podcast dating service? Come on, people get it together. That's
great. I'm a geek. I'm proud to admit it. I am. I just let my wife dress me up pretty once in a
while. That's all you got to do. You know, let them clean up once in a while and then and give you
that, you know, that salmon Dave haircut. No, whatever. Yeah, let them do all that. Be a Barbie doll.
And then that's cool. You've got to cross over to the dark side once in a while.
Skinny on sports, fastest 10 minutes on your iPod, my favorite sports podcast. It's
Skinny on sports dot com. They put together the first sports award show podcast that I know of at
least. So go ahead, email me and tell me you were first. The human rented it. You invented a
award shows. What they did is it's very cool. They got a whole bunch of really well-known
podcasters. To basically do category categories of awards and had them all recorded. Oh, no,
I'm sorry. It wasn't pre-recorded. It was all happened in life, right? Just like Michael Geek,
Michael Butler, Rockin' Roll Geek, that turned off. That's not the venue.
Next, we're going to have to move outside where the pre-party and the post-party for the Skinny's
are going to be happening. Michael Butler is outside there with American heartbreak. And you know,
he always shows up with a full-on-terogent tonight at Skinny's. That's no exception. Michael, take it away.
I just blew it all away from San Francisco. And I got to take it. Boy, oh my god, I'm so tired.
Okay, so make sure you check that out. Don and Drew showed up. Michael Gohagan,
Dave Slusher, you know, the the pod squads there and full effect. It's definitely something you
got to check out. Skinny on sports, the first annual Skinny Awards. And my friend Kai Chesent me this,
she Skype instant message this, this MP3 to me. I've heard this before. It's a Monty Python
comedy skit. Although I don't think it's an actual one of the cast members who does the voice.
But it's something that if you haven't heard it, you just got to hear it again. It's only two and a
half minutes. It's not safe for work. And it is titled, what is it? The meaning of the word fuck.
Perhaps one of the most interesting words in the English language today is the word fuck.
Out of all of the English words that begin with a letter F, fuck is the only word that is referred to
as the F word. It's the one magical word. Just by its sound, can describe pain, pleasure, hate, and love.
Fuck, as most words in the English language is derived from German, the word freaking which means
to strike. In English, fuck falls into many grammatical categories as a transit of verb, for instance,
John fucks Shirley. As an intransitive verb, Shirley fucks. It's meanings not always sexual.
It can be used as an adjective, such as John's doing all the fucking work. As part of an adverb,
Shirley talks to fucking much. As an adverb, enhancing an adjective, Shirley is fucking beautiful.
As a noun, I don't give a fuck. As part of a word, absolutely, or in fucking credible.
And, as almost every word in a sentence, fuck the fucking fuckers.
As you must realize, there aren't too many words with the versatility of fuck. As in these examples,
describing situations such as fraud, I got fucked up a used carlaught. This may,
oh, fuck it. Trouble. I guess I'm really fucked now. Aggression. Don't fuck with me, buddy.
Difficulty. I don't understand this fucking question. Inquiry. Who the fuck was that?
This satisfaction. I don't like what the fuck is going on here. In confidence, he's a fuck off.
This missile. Why don't you go outside and play hide and go fuck yourself?
I'm sure you can think of many more examples. With all of these multipurpose applications,
how can anyone be offended when you use the word? We say, use this unique flexible word,
more often than your daily speech. It will identify the quality of your character immediately.
Say it loudly and proudly. Fuck you.
You know, that's one of those audio clips that circulates around the radio business every
couple of years. It got sent to me, as I said, just today. I figured I'd let you into the family.
If you hadn't heard that before, you know, now you remember that secret society. All you need to hear
now is the infamous KCK some dead puppy long distance dedication in your set.
I am again. All right, but another hit test. We're going to start right away. This is number one.
Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. You did that twice. Sharp breast man.
G G top. Yep, reminding you to tell you that my G G top is number two.
Don't waste my time. It's either things that don't waste my time.
Okay. Say, say, say, say. This is a good one, John. I like him. Michael Jackson. Say, say, say,
down in before the bell. And time's up and the yardy answers this is answer number one. Okay.
Uh, like a tie. It's the season top. It's sharp, dressed man.
Listen black tie.
My favorite part of the record. Uh, just play it.
And number two. Hey, very distinctive sounds. The sound of bad habits. This is Jimmy
Virgin. That's the song I meant, actually. Look at half a point.
Why can't I remember all the lyrics? Not the title of the song.
It's going to be easy.
Jenny birthday answer number two in today's hit test. And this is answer number three.
Oh, McCartney together with the trouble Michael Jackson.
This is, say, say, say, say. I guess I want to have a point for that too.
I want to say Michael Jackson.
Well, the reaction.
Answer number three. Full McCartney in Michael Jackson.
Well, let's hit again for today. It's a quick hit test.
You know what to do with the hit test at gmail.com. And you've been finding information at G and
the OLHE. And that stands for young folk at death in L. But I don't see you next time for another hit
missed. Bye. Bye. Actually, uh, so actually, as I sang along with that song reminded me
something we did on the on the radio show in the morning show that didn't haunt.
You know, uh, how sometimes you'll think that lyric goes a certain way and you'll be singing it,
but it's completely wrong. And it turns out to be actually pretty funny.
If you've had that happen to you, who's that? Oh, it's Ron Bloom. I'll tell you what. So we should
we put him on the show. Do that. So joining joining us now on the daily source code from Miami
Florida, it's Ron Bloom. Good morning. South Beach. I'm sorry. I'm in South Beach. I'm sorry for the
faux pas. It's just another planet. Hey, dude, how you doing? All right, man. How's it going?
Yeah, it's good. Daily source code land. Yeah, I just finished up the hit test almost done with a show.
You guys clear what a revival. 1983. What's the question? Uh, uh, what, uh,
band that John Fogretty played in. Is that it? Yeah, John Fogretty. Do I get another one?
Well, once it once was the largest band in the world. What? CCR? Yeah, so we did.
Didn't you get into like a big fight with Warner Brothers or something? Yeah, you know, they should
form a label with Springsteen. What do you mean Springsteen's in the same trouble? He went through
the thing where he couldn't record for five years and creed instead of that sort of kind of thing.
Yeah, well, so did Prince and wasn't that all was, so it wasn't all Warner Brothers then.
Yeah, just just artists being themselves. Mm-hmm. Anything to report, Ron, or uh,
if you could talk about it, you got any damage announcement? Yeah, I got any damage announcements,
did. Hey, come on, all the kids are doing it. You today. I think I can tell you that things look great.
And it was just fun. I was jumping around a room like a one-legged man that announced kick in front.
Oh, one of those days, huh? Yeah. Okay. Things are going well. Okay, cool. I'll uh,
I'll call in and check you later. I just wanted to check it and see how the show was going. Okay,
but thank you very much. Dr. Lateron. Bye bye. Yes, ladies and gentlemen. Okay, so there you have it.
First hand, he's excited. What was that excited as a one-legged man in a
ass-kicking contest? I'm not quite sure what that man. But anyway,
remind me to tell you this easy top story some other time. Okay.
That's it for your source code for today. March 24, 2005. Comments are welcome.
Adam at curie.com. You can leave some on our weblog www.curie.com.
DannySourceCode.com is where you can find the show notes. We can find the latest episodes.
And of course, the podcast. I'll be back tomorrow. The in-laws are here. So, hey, let's do some
sounds seen tour of the cottage with the in-laws. Then again, maybe now. I'll talk to my
everybody. Take care. Bye bye.