Delta Sierra Charlie 220.
A voice 65 million years in the making.
I'm a mysterious.
I'm like a horse.
Rated R17 not admitted without parent.
Well, we prepared to move on to the ceremony.
Prepare.
Nothing could ever prepare you for what awaits you at the ceremony.
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who managed what you can hear since radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
No one's going to stop you down in FCC to stick a kick at the revolutions.
This is great St. Clair from cruise box.
You're listening to Adam Curry.
On the daily source gun.
Kick it.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying.
How about that opening, huh?
It's July 4, 2005.
I love it.
Two minutes of doing nothing.
Just watching Megaseg roll on my eye.
Although I have to be honest and admit that it crashed.
I just upon opening the rock money enough.
So this is actually the restart of data source code episode
So 220 for August 5, 2005.
I'm sorry, August 4, 2005.
And you know what tomorrow is August 5.
That's actually, I think the fifth is our wedding anniversary.
We can never get it right.
We both keep forgetting it.
Look at our wedding certificate to see what year it was.
August 5, that's right.
1988?
Yeah.
Seems like a long time ago.
Then again, it seems only like yesterday.
All right, I'm the show today.
We've got a bit of the daily download I want to play for you.
Got an excellent, excellent number of little promos and bits.
And of course, some pod save music.
And of course, a mashover before you.
I want to talk about my GPS mania.
See, tomorrow, of course, we're going on vacation.
And I've spent quite a bit of time booking that over the past 48 hours.
I'd love to spew some about credit card companies.
How they operate.
And the weather is kind of, you know, it's kind of mellow today.
Maybe 21, 22 degrees centigrade.
So it's, it's not chilly, but the consensus is no sunshine.
Just on the edge.
But it's been a good day to sit inside and do all kinds of admin.
And sit on the phone with credit card companies.
All right, I've been playing a lot of DJ earworm mashups lately.
Today, something different to eight of sent it to me, eight of from mashuptown.com.
This one's titled We Belong Together, Time After Time.
And it's done by Arty Fuffkin.
So I can only imagine that Arty Fuffkin might be a duck, but I'm going to do that in a minute.
It's Mariah Carey and see you all.
I didn't mean it when I said I didn't love you still.
I should have held on time.
I never should have let you go.
I didn't know nothing, I was stupid.
I was foolish.
I would like to myself.
I couldn't rather know whatever being without your love.
Never imagined I'd be sitting there by myself.
Because I didn't know you, because I didn't know me.
But if I knew everything, I didn't want to be with you.
So please, I'm glad I feel it's not that I don't feel it.
Oh, you touch and kiss your lips, cos I don't have a choice.
All I wouldn't get an abulant, I'm not the same right here.
Cos we make no love, you can love, you will find this.
I love the time.
If you fall, I will catch you, I'll be waiting.
If you love, you can't love, can you will find this.
I love the time.
If you fall, I will catch you, I'll be waiting.
If you fall, I will keep in love.
I've been tired of my own
I've been all alone
You know, they would make total sense with a do something together.
A great idea, Cindy Lauberon, where I carry.
And like that.
Very cool.
Artie Fuffkin, brought to you by mashuptown.com.
Yeah, mashup for today for this Thursday, the fourth of August.
We belong together time after time.
Okay, first I want to talk about my carpal tunnel syndrome.
You know, keep talking about my shoulder and my hand.
But now I'm 99.9% convinced.
And you know, some doctors have told me that I basically have carpal tunnel syndrome.
And it's from yanking my yolk.
And that was from the weakstrate of anxiety training for my fixed wing pilot's license.
And I know that after this weekend, I flew for a couple hours on Saturday.
Actually for quite a while, you know, like maybe four or five hours.
And yep, most definitely.
That's what it's from.
So, and it seems like someday it seems better than others.
I'm not sure if I'm just getting more used to this kind of prickly, almost falling asleep like feeling in my left hand.
I can use everything fine.
I just don't have quite all the sensation in my index finger and thumb.
You know, so I can't really, you know, I have enough power in it.
But I can't really feel like if I'm grasping something properly.
It's, it's actually pretty fun.
Of is what it is.
But I guess I'm just going to take it easy for the next two weeks.
I don't know where you're ganking and see if it gets better.
There's a lot of different ways you can get rid of carpal tunnel syndrome.
But the best way, of course, is to give your is to give the problem area rest.
So, no more you're ganking.
It's been most of the day trying to actually I booked tickets yesterday for the New York leg of our trip with Virgin.
I had a whole bunch of miles, which I wanted to cash in for Christina and so we can all fly up or deck.
And, you know, so we can have a real experience.
And I booked the tickets and, you know, I have credit cards that go to Banking United States.
Man, you get red flagged on everything.
And then, you know, the total amount was over whatever limit had somehow magically been set.
And what could be spent per day anywhere abroad, since I'm ordering them in the United Kingdom.
So I had to split it up amongst two different cards.
And then, you know, so one card would be blocked and then I cleared that up.
And then, went back to the airline and then they split it up.
And just because of the, the weird nature of, do you hear this and say, oh, come on.
Just because of the weird nature of the purchase, all of a sudden in the United Kingdom,
they blocked the other cards.
It's just been around about everyone's been really helpful.
But, you know, it's all for your protection, sir.
You do understand this.
Like, fuck, no, it's for your protection.
Because, you know, the credit card companies guarantee the purchases.
It's certainly very obvious that US cards seem to be much more prone to fraud detection,
whether it's real or not.
But flags do seem to go off a lot more sooner than any of the European credit cards I have.
And you think that it's kind of like, you know, it would be the same everywhere,
but there's a few mungus difference.
And I can order just, oh, about anything on my European, my European credit cards.
And there's no problem at all.
And there's no real maximums.
And I don't know.
It's, uh, I guess there's just that much more fraud going on in the States,
and then you got to wonder why.
You know, why is there a difference?
Um, so just before I started the show,
my mother-in-law came running in big problem, big issue,
because one of the pieces of wood that we got yesterday for the table that my father-in-law
was going to build for me was missing when they delivered it today.
Oh, by the way, here's a joke, not to try in the United Kingdom.
Oh, uh, we, you know, we got all these huge pieces of 18 millimeter.
Uh, what is it?
Mf, whatever would, uh, Mf, I wanted to Mfc, but Mfp, Mfd, whatever.
Um, and we got them all saw it all the right pieces.
You know, I was supervising it there.
Myself the whole time to make sure we got everything right.
Um, and then I went, you know, it was just one of the,
basically the backboard of this whole table that my father-in-law is building me,
so that I can have my whole studio set up at the right height.
I don't have to bend over to get to the laptop and the mixer.
Um, and I like working standing up.
Um, so they, it was too big the backboard to put into the car,
so we had a delivered, which was 27 and a half pounds extra.
That's like, you know, 50 bucks to deliver it.
And I, of course, said, wow, do I get a blowjob with that?
And I got the blanket stare.
And like, no response whatsoever.
And I guess the guy didn't appreciate the joke.
Anyway, so they apparently misdelivered one piece.
So I have to go running after that before we leave tomorrow somehow.
Um, but he's busy.
He's in the garage.
He's starting to build it.
And the only bummer is that I'm not here really to document the process,
which sucks.
You know, I've got the plans.
I've got his blueprint.
I've got, uh, I took pictures in the store when we, um, bought the pieces.
And now I guess I'll get a couple pictures before we leave.
I think he's been putting some things together.
But this is going to be awesome.
And it's so cool to have someone, you know, just offered to do that.
So I'm, um, I'm, um, really flattered.
It's, uh, it's awesome.
It, it is awesome.
So can't wait.
What it's going to be like in two weeks when we come back.
Because tomorrow is our lead for vacation day.
And I've been talking a lot about the pod safe music network.
And, um, this, of course, is the place where artists, listeners,
and podcasters come together where we're really building the promotional vehicle
around this concept of pod safe music.
So the podcasters can have a place to find the music to play.
And, um, and report back on it.
So we know who's getting a lot of pod play.
And, you know, listeners tuning to that.
And that's how you discover new music.
It's basically one big discovery engine.
So that's, uh, been basically been built by, uh, three people, uh,
CC Chapman, uh, Chris Rockwell from the Daily Download,
and CC from the accident hash podcast.
And then, uh, two from, uh, the super super freaking action show.
Got that.
I'm just going to kill me now.
That's okay.
Because it's going to get mentioned again here.
Yesterday, I was listening to, uh, Chris Rockwell,
the Daily Download.
Now, you probably know him as the poop guy.
Uh, but, uh, to me as a guy.
This is, this is just a fantastic podcast.
The whole concept is, you know, this, it's a,
pooping is a guy thing.
Let's be honest about it.
So he started talking about, um, about the pod safe music network
and about Sue in, in particular.
Now, if you grow stout about poop, don't listen to this piece.
Uh, I think it's hilarious.
First, I wanted to think somebody, you know,
CC Chapman and I have been getting a lot of credit for the pod safe music network.
But one of the people that made it happen always seems to be left out.
And that's Sue from the extra super action show.
There you go.
She's really, I almost had an extra super action show.
So, so Chris clearly, um, uh, has tagged onto the right thing
because it just true Sue doesn't get enough of the credit in the mention.
She's also not, well, that's just not Sue.
So, uh, here come her, here come her props.
Or should I say plops?
One of the big stars of the PMN.
If it wasn't for Sue's design and willingness to make
shit happen super quick, there would be no PMN.
So, today I thought I would dedicate my poop to Sue.
So I'm going to sit down here.
And while I push, I'm going to say Sue's name out of appreciation.
So this is a one butt hole salute to Sue.
Sue.
What a interview.
So.
Sue.
just to talk to when I just handed the headphones off.
And so here's what happened.
So I had the headphones back on.
And this, you know, Christina's here with a girlfriend
and Patricia's rock walking around the in-laws.
And it's a lot of noise in the house.
And Samadcha's, oh, put Christina on it.
So I call Christina, I call her again.
And it's like unbelievable, you know,
I know she just walked away.
So how can she not hear me?
But there's also this general noise
that we have at the cottage, now the in-laws are here.
And it was just a full house.
And both Madge and Reagan Fox kind of glomed
on to the same thing here.
Check this out.
I was listening to East Radio today in Madge
interviewed Adam Curry and Adam Curry
had a very, very Joan Crawford moment.
His daughter's name is Christina.
Christina Curry, not to be confused with the other CC.
Christina Crawford.
I'm just talking to Madge, Christina.
Tell her hello for me.
Yeah, Christina says hi.
Can you put her on the phone or something?
Oh, Christina, Christina.
I'm not mad at you.
Christina.
I'm mad at the Christina.
I'm not going to do it now.
It sounds like I don't Crawford and let me
do her as a 10-year-old girl.
Yeah, Christina.
I'm just talking to Madge.
Can you put her on the phone or something?
Oh, Christina.
Christina.
Hi, I'm Christina.
Oh my God.
You sound like a Joan Crawford mommy,
do you hear us 10-year-old go death?
If you can't do that.
I don't do it at all.
These are the moments that make life worth living.
Christina.
Why are you doing that, Calvin?
No, no.
This is the teacher.
Christina.
No, I'm just going to the police.
Police is going and looking like a truck.
Christina, Christina, Christina, Christina, Christina.
Christina.
Oh my God.
This moment of podcasting hilarity is brought to you
by Reagan Fox.
Fox in the city.
Reagan Fox.com.
That's R-A-G-A-N.
Amazingly funny, yet somehow very disturbing.
Thank you very much.
It's brought a love summertime in the source code.
When I was young, I'm talking about the good times.
Just doing it.
Ha-ha.
When the time we ever cared about,
we had it all, we had it all, oh.
I'm talking about the good times.
Drinking all day, drinking all night.
Dance by the firelight.
Come on.
Because you are the one that's hard at the end.
You know that you are the one that's hard at the end.
You didn't put that on.
So much time.
You're all ready.
What?
I'm talking about the simple times.
Hey, it's a cool, no right, no road.
Read the lies from the obvious song.
Make our way up to Prost-Ret's Fund.
I'm talking about the good times.
No reason to find, because Bradley is tied,
and never think it's alright.
Make our way up to Prost-Ret's Fund.
You know that you are the one that's hard at the end.
I'm talking about the good times.
Currently number one on the podcast music network in pod plays.
It's brother love summertime.
And it's unbelievable.
This thing has the most plays.
I think the most listens.
Not the highest rated though, which is interesting,
because listeners can rate songs on the podcast music network.com or music.podshow.com.
I am so loving what's going on there.
It's really quite amazing.
Particularly the top 10 list.
So I'm wondering, is that something that gets cleared out at the beginning of
the month or is it top, you know,
the pod plays be of all time.
Because then, you know, we may not get new bands on very quickly in the top 10 list,
which is I think the same way podcast alley does it now,
where you have the top 10 is reset every month.
And on Fridays, we actually air the podcast alley top 10 on serious satellite.
Four hours worth of podcast.
And it is, it is very cool to see that, you know, now that everything's been cleared out,
usually it takes two or two and a half weeks before stuff kind of settles.
And then it gets cleared out again right after, after four weeks.
So the chart is constantly changing.
There's a pretty fair way of doing it.
So yesterday, I didn't do a source code because so many people had problems getting
to the source code due to my error of placing a hash mark in the URL.
Learn something new there.
Won't be doing that.
Although we're experimenting with some of our infrastructure over the next four
to eight hours, so you may not get this file as usual,
or you might have to wait for repose.
I'm not quite sure what's going to happen.
So bear with me and I really appreciate it when you tell me when you send me reports.
Yeah, I appreciate it.
I get lots of them.
When something goes wrong with the show, I get lots of reports.
But I do appreciate you letting me know.
Usually people say, well, this is probably the five hundred email you've received.
And I'm always worried about saying, don't send it to me because then, you know,
people might not send anything thinking that someone already did send it to me.
So you know, keep the warnings coming.
It's okay.
I can sit through the email.
So I did have some time yesterday to geek out some more on this GPS stuff.
And I'm not quite sure where it's going still.
And what the use to mankind is going to be,
but I'm really totally enjoying this.
We went to get the wood.
And so this, what is it?
Blue tech, a real tech GPS, bluetooth GPS unit that I have.
It can log 30,000 data points internally just by itself.
So you don't need to hook it up to your pocket PC or anything.
And you can just take this little box along.
Just put it on your dashboard and you're good to go.
So it recorded the route.
You know, from the cottage all the way to the, to the hardware store.
And then back to the cottage.
And then I finally figured out how to turn that into pure,
NEMA data, N Mia data, November, Mike echo alpha data.
Whatever the hell that stands for.
Notical, meteorological, something or other.
And then the real format that seems to be whatever one's developing against is
GPS, the GPS exchange format, which is a version of, it's an XML format.
And I'm already here in some people going, well,
Boo, this may not be whatever, but I'm telling you,
GPS seems to be the prevalent format.
And there are lots of cool little sites where you can upload your GPS
and it'll draw you a Google map.
But the most exhilarating thing I saw was with Google Earth.
If you haven't downloaded Google Earth yet, do it.
Because it's a free application.
And it's basically a 3D rendering of the globe.
And you can fly to places.
You can swoop in and see both road maps.
And you know, hybrid with photographic overlays.
Although the US is much better than the rest of the world.
You can get down to much greater detail.
But at least you can kind of see, you know, like the leisure centering
Guilford.
It's big enough for me to see kind of the white colors on the photograph.
Hey, huh?
What's up?
Packing.
Packing?
Oh, that's right.
She's packing for tomorrow.
I have the most amazing suitcase.
It's the automatic self-packing unpacking suitcase.
Yeah.
What do I have to do?
What stuff do I have to do?
Oh, everything got taken care of.
Take it to a paid for credit card companies happy.
We have a hotel.
I'll see that you are far.
I know.
But that took fucking hours this time.
Usually it's really easy.
I try to get the better end of the deal.
I know.
Okay.
So anyway, GPX format.
I'm sorry.
I'm geeking out here, huh?
I know you're geeking.
Yeah.
And GPS shit.
So you load that into Google Earth.
When you're so geeky.
Really?
Yeah.
I'll show you how to load my GPX into your Google Earth.
Hold on.
Well, I just got a message.
What was that?
Still in Florida.
Okay.
I guess Ron didn't go to Texas yet.
He's still in Florida.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe he's still able to get some more stuff ready before leaving.
Yeah.
They're going to be in San Francisco for a long time.
Oh, when we are there, they're going to be there too.
Yeah.
Well, first they go.
They're going to Texas.
Remember for a wedding?
Can't get rid of this guy anymore.
Can't be.
No, of course not.
No, no.
All right.
So now my mother-in-law's walked into.
Hey, Alice.
Hi.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
Hi.
All right.
I'm going to continue with the GPX format if you don't mind.
So you can load this into Google Earth.
And you can, you know, you can set the camera angle.
You can set how far out you're viewing.
You can fly over the route that you took.
It's really, it's really cool.
So now I want to spend a little more time figuring out how to add waypoints.
I guess I can figure that out.
I'd like it to be automatic where I kind of just drop in a file of pictures.
And it picks up the time code and paste them in the appropriate spot.
And then, of course, the real trick is to synchronize that with audio.
And once we have those three pieces together, and I think maybe the Google Earth viewer
is the right application to develop this against.
And unless, of course, someone's even better on maybe the Google Maps API is better to use
because the API is there.
I haven't looked at it.
And I don't know what it can do.
But essentially what you want to do is you want to upload your GPX data file.
You want to upload your pictures and your pictures all have time stamps in the file.
So you can align those two up with waypoints or data protract points.
And then, of course, you want to have it synced in real time to a podcast, to an MP3 file,
which I think also has, I wonder how we do the time code on the MP3.
Well, I have to think about that.
Maybe you'd have to sync it up somehow.
But if we could have that and the output be a quick time movie or the output be something that runs
in flash or just runs on the internet like the Google Maps API is interactive.
If we have that, and these pictures can pop up at certain points and you could stop,
and you could take a bigger look at the picture and you could add URLs.
Then, I think we've got something really fucking cool.
So that's just my shout out.
Please don't make me develop this.
You heard him at the opening of the show.
Might as well roll him out at the end of the show.
Cruise box.
Tell the FCC to stick a kick and I heard it on the podcast.
Do you remember?
We back last summer.
When mainstream radio was such a fucking monomer.
No Indian music.
Nothing to funny.
Cleared channel.
Motherfuckers.
They had a problem on it.
But somebody heard it wrong.
Now you can have it all.
I heard it on the podcast.
Rock and fucking radio.
You want it.
Got it.
Just download it and hide it on the podcast.
No one's going to stop.
You're telling FCC to stick and pick it.
The revolution is on.
Do you remember?
Your first computer.
That piece of shit was like a freaking rotor.
Now we've got Wi-Fi.
Downloading files fast.
This meant to everyone who's ever done on podcast.
It's his duty.
Now you see.
Each and every nation.
The radio is got to cool.
It's our imagination.
Me that song.
Sing a loud mash it up.
It makes it real.
It's fucking built up.
I can't fix it.
You're so bad.
Hear it.
Come on.
Now you can have it all.
You can make your real sound.
I heard it on the podcast.
Rock and fucking radio.
You want it.
Got it.
Just download it and hide it on the podcast.
No one's going to stop.
You're telling FCC to stick and pick it.
The revolution is on the podcast.
Rock and fucking radio.
You want it.
Got it.
Just download it and hide it on the podcast.
No one's going to stop.
You're telling FCC to stick and pick it.
The revolution is on the podcast.
Crew's box.
FCC.
Stick it.
Kick it.
The revolution is on.
That's it for the source code for today.
August 4th.
2005.
It's not anniversary tomorrow.
Is it tomorrow when we're flying?
Tomorrow's the 5th, right?
August 5th.
I told you I told you she didn't know either.
But how long has it been?
Long time.
You love me.
I love you.
Long time.
18.
But it feels like.
20 new old 19 years.
We know each other.
Yeah.
Feels like the first time baby.
I was such a kid.
I'm no longer a call.
I don't.
I don't qualify.
I was a young boy.
Now I'm a smelly man.
Yeah.
All right.
Thank you very much for checking us out.
Tomorrow starts the vacation cast.
I guess there'll be lots of little bits from the road.
Kind of sound seen to it, right?
I guess so.
It's time we go out.
We always wear a mic.
We have to take everybody.
If life is worth living, it's worth documenting.
That's what ever we do.
That's right.
No.
It's very different.
It's not edited.
Okay, baby.
My little clown was hurt.
All right.
Adam at curie.com.
statelysourcecode.com for the podcast feed etc.
Thanks for subscribing.
Talk to you very soon.
Bye bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Thank you.