Daily source code, 2-1-2000 meters, we don't need no stinkin' transmitters!
Get ready for the generation of rockers!
Augustine, it's Adam Curry!
Hey everybody, welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Today is Wednesday, the first of all.
Coming to you from Curry Cottage and the lovely affluent Surrey Suburb of Gilford.
This is the Daily Source Code today.
As Wednesday, it's February 1, 2005.
I guess we're supposed to say, what is it?
Rabbit, rabbit, or bunny bunny?
Something like that.
It's supposed to bring you big buck and big bucks.
It's a little different show today.
I think I mentioned yesterday that I was being interviewed by CNN.
So if you think yesterday was wacky, today is going to be even more interesting.
It's about a thousand degrees in the quote studio with all the lights on.
And I've got eyes in my back.
So the next 40 minutes I'll bring you a couple of promos, got some pot-safe music.
I'm also going to talk about, I've got some techno bits to talk about as well.
As usual, I'll show about nothing.
I guess the couple of the, what was it?
The cheap trick record fell off the wall.
Not once at the beginning of the show, but twice at the end of the show.
I got a lot of email from people saying that perhaps the cottage is a bit haunted,
or perhaps it's a message.
Actually, I'm looking at my show notes right now, and of course you can check that out at curry.com.
A message from Bob said, is it possible that maybe this was just cheap trick trying to give you a message that they really want you to play one of their tunes?
Good idea.
I want you to want me on your daily source code.
I want you to want me.
By the way, Michael Butler, but you didn't enjoy this one, buddy.
I believe you.
I love you, I believe.
I believe you to make me.
I want you to want me.
I love you, to love me.
Shout out for those who used to draw their mission.
They don't hurt them.
You may say that you know me.
I want you to want me.
I love you, I love you, I love you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you
, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you. you, you, you, you,
Teamtime
I want to be with you
I'll be with you
I know you will be with me
To beg me
I want you to want me
It was a good thing seeing an end to you
How else would I have known that there is no Wednesday February first
Of course it's Tuesday
And were you sitting there in the car during that song saying
I'm sorry
I want you to want me to keep track on a daily source code for Tuesday February first 2005
That of course played because yesterday the platinum cheap trick record that I gave me in the
I guess was it early nineties
What is that?
Let me see what the date is on that
It's a
I can't even see it because the cassette is on
Remember the cassette shifted in when it fell
I can't tell
What has it been?
I don't know
I do know that Patricia and I went to the Montro
It was at the time was the Montro Rock Festival
Which was held right around the time of the Montro Jazz Festival
In Switzerland
And at that I see me see it was Robert Palmer was there
I think I've told you the Robert Palmer story
But I don't know if I've told you the cheap trick story
Because Rob and Zander who he celebrated a birthday
Just recently I heard on the rock and roll geek show
Michael Butler said he turned like
He was in the 50s now Rob and Zander from cheap trick
I think he must be close to it
He was hitting on my wife like no one else is business
At the casino until I walked in
Of course and give him a piece of my mind
Hey Adam this is Chris Chapman
I'd like to respond to your podcast from January 28
Okay Chris
The Friday edition the 28
You're as bad as dates with I am Chris
You were speaking very early on in the show about
The glitches and recordings that the dropping on the sound
Alright this is where I did the sound seeing tour of
I think it was the sound seeing tour of
Guildford or was it the MTV Chronicles that I did with Ken
Where we had some dropouts in the audio
And what had you?
Yeah
I thought I'd pass along a few tips of how to
Avoid that
Okay
First of all
It's a really good idea to record on a secondary
Hard disk other than your boot drive
Especially truly in Mac OS 10
I'm not sure about the Windows environment so much
The problem with that Chris is that
Then I've got to be slipping along
Firewire drives and stuff
And even if you're talking about a secondary hard drive
Even with Firewire I think it's still going to be
It's going to be some latency
I've done all this stuff with Final Cut Pro
And other big media programs
And eventually these hard drives get sick
And I don't think our computers were made to do this
To actually play back audio files
And record them at the same time
That's what it seems like to me
What that allows you to do
It is right and a free stream
That's unencumbered by the system
Trying to maintain itself right
It's log files and process system events
Especially if you're doing audio hijack
Or you're saving mail or you're doing Skype calls
I think the problem was just that I was
Playing back a huge file
Must have been 600 megabytes because it was an AIFF
And then recording to AIFF
I think that's for the problem came in
But maybe we'll try that
We'll try recording on an external drive
Next time I do a soundseeing tour
If it doesn't work, then I'll just revert back to the old system
Okay
Well Adam, the truth is out
Grant Piccolo and dumb price
Are the creators of PWFenton
PWFenton is a fictional character
Who in their strange twisted world
produces the podcast Digital Flatsom
I hope you're satisfied
So this is the big Doctor Floyd versus PWFenton controversy
So now we're all straight now
Actually our team suffrage
Holded the microphone
Yes
Did you hear that?
Let's just listen to the CNN guys
Yeah, well did you say that cheap trick was playing at a gay club
What club is that?
A story
A story?
Where?
In the top and top road
Really?
When are they playing?
Oh five years ago
Okay, I was like, wow I got to go see
I'm going to go beat Rob and Zander up
I'm going to hit on my wife again
Something that we've been doing for the past couple
Actually about a week and a half here on the daily source code
Is the the trivia of the day
Which some are calling the stump the stupid podcaster
Others, I mean there's a lot of production
It's going to this of course
I think it was our body
From the Netherlands who started that off
Yon Polet
He started that off
It's a really high production value
Which I liked a lot
I have yet another trivia
MP3 that was sent to me today
Let me see if I can
Who did suicide this to me
Probably mentioned it in the opening
Listen
Hi Adam
I have four short clips with distinctive intros
Okay
From the 60s and 70s
All right
Four short clips distinctive intros from the 60s and 70s
I should be able to do this
I'm sure you'll get these
Yeah, okay
Answer's at the end
All right, hit me baby
Oh
Okay, you got me
I don't know the first one
I don't know what that is
I bowed
Okay, one down
What's the next one?
Sam and Dave hold on
I'm coming
Or as we like to say here
Tony and Guy
That was easy
Next one
Third one in the list
Brickhouse Commodore's
Okay
That's actually
Isn't that 80s?
That still qualifies the 70s
I'm lying on richy head then
Horrible Afro
Okay
And now for the fourth one
I've got two out of three so far
I should know this
I know you're sitting here car going
I know the answer
Oh
Shoot what is this
Of course I bang a gun
T-Rex
All right, here come the answers
Hello
Okay, the answers are
Number one
Farmer John by the premieres
Please
Got a room for the guy to go in
Uh
No
That's my birth year
Okay
Number two
Hold on, I'm coming
Sam Dave
I got that
166 and then the Commodore's
Number three
Brickhouse
Commodore's
Okay
Number four
Long cool woman
In a black dress
The Holly's
Long cool woman in a black dress
Oh man
So I got like two out of four
It's official
I suck
Hey Adam
It's KCT of KCTs digital world.com
And I'm sending you a
Link to my commute cast
I sent you an email
The other day on the commute cast
As a concept
I've cleaned it up a little bit
To make it a little bit better
And I hope you give it a listen
My goal is to
Once a week
Do a cast in my commute
And take questions
And be a audio feed that I can learn to
C.D. and play during the commute
And hey
Well I'll come meet together
Sure beats radio
And C.D.
So
We'll see what happens
Give it a shot
And tell me what you think
Thanks
KCTs digital world.com
The commute cast
Definitely subscribe to that
Also thank you very much for all the
The pointers to the sound
Seeing tours that I keep updating the feed
With
SoundSayingTours.com
What was I going to say?
Oh yeah
Remember yesterday we did the wake cast
I just got a Skype message
From Ron Bloom
Let me see
Okay
Said
Hi Adam
I heard the wake cast
This was due to the death of his father
90 years old
So more celebration of life than anything
So Ron Skype me said
Hear the wake cast
We'll be playing for those
Sober enough to make it to breakfast
That's morning
Thanks so much for all the kind
Wishes.
The funeral was beautiful
And many kind words said
And much good humor
There were 50 to 75
Attending which was a surprise
In my eulogy
I thanked them and told them about
The good wishes for dad
From around the world
It was a theory moment
So that is of course
Coming from
Even from podcast
And then a second message from Ron
I think this is great
It said thanks again to all the
Daily source code listeners
For the kind wishes and good vibes
As for the show
I was told by the rabbi
The Jewish tradition has it
Upon reaching heaven
Everyone is given a white
iPod
Stay tuned for the heaven cast
That's something
Belonged under our godcast
Quarter category
Don't you think
Continuing with the
You don't own me vibe
We've been on for the past week and a half
And start off with the
LeCivius Bitties
With their cover
You don't own me
We've gone through
The original Leslie Gore
We've had Rasputina
All of these of course
Except for Leslie Gore
And today
And this actually was suggested by
Number of people
Through email again
All of this on the show notes
It's curry dot com
Or daily source code dot com
This comes from Greg
And Boston says
Love Rasputina
Maybe you'd like to
Regale your audience
With yet another cover
For your consideration
Attached
You don't own me by
Clouse Nomi
It's from his uncore album
That's from 1983
And it's different
That's for sure
Check this out
It's kind of like a
Rock opera
Depressed version
It's like you want to grab the
Toaster and jump into the bathtub
Along with a Leonard Cohen wreck
You don't own me
You don't know me
I'm not just a
Not your little toy
You don't own me
Don't say I can't claim it
But
You don't own me
I'm just a
Love Rasputina
And Boston say
What
Don't say I can't claim it
You don't own me
Don't try me down, all I need is to take
And go and tell me what to say
Don't try, what to do
Just imagine me being myself
That's all I have for you
I know, then I'll be next to you
And I'll be next to you
To give my life the way I want
Take care of the two
Whatever life will be
And I'll be next to you
You don't know me
I'm not just one of your little toys
Don't say I can't play with other boys
And I'll tell you what to say
And I'll be next to you
To give my life the way I want
Okay, be honest, did you skip forward through it
Or did you like it?
Definitely different, that's for sure
You know, I actually have a bruise on my knee
From hitting the Louis XIV
I turned around
We did this new set up
Patricia and I cleaned up the whole office studio
It's working okay
But the desk and the chair, the combination
For some reason just doesn't
Maybe I need a different
I could actually do with a mic stand
Maybe that's what I need
Not just the one that sits on the desk
But one that comes around from the side
Something like the professionals use
Her great montage
Last night I was in the bathtub
Pulled the iPod in
Not into the tub but close enough
And I was listening to
The title of the podcast caught my eye
Used radios symphonic magic
And I just decided to play this
So haven't queued it up
Let me just see if I can find this
My pussy out
Oh please, magic
You're horrible as usual
Okay, here it comes
Let's just go back a little bit
Okay
This is the best thing on the internet
It is a deep sense
Adam Curry
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Gosh, you're so asleep
I wasn't going to sleep
What?
I'm not in a haze
The affluent neighborhood of the
Sorry, yes
Engel it
Yes, Gilford
The money
The next door to Madonna
And the downtown Julie Brown
Listen
It is absolutely impossible
That I can live next door to Madonna
And downtown Julie Brown
Okay
Just does not exist
Alright, this is it
This is so amazing
And whoever did this
I didn't see your email or anything
So whoever did this
It gets a free Madge Weinstein DVD
You just have to email me
Because this is a wonderful
Oh my god
Too much build up
You'll probably hate it
But I love it
Hello everyone
Madge Weinstein here
I don't know if you can hear that
Wonderful sound
In the background
But that is the sound
As a California pizza kitchen
Pizza being ready
To stop for Madge Weinstein's highhold
And when I talk in the morning
Oh we can't
Oh, you know how easy it is
Being me it's not
You know
It's not easy to be a mental patient
I'll tell you why
Because what happens is
The slightest thing goes wrong
And you get an anxiety
An anxiety is worse than depression
But I have both
An anxiety is this all-consuming
Sort of psychosis
It's just sort of below the surface
All the time
You never know what is going to come
And take over your consciousness
So Madge had a go
And I told her I would finish for her
Um
She wanted me to tell you
That um
She'll be back very soon
But she was having um
What did she call it
Spirish who will difficulties
She was feeling fact
It's really the bottom line
I know what to close with
You know you can tell me a lot of things
You can call me a country you can call me a lawyer
You can tell me to go fuck myself
You can tell me I'm in sensitive to breast cancer
Because I think yeast is worse or whatever
But don't tell me I don't exist
Sure
What ever married
In a beautiful
Oh my that was so lovely
I love
Um
So if you haven't checked it out yet
That's a podcast you uh
It's not safe for work I'll point that out right at the beginning
But it's something you do not want to miss
This is Madge Weinstein at her best
yeastradio.com
It's a great podcast
And especially if um
If you're in a technology as well
Manch has has a down
You know knows a lot about the McIntosh
Wants a Mac
And once someone to buy her a G5
One with less fan noise
Um
But it's a great podcast
Definitely something you uh
You should listen to
I'm going to do uh
Actually I'm going to keep it short today
Um
Because I'm tired
So it's for the afternoon
I'm done
Let's leave it at that shall we
As always
Your comments are welcome
You can send your MP3s to MP3 feedback at gmail.com
Please only MP3s to that address
So I kind of keep the mail separate
I'm in email hell again
You know everyone sends all these nice emails
It's great but just have no time to reply
I don't even get to
And Adamacurry.com is uh
The regular email address
All the latest shows at dailysourcecode.com
For the archives
The new shows and of course
The podcast feed
And the weblog
www.curry.com
Tomorrow it will be Wednesday
I promise you that
It will be the second of February
And we'll be back with more
Promost Potsafe tunes
And some techno bits
That's it for me
Take care everybody
See you tomorrow
Bye
Thank you