Daily source code February 3rd 2005.
Transmators?
We don't need no stinkin' transmators.
Get ready for the generation of rocker.
Autistic is Adam Curry.
It's Thursday, February 3rd 2005.
The power of the Lord is the Lord.
Once again, welcome to the Daily source code.
Hi everybody, my name is Adam Curry.
Coming to you from a brand new studio setup,
which I thought was going to be really convenient.
But it's actually not.
I got to take a picture of this.
I've now completed my podcast console armchair studio.
You need to see this picture.
Got this huge green recliner.
I think let me see if I can take a picture of my camera phone right now.
While I'm at this, this is just too good.
I've got it totally tricked down now.
Hold on.
Let's get the camera portion of this.
Okay.
Of course, I won't actually take a picture of my hair, right?
That would be bad.
There we go.
I have that look.
Hmm.
Lots to do some more.
Hey, today is trivia Thursday.
That means we've got lots and lots of trivia.
Some promos and pod safe tunes right here on your source code.
So I've actually been shooting now.
This thing is already into delayed mode.
I'm sounding like I'm drunk as usual.
Let me just grab a little cup of coffee.
It's 120 in the afternoon on Thursday here and go for the curry cottage.
I was going to bring Patricia into talks and show her his crap and stuff.
But I didn't know that she had a appointment at the nail salon.
So unfortunately, won't be able to bring her into the show today.
But I had a great morning.
As I said, getting the pod cast armchair console all ready to roll.
Oh, I've got the breakout box to my left here.
Coffee's on top of that.
Got this thing called it's the plateau de foté, which is kind of like a,
What would you call that?
A tray, kind of like a tray that you use for TV dinners.
And it clips onto the side of this huge green armchair that I have.
This is a recliner.
And there's probably about at least 100 people who know this chair.
Because this is the chair that I had in my office in New York at Think New
Ideas.
And it's just this huge, gotty green leather reclining chair.
It has kind of a, yeah, a little bit of a chest of field vibe to it.
Like a modern chest of field.
And you can almost recline completely flat out.
You control the reclining level kind of by balancing your feet on the,
On the footstool that comes up and the pressure you put on your back.
So I got the laptop on that tray.
I have the microphone right here to my left.
Actually, I've set it up so that I now can test the other mic that I have.
Hold on.
I want to turn this one off.
And here's the, oh, that does sound kind of different.
Doesn't, hold on.
Turn that up a second.
Hold on.
Let me just set this hijacked thing to.
Well, I'm at it.
Okay.
There we go.
The reason I hope this up is because I now have two microphones in, in the breakout box.
It does sound different.
It's also significantly less quality, or let's,
Maybe the price to quality performance actually isn't that bad.
Because this is a realistic microphone.
That's right.
It's from radio shack.
It's the one that kind of looks like a sure microphone.
I don't have a, a windscreen on it.
Let me see.
Was there a model number on this?
It's, I'll turn on the other microphone.
I'll turn on this one while I'm talking.
It's a 33-1070B.
Whatever that means dynamic microphone.
On the directional made in Mexico.
So now I'm talking on the, on the radio shack mic.
And now I'm back on the sure microphone.
I know you can tell the difference, but in a pinch,
you know, if Patricia walks in,
I can finally just hand her a mic.
And she can participate in the show.
And that's what I was already for.
Uh-huh.
Guess what?
Ain't gonna happen.
Michael Jackson says he's innocent.
Ronald says so too.
With rimpters like this voice bomb.
One can a humanitarian do.
The second phase of jury selection has begun.
When their chosen will one side already have one.
Hillary Clinton fainted as she tried to give a speech.
Does this mean she won't be painted?
Is the residency in her reach?
Or will momentum shift?
The bar brought boxer?
A little attack.
This might have boxer.
Leonardo DiCaprio's life of achievements.
At the elderly age of 30.
Let to an Oscar usually given prior to bereavements.
At least as acceptance speech will not be worthy.
A rackie votes are being counted.
Press the fire on the skin of stop.
But the Shiites are sure they won't.
So they're not likely just to drop it.
They said the government will allow the suitees in.
It's too silly to tell.
If all will go well.
But then again it will demand the bomb to spin.
Stay tuned for light breaking.
All done.
That's the tap dancing.
Podcasting news.
Yeah.
Always great to hear another tap dancing podcast.
The news update.
On the today's show as I tease the beginning.
It's Thursday.
So we're going to try and keep Thursday for trivia day.
Young polette has been sending in these hit tests, which are so highly produced and so exciting.
And surprising actually yesterday.
He slipped in an old air check of mine from Z100 in New York.
Which is me just puke and all over the place man.
Hey everybody.
I can see 100.
You wonder why I can do that so well.
Because I'm just I've done it so long.
A couple of the things we were talking about yesterday.
One I was talking about typing that my typing skills are a good.
I'm a very fast typeer.
But that I just can't type blindly.
I've gotten a lot of comments.
And by the way, we've got to figure out a way to incorporate all this stuff.
Maybe I need some kind of different weblogs set up or something.
Because often.
So if you listen to a podcast and you go back to the entry on daily source code.com.
There's a link to the show notes.
You also want to look at the comments.
Because comments often contain links to things that I've talked about.
Or just good ideas.
Or maybe there's an MP3 that I couldn't find.
You want to look at those comments.
So really what we need to do is start to aggregate all this stuff together.
So that when you listen to a show or if you go back and listen to an archive show.
Or you know, however you are checking it out if you want to hear more.
You know, that you'll be able to find a kind of all in one place.
So already it's starting to get a bit of control.
I figured this out.
So Cindy, better known as squipper.
Who is one half of the Ken and Squip show.
Said, Adam, it's easy for you to break the habit of looking at the keys while you type.
Just get yourself a poster size keyboard layout that you can hang on a wall in front of your laptop or desktop.
Force yourself to look up at the poster and not at the keyboard.
And you'll get the hang of it in no time.
And of course there's a link there to a poster, which haven't printed out yet.
But what I will do and I actually have been trying this.
I've been forcing myself to look at the screen not the keyboard as I'm typing.
It makes for some interesting typing.
I'll tell you that.
It's some interesting words pop up.
But I'm getting better.
I think you're right.
Cindy, I think it is just a question of, yeah, just doing it.
Also some people have sent in comments saying that I shouldn't necessarily discount
our computer-based programming that will help you learn how to type blind.
Excuse me, don't I just have a sip of my coffee here?
Hmm.
Oh man.
So since we have, since it's trivia Thursday, we're not only going to do young
Polettes trivia, we'll also be doing a couple other ones.
Some different types of trivia came in today.
So that's on the way.
And also, as usual, some questions, comments, and some podcasts.
If music coming up.
Hello Adam, this is Jeff Venture from Poland.
Hello.
I'm going to make crank up.
I'm going to crank up that sound.
See, this is the problem when I get shoot.
When I get MP3s that recorded just in a very, very low volume.
And then you don't notice it until you're actually on the, well, on the, until you're doing
the show.
I'm going to crank this one up as far as it can go.
So I'm actually opening up the quick time player preferences for this MP3 file.
Sounds like this is also one channel, hold on a second.
Let's see what's going on.
Hello Adam.
This is Jeff Venture from Cooking on the Radio.
And listening to today's show, I heard somebody talking a little bit about
MP3 players that will display song lyrics.
And it may be a way to get show notes, which got me thinking about the new photo iPods.
This might be something that could be scripted for the sound seeing tours.
Now, hearing people snapping pictures along the way and being able to get the visual element
with the podcast as some people have been doing online has certainly been great.
But wouldn't it be really cool if as you're listening to your podcast on your photo,
based iPod, if the images would appear on the screen synchronized to the podcast.
Yeah, it's actually something we've been talking about.
Well, hold on a second for your technical question.
Yeah, we haven't talking about that.
I'm not quite sure how it works on the iPod photo.
I also don't know how many of those.
I have a feeling for some reason.
I could be wrong that the iPod photo is maybe the cube of the iPod line up that
maybe this is just something that's so pretty and so beautiful,
but so not extra functional that people don't buy it.
I have no idea what the sales statistics are on the iPod photo,
but clearly that would be great.
I mean, Apple has all of the capability to make that, you know,
make that work.
And maybe we'd have to use AAC files or something that can send along a tone to kick the
iPod photo into switching the next photo in the slideshow.
But yeah, it would be nice.
Okay, now back to your technical question.
Which is what I'm using to record right now.
I know that when you record with yours, you use a wireless microphone set up.
I'm using a wired-level ear mic.
And when I record in mono mode,
I don't get any audio recorded on the device at all.
It seems that my mono microphone is coming in on the left channel.
Yeah, no shit.
Which the Irivers default settings to record mono.
It records the right channel.
Which is that being completely blank of audio.
Because you don't, yeah, it does.
It's one of if you had any experience with this,
would love to hear your feedback and love to show.
No.
Keep it up.
Yeah, do it.
Totally.
What you need to do is you need to put the Irivers.
As far as I know, once a stereo jack to be inserted,
you're probably inserting a mono jack.
Don't ever insert anything that's just mono.
And that's why it's probably only hitting the left channel.
That's probably also why it's so damn soft.
Although, I think on the Iriver, you can set the levels.
I was just really almost inaudible.
And I know that people sitting there going,
can't hear it cranking up the volume.
I know, I know.
We try to do our best with these things.
So I would suggest getting a conversion wire,
or maybe waking up making one,
that'll take your, have a female mono jack going into a stereo
and just basically combining those two channels together
because obviously that sucks to have it only record one channel.
And I think it's not a question of the, of the Iriver
only wanting to record one channel.
You probably just have the wrong jack.
And it's probably even fucking up the volume.
Also, yesterday, what we're talking about,
we talked about Steve Leeds and,
and serious, sadly I was talking about the bandwidth
of the satellite that's serious.
It's pretty much, they can't add any more channels
because they don't have any more spectrum available.
And I was saying that this is probably measured in megabits per second
and therefore no more bandwidth.
They even have some of the torque channels now in mono
so that they can squeeze more channels in.
Email from Rob Freedon says Adam,
answer to your question about the satellite bandwidth is measured.
The unit of capacity for satellites is the transponder.
Transponders?
We don't.
No stink in transponders.
These units are measured in megahertz.
Usually 36 to 72 megahertz.
Of course, you can make a conversion from bandwidth
to throughput, which is a digital environment
and it's measured in bits per second.
I am a telecom's professor at Penn State University
and teach this stuff.
You might have interest in a tech course syllabus
on my web page.
And of course, you provide the link
which you can find in the show notes for today.
Cool.
Very cool.
I'd like to know more.
Maybe you couldn't help me out with some of this
conversion stuff and let's figure out how much
it would be kind of cool to figure that out.
Because I think that I believe serious
is actually using the AAC codec,
which is what Apple uses for bookmarking
capabilities, what Apple uses.
Although it's pretty much similar to MP3,
I believe, and it's licensing capabilities
and it's probably even compresses a little bit better.
But I'd like to know how many bits per second
they're using per channel and just what exactly
their capacity is.
By the way, can I just say that I'm very proud
of Professor's listening to the show?
No, I never would have thought it.
Hi, Adam. This is Jaime Wattis.
I wanted to talk to you about two things.
First of all, podcast, avalemos.
So slowly but surely, it's coming along.
I got my first interview done.
It's both in Spanish and in English.
Just subscribe to the appropriate feed
and you'll get the right language.
So there were URL for it.
It's www.battis.org-ablemos-ablemos.cgi.
And Battis is spelled B-A-T-I-Z.
Ablemos is spelled H-A-B-L-E-M-O-S.
And I hope you'll have a chance to listen to it
and to mention it in your show
so that a lot more people might want to check it out.
Second thing is about this,
so the Spanish node has a couple of entries of mine.
Now, this avalemos podcast and my first one.
So I want to volunteer.
If nobody else has volunteer already
to maintain that part of the directory.
So you'll just have to walk me through
about OPML, what do I have to do in my own server
to get that going, but I love to help with that?
So please stay in touch.
My email is jb.podcast.com
and looking forward to listening for me
from you.
Okay.
Okay, thanks a lot.
Hi, my excellent.
Of course, if you don't have me for a while,
he's been doing these Spanish language podcast,
also some Spanish podcast.
And he mentioned the, I potted out org directory.
Yes, I'd love for you to maintain the Spanish node.
And this is actually something we haven't talked about
in a while, but pretty important.
The I potted out org directory is different
from other podcast directories that you'll see.
First of all, it's not really a directory,
like for instance, we have podcast alley,
which I like a lot because it has a voting feature
and rating feature and people love those
and it drives a lot of traffic to the directory.
But when it comes to really maintaining a useful resource,
I think I potted out org does someone better job.
Also, all the information from I potted out org,
the actual directory itself,
is made available through an opml file,
which anyone can use to populate their own directory,
which I don't know if podcast alley does it,
but I know a number of others do.
So feel free to just click on the XML icon
in the podcast directory at ipotted.org.
That is the opml file, which you can suck in periodically.
And it's just an opml file full of RSS URLs,
which you can then parse to get channel names,
titles, descriptions, et cetera.
But what's great about it is I don't maintain it all by myself.
In fact, I do very little work on it,
except for what's new and categories
that aren't currently maintained by someone else.
But all I have to do is just receive a URL from
Limey for instance, which he'll create an opml file for
and he just plugs in some RSS links to podcast feeds.
And all I have to do is paste the URL of his opml file
into my outline for the ipotted.org directory,
and it's all taken care of.
So when you're in the directory and you actually click on
the language node and go into Spanish,
then you'll get Himey's listing.
And on the website for ipotted.org,
if you're in that level of the directory and you want to add a link,
there'll be a suggest a link that you just click on.
It'll automatically go to the maintainer of that node.
Anybody can participate.
Just send me an email, adamaccurry.com.
If you want to know how to do these opml files
as a whole bunch of documentation,
it's ipotted.org slash contribute.
And if you want to know more about how it all works,
Ipotted.org slash documentation.
All of that can be found.
Once again, ipotted.org.
Love to have your opml file as a part of this Himey.
It's a great way to maintain a directory
because there's no real top level.
Nobody actually has full control.
And when you put it into the ipotted.org directory,
it will eventually flow through to other directories
that are out there and into most ipotted software.
So love to see some more Spanish stuff in there.
I've been getting a lot of emails about Brad Sox.
We've played Brad Sox on the show before.
Brad Sox is a guy that does everything all by himself.
Makes his own music, plays it, records it,
and is getting lots of airplane podcasts.
And I received two new songs.
Would say they're demos, but I like them.
So I'm a son and I know why.
Then I'll read and try to tell it.
Tell me, tell me, then I'm out as well.
In a book, in a book, in a book, in a book.
In a book, in a book, in a book.
In a book, in a book.
In a book.
He's got some great tunes going on. Okay, it's trivia Thursday. I have one, two, three, four,
five different trivia quizzes that have come in. I think it's only fair to start off with the
granddaddy of the trivia test. Well, other people have sent in trivia tests before,
but young Paulette, this guy from Holland who started off with a mix between a Dutch version
of you don't own me and the Bitties version of you don't own me. Really has put together
these wonderfully produced tests that just blow me away. And young, by the way, you don't have
to do on every single day. I mean, he's already saying dude, you know, like, I don't know if I
can produce one or everything. You don't have to. I really appreciate it. And anything you do is just
so incredibly cool. And today's, uh, today's, once again, he's not only produced, but it's got
jingles and sweepers and all kinds of beautiful stuff. Let's get tranquil.
Hi, Adam. This is young Paulette with another hit this day young. As you've probably noticed,
I've got a new segments opener or a leader. I love and courtesy of Kevin, one of the members
of RadioDeady.com he provided me with things I could really work with. But by the way, RadioDeady.com
is fucking great. I think I'm going to participate in that pretty soon. That seems like a great
community where we just kind of create jingles and sweepers for each other. It's a big trading post.
Love it. Love that opener by the way. Thanks to him and thanks to RadioDeady.com for providing
a great service. I also saw a lot of comments about the air check I used in yesterday's hit
test. Unfortunately, this was the only one I could really use. I've got one other, but I don't know
which records being played. So maybe you could help me out with it. Here it is.
It's really strange to notice that when you're listening to these kinds of things and you feel the
power of the leaders and the sweepers and the music, your voice automatically locks in DJI position.
Everybody that's right. Rock and play throw. One hundred. By the way, we always had to end with
either Z100 or W HTZ New York. Those were the rules. You could not end with anything else.
You also couldn't front announce a song. That's actually I think that's still illegal technically.
I think that was, I can't remember the name of that song. This was like late 80s, early 90s.
This was all that girl group disco shit. I don't remember and it probably wouldn't have been a good
one for Holda, drunkenness. It probably wouldn't have been a good one for
for the hit test because well, I wouldn't have guessed it.
All right. Just like I would like to address the daily source code listeners if you
don't mind. Because I assume amongst them there are a lot of people that have been following you
for a while now. If so and if they do have actually extra recordings of shows from the past,
I would really like it if they could send them to me.
There's, oh, that's not the only have. Well, wait a minute. I sent my box of tapes to
Tom Schooting, who lives in Australia. He has a podcast feed. A lot of that is the Dutch stuff,
which of course I know you'll appreciate. It's in the iPod.org directory under
radio shows, the Korean Van English show. I'm pretty sure though, Tom also has some Z100 air
checks and maybe some other stuff. I'll just threw everything into that box. So maybe he can
help you out with that. Pinto a Gmail account. It's hittest at gmail.com. So it's hit.txt at gmail.com or in
an increased dial or aviation style. It's hotel in the at 10 o'clock angle. Echoes at gmail.com.
It would be really great to be able to put some objects in a house once in a while. Talking about
hit tests. Okay. We go. Yeah. Now put the air books and get out your pencil. It's time for Adam
Curry to take the hit test. All right, you don't pull it. All right, but this is a big
different from the earlier ones. Okay. Um, it's a special one. It's an 80s pill ball. He did
it. Yeah, baby cowbells. So here we go. This is number one. Crank it.
Cowbell is killing me.
Feels like heaven. Is that, uh, is that, uh, timid thing? Fiction, uh, fiction factor? Feels like
heaven. Siction factor. That's one. Number two. Cowbell is distracting. Is this street life?
Ready Crawford and was it the persuaded street life? It's the only way I know. No, maybe it's not street life.
No, I'm, I don't know the shore. Number three. All right.
Wow. Uh, this is, it does not deserve cowbell. It wasn't that big a hit. Is this, uh,
Kaji Guga? Boom. I think it's, be the Le Mansollo or Kaji Guga? I can't remember.
You can tell just by the baseline. All right. Answer. All right, let's get to the ancestors right away.
Okay, this was number one
From 1984
Yeah, and still going to have a big got one right
Sing along
Number two
Street live in 1981
Never too much, this is loop of ocean
Of course, loop of band rows
Oh man, I'll put it messed up one
Yeah
And this is number three
Can't you go?
Yeah, can't you go?
Big got up all that's the time, right?
Okay, two out of three ain't bad
I think?
Not bad for today
There you go
Well, that's it for today
If you do have an act check of how I'm doing
Please send it to us at email.com
To send your feedback or suggestions
See you all next time for another contest
Oh, young, thank you very much
I can't tell you how much I appreciate all the work you put into that
It's really really awesome
I have a lot of fun doing that
And the feedback I get from people is just amazing
Who are sitting in their cars or in buses or on the subway and are playing along with it
It's really a lot of fun
Okay, it is tribute Thursday
So besides, well, that is the example that we have to live by what young is doing
But some other interesting submissions came in
Let's see, which one was this, let me see
Oh, no, another shit, another thing I just got a crank
So the reason why I can't use a compressor limiter is because
And we're talking about this later on in the show if we have time for it
Is because if I put that in audio hijack pro, which I'm using
What happens is it also cranks up the microphone
So, yeah, I can't separate the two channels
Let's see how it works now
We're really getting a kick from these song trivia
MP3s you keep getting in
Anyway, I've got a little trivia here for you
It's 80s, classic TV things
Anyway, here they go
I don't give you the answer straight afterwards
Magna PI
Okay, here what that is
That would be the 80s
Growing pains or family ties
I think it's
Believe it or not, it's just me
Is that going on?
No, you need to try humming that theme
The answer is the first one is Magnum
Magnum
Magna PI got that one
Okay, number three is the 80s
18, what was four?
Number four, the greatest American hero
Greatest American hero
Okay, damn, 50% not too good today on the trivia
I was able to crank it up a little bit by the way
But now of course the next one will be a thousand times too loud
Let's see, this is the next trivia quiz
Yet another idea came in here
Hey Adam, it's Todd Maffin from iLoveRidio.org
You took a game show for you
This one's called Lost in Translation
Here's how it works, okay. I'm going to read you the lyrics of a song from the 80s
However, they're not the lyrics you're probably used to
These are lyrics that have been put through the altivist a translator
Translated from English to German
Then I take that translation
And I will translate them back from German to English
And I will read you the lyrics as they come out by the computer
Lost in translation trivia, I love the idea
We'll be a bit garbled
Your task is to figure out what the computer is trying to say with these lyrics
What is the original source song?
I like this, good. I'm going to be the answer at the end
Bring it on
If you do not leave to be in this way, which I cannot survive
Oh baby, cannot remain alive
Leaves to me in this way not
Without your love
What the hell is that?
I thought it was going to be Chicago if you leave me now
But then you take away the biggest part of me, it doesn't fit
So I'm not sure what this is supposed to be
Is it tough man?
Oh, this is my thinking time here
Of course, it's the commune of the story
Of course, the commune of the story is the commune of the story
But don't leave me this way
Both don't leave me this way
Oh, your hands are the air on the forehead
Like your best times
Excellent dude. I like that. That's pretty cool actually. That's a good good idea for a trivia test
We continue with our Thursday trivia with our next submission
Now I've got to watch the levels here because I've cranked everything up. It's blowing my eardrums out
Hey there, Adam. It's Howard Greenstein from New York. Oh, Howard. This is a trivia stuff people have been by the way. Harry Howard Greenstein is the
Is shoot who's this car?
Sorry, I'm in the middle of a podcast. I have no time for you. He turned me on to a very coral. He's related. You same
Way too easy. So I figured I'd give you a little bit of a challenge today
So this time I'm giving you a montage. It's no no whole intro is to song
You've got to pick out a piece of a song one DJ to another. Let's see how you do with this montage on the theme of
Daily for the Daily Source code. Okay. Can you figure out who sang these songs?
Deleting to the days of the week. Hit me. Let's go
One more try
Stop stop stop stop stop stop. Whoa that went way too fast. Okay, first of all
I heard I heard of beetles in there
For Wednesday. I heard Saturday in the park Chicago
We winded a bit. Hold on. Let's listen again
One more try
Monday
I don't know what that is. Let me try it again
Well, wait Tuesday is Ruby Tuesday rolling stones Wednesday. It's the beetles
I don't know the name of track. Let's see you the next one
There's a none and it's also beetles Thursday Friday is
Saturday in the park
Oh, man. This is really hard. Okay. So what do we have money? I didn't get Ruby Tuesday Wednesdays the beetles Thursdays the beetles
Saturday in the park Chicago, so I haven't heard and I don't know Monday
What are I missing Monday Friday and Sunday? Okay, hold on. Let's try this again
One more try
Shit, that's hard. Okay, I didn't see how you did. Yeah
Did you know that this one was
New moon on Monday. Oh, the grand RAM. Oh, dude. That was tough
I sure you got me. Oh, yeah, yeah, I got slow
Well, it's the middle of the week and it's the beetles. She's leaving home. She's leaving home, right?
Wednesday morning
She beetles in a row. This one was from Lady Madonna
What was Friday?
A bad time in the stock market but still he danced things about black Friday
I would have I wouldn't have known that I would not have known that when he was even if I could hear it
I would have chosen easy beats Friday at my mind to make it easier for me, of course
Oops, come on come back. What happened there?
Whoa did something just hello?
Hello
And if you got this far you probably read about it in the Sunday paper
That's the trick you had. I'm hoping you had a good time with it and that actually soon take care
All right Howard you got me that was tough though. That was tough
Okay
Let's get rid of that
What are we at? 36 minutes. I have so much more to do but I did promise it Thursday, trivia day so
Because what I want to still want to talk about is lyrics on MP3 players
I have another I don't see so I have some promos
I want to talk well, let me just move all this stuff to tomorrow's show because I'm never going to get through it
I also want to talk about audio hijack pro
Let me just put all that down for tomorrow's show
All done
Copying and pasting stuff then we have one final
trivia quiz that we can get to today for Thursday, trivia day
Adam this is Simon Strong out in Fort Collins, Colorado got a
interesting idea here for trivia game that that you might enjoy and the listeners
So I'm going to read the lyrics from the song and you have to guess what song it's from
You know, you need more cowbell to go with that reverb
answers at the end
So here we go first song
Steve walks where Lee down the street with the brim pulled way down low
Ain't no sound but the sound of his feet
Machine guns ready to go
Steve walks down
Let's do tough for me, man
Dude, this is really hard
And number three, this is my favorite song actually
Okay
Her name was McGill and she called herself a little
But everyone knew her as Nancy
God
I think this will be so far I'm batten
Mears on the ceiling pink champagne on eye hotel California
She said that was just prisoners here of our own device. Okay, so I got like one out of four
Okay, okay, the answer to the first one is
Cool and bad to dust
And the answer to number two
Herosmith Dremon
Oh, man, I should have known that one
Yes, that was Dremon
And the answer to number three
The Beatles Rocky Raccoon
Oh, I know some people got that
Yeah, and of course the last one was hotel California, right?
The last one was hotel California the Eagles
Okay, so that is nice
Let's check it out
As far as a plug, I guess I can plug the podcast. I'm still kind of developing it's pod jam.com
Absolutely
That's p-o-d-j-a-m.com
It's gonna be for guitars, so
Cool
I'm looking for contributions and you can check it out. Thanks Adam and
I really enjoy your show, so look forward to more
Take care
Okay, and really I really appreciate all the trivia that everyone sent in today
All the work you did and that's gonna do it for the source code for the
What is it? What are the third of February 2005?
So tomorrow we definitely have to talk more about audio hijack pro
Got some some more promos that were left over because it's just some really good stuff to
To yapp about and also I think tomorrow I might do some sound seeing I was thinking about going up to a black bush airport to
Look into my fixed wing
I'm supposed to go up today, but I think you'll open up and have a coffee with those guys tomorrow
So you would see what it's like up there at at our local airfield
Okay, well if you have comments of the audio form anything you want to send an MP3 format send it to
MP3 feedback at gmail.com anything else go to adamacroid.com
I'm going to go to my weblog at
www.curry.com and of course the latest show the archives and
The podcast feed at DavySourceCode.com
See tomorrow for the thank god it's Friday and each of the source code take care everybody bye bye