Delta Sierra Charlie 2-8-1 The West, in the last few days when the surge of civilization
pushed on with to broader horizons, an almighty breed of man rested new life from the
wilderness. But, close on the pioneer trail, came the Renegade Horde, land sharks,
dry women, cattle thieves, terrorizing settler and tribesmen alike, until one man rose to
challenge their lawlessness. His face masked, his true identity unknown. A company always
by a faithful Indian companion, it funded across the frontier, appearing out of nowhere
just like down in justice, is fine, a silver bullet, is name. Adam Kurran, Kurri was $60 million
worth of airplane strapped to my ass. Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hey, everybody, how are you doing? Welcome to the Kurri Kondo. It's Thursday. Technically, it's
Thursday that is. Well, let me see, how's that? I peed up, said I was a little bit hot on the
last show, so I want to make sure I don't overmodulate. It is technically Thursday because
it's past midnight. Once again, I feel so incredibly behind the rest of the world, because
of course, the rest of the world is already up and at them, at least not in the United States,
but in Europe, which I consider to be the rest of the world. I think maybe I should consider
doing the show at night when I'm on the west coast, so that we can kind of be in sync,
because I'm sure that you're one, if not two days behind on the show, just because of when I
release them and when you're able to get them. That's just a hunch I have.
So this will be my Thursday show, and yeah, so Friday I can do a show because I arrive Friday
morning in the UK. Great. I'll be completely rective of course, but I'll do it. As you can tell,
I'm on the Highell microphone. This is the PR-40. The PR-40, the Pro-40. I can't remember.
I love this microphone, not getting paid for that. I'll tell you, I love it with
I'm getting paid for it or not. Same with everything on the show. But I haven't noticed one drawback.
I have one of these, one is like a cast iron foot with a little mic stand, and I screwed the
mic on top of that. But it's too low to use in my normal configuration in front of the the
I-Mac on the kitchen bar. And I can't tilt the back, because if I tilt the back, then this mic
is so massive, so heavy, then the mic continuously falls over backwards. And also, because I just
stuffed my AKG mic into my bag without bringing the handy little box. That was the perfect height to
extend the mic stand. So what I've done now is I'm sitting on the couch. By the way, I've already
dropped ashes on the couch, and of course, it's made a nasty stain, but Trisha's going to freaking
kill me. Let me just see. It's like, it's a suede. It's a suede couch.
And that has some kind of scotch guard on it, but there's still you can see a little spot there,
so that by anyway, I've drawn the living room table towards me, and it's a glass table top.
There you go. And I've put the effects processor on that, put the mixer, the little sound
craft mixer on top of that, and the mic stand is also on top of this 19-inch rack thing.
Oh, man, I saw, did I tell you that that I saw? There's awesome mixer on podcast rigs.com.
Let me see if I can bring that up, hold on. Oh, man, that was so incredibly cool.
This is exactly what I need. Let me see, pod. I think it's oops, podcast rigs.com. There we go.
Hold on. Check this out. It's exactly what the model is.
It's a little portable mixer, and it has basically two faders on it. One for your microphone,
and it has everything you'd want in the microphone. It has a preamp, it has phantom power, it has,
hold on. I got the specs right here. It's the rammy PGO 550 Pro mixer. I know this is geeky,
but man, this thing is what I've been looking for. Here we go. Specifically, a stereo line signal,
a balanced mic, and auxiliary balanced line signals can be mixed and routed to a computer via USB.
The mixer also includes phantom power, equalizer, limiter, balanced stereo output, and a balanced
channel insert for voice processing. God, this thing is exactly what I need for the road,
and then all I need is just a very small portable effects processor for the microphone,
and then I'm set, and then you know, man, I'll have such a beautiful compact system. That'll be just awesome.
So tomorrow, I fly home. I get picked up at 145 here at the condo, and then it's upper class,
all the way home, baby, but to see the girls who actually will be taking off for the weekend,
that's a secret they're going to go surprise. Patricia's dad for his 80th birthday.
I'm staying home, because someone has to stay with the dogs in the cats in the house,
and whatever our dogs are, both our dogs are getting up there in age, and one just had some kidney,
stone removal. It wasn't really stones, but it was kind of like kidney dust or whatever,
so poor Jesse. Anyway, so it's been extremely productive. Of course, I, you know,
like I was in Seattle, and that was great, and today, which was, especially was cool,
is that I did the show on Wednesday, so I didn't have a show to do this morning, and I got to the
office, actually it was nice to slip until 8 o'clock. That was fantastic. Then I got to the office,
and I ran and I hooked up with Chris, Brian, and Rosie, and we were all in the new space,
which is coming along, and of course, I've leaned against all the walls, and I've paint everywhere,
I'm a sweater, I'm a pants, I'm a jacket, such as spas. Then I had it off for the valley,
because we had a couple of really, it was, they was rocket science day, rocket scientists day, actually.
First, we had lunch with the rocket scientists, and it's lovely wife, and that was in Palo Alto.
Was it Palo Alto? Yeah, it was in Palo Alto then, and this was extremely cool. We went over to
a mountain view for a meeting at Google. Then I was pretty excited, and I've never been to Google,
and I forgive you here so much about the culture and what it's like over there, and everyone's
really, really smart, and we had, you know, some of the top people in the company to talk with,
but, oh, dude, smart, smart, smart people. Jesus Christ, and focused, really, and this was,
I mean, it was just so refreshing to, you know, to feel that vibe. There's like,
what can I say? It's a real, it's not a warm, fuzzy vibe, it's like a
work-kick-and-ass vibe, you can really feel that. You can feel that when a company is breathing that,
and what was cool, though, is that all the people that we, I think was, there were four people
in the room, and Ron and I were both together on this meeting and Chris went along.
Is that they had all watched me on MTV, and they were actually, they said, oh, man,
I'm almost nervous to be in the room with you, because they, you know, when they were 12 or 13,
they had watched me on MTV. Oh, my goodness, that was very flattering, of course.
Okay, what's really good, though, about a day like today, and we go into the valley,
and then we actually went back to, would we go from there? Oh, man, I remember any more.
And we went back to Paula Walter to San Hill Road to
kind of Perkins meeting some people that basically using the office there, because it was in the neighborhood,
and this pertains to the PDN. Oh, man, we've got so much cool stuff to talk about.
Jesus Christ, we got the stuff's really going to start coming now.
What was it looking for over here? What I'm saying is that it's such an effective use of our
time, because basically Ron and I are in the car for at least an hour. Now, the cell phone coverage,
for some reason, where this is in San Hill Road is where all these venture capital companies are,
and everyone knows it's like the best kept secret that that is almost a dead zone for any cell
phone carrier in the world. But that does make it nice because no calls are coming through,
and we actually had some real good quality time to just talk about what's going on, without interruption.
And we talked, I'd have to say 99% of the time about the pod safe music network, about what I talked
about on a yesterday show, about selling MP3s, and let me tell you, we're now looking for
what we're hiring. We're going to get this done. This is a great idea. So we're doing a number of
things in parallel. At the same time, there's so many new bands pouring into the pod safe music network,
everyone's catching on to this. And please, artists, record something, give me some feedback.
I want to hear what you're thinking. I want to go through the Gmail with you, because that's
always a good way to excuse me. You want to play song first? Let me say, oh man,
I'm totally disorganized, really, really disorganized. What is this? I don't want that.
I just like to play a song. I think that'll be kind of cool. What are we talking about the other
day? I had dinner with the Big Mike and Sue and Chris Rockwell. Oh yeah, we were talking about
the muffs. I'll play some muffs, and then we'll go through the Gmail and go through some of the
feedback and the excellent comments I'm getting on, pure pod safe pod casting.
How sharp crap that sucked ass.
That's the feeling that you're all I need
You get all my everything I do
But I can only get you in my ear
And I need a little opportunity
With your arms around me
And the feeling that you're all I need
I'm the great, the I care
And I'm forever
And I need a little opportunity
With your arms around me
And the feeling that you're all I need
I need a little opportunity
With your arms around me
And the feeling that you're all I need
Yeah, I need a little opportunity
The pot's a music network
I've got so many cool bands in there
I have this theory about social network
I can't get enough of them
I have this theory about social networks
Social networks like my space
What else is there?
There's a friendster
And there's another one
Well, there's a whole thing you know what I'm talking about
Is that these things basically
You can architect them over and over again
You can try and make something that you know
Build it and then expect them to come
But what happens is what I've seen happen
Time and time again is that
One little community will
Start doing something
And as long as you start bringing in features
Listening and feeding back and being a part of that community
Then you build it out
Now it's not necessarily an all-encompassing thing
For instance, my space is really built around
Music and music videos that have to say
Mainly and you're seeing mainstream bands
Now release their music on my space
That's an incredible phenomenon
And I think that we'll definitely be working with my space
One way the other is just it's unavoidable
Those guys have got something really good going on
And it's what Chris and Tom, you know, those guys are smart
And they get it, they totally get it
Now you take something like a friendster
Which was a social network
Which I think was built from the ground
I think was built from the ground up with the idea of
Okay, we're going to build a social network
And we're going to make all the technology right
And what happened is
A community from Manila
Started to use it and you know, so they have lots of users
But they're all from the Philippines
And it kind of gets stuck that way, you know
It's very hard to bring in other communities
Once your community is started to grow
I'm trying to think there was another great example of that
Who was telling me about Brazil
There was some other social network
That had been lingering around for a while
All sudden Brazil started to use it
Gosh, I'm real fuzzy, I'm sorry I can't remember what it was
So that's what I'm seeing happening here with the Podsake music network
And I'm quite confident now that this is going to be a big
Well, we kind of knew it and we worked on it
I mean the Podsake music network was, you know, built months and months
And months ago and before that even was a pod show
We were already working on this because it's funny
I wonder what started us on that
I guess we got the music podcasters together
Oh man, who cares?
Let's look forward instead of backwards
Oh, here's something interesting
Magic gave me an emergency phone call, Adam Adam, come me
Apparently we've had our first victim of
Well, I can only presume it's a business model that is not working for them at least
In Pod casting, pure cast where apparently
I don't know how many people they were hosting on their servers
But it was under 50 I believe
Including 10 to 20 queue potters
All of a sudden, these guys just turned everything off
The website is for sale, the domain name
For just under 2,000 bucks
And everyone's shit is gone and it's over
And so, Madge called me and said, Adam, Adam, I want to get to do this
Well, Madge, come on, bring them on over
We haven't opened up the podcast delivery network yet
But, you know, I think we can park these folks in some space that will work
And we'll get them up and running
It also includes soccer girl incorporated
So we're jumping in and getting them all hooked up
So for those of you who are missing a number of queue potters
Podcasts, excuse me
As well as soccer girl incorporated
It's being taken care of and hopefully everything will be up to tomorrow
We probably won't be able to redirect their feeds
Unless they're using feed burner then we can then the feeds will remain the same
But we'll help them publish their new feeds
So that sucks when that happens
That bites, hey that
Okay, let's look at my daily source code label
Here in Gmail
Okay, let me see
Right off the bat, we've got a comment about ID3 tags
I'm just going to play whatever pops up
If I don't like it, I'll shut it off
Hey Adam, I've heard you complain about people not putting the information that you want
In the ID3 tags, but you have to tell us what information you want
So, let's start with my proposal for a basic ID3 tagging standard
First of all, comments
Title field should be CMT followed by RECOLIN, just like an email
And then either a show number, DSE number, or a specific topic
A promo will be given the prefix in the title field of promo colon
And for pod safe music, PSM at the beginning of the title field
As far as pod safe music goes, all the other fields should be left as they are
Continuing the information with the pertain to the song
And any other information should be added into the comments or lyrics
Fields of the ID3 tag
And then going back to comments and promos, we'll say the artist's field
Should be an email address and the album field should be a website address
And or pod cast feet, if available
Anyone taking notes on this?
If this system wouldn't work for your production system, let us know what would work
Yeah, and if you're not going to plug my podcast, the high-ponency music podcast
You can check it out at feeds.feetburner.com slash hotel pop a mic test
Or www.highponencymusic.com
Thank you
That's a great idea
But I don't think anyone's going to do it
Email from audio collective, great show Adam, one comment about
It's a danger mouse song, I don't think it was danger mouse, it was danger
Something else that I played, it was a danger mouse yesterday
It was that hip-hop song
The record label, epitaph, is pronounced
Like the saying that is on a gravestone, so it is epitaph
Like they did it themselves, we'll soon be the music industry's epitaph
Also check out Joe Stromer, oh that's right, oh man
I gotta get my act together on this
You remember the clash don't you, oh Joe Stromer from the clash
Through epitaph records is now on the pod safe music network
And I'm going to play this song right now
How fucking cool is this
Just give me a tequila
I'll slam it the pod the way
When I got there you know
It hurt
Certain similarities
Like no smoking anywhere
And hiding in the cosy to avoid man
The best
For the tequila anyone
And don't think we didn't dance
Direct us by no different dimension
And the disc was still
Like the black coat
And it was pretty got out as it is
And on the illness that I've met
Like we're cleaning to the theme park
But just you're right
For the bench I'll climb
Make up all right
Well I was feeling tired
Back and forth
And tired
And mathematics and pride
We've gone wrong
We've gone wrong anyway
Just like the other
Some world
Yeah, that's not something
But always
Yeah, we've gone wrong
And you will lose this way
Yeah, that's how the next room is today
Yeah, that's not something
But always
Yeah, we've gone wrong
And you will lose this way
Yeah, that's how the next room is today
But always
And it's time
We've gone wrong anyway
Wow, you know, at first when the song just started
I was like, oh man, don't tell me that this
Joe Stromer song is going to suck ass
Yeah, I would feel bad turning it off
But I liked it
It really opened up at the end
That was awesome
And this is not working out with with a laptop
And my head has to be twisted
Oh, I met Steve Harris at
At the expo last weekend
And he said that he had switched from British airways
to Virgin Atlantic
He didn't fly up her class
But he switched to Virgin Atlantic
Based upon my ranting and raving about how good the services
And mind you
I've flown Virgin Atlantic in
What is the, well they call that
Not the, you have like a middle class
It's not business class
Because you know
Ah, executive class
Maybe that's what it is
So it is definitely more expensive than
Then economy
But you do get a really nice ride
And so when you're paying for something under your own pocket
And you want to be able to sleep a bit
Or at least have some of the amenities
Anyway, so he came out to me
He told me that and said, dude, that's great
But would you please send me some audio feedback
So that I can really share that with all of this
I was just reinvented software
We met at the expo in Ontario last week
And spoke a little bit about Virgin Atlantic
It was my first time in a Virgin flight
And I thought I'd fly back before commenting
To see everything around the house
I thought I'd fly back before commenting
And lots of other airlines
Other places, but I probably would have booked
A British Airways flight
To the expo this year
However
But at the same time
There were the gate gommies
Strikes that crippled BA in the summer
And also around that time
You were raving about Virgin on your show
So I decided to take your recommendation
And check it out
First of all I would say
It was a really great price in the tickets
It was probably the most affordable direct flight
From Heathrow to San Francisco
Where I needed to be before the expo
Not enough for class unfortunately
But economy class
And it makes you wonder with margin so tight
How can you improve
Well first of all I say there was great service at the airport
Fast check in both that Heathrow and San Francisco
On the way back
Can Heathrow they have these DRI machines
Where you can just pop in your ticket
Choose a seat and drop your bag off
And in San Francisco they just weren't okay
I didn't end up in line for an hour waiting to check in
Once you're on the plane
They have this accent, V-port
Undimand and Taint system
Which basically means you can choose what you want to see
When you want to see it
And it helps all our TV shows, movies, music
And enormous amount of stuff
So it helps you don't end up staring at the map
30 minutes to pass the time
And also Charlie and the chocolate factory begins
Another thing was great food
It was much more imaginative than usual airline fare
Never one of these will be for chicken thing
Where they tell me that they're all at a beef
And what other airline gives you a hot vegetable
Or ham panini as a snack
This is the most important thing
I think is that I thought there was extra leg room where I was
And they'd be a couple of inches
I haven't checked this out
But I really didn't feel that cramped on the flight
And that makes all the difference when you're stuck in capital class
All in all, I really recommend it
It was good food, great service
Add an excellent price
I told you that
It was great to meet you at the expo
And I keep up the great work of the show
And I hope to see you again soon
Take care
Thank you
Something frightening just happened
I think I felt the building move
I swear to God
I wonder if there's like a little mini tremor or something
And I'm not imagining this
I really felt something move
And I have to say it kind of freaking out for a second there
It's one of those things
I never think about it
Okay
Wow
That seriously did kind of bum me
I for just a moment there
It got something
And I'm just trying to get through all the feedback that I think I need to share with you as soon as possible
I talked about
Hooking up with Steve Webb
He's one of the Godcassers life spring podcast
And we had a conversation
On his podcast about
He had his son there and his lovely wife
And they also dropped by poolside
Lots of people dropped by poolside
Actually
So we talked about advertising in
In Godcass
And actually about there being
A rule that the Godcass network
will not carry advertising ever
And it was a really interesting discussion
And I really enjoyed it very much
And I appreciate all the work that Steve is doing
And I've told you before I love these Godcass
I've listened to all kinds of Godcass
Because it's really short, inspirational, nice messages
And well produced most of them
So Craig Patchett, Patchett
who runs the Godcass network
Send me an email
And he heard, of course he heard the show
And he has some feedback
He has a response
So let's listen to that
Because this is very interesting
You know
So I haven't listened to this myself
So who knows what we're going to hear
Come on in
Craig
Hey Adam, this is Craig Patchett
From the Godcass network
And Godcass.org
He's got some pipes on him
Kind of microphone you use him
And I like that sound
I've just finished listening to
I think with Delta Sierra Charlie
79er
And also listen to the interview that you did with Steve Webb
On the new life spring podcast
Both of which talked about advertising in Godcass
And I wanted to clear up a couple of things
And talk about my decision
Not to accept advertising on the Godcass network
First of all
The Godcass network does not accept
Any kind of sponsorship
Or advertising
Not just ads in the podcast
There is no pledge drive
Something you mentioned in the daily source code
There are no PayPal buttons
There is absolutely nothing on the site
Or within the podcasts that asked for money
Or is in any way associated with that
And that was done quite specifically
When I started the Godcass network
And Steve alluded to that
In his interview with you
I wanted to make sure that the message that we portray
On the network basically was
Not in any way
Made questionable by
Commercial content
And I think my best thing I could compare it to
It would be something like Jim and Tammy Fadebaker
And that whole debacle
Or any of the other
Ministries that are out there
In my mind
At least
Time money into
Some kind of game
They are basically selling you hope
And that's not what Christianity is about
That's not what Jesus is about
And it's certainly not what I want
The Godcass network to be about
I just don't want any kind of
Connection with that at all
I want people to realize that
What's on the Godcass network
The message the shows
The information
Is all there simply for
You know for one reason
And that is that because
Each podcaster that has a show
On the network has a passion for the information
That they're putting out
And they want to share it with others
They want to break the stereotypes
And they want to give people an opportunity
To check out
You know what Christianity really is
And I may not be for everybody
But at least you know you can
Explore it in an unadulterated format
And make up your own mind about it
So that's why the Godcass network is about
And that's why it does not
And will not carry advertising
Or solicit money
In any way
Now at the same time
I don't begrudge any of the
Godcasters the desire
To be able to
Create their podcasts full time
And you know I've told this to Steve
And I've told this to the others as well
And yes, if a
Godcast
Or if a show on the Godcass network
Does start carrying advertising
Then you know it no longer qualifies
To be part of the Godcass network
But you know I would I would hope
That would be true for for some of the the Godcass
You know I would love to see Steve
Be able to to Godcast full time
And be able to earn a living in it
I think he's very good
At what he does I think his show is excellent
And I think he deserves to be able to do it full time
If the Godcass network
Conserves a vehicle to build traffic
For the shows that are on it to the point
Where they are able to draw sponsors
And then you know I feel that I've been successful
With it in that respect
So it's not something that I discourage at all
I also have
Some plans that are on the back burner
For expanding the network
That would possibly allow for
Advertising the future for an offshoot of the network
I've also been talking with Alan Aguire
From the Zani Aguire's Drew Donkis's brother
About working with him
He currently runs a site called podcastmedia.net
Which is well worth checking out that has some shows of its own
And so you know there are some plans on targeting Christian specifically
Because as I mentioned I don't think that this is a problem
If you have integrity in the way that you approach it
And if you're addressing Christian specifically
Okay
I got it
That's cool
If it's anyway we can help
Let me know
He goes on for even a little bit longer
But I think the point was made so that's very cool
Oh my goodness
I am so tired
I can't wait to get on to get on board
And go to sleep and just catch a couple hours
Oh wait a minute
There's a new lost episode too I guess
Yeah
Oh man I'm going to download that for my video iPod
That stuff is totally working for me
Although dude when you run a video on the video iPod
I think you can probably watch
If you listen to a couple tunes or maybe one podcast
And you watch two episodes of loss
That's it for your battery
But still when you think about it that's
No, it's almost a
Two hours probably
So this is in
Just hop over the pod
Say
The real content
It's chosen by the people
For the people
So you have no excuse
None of the time in your busy day to search
All the wonderful music at the pod
Say music network
Maybe I can help
By giving you the top rated music on the PMN
Ready to play in one easy podcast
I may not have the sweet silky sensei
Voice of that I'm curry
But it's all about the music after all
Come listen in
At www.crushland.com
That's CRUSH L-A-N-D.com
Thank you
Ron and I did some really old school in the car today
While we were driving
I had the laptop open
And I was just playing a whole bunch of tunes
From the pod
Say music network
We were really vibing on it
We were like, he's a musician
So we were just, oh wait a minute
That reminds me
I think big mic had this too
Got a piece of
See if this is
Shoot
Let me see if I can find it
Bloom was in a big mic's record store
Let me read this to you first
Before I lose this
I just bought this up on email
This is the power of pod
Say music and podcast
And you'll love this
Matt Volk says
Adam I just bought the candy butcher's album
Off iTunes
That's the song I want to do about Michael
But I played a couple times now
But on a whim
On a whim
I went and looked at sales rank on Amazon
Yesterday it ranked 53,700 today
Which is Wednesday
It is up to 8,258
He says
You don't quite have the slash dot effect yet
But your podcast is affecting record sales
Uh-huh
Say no more
I hear you
Okay, what was I gonna look for
Oh yeah, that was the thing of
Hold on
That's funny
I was thinking of detuning it
Making it sound like shit
But I guess you just picked up a
Yeah
Let me see
Where is he?
So this is very difficult
In Gmail I'm looking for Adam Bloom
And of course if you type
Adam Bloom
Then you get all kinds of email
Let me run and vice versa
Let me say that's out
This sucks
I'm sorry
I really apologize about this
Disorganization
Let me just try one more time
Because it was really
Pretty cool to listen to
I don't know
I want to put
Jesus
I'm retarded
Okay
This is the last
Last try here
I thought I had already downloaded that
I gave it for the source code
But I guess I didn't
Oh, here we go
Got it
Okay
This is
I wish I knew the name of the record
Storts in
Right
It was at HATE
HATE and something
And this is a Ron Bloom
Playing
In a record stuff
So I got one more piece of feedback from Angie B from Love Spirals
Which by the way in the show notes
Love Spirals
So I got one more piece of feedback from Angie B from Love Spirals
Which by the way in the show notes
Love Spirals
The spell was spelled as two separate words
But it's supposed to be one word
Love Spirals
Check them out at LoveSpirals.com
Angie B had a question about
And I guess Love Spirals
So I sold over 50,000 records
Complete in the pod save
Have music up on the pod save
Music network
And
So she sent in a question
Which I discussed on yesterday source code
And I guess she has a response back
So let's
Check that out
Hold on
Let me turn this off
There we go
Now
Hit me baby
Come on
Adam
It's Angie B of Love Spirals again
Thanks for the compliment
You have a sexy voice too
So it keeps me coming back to listen
Oh yeah, that lets her
Lovely wife
Don't worry about her
She hasn't listened to any shows this week Angie
Is that why you keep coming back baby
Is that really the reason
Well you're welcome to do it
jealous now
Back to business
Okay
It wasn't so much that I
Expected to give me legal advice
Because I'm pretty well versed in these things
It's just the whole
Cool factor that creative common seems to have
I mean I do listen to a number of music podcasts
And
People definitely seem to respect creative common artists
And a certain way
And
Especially with all the BMI bashing that you've done lately
I'm just a little worried that podcasters
Are going to be turned off to playing
Love Spirals
Because we do sign up our songs with BMI
Get them copyrighted the old fashioned way
So
You know I just want to kind of bring that
That tier tension that some of us independent artists
That are a
Kind of really need coffee
I still going to need to rely on some of the old school
Of course
Business
Absolutely
Set ups for now
You know until something else happens
But I did want to thank you for including my audio feedback
And 280 because I got some emails from your listeners
And a few sales
So it's really great all the way around
And podsake music network
Podcasters be sure to check out Love Spirals on the site
Very cool
Okay
No of course
I had this horrible thought that just flashed my mind
For a nanosecond
It would be horrible
If the music industry said
You can't even play
You can't play any music on a podcast
They had some kind of trick
Paragraph somewhere
And something that was passed in the middle of the night
And that we couldn't play any music at all
And that music could be outlawed
It would be illegal unless it was from Warner or Sony
Or EMI
My goodness
So let me just wind up with this bit now
About this Christmas song
Because I'd rather love call me
And you know he was just
You know he's been asked to participate on this Christmas song
So what the whole point was
Just I really wanted to try and experiment
And it's not so much about the Christmas song
Other than going to be cool if we could actually produce something
And do it with a whole bunch of podsake music artists
And produce it over the wire if it were
So people doing their bits that are going to contribute
In their own home studios and then assembling it
And of course when you think about it
Maybe you should have gotten a lot of
Or maybe for a project like this
You might want to get a whole bunch of songwriters together
Because everyone has ideas
And of course you need to coin sea jones and a Michael Jackson
And people like that
But the idea here was just to have some fun
And see if we could do something as a group as a community
And it's starting to come together
And this is the song that I talked about
Slowed it, what if everyday could be Christmas
It's real sappy
It's real we are the worldish
But I must say those kinds of songs have super broad appeal
They really do
And I was just hoping that maybe maybe maybe maybe
This could kind of break out
Maybe we would get some play on the radio
And it would bring more people into what's happening here in podcasting
And I believe the song is going to be registered
Or the proceeds will go to Unicef
You know what?
That happens to be a promo that I have
Right here, let's listen
Everybody, this is Slowed
Inviting everyone who's registered as an artist with the pod safe music network
To join in the chorus in an unprecedented recording project
To benefit the United Nations Children's Fund UNICEF
If everyday work Christmas will feature pod safe artists from around the globe
We don't all have to be in the same room in order to sing together
The internet has changed the way music is produced and distributed
And now, pod casting will change the way a worldwide community can come together
To benefit a worthy cause during the holidays
This project will be a great ambassador to the world
For pod safe music and pod casting in general
So, if you're an artist member of the pod safe music network
Go to music.potshow.com and find out how you can help make this dream come true
And thank you Adam for getting this Christmas ball rolling
Yeah, let's have some fun!
Cool!
Now, I wonder, of course, if there actually is something about this
Music.potshow.com, let me see
Okay, so much for the coordination, let me see
Didn't know
Okay, CC, if you're within the sound of my voice
We've got to get something up here
So, we've got to get a page up
Maybe I pop this promo too soon
If so, I apologize
All right, what do we do?
Let's just do a more kick and song
I want to do something really good to get out of here
So, we can, you know, one of those just almost
Almost weekend songs
Let me see what do I have for you
Something that'll be really, really, really kick and
I'll be going to my iTunes all pod safe
Except for, I still have a lot of mashups in there
Which I'm removing one by one
I'm listening to them then I'm removing them
Which is really, really pretty sad
Dude, I don't know what to play
I don't know what to play
Dream of Thorpe, she's kind of cool
Just play one of her
I'm so far behind
Like I can play
If I find nothing seems to matter
I'll let you hear beside me
If I can play when you're with you
I'll feel like I'm all the cause
What am I?
Emotion to see you like
They could be paralyzed
And the light inside me
Feel so bright, it's home for me to do me
Like I can move my life
I've got nothing to do
I'll let you hear beside me
Like I can play when you're with you
I've got nothing to do
I'll let you hear beside me
If I can play when you're with you
I'll feel like I'm all the cause
What am I?
Emotion to see you like I'm all the cause
Emotion to see you like my life
What am I?
Emotion to see you like I'm all the Cause
Emotion to see you like I'm all the cause
You're nothing seems better
You're here beside me
Life life life life when I'm here with you
I feel like
Life life life nothing seems better
You're here beside me
Life life life when you're with you
Life life life everything seems better
It's so cool, man
You know where we really start out doing a lot of talk podcasts
Because early on we all agreed that we really shouldn't be playing license music
And even though we were kind of breaking the rules now and then we just decided to talk and it was really nice
And now I think we're flooding the ethernets
We're flooding it with beautiful music
Adrenal Thorpe fly fly fly
From the Podsame Music Network
You can find that at music.podshow.com
All that stuff we've been talking about
We're building it, okay
I'm so excited about this
And keep your feedback coming, keep your thoughts coming
We're going to make something incredibly beautiful happen
I'm convinced of it
Hey, I'll talk to you Friday from the cottage. Take care everybody
Bye-bye
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear
Shoot
Oh man, how how the hell could I mess that up
You see for those of you who've been wondering
I make these shows 49 minutes exactly
And we do that because I air it on it airs on serious
Every single week afternoon
And I don't know
I thought it was coming up on 49 minutes
But it was 48 minutes
But actually I've been enjoying keeping myself to a time limit
Because it really helps me drive towards something
And make something happen
Pacific Coast Hellways next
If you're listening to this some serious otherwise I'll talk to you on Friday
As I said from the cottage, bye-bye