Delta Shara Charley 2, 4, 3.
And now, coming to you from high-o-top podshow headquarters in beautiful Newark, Ohio, home of the world's largest basket.
Here at home, hey!
6 million dollars worth of your place wrapped in my ass.
Transmitters?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky and crispy.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
Fantastic!
It's Adam Curry.
And it is.
What is it?
It's Wednesday, September 21st, good morning.
How are you?
Coming to you directs from Northern California, where it is foggy.
It is German.
Very, very foggy.
It's your daily source code from Curry Condo.
I can barely see the marina today.
It's chilly, but I'm back home kind of.
How are you?
You know, that home, of course, is a very relative statement.
This is home for when I'm out on the west coast.
But it's, as was Ron's wife, Martessa.
Yes, home is where the heart is.
Well, it changes with the time zones.
Back from Chicago, had a lightning round trip to Chicago.
We'll talk about that a little bit today.
And it's early.
It's early for me to do a source code.
It's a five past nine, but we've discussed this, right?
I feel so behind the eight ball on the west coast.
So the plan is on days where on the days that I actually am physically able to record a source code.
I guess I'm just going to have to do it in the morning.
So I haven't had breakfast yet.
I got up at seven, went through the email, which by the way, this is how this is how bad I have.
If now resorted to, basically waking up in the morning and going, oh, yeah, okay.
Let me just check the blackberry for the email.
I sit there and bed.
Which is in some ways very efficient.
It's kind of free to.
Scary.
Alright, to get into the mood and get everybody ready.
Well, I put the coffee maker on.
Ada found another mashup for me, which is just freaking awesome.
I love this one.
It's as he said himself in the email,
there's just no way that these two songs should actually be fitting together.
You like it?
Should I stay or should I fucking?
You Tipe me.
Oh, I love the coffee, but it's so much easier Grapes!
But I'm never gonna let you eat me.
I'd kinda stop it for the next week.
It's here that I can lay my ass above baby.
You take her eyes upon me.
Don't run like such!
And run the moonlight, don't run thegood time.
You should I stay or should I come there?
Don't let me go, don't let me go
There's my difference between, I'm supposed to be the devil's house
The devil's house is the same
There's space, I'm holding my feet behind the fire press
I'm sorry, I'm looking for a place to find a place
Don't let me go, don't let me go, don't let me go
Don't run away, don't run away
Not run away, don't run away
Don't run away, run away
Stop theんだ
Don't run away, don't run away
Dude, I can say it will be called
Dude, Imma turn in
Don't run away, don't run away
That's good before breakfast, should I stay or should I book gay right here on the daily source code?
You know this feels so much like the old days when I was doing pirate radio
Because what I've gotten into at the cottage because she's we were back for like what I was back in the UK for almost a month
Which is pretty much a record for me
You know I resorted into making beautiful outlines and getting everything all set up
And then you really do all the show prep before recording the show which is great because you're so organized
But it does miss kind of a certain element that we used to have at the pirate radio stations
We basically walk in you know five minutes before your shift as we called it and the previous guy was
You know there was spinning his last records or whatever
You might need even been packing up his stuff and getting ready to leave and just put the last record on
Assuming that you'd be in there on time right
And then you'd dive into the record library which in the case of the biggest station biggest pirate radio station
I've worked at was kind of like a closet
And sometimes there would be two or three people in the closet doing other things than checking out our records
And this is oh man, I got an inch under my
Oh, I'm wearing my
My sneakers
Oh, man, oh don't you hate it when you have an inch underneath your foot and you
Oh, man, I couldn't get to it
Oh, that's nice
Anyway, so you just grab like you kind of know what your first record was going to be like, oh, I want to play that this is going to be my first record
Which in my cases usually the mashup of the day if we have a good one
And then you just kind of free wheel it, you know, you play whatever comes and whatever feels right
And so I'm doing a little bit of that and it's really I just I don't have the energy
I'm wanting to to really go through everything meticulously
So I guess what I'm going to have to do is I'm going to have to find someone to help me out to create
To show notes post the show which is complicated because it has to be someone who's available 24 hours
So the minute I'm done with the show, I said listen to the show and write down the show notes and here's the information that I got
So I don't have to figure that one out
In Chicago we
We present it actually have a picture is great
It was Ron and I do this awesome show if I if I can say so myself
Where we have I bring the workstation we've got two computers everything's hooked together
We're both mic we basically do a podcast and and we talk about
Pod show and pod casting and opportunities in the pod safe music network and and how we'd like
Advertisers to think about new ways of advertising and kind of break the mold of the 60 second spot
It's going to be a while you know there
Still pretty traditional in many ways and lots of these advertisers are very excited
By the way, I've told you just before they're so excited because it's so hard for them to reach their audience
Because well shit, we're all listening to MP3 players and iTunes, you know, so our iPods
There it is so the reason I brought that up is because this was the agency that handles the senseo account
And we talked about it in depth, but there was like I didn't get all the senseo love I was expecting
I was like okay, and here's the golden senseo machine
So oops, hold on I got to do the milk froth hold on don't don't go away bear with me. We've done this before
So the coffee's done now we switch the knob and
Whoo
We've got a lot of steam today
Do in my bird you'll think milk again come on straw rock
Somehow frothing in plastic cup just doesn't work as well as in a crockery
Okay, so we kind of
I was rather disappointed, hold on let me just get this ready and when we continue
I got lots of cool stuff to talk about
There we go
Oh yeah, this is coffee
It's the rocket fuel of the industry
Okay, so
Let me go my mic up again there
Despite that we had we had a great meeting
And it was good to be in Chicago I had been in Chicago for
I'm gonna say 10 or 11 years
And I'm amazed at how beautiful the city is
I remember going there before and thinking wow what a beautiful city
There's lots of new buildings and the skyline we came in
Was it Monday evening around a 930 10 o'clock from the airport
It was just so beautiful the skyline was phenomenal
And yeah, it's just
Actually Ron had lived there before
It was one of his previous lives and he said you know the difference between New York
I say this is so nice like every sidewalk is almost like a promenade
And so yeah the big difference between New York and Chicago is the concept of
Alice because in Chicago all the trash
Goes out in the back alley instead of on the on the front sidewalk
And that really ended boy doesn't make a difference
So as I said it's like a promenade the sidewalks are clean
Yeah, it was just it was just really really nice
So got back late last night
It's you know Chicago is just a little bit too far from San Francisco
You might as well go all the way to New York you know
It's maybe it's just an hour an hour further flight
So let's excuse me. Okay, we'll do this and say a plug for that burp
And then I got in last night
Kind of you know through everything down suitcase down
But did crack open the laptop and I think I told you that
Christina had been doing something with Martina
Martina is Michael Butler's daughter
And she has her own podcast called Emo Girl Talk
And I'd wanted to get this a couple days ago because the show was already out
But I guess you put it on a different server
And of course it ran out of bandwidth within three seconds
It's Emo Girl Talk dot com is where you can find the show
And I told Christina I said you know tell Martina to put this on the pod
Show server so that you guys have enough bandwidth and you don't run out
And I listened to the to the show last night
I want to share you know I'll play a little bit of it for you
And I was you know you think you know everything that your kids are into
Right and what they're talking about and what they're listening to
And boy did I get an education
So yeah that was panic at the discount
So Christina
What kind of music do you like
Well I of course like Emo and stuff
I like follow up boy as I like dying
But for my valentine bright eyes
Taking Max Sunday
James and Parker which by the way a really good band
If you haven't heard of them check them out
www.jamisonparker.com
And James and Comington's really hot
So yeah check out that band
Whoa
She just mentioned five bands I've never heard of before in my life
And I was like
Huh
When I get back to the London to the cottage
I got to get an education in this stuff man
She's listening to stuff
I have no idea I've never heard of when I'm very curious
That's heard
I also like
Just basically some rock and some Emo just so much stuff
But you know when you don't feel the Emo mood
Some pop music like Gwen Stefani
Yeah
Pop is our guilty pleasure
Me and Christina
Yeah
Yeah we're poser so
Send us some hate mail
Christina and I have
Long time ago we came to the conclusion
That we were the same person
We have the same pass
When we were about like 12
We thought we were really punk
And we liked our little bit
We thought we were out of the beam too
We had the ties going on
We're secretly a double person
We're Tina to the power of two
And so if you know we're like better than Paris
The power of two
We're taking over
Okay
Emo girl talk dot com
Fantastic show
Some great music on there as well
Just stuff that I've never heard of before
So this is kicking me in the ass
You know like I know what the hell is going on
First of all I don't know what the hell my daughter's listening to
That would be one
I never hear the you know she's she's got the iPod on
So of course you don't hear what she's listening to
Or you know
God knows but I am certainly missing out on some tunes
So something a little a little note there to self
Now what I've told you that
I've been using the blackberry
Yes, it's true
It is a crackberry
It is freaking addictive
The whole concept of push email
Which means that you basically you're connected full time
To the network and when an email comes in
It shows up literally
Seconds if not the second later on the blackberry
The keyboard is nice the layout is really good
Once you have this got they've got lots of keyboard shortcuts
Particularly in in the in the message system
So for email works very much like Gmail actually
With the J in the K keys for
Conversations and threads and
I've I've certainly berated friends and colleagues over and over again
For the use of blackberries but I understand it now
It really is true
I miss the I miss the camera
That I have I miss
I miss certain elements of the MDA
Which of course I carry with me right?
I have that in my bag as a backup
And nothing can replace
The beauty of the GPS that runs on the MDA and all that stuff
But just for and also
It has a real sturdy feel
You know it's like you could drive your car over this
No blackberry is still good
Maybe a little bit scratched
And you you can drop it and the cover may pop off
But that's about it. It feels good it slips into the pocket
Nicely very impressed very impressed
But also they've been
They've been making these for like 10 years
So you got to figure that once the executives got hold of it and they started
Provided that I think that this device really was
Built based on user feedback
You know say hey if only could do this boom
There's that feature you know everything that I think would be a perfect feature
Find it and it's in there and
And the battery life is also
More than more than sufficient
Okay so
Of course what I don't have is
The ease of Gmail's labels
And I know that there's a Gmail mobile application
But it's no good
If it's not push email then it cannot compete no matter what
I'd rather deal with
Searching stuff out later than you know
Then having to log in and wait because it just takes time
You know just trying to get your email
You spend an average of
8 or 9 minutes just getting the email and waiting for pages to load
Whereas when everything's on the blackberry goes pretty fast
So I don't have the luxury of being able to tag something as you know for the daily source code
So basically I'm saving messages
That I think are going to be relevant for the show
I'm going to be relevant for the show
And I'm trying to navigate as we speak
Because there's lots of lots of little things that people have been sending me
Hold on a second
Lots of schedules
Okay
Lots of senseo stuff in here, lots of sound
So this is a good one Samuel Fineberg said
You know listen to your daily source code
Heard you were hanging a mirror in your condo
I'm not sure if you thought about it
But usually I use earthquake hangers
Especially when I hang anything heavy or anything
That hangs over a place where people sit or sleep
And he has a link to
To the ones that he uses
That's a very good point I hadn't thought about that
And I think that
Well I really don't know
I mean I hung up this mirror and I think
The the wall fasteners that I use
I mean they're not going to come out of the wall anytime soon
But then again I've never been in earthquake and California
So I have no idea
If that you know how severe that can be
But that's it. Thank you very much at a very very good point
Um
Lots of people inviting me to drop by in Chicago
Which I'm in
You know when we do these trips it's just no way I have time to
Pretty tightly scheduled because that's just so much to do
Here in San Francisco that we don't want to
You know we just don't want to
Hang around too long and you know
Hopefully in the future there will be more time as
As I move away a little bit more from the selling
And talking to advertisers into the pure production
And we get some more infrastructure in the production set up
And we'll have time to do some of that
What I did see as I
As I woke up this morning is there is an update for iTunes
Yes five dot o dot one has been released
And haven't been
Been slamming anyone too hard
But I've had some major problems with with iTunes since the 5.0 upgrade
And these are the same problems lots of
But predominantly macusers have seen
Is that you lose all of your podcast subscriptions
And only you have to go resubscribed to stuff
And I think that the engineers that Apple
Or pretty aware that there were some problems
So it's funny the way they can you have in the software update panel
It describes what the update is. I haven't installed it yet
It has iTunes 5 features a new and even more powerful instance search
Including the new search bar which helps you find exactly what you're looking for in iTunes
Or from among 2 million songs on the music store
Folders for organizing playlist and new parental controls
From music music sharing and podcasts
And here comes iTunes 5 dot o dot one features several stability improvements
Over iTunes 5 so good deal guys
I'm sure you can stomp on a couple of those buggies and I will definitely
Report back on that after I've installed it later today
This week on the squad cast
Two weeks ago we spoke with you about
Hooking up the iPod
My brother-in-law and I tried to do it tonight
We tried to do the old USB
Securities and you still didn't get it
What what what is your brother? What is his occupation? Why are you guys having so much difficulty here?
He's a florist
Who else makes color arrangements to subject of the five-minute diatribe and otherwise
Handedly run podcast
There comes a sign
Nobody came to my defense here
We all got really quiet after that
I just sit down at the front myself
Patience
Yeah, they're hot. I told you I dated ones
No, no, no
No, we were talking about not calling them orientals
You know that can hard on with a person attached to it
Squad cast
Gmail dot com squad cast
dot com dot com
Hot chill
Content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother
Are you addicted to race?
Hi, I'm Jan Chow
And I'm Carmen Vancouver of
And we're co-hosts of addicted to race
A podcast about America's obsession with race with a specific focus on mixed race identity
And interracial relationships
Check us out at www.addictedtorac.com
But then on the other end of the spectrum
It seems like there are other people taking these tests
Hoping to discover some kind of quote unquote
Ethnic background
Because they think that it will bring my flavor to their lives
Totally
But really this whole phenomenon of DNA tests is ridiculous
Apart from the fact that this scientific basis for these tests is very shaky
More on that in a minute
It's this whole realization thing that annoys me so much
We always hear stories of people taking these tests
And there are results that they're supposedly like 6%
Sub-Saharan Africa
And they think it explains all these things in their life
Like
Oh no wonder I was so into that Harlan Renaissance literature class
And politics
Or
Oh no wonder it helps such big lips
Oh no wonder I've always been such a great dancer
And if you're feeling a little offended right now
By what I just said you should
Because that is the point
These so-called realizations that people are trying to tie back
To their supposed black ancestry
But pretty much always based on the worst racist stereotypes
Stuff like all black people have written
Remember that's injected two days
At www.andictedterraise.com
So this promo comes at a very appropriate time
Because we have something to talk about
Regarding race and racism
Now I am not a racist
I am also not politically correct
As you know if you listen to the daily source code
So I call it as I see it
But my parents installed the proper version of software in my brain
And I grew up in the Netherlands
Where a country where two million Jews were annihilated
Ship often trains to concentration camps by Nazis
I went to a very mixed race college
Not for a long time three months
But I was there my roommate Tyree
From Trenton New Jersey was black
I actually pledged
Kappa fraternity
Which is kind of funny
I was the shadow
And I just I see no color
I really don't
But if I see someone who's
As we would say African-American
He's black
You're yellow you're red whatever the fuck
We're all red on the inside
Um
So for me there's uh
I am completely color blind
But you see it you call it
So that's not really what I'm what I want to talk about
We have an issue and this is a community issue
And I want to discuss this with the community
IndiePotter.org as you know
Is a directory
That although we as in podshow operate it
All of the nodes are maintained
Actually the nodes the files themselves are hosted on servers maintained by the node managers
So the content of that I'm basically linking to these nodes
If you look at you know it looks like it's all in one place
Which of course is the point right that's that's the beauty of these OPML distributed directories
And which means that a node can be added or dropped whenever you want
What I can't do is I can't manage what's in the node
Nor do I want to because then you run into huge problems
Basically doing directory management and you need a big staff
We have about a hundred volunteers maintaining these nodes now
Which is the only way it works
Um and usually
When we have some kind of conflict as an easy way to resolve it
The conflicts usually are I can't get into the category
The node manager isn't responsive
Or
People say I don't feel like maintaining it anymore
Can you find someone to take over the node for me
And that's really it doesn't happen very often
But now I got an email from
The podcast shuffle
And he says look I don't think that you should be linking to
This racist podcast and it took me a little while
To understand what exactly was going on
But finally I tracked it all down in the
Politics node which is maintained by guy named Mike Murray
There is a link to the Goi Fire podcast
And that is and I'd listen to it last night
Without a doubt
Um a hate based podcast
So you know personally I don't mind if you call me white honky
You know whatever
But if you say I should die or I don't deserve to be a member of society
Then I do have a problem with it
Then of course on the other end you have free speech
So if I were maintaining a node I would not put this this type of podcast in the node
By the way a daily source code is linked in that category as well
As a political podcast so I don't entirely agree with that
I mean everyone has some kind of political statement sometime
But this show is far from about politics
So now the approach that the podcast shuffle made in email
I didn't like because it was basically saying hey
You know if you don't remove that I'm going to call you out
And I don't think you'd like that if people knew that you were promoting hate
And I'm like whoa whoa whoa whoa
Back up that is not the way to approach this problem
So that's really irrelevant I just want to get that out there
So I listen to the podcast
And it is something I personally do not want to be associated with but I'm not
Indirectly of course we are because indie potter links to this OPML node
Which in turn has a link to this podcast
So I emailed Mike Mike Murray and said you know dude what's your take on this
And actually let me just read the email because I really liked the way he responded
Even though I may not agree with his viewpoint he said
Adam was hoping that situations like this could be avoided when I decided to maintain the politics
node I knew that this would be the node that would have the most potential for controversy
I also thought that it was important that the right to free speech
No matter how offensive some may find it should be given a high priority now
I of course am so this is me Adam speaking I am of course someone who
Finds free speech extremely important
So Mike goes on as to whether that show belongs in the politics node
I think that I question whether it belongs in the in the politics node
Because I didn't hear him talking about politics I heard a lot of hate
Hate talk
He says I think that most people would think of white nationalism as a political movement
Politics is a pretty broad category for example socialism
Though commonly thought of as a political system is really an economic system
But most would agree that a socialist podcast belongs in the politics node
I don't want to get into a battle over semantics
But I want you to understand the way I view this node so that I understand
Here's the part that I think is extremely grown up that Mike wrote
If you feel that this show should not be in the directory
I would ask that you remove me as the maintainer of the node
I don't ask this out of anger or hard feelings
I feel very strongly about free speech and don't want to have to deal with removing feeds when people don't like the content
Let me know if you need the latest copy of the node and I will send it to you
So again that was a extra that's the way this is supposed to work
But now my question to you is where how do we do this?
How do we draw the line?
I know that personally we can do whatever we want
We could basically get a copy of the politics node from Mike
And we could drop that particular link and maintain it
I could maintain it or hand it off to someone else
But I don't want to. I don't know. I want this to be resolved
Or I want us to have some kind of thoughts about how we deal with these things
And you know at what point?
Where is the where do you draw the line with free speech?
Is there a legal definition? Are there legal boundaries?
I'm not a lawyer obviously.
Is there a line that could be drawn in the sand where something is just illegal?
I mean if it's clear that if there was a podcast about
And of course everyone used the same for an example
If there was a podcast about pedophilia
It would be removed everyone would say yes of course
Because that's basically harmful to children
But I think that all people are basically children
And any type of hate
Directed towards anybody is wrong
But I would like your feedback on this
I would like some suggestions ideas
Clearly there's no conflict here because Michael is willing to do whatever
And go with whatever flow and I really really appreciate that
But let's and don't just fire off an email
You know do your research listen to listen to that show
And and help me out here because I definitely need a little bit of guidance
And if I were just going to get guidance from my own conscience
Or potentially from pod show lawyers
You know they would say remove it immediately
And I'm again I wouldn't want it in my note
But it's not in my note but it is linked from our directory
So help me out and let me know what you think
Adam at curry.com
Hi Adam
This is Cory over at the 501c3 cast
A podcast for nonprofit professionals volunteers
And all around do gooders
As we know Hurricane Katrina has brought enormous devastation
And grief to New Orleans and the surrounding areas
Over the past few weeks we have watched some horrible images of human loss
But have also been touched by equally powerful displays of charity and support
It's important for all of us to remember that as the media hype declines
The work of the red cross and other nonprofits continues
Could you please share a few of these reminders with your listeners?
Remember the recovery efforts don't stop when the news stories do
There are going to be needs in Louisiana and beyond for years to come
Find out what you can do to help with the long term efforts
Also as the holiday giving season approaches
Remember that your generous contributions to hurricane relief efforts
Is not a replacement for donations that you would normally make
To your favorite charities and nonprofits
As funds have been diverted to support the survivors of hurricane Katrina
Your local nonprofits need your regular support more than ever
Please don't forget them
Also remember that all tragedies strike suddenly and unexpectedly
Unfortunately there will be other events in the future that will require your help
The best way to aid in these events is become a trained volunteer now
If you felt helpless watching the images of the recent hurricane
And wish there was a way you could help then then sign up now
If you or anyone you know has a strong interest in the work of nonprofits and their stories
I also welcome you to check out the 501c3cast
You can find us at www.501c3cast.com
Or by searching for nonprofit in the iTunes directory
And remember if we keep working together it will get better
It was born on July 15, 2005
And now the seven headed monster from Pod Show Music
Is about to make landfall
Music
Starting Monday, September 26, coming to a media player near you
See see what the hell are you doing man? What's going on?
I don't even know what this is
I can't wait
The 26 I will definitely be tuned in with my media player
Excellent
Hey, so there's a big, big, big mega
Music industry bash
Taking place in Las Vegas Friday night
It is a party
It is a
Dremaine de Priz birthday birthday party
I think he has like the number one record in the country
Now I really don't follow the charts anymore
But of course I know him he's been Janet Jackson's boyfriend
For many, many years
Who wasn't that
And through Greg Lawley we talked about him
He hooked up with him after 11 years
He has set up some meetings
This is basically one of those
If you have a number one record in the country in the old school music business
Everybody wants to be your buddy of course
And it's huge and it's a weekend
And he's throwing a birthday bash
And he's invited all the right people
He's a rat pack dress
Which sucks because I don't have my rat pack clothes
I don't know where I'm going to find time to shop for rat pack clothing
So I'm basically trying to get a hat and a cane
And try and play it off that way
And some gold cufflinks I guess
And so Greg has set up a couple
Because we talk for hours about pod safe music
And basically there's a two way street that I'd like to open up
I'd like for pod safe music to be able to go
Through some of the traditional distribution channels
Which means and really is distribution
I'm not talking about getting pod safe artists
Signed up to record labels but distribution
Distribution and promotion
Which equals sales
And I think that people who are serious about their profession as musicians
Either you go work in a bar
You play gigs on weekends
Or you find other means to make money
And the pod safe music not work as one way
With direct sales
And through lots of promotion on podcast
Which is fantastic
And I think if something gets really popular
Be great if we could have somewhat broader traditional distribution
So that's one thing I'm going to talk about
Some of these execs about
And of course the other one is
Okay, so what if there's a great song
That is licensed by the RIAA
Which by the way
It's the RIAA is just an association
It's the owner of the masters
So it's the record label in most cases
The master
And if you want to play a
Traditional music business song on your podcast
You have to have as far as we know at this point
Because of course no one has a straight answer
You have to have two things taken care of
One is you have to have
You have to pay your ASCAP BMI license fee
Which is not a huge amount of money
But if you...
Well it's significant
I mean it's like a thousand bucks a year
At least
And if you make money with your podcast
You have to have a percentage of your gross income
Okay
That's fair
Makes sense and that's a deal
It's been around for a long time
But then you also have to have permission
In this case
Because we're talking about digital downloads
And that's a very, very fuzzy area
And of course 99% of all record executives
Have never
Have never listened to a podcast
They probably think it's playlists of music being played
Not that
They have to have an listen
So I don't know what's going on
It's like radio except it's our kind of radio
You know what we do what we want
So you have to have permission in order to play it
And then of course you technically could
So what I'd like to talk to some of these labels about
Is
Waving both fees if possible
And again I'm not a lawyer
But if we get some written permission on stuff
Then it could be interesting to see what shows up
Because look I'm not interested in playing
Jermaine Dupree because the radio stations do a fine job of that
And it's a number one song
But I am interested in playing lots of back catalog as an example
And I think that it's we know it results in sales
People go to iTunes
I play that French song
Schonce Lise
On was it Monday show
I got so many responses
So many people
And it sounds from 1969
It's almost as old as I am
And people loved it
And of course I was in total violation
Because I don't have the rights to play that song
But it is a part of the soundtrack of my life
And that's something that's really important
I want to be able to mash stuff up
Mashups is another blatant violation
I want that to be legal and I want there to be an incentive
And I want there to be everyone to win
So I want to be able to add a mash up to the iTunes music story
So the people can download that
And also download the original tracks
So there's a, as I said, big power
Big power I'm going to go
Vegas is great
Because it's only about an hour and 15 minutes from San Francisco
So I think when we go we have dinner with the guys from Deaf Jam
And from Virgin
And then of course
Well, shocks
I guess I'll have to
I guess I'll have to go to the party
Oh man, that's going to be so hard
You know how I hate parties
Hey, this one showed up on the pod
Safe Music Network
Two days ago
Brand new brother love
There she goes
She goes
So I'm shot in the so good to you
What happened?
Don't leave it so soon
It's alright
When it's okay
Yeah
Get it over there
So anybody else says
Such a stuff and what I think I'm in love with you
I come out
You're so sweet little honey
You're smiling at least in the love me
Just like that
We'll go outside
I know we're willing to do it
Yeah, I go
And I've been told
I can't wait until there it is
First you say you can't
Let me say you can
You don't want to take it's you
Well
My names are there
I'm on the road
I must be the biggest
I've got the status
Good evening man
Yes it goes
Now this's
God knows
Now this is God knows
Now this is God most
God knows
To the world.
Show me that you are.
So strange.
How?
She back and tell the story.
Oh, she back and tell the story.
Oh, she back and tell the story, how she told the story.
Just tell the stories, just to keep it by.
And I'm going to love you so, that's the first thing.
No, I don't want to be a loom.
I don't want to be your brother, I don't want to say anything
I don't want to be your brother, I don't want to be your brother
Man you in place in the recib are nothing under the sun
I follow me, follow you, follow me, with no темers
This goes again, this goes again
What's going on?
I feel like I should be back again, yeah, yeah
As you go, as you slip, as you go is like it Yeah
You can't get away, you gotta relax like it
In your mouth is lied. I'll try to figure out
I know you don't really love this
I'm out of my mind, she's at times
I believe it's what you think of your mind
Go in, go in, go in
Come on and let me in
I'm not gonna get in though
Not up again
No
I'm out of my mind
Oficant saying dogs and dogs,Ts are dance girls, let's get you on!
I've got cable for once.
Such a super.
Had no idea what you think.
Left in love.
Bye!
Grab the love.
There she goes!
I can't believe it did 43 minutes, even though I was planning to do like 25.
I just haven't too much fun here in the condo.
Hey everybody, I'm off to the office.
I'm going to put the show up on the server, get some former show notes going,
and I will be back with you tomorrow.
Another Potsho podcast, stick it in your ear.