Delta Sierra Charlie 2-5-1 Please save me from people who've been told what to like and
then like it.
In my opinion, if you're over six years of age and you're still getting your music
from the radio, something is desperately wrong with you.
I can only hope that somehow MP3 players and file sharing will destroy FM radio the way
they're destroying record companies.
Then even though the air will probably never be safe to breathe again, maybe it will
be safer to listen to.
Hi everybody, welcome to the Daily Source Code Sunday.
Today's October 2nd, 2005 special source code today.
I'm back home.
Hello.
Hello darling.
This is not good to have you home.
Thank you dear.
This is a horrible.
The studio is not set up for this.
Are you the base?
Why?
Because you're looking at my ass.
Oh yeah.
Well that's nice.
I've been thinking about it all the time and now it's there.
Uh-huh.
Oh yeah baby.
Do you remember?
What the ass?
Not the ass.
Oh.
Yesterday when I came home.
I Christina, how are you?
Look at her face.
What?
More to five.
That's how you get her out of it.
So you get her out of the studio.
Yeah.
Goodbye.
Bye.
So I've been gone for like two and a half weeks.
We're back.
That was long.
That was a long time.
Yeah.
That part sucked.
It was really quiet though.
Although.
I think it's always nice to, you know, to just be a part for a while.
And then when you come home, it's so much fun.
That's true.
You know, it's, it's so happy.
I'm so happy to see you then.
Well also when we're together then we're, it's like 24 hours because I never leave
that.
Well that's it.
That's it.
You always hear.
I'm always here walking around on my bathrobe.
Yeah.
That's not true.
No.
Sometimes.
I live it too long.
But now I could spend a little bit more time with Christina.
Yeah.
And you know, which is nice.
Because you ask, you always ask for a lot of attention.
No, I receive.
I don't ask.
But yeah.
But you do that in a sort of sneaky way.
Okay.
Yeah.
So we were talking.
At first of all, that was the legendary George Carlin from his latest book.
I love him.
Yeah.
What the hell?
It doesn't say here.
Someone sent me this.
Yeah.
It's he has a new audio book out, which I got from audible.
But this is like, when will Jesus bring the pork?
I think is the name of it.
But it's so true.
And the Patricia, I've been talking about pot-safe music for a while.
We always talk about music actually because it's our main interest.
Yeah.
And it can be enjoyable.
It can be very irritating.
But in a meanwhile, it's entertainment.
Oh, it was last night that we were watching X-factor.
Yeah.
Sharon Osborn, Simon Cowell, those two.
Right?
Is that a person?
No, it's just those two, right?
No, no, no.
And the other one.
Who's the dude with the orange beret and the green and blue blue?
I don't know.
That was just a...
He's a he's irritating.
Yeah.
I think that was a special guy.
I think so.
The X producer or a music authority that helped her.
Because they all have categories that they take care of.
What?
Absolutely.
No, that's the other guy.
That's what you mean.
From the X-factor, that's the other...
His name is Louis with the beard?
No, no, no.
It's not with the beard.
Yeah.
They're the three of them.
Right, but I want to hear the dude with the beard.
No, I don't know.
It's an English thing.
But he's an American.
Oh, is he?
Oh, maybe he's famous here.
I didn't get it.
But I know.
Yeah, but I know.
He's in a music authority.
That's why he was sitting there.
But anyway.
So we were at one point when Pope Idle started in the Netherlands.
Three years ago, two years ago.
Yeah.
Some things maybe three years ago.
Yeah, three years ago.
I was asked to be the host of the show, which I declined.
But I said, look, if you don't put Patricia in as a judge, you're crazy.
And of course, I was right.
It was not that big.
No, no, but you...
I should have chosen me.
But you would have loved doing that.
Well, they thought it was a bit too much.
You and me.
I did...
I declined anyway.
It doesn't matter.
That doesn't matter.
But you would have thoroughly enjoyed doing that.
Because you do know a lot about music.
Well, not just music, but performance and styling and the whole packaging.
And also, I can always predict when it's something.
When it's something, when someone's going to be hit, that's right.
Do you have a coat on?
My girl's going.
My very girl.
Be very careful.
For bad English man.
Be careful.
Get your credits first.
Be on time, eh?
Okay.
And don't eat that old crap.
Hey, and don't eat all the crap.
Yeah.
So, throughout...
On the food core.
On the dogs.
This is ruining our show.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
No one cares about the show.
It's real.
I just want to say that.
No one cares about the show.
The dogs don't know.
So, during the week on the daily source code,
which I might point out Patricia never listens to.
That's probably better, by the way.
Um.
Overdose of anime.
Yeah.
I play all bunch of, you know, whole bunch of pod safe songs.
And songs that I think, you know, that I like or, you know,
I think I can pick them too, actually.
I guess that's what I'm saying.
But Patricia has, you know, she'll look at someone and say,
Oh, that person has it.
That person has the X factor in fact.
That's, uh, that's what you can exactly say now.
Yeah, it's just it.
But also it.
It.
Right.
The it factor.
Yeah.
So when I'm playing tunes here in the studio,
which is right next door to Patricia's studio.
My Padua.
Yeah, Padua.
Sometimes she'll come in and say, I like that.
Yeah, come running in and say, Oh, I like that.
Yeah, who's that? Who's that?
Beautiful.
So I figured I just play a couple of, uh,
uh, a couple of the songs that I've been playing in the past week.
And then you, you, you tell me what you think about them.
You like you, you like the idea?
Good.
Okay. So I'll put it on the speakers in a second so you can hear a little bit better.
This first one is, uh, Natalie Brown is called in my dreams.
Even though we said goodbye, quite some time ago,
there's a strain of loving my heart.
That just came and let you grow.
It seems that even when I go to sleep,
images of you, my mind's still clear.
And I still see you in my dreams.
No matter how I try it seems,
that it depot of me just can't forget.
That it depot of me still has a request.
And I can't seem to let all the love I had for you grow.
Yes, I still see you in my dreams.
Sometimes I wait with your face in my mind.
Somehow I thought that I'd left those memories behind.
It seems that you have left my heart frustrated
with vivid memories of your smile clear.
That just came and let me dream.
No matter how I try it seems,
that it depot of me just can't forget.
That it depot of me still has a request.
And I can't seem to let all the love I had for you grow.
I still see you in my dreams.
Yes, I still see you in my dream.
Okay, that was not the brown in my dreams.
What is her name?
Natalie Brown.
I'll tell you something about her here.
Yeah, I don't think she is brown.
No, in fact, she is very white.
Yes, she is.
From the pod-set music that we're biopathes,
there's little chance that you'll hear Natalie Brown sing or speak,
and not be moved by the refreshing texture in her voice.
This emotive singer songwriter with a soulful and powerful 4.5 octave range
translates her life experiences into songs that inspire entertain and provoke.
Well, what do we have here?
It's another Mariah Carey.
Yeah, that's Mariah Carey.
Yeah, yeah.
But I thought actually kind of nicer than Mariah Carey.
How sweeter?
Yeah, a little bit more sweeter, very warm, very sensitive.
It really grabbed me.
The song?
No, it's a little bit.
Goes on a little bit too long.
It's like one of those early, it's like one of those early Whitney Houston songs.
Yeah, exactly.
I was thinking about how I was thinking about how I was thinking about her voice.
But her voice?
I don't know how she looks if she has the looks.
Yes, she's got huge hudders.
Oh, that's always nice.
No, I can.
That's too far away.
But that's always nice, you know.
It helps a little bit.
But.
Yeah, okay.
You need something.
We should make that a tag on the podcast.
But her voice is, I think, very she's, she's, she's got a totally on the control.
Yeah.
I like that.
I don't know if she really, if she stopped somewhere and they, you know, did it in part.
But the way it sounds.
I mean, the recording.
Yeah, the recording.
I don't know that.
Interesting.
But it sounds very, very clear.
But it doesn't matter.
It doesn't, I mean, even if you record it that way, that's okay.
Well, it matters if you sing live and you cannot do it the way you recorded it.
It's a bit of bummer, of course.
No.
But it sounded, I like her voice.
I like her voice very much.
Beautiful.
Very warm.
Very sensitive.
And she sings with her heart.
I can tell.
Yeah.
The song is a little bit too weepy too.
All right.
So the chords you sung for an album.
So we should keep our eye on her then.
Yeah.
Definitely.
Good.
Okay.
Let's play a guide then.
Lee, three Harris.
I don't know when I play this.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Actually, I kind of like this one.
Nothing to believe it.
You got MTV and VH1.
And I'm on planet in Nickelodeon.
And a net and a satellite dish and a big tanker,
Dr. Go Fish and a, you don't have this word you whisper.
Nothing to believe in.
Got a pretty girl friend and a big big car.
Everybody knows your name at the bar.
Call that a designer sneakers.
There we go with fancy speakers.
We don't have just what you deserve.
Nothing to believe in.
Right here's right.
When you say you're so.
Nothing more to do.
When you know to learn all that's to fade in.
And ain't gonna say you ain't gonna say you.
Books and books are found in the shell.
Down on the corner.
There's a taco bell.
Nothing to believe in.
Hold on.
That's some of all the things that an American guy needs.
I love the words.
I think it's a great song.
I love it.
Yeah.
Absolutely true.
What are you singing?
What do you mean by that?
Well, we've been there the last time.
I noticed exactly what he was singing.
Yeah.
The sneakers.
We've got this one.
That's also the other side.
The emptiness.
That's actually the Lee Harris III.
It's from Central Virginia.
This song.
The Lee show.
I think they have a podcast too.
Good.
Very interesting.
That's cool.
You should see the picture here.
These guys have their farm around fits on.
Donkey.
That's typical.
You know, you're right.
It's real American rock.
Yeah.
I totally dig that.
Oh man.
I have to do so much work and putting the show notes together.
Putting all these links in.
Yeah.
Doesn't matter.
Okay.
Here's a guy that I think is he's from New York City.
And I really like this guy.
Don't say anything.
Just don't say.
I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to do that.
His name is Brother Love.
This is There She Goes.
So good to you.
Whatever happens, don't leave it so soon.
I'm so good to you.
Ooh.
It's so right when it's okay.
Yeah.
Gonna do that.
I can't win.
Yeah.
Girls, girls, this is girls I can't hear
Girls, girls, no one knows
All of my sins, bad
And I should know that
I shall be back again
This is girls, this is girls
Girls, girls I can't hear
There's no stairs
She'd like to tell the story
Oh, she'd like to tell the stories
Girls, girls, this is the key to my
And I'm gonna love you, girl
I'm a bird friend
No, I don't want to be a loom
I don't want to be a loom
I don't want to be a brother of this toy
To set you up
We'll go outside
I know where that lead
We're gonna do it
Yeah, I know
I've been told
I can't grow up
So there it is, a child's child
I want to be the guy
Because I'm a new to me
Oh, my heart
Oh, do you praise it or not
Like I don't get it getting
Spread all your time
But I'm not up for that
But no real man
Oh, this is girls
This is the key to my
Girls, girls
Girls, this is the key
And I'm gonna love you
I'm a bird friend
This is the key to my
And I'm gonna love you
Yeah, I know you got a lot to learn
Yeah, I know it's not
I'm a bird friend
I know you got a lot of faith
Oh, my heart is in charge
But please, once you think of your mind
We're gonna always go in
Come on and love me
Look up to me
I want to be one
φο
This is the key to my
Girls, this is girls
This is girls
This is girl
This is the key to my
Girls, this is the key
To my girl
Let's get onß 태
I'm deciding
I guess you gotta
I disappointing I guess you gotta
What did you want...