This is the source code for Wednesday, January 19th, 2005.
Transmators, we don't need no stinkin' transmators.
Oncoming casting with Adam Curry.
It is Wednesday, January 19th, 2005.
Everybody, how you doing?
Oh man, this is gonna be a legendary podcast.
I can feel it already, not just because I'm sitting on the couch today,
using everything on the laptop, not hooked up to the monitor the keyboard in the mouse.
I am hooked up to the Firewire Breakout box, of course.
Power, power, power, power, power.
But we've got something celebrated, everybody.
That's right, I got a can of Coke right here.
There you go.
And even though it is 11.36 in the AM,
I'm sitting right underneath the window.
So it's not to leave any traces of the celebratory cigar.
I am smoking right now.
Oh yeah.
We got a lot to talk about today.
We're gonna listen some promos, some pod save music, some great covers.
First, hold on, let's, let's, this is what I was looking for yesterday.
Um, let's see if we can get a little, uh, tympany role going here.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, because, as of yesterday afternoon,
the cottage is connected.
Yeah, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I got some broadband pipe right here on my laptop.
Baby, oh yeah.
And as a guest, you, uh, spark up yourself there.
A little terribly good some other stuff.
I'll be smoking that tonight as a celebration about it.
I've got to tell you all about what happened.
It is unbelievable what has been going on.
And by the way, even though I have broadband in the house,
as we speak, there's a guy outside digging a trench.
It's just, it's unbelievable what's been happening.
I'm gonna place some phone calls for you so you can figure out exactly what went down.
But first, let's celebrate with the whole.
I'm free.
I used 22 gold, I won't have the guts to leave the temple
I'm free, I'm free
And freedom days of reality
And I'm waiting for you to follow me
I'm free, I'm free
I'm free, I'm free, I'm free
I'm free, I'm waiting for you to follow me
Come down to reality, it's the who on the daily source code
And yesterday we'll go down as a great day in my life, that's for sure
Tuesday the 18th
Things started to happen as I really got into the British Telecom
EasyNet broadband issue, I was really getting upset
Now I recorded everything I did yesterday
I'm not going to play the bits where I called up BT
and tried to re-explain everything to them
I'm not going to explain how I'm not going to play the bit where I called
EasyNet again and then went through a whole bunch of guys
until finally I was promised that a manager would call back
which he actually did
but I do want to give you a couple of the bits where the magic started to happen
as I was at Starbucks and there's more to talk about
because it's not all good news
but I was at a hair appointment at
one of those guys named Sam and Dave
No, that's Sam and Dave
Tony and Guy, apparently they're all over the world now
these hair slons and it's a very very hip hair slons
So Patricia went with me down to Guilford to the town
I went into Sam and I'm going to call him Sam and Dave
went into Sam and Dave's
and she opened a book and said this is what I wanted
his hair to look like and she then left
as I went off to Starbucks to go and upload yesterday's source code
So Matt Starbucks, the phone rings
and of course I fumble as much as I can
and I hit the record button because
well you can't hit the record button until
the connection has actually been made
you can't do it while the phone is ringing
either it's ringing on my end on the other end
I saw that it was a cell phone though
and I figured that might be someone who's trying to help me out
so I picked it up
This is the British telecom engineer who came out to the house
and well you heard it
they made a right mess of the whole order he said
hey yeah right
I think it's in the job notes here
that the telecom number
that's the job that I've got
he's full of knowledge
residential lines
yeah it's that already working in solar premises
yeah that's been working
every since we moved in which was two months ago
so yeah that's the second one that's been created
see there's another confusion here still
I'm sorry
you're just having one line in the premises
no this this is the second line
because apparently
there is no wiring to run two lines
there's no existing wiring to run two lines
so basically here I'm going through
explaining this but I figured here's a guy
who actually cares and is trying to help me out
and is admitting that BT is fucked it up
the wiring is there at the house part
let me fast forward a bit let me just see
well I'll tell you let me let me give you the whole history
and maybe that'll give you some
oh no we don't want the whole history
well you couldn't
what you could do
yeah help
bring the doorbell my wife is home
and she knows that you're there
and she'll take you up to the room
and she'll make you feel very happy
if you give her husband broadband
where the box is there's a number on the box
on the
it's like it's not a telephone
so basically I went through
explanations there let's just get the end of this call here
you can find out what nerf is going on here
and see if we can get some form of light
to get the job really raised properly
because I can't do anything
without a job for you and make the BT won't do it
right
the line test okay so I got the wrong number
they put you down here first line
which is a full full nine six
I'm sure that line works fine
it's probably busy because we're dialed into the
internet all day so I'll come down
to this go on a full for January then
yes yes exactly
I'll try and sort something out for you
I'll give you a call back show
and I really appreciate the calls back
that's the only thing I really asked for
just to be letting me know
I'll see if I can get to the bottom of this for you
okay thank you
thank you
so I reviewed this phone call like wait a minute
there's something really funky going on
because British telecom thinks that
our normal house line which you heard
starts with 449
that that was
essentially the line that they were testing
so they were testing the the wrong number entirely
and getting proper tests but now
what does that mean does that mean
that that original line was broad band enabled
so that was pretty confusing
then literally seconds after that I get a call
from easy net
hello hello hello is Adam
yes speaking oh hello Adam is
Adam from meeting that calling
hi I just been speaking to to fill
and we're actually dealing with this case
on Friday but unfortunately
look like nobody's actually updated
what has actually been done
yeah um we've um
I spoke to the the LLU manager actually
that's rechargeable these lines on Friday
and that basically what's happening
is they reopen the job for provisioning
engineer to come back out and actually
get the the piece of cable
is actually missing
and um I think there were
I think there were hoping to try and do that
today but obviously we thought they have
and I just told the manager that
unfortunately she wasn't available so I've left
the message with her
but I'll try and I'll try and get back to
as soon as I found out a bit more
okay so at this point I'm like all right
this guy's pretty good you know and I went
through a couple bits of history with him
I'll fast forward to the end of this call as well
just kidding he's pretty me
which is even more number there
to call in case I needed some more
or had some info for him actually
three
okay um if we at least can keep each other updated
on whatever status then you know
that's going to be a step in the right direction
yeah definitely
because this is just this is driving me crazy
yeah and also no surprise yeah
okay so
when when this guy calls me back
I'll let you know what he says and what he's
figured out okay if you don't
if you hear anything please give me a call
good deal then okay thanks
thank you bye
okay so um I was feeling a little bit
bit about that phone call
and then minutes later and remember
I'm still sitting at Sart
hold on
the drunken bit
I'm still sitting at Starbucks
and then the BT engineer calls me back
how are you?
hello not safe at how would you
feel if I could put proof and on your
phone call
do you like men kissing you
with that work
yeah what are you going to tell me all about it
what I've got is basically what we just discussed
but is exactly the problem and nobody can pick up
this number that you've got written on the
socket because it's very easy
right so basically what we're going to do is
I'm going to put you an extension socket
right next to that other one
yeah all right
if you're talking to that when you get home
you should be able to sign
straight on to free BT
all right this is I'm like
whoa wait a minute
so he's got broadband enabled now
on the original house line which
means somehow a port freed up
or BT freed up a port
and connected my regular line to
ADSL I'm like
huh boy
so we've hooked up and ready to go
well that's certainly a great
solution for now yes
yeah
the only problem I've got is whether you
have to actually sign straight on to it
you may well have to sign up
sales on one five zero
so it's the point my brain is going
a thousand miles admitted I'm like
god damn I never ordered broadband
through British telecom because they have
a metered servers you only get like
twenty megs or twenty gigs a month
I'm like well but shit you know I'll take anything at this point
right so
and I knew that oh man it's going to be a pain in the
past have to go sign on and get everything
working through British telecom because you know
they're going to be like who? how can you have the line already
but not have an order and a log on
well then to
locate you on the line all right
but so that's so that's
so I'll be on BT broadband now
an easy net that's right yeah
it's that kind
well it's certainly fixed it for now but obviously
easy net's going to have to figure out their
problems and get that right right
more batteries about the dollar
or something on the phone so much
I'll do that for you now I'll get the extension
and if you plug into that and log on to
no you should find you'll be up and run
I appreciate it
all right okay thank you very much
fine well so even though I got that message yesterday
I wasn't about to post that on the web
log or put it in any kind of show yet because I'm like
well I don't know what that means so
I went home
plugged in I still had the
router from UK online
the original provider who I
who I'd contacted because they have
a unmetered service you can download
as an upload as much as you want
although it's not you know for
megabits per second as easy net I'm like
oh shit so I went back and I
didn't call BT broadband I called
UK online
explain the situation now this by the way
is I think the residential arm
of easy net and
immediately they said oh no problem
I said look I see the light
on I know that my account was cancelled
I got put through to an engineer
within three seconds he helped me configure
the router out of change one parameter
from 38 to 35 or something
and bingo
I was connected
and the first person actually to
notice it was Steve Gilmore
he sent me a Skype message
which I didn't see until this morning
said look I've seen you pop up on
Skype twice today does that mean
broadband has arrived at the cottage
so indeed
he was right
and it was working last night
and I've been you know I
potters been running for hours
I've been listening to shit I've been
able to go through my email
and get all kinds of you know
promos and sound songs and
sound sing tours and stuff that
y'all have been emailing me
and then the morning as I was
in the car taking Christina to school
Patricia calls up and she says well
he's got his digging tools
do I let him dig and I said fuck yeah
let the man dig so the guy is
let me just see
he's still outside digging
I have the window open so you'll probably
hear some digging sounds and his equipment
one guy he's been here since
he's right now it's 10 to 12 he's been here since
shoot
quarter to nine this morning
just about nine o'clock
he's been here for almost three hours
even though the comments on the
weblog suggested you know you should
give me a cup of coffee or tea
I've offered him more than that
obviously by the way the beat the
bt engineer that was here yesterday
Patricia really laid into him and
unfortunately she and Ivana Roxy
her sister's daughter
have gone off to London today
otherwise Patricia would have gladly told
me the story and told you the story
so I'll get her on tomorrow
because she has to talk about a couple
of them missed all of this joy
this just fantastic great news
Tony and guy fucked up my hair
my head looks like a knob
momentarily it's not pretty at all
they cut it way too short I didn't
my glasses on and I look horrible
no pictures please and we'll have
Patricia talk about that tomorrow as well
because well you know about her
and the curries right so
we'll have an interesting show
I'll make sure I get Patricia on the show tomorrow
oh shit no I can't get on the show tomorrow
because I'm flying to Amsterdam
Kaka
right then maybe Friday or maybe Monday
will have to see
but it doesn't matter
because you know and the girls are
cracking jokes on my hair you know
the same oh well you know it'll grow back
all the crappy things you say to someone
who's a hair got fucked
and actually it's a very English kind of
looking hairdo you know so
I guess it kind of fits the
the area but no it was it was not
what I wanted unfortunately
doesn't matter though I was like I don't
fucking care I could be bald
I got my god damn broad band
hi Adam Matthew Bishop here
your fact guy
I've got an interesting page here
at Skype.com it's at Skype.com
slash helps slash guides
messaging all on word.html
and it has a whole explanation
of the voice messaging system
you should go check it out
the invites are called vouchers
and they're available on the my account page
you probably would have gotten an email
but they're going to slowly phase out
voice messaging and I can tell here
from the page in one of the last FAQs
let's see
or actually maybe
yeah here the second FAQ question
how much will voice messaging cost
and then the answer from Skype
is exact pricing details
have yet to be finalized
you'll be informed of the subscription
cost before the trial ends
so it will not be free
but as you said you'd be willing to pay
for some extra features and voice mail
and I'm hoping recording
will be some of those features
there's also a question how can I invite
friends to join Skype voice messaging
and it says once we are ready to expand
our testing you will see a link
in my account page where you can invite new users
so invitations are hopefully on the way
I know I didn't get an email
from Skype but I would love to get one as well
another interesting thing is that
you can leave messages for people who are offline
and they'll receive them
once they're online
and you can create your own
status message
and there's an option for
I'm looking at a screenshot
when I reject an incoming call
send call to voice mail
or play busy tone
or another option is
when I'm in a call
send incoming call to voice mail
and then there's an idol if I don't answer
within certain number of seconds
so go check it out
Skype.com slash help slash guys
thank you very much Matthew
my fact guy appreciated
apparently only windows users
and select windows users
received an invitation from Skype to use
voice mail
Mac people are not included in the trial
but looking forward to that
I would definitely buy that service from Skype
I've actually ordered one of those
cordless Skype phones
because I want to
I have to admit I'm also in the
in the throes of getting a windows machine
for downstairs
the Skype wireless phone is great
you just plug it into a USB port on the phone
and I'm going to give Patricia
Skype account and in the hand set itself
which can also be used
wireless to use your regular phone
line in coming and outgoing
you see your buddy list right there
in the phone is to who's online
who's on Skype and it's going to be great
because now I think the Skype global
call-out rate is
1.7 euro since per
per minute
which is oh god that's so much cheaper
than the regular BT phone line
now you don't have an incoming
but it really doesn't matter for the type of
phone calls that we're doing
excuse me
too much excitement too much coke and too much
of the cigar
lots of people responding
about sound seeing
it's so good now
that I am setting up a domain
and thank you all very much multiple people
have registered
variations of sound seeing
dot com sound seeing tours
sound scape and what's beautiful about
you know
donating these domain names to me
which is fucking awesome so I'm going to
create a new site
and all of those domain names will
point to it to that new site
hold on
and
I'm basically just going to put up
MP3's to great sound seeing tours
I guess I'm not quite sure how I'm going to do it
there will be a podcast feed of course
and I've received a couple of
see I put these in the show notes for today
and it's actually put up a
great fucking system
the mob casting and bush protest
to blogspot.com websites
and he's tricked out
audio blogging.com
and blogspot.com
combining it with feed burner
to create some kind of automatic
system that
lets you call a phone number
hit a pin code
record something and then it shows up
in the RSS feed and the podcast feed
site so
the bush protest clearly is for
the inauguration and the mob casting
is his first experiment
with a mob casting tool
so check those out. I've asked him
for technical details which I'm sure he'll
give us loads of know how we can set that up
because that is very cool and I love it
when you can tie a couple of services together
because that's shit that's pretty much
how I started with iPotter
and then another one came in
I'll just play a little bit
a bit from Alan Joyce
who did a sound scene to work inside
office depot
let me say it
what was really cool is he
when over to the problems or
static or what
I wonder what it was that I was doing
with that microphone on my
front
yeah
it's a handset
right here's some
sates
let's get back to the digital stuff
okay
so not bad actually any
in that particular sound scene
to we talked about the microphone
that he used
which actually sounds pretty damn good
so again all of that linked as usual
from the production show
for today's podcast
and buyer and lease sent me an email
Adam really love the idea of sound
seeing especially since I'm legally blind
think it's cool when sighted people experience
the world through sound
the world I would like to thank you for getting
people excited about sound seeing
like to ask you if you could start a note on i
potter for sound seeing
definitely consider it done
thanks for taking me around Gilford and south floor to keep it up
maybe we can go on a tour in the Netherlands next week
yes this week we're going to do a tour
totally
I was thinking about
doing the easy jet tour but i'm not going to be a
big pain in the fucking ass with you know i got
transmitters and recording devices and everything
is not allowed so maybe i'll pick it up at
it's people airport or something like that
or maybe i don't know we'll have to see
definitely want to do some more sound seeing for you
because people love it you know this is
a part of a threat of podcasting that is catching on so
shit let's give the people what they want
definitely we'll start a a
a note in the i potter.org directory
James Carter says hey Adam love the show
but i'm driven mad by your mispronouncing of
Surrey
Adam curry
from Surrey never in a hurry
but i got my fat pie
you
Adam thanks for doing what you do
thought i dropped you an email
let you know that you Dave and the rest
of the podcast in pioneers have been
spying me to start my own little show
it's not about fear i'm sorry
for god haven't prepared
or even drum cadences
if you hadn't already figured out
by the wacky music bed
it's all about Disney
it's called the mouse pod
and our goal is to talk about the movies
the theme parks the TV shows the music the books
the DVDs and the legacy of the guy from Kansas
and this little mouse
we're going to be developing a pretty deep into
the Disney Arcana
but we're going to stay entertaining
i promise
anyway
we can check out our debut podcast
at www.pocketsimphony.com
just click on the word mouse pod
for details
and just because i had yet to hear a promo with
related trivia question
here we go
there's at least one attraction
and it's just Disney's work to ride
okay
first to add dancer
get to pick the theme music
for the next mouse pod
set your answers to
mouse pod
at pocketsimphony
see you real soon
slots at the Caribbean
funger me mountain
space trip
the mouse pod
new podcast
of course you can find all the new podcast
and i potter.org
new ones are launched on the home page
and of course they're automatically
filed away in the
the directory which you can get to
from the link podcast directory
and of course don't forget audio.weblogs.com
that's the place where new podcast
that have just been released
so not necessarily a new podcast
you can subscribe to but
new ones that have just been thrown out
into the potter sphere
where you can check them out
so an XML button there where you can
copy that podcast feed
remember we were talking about
I had got a promo in
from podcast Paul
and he had some music playing the background
which was by an out-of-called
dynamo rhythmases
and i couldn't get
an MP3 well of course
mentioning that just once on the source code was enough
and yeah you bet you here are the dynamo rhythmases
with the fight for your right
to partying
on the day the source code
let's party
you wake a little school man
you don't want to go you ask him
I'm a please but still says no
give the two classes and no home work
teach teachers there's like some kind of
you got a fight
you're right
to party
oh
yeah
all
like
yeah
all
Yeah pumped up.
Yeah pumped it, pumped it.
Yeah pumped it, pumped it, pumped it.
Wow right.
Yeah pumped it.
Yeah pumped it, pumped it.
Yeah, yeah, you got a fight for you, right?
Support it.
Everybody's now.
Oh, yeah.
Support it.
Get out of this house without the clothing on the way.
Get out of this house, move.
Come back out.
Months isn't in a sense.
That's fantastic.
Mommy and Josie's not the boy that's gonna fight.
But it's right.
Support.
I'll say.
Oh, they're everybody now.
Oh, yeah.
Support it.
We'll...
You wake the Blitz club before you don't want to go.
Ask them all the fleas butt just doesn't know.
Skip to class that no homework.
Teach it easy to stand like some kind of dick.
You got a fight for your rights.
Support it.
All day, everybody's now home
Weird up no
Come on, people
Go, up
Baby, how am I"?
Don't know where the Mason is.
On dudes?
Yeah, baby.
Fight for your right to partay.
The original, of course, by the Beastie Boys.
Well, I was playing.
I was going to say something.
I was going to say, oh, yeah.
They're with my newfound broadband last night.
I immediately started to make all kinds of Skype out calls.
I talked to Lee Ann Wester.
Lee Ann from the Sylvia's Bitties.
They were having a band meeting.
That evening, yesterday evening,
about the first Bitties podcast.
And so we talked a little bit about that.
Man, those girls are great.
They are my angels from Nueva York.
I love them.
And I guess sometime around February,
I'll probably be in New York and going to San Francisco
to the Wired Rave Awards.
I'd like to swing by there and check out the scene.
Who knows where else we'll wind up.
But definitely, it'll be time for an America trip.
Round midfab.
It's going to be busy month actually.
Got a lot to do.
Who else had talked to?
Told you to talk to Drew, right?
I was supposed to have a call with Mad Weinstein.
But it was too late,
because she doesn't get off work until 6pm,
which would have been midnight here.
And I was just so happy.
And I've been bouncing around so much.
I fell asleep around 11.
So that's a call I'm going to make later on today.
But it's just great.
It's great to be back.
It's great to have bandwidth.
And you know, come up with all these cool things
that have been sent to me.
As I said earlier in an email,
which I just haven't been able to get to.
You know, kind of overlooked because I saw.
Oops, that's five mags.
You know, let me calculate.
That's, uh,
Oh, that's going to be about 25 minutes,
30 minutes to download.
And I'm actually having to relearn how to click on stuff.
I said, yeah, I can look at that.
Yes, I can listen to that.
Yes, it will be here almost immediately.
It's kind of like, you know,
being constipated for a couple of weeks.
And then, you know,
and then having a full release.
Well, now let's see what the guy is doing outside.
Oh, man.
That's a bigger job.
And I thought it was actually to be quite honest.
And by the way, I went out and when I bought him his coffee,
he just lays down the pipe.
He doesn't actually do the connections.
So I have to see how long it takes before that shows up.
Here's something cool.
A lot of complaints about people not being able to see
the Steve Jobs keynote of late in real time
when he was introducing the iPod Mini.
Sorry, let me say that right.
The shuffle and the Mac Mini.
But there's a solution to that.
The solution is something that Brian storms put together
or is it Brian storms.
That would be the Steve Jobs keynote in 60 seconds.
And it's not incredible.
It's not incredible.
It's really beautiful.
And I am thrilled.
Really easy to do.
Not incredible.
Your power is free.
It's very, very tiny.
And it's in a building that's owned by the crown.
Anyway, we can really screw up music this way.
And it is spectacular.
It's not incredible.
Your mortals can set this up.
And you can do almost anything.
And it is spectacular.
It's not incredible.
You're going to search for love.
It's really unique.
It's in a building that's owned by the crown.
Anyway, we can really screw up music this way.
If you have a passion for wine, come join us at GreyPredio.com.
We're dedicated to sharing a passion for wine.
There's no wine stops here.
Just straight talk about wine.
We'll also bring your interviews with wine makers,
Vineyard owners, wine retailers, restaurant tours, and so on.
It's easy to subscribe.
Just go to GreyPredio.com, click on our RSS feed,
or find us at all the podcast directors.
So come share glass with us and make sure that you're subscribing to GreyPredio at www. GreyPredio.com.
You have another podcast from the Brilliant Mine and Michael Gohagan.
We know from real reviews.
Great radio.
Oh, man.
Excuse me.
Oh, let me get rid of this thing in my throat.
There we go.
Oh, God, sorry.
Right, oh.
What are we at now?
34 minutes.
Okay.
Good timing is almost perfect today.
I guess I said emails.
This one's from before Christmas, December 23rd from Peter Gyros,
who sent me a nice email sympathizing with my dial-up woes.
Oh, I'm all over that now, my friend.
But he created something so freaking beautiful.
And today is a day where you got the fever and the only thing they can cure
is more cowbell.
Back to the reverb.
So the reverb is basically off.
However, I have added some more cowbell.
I think that makes the show much better.
Don't you?
I can never have too much cal but oh hey.
I'll call.
I think that makes the show much better.
I think that makes the show better.
You can never have too much cal but oh hey.
I'll call.
I can never have too much cal but oh.
I can never have too much cal but oh hey.
too much cowbelly, but basically...
I'm sorry. That really sucked.
That's just no good. We're going to have to do that again, I'm sorry.
You know what I need right now?
You know what I really need?
Put your hands on your iPod or your N.D.
Reware at this moment, my brothers and sisters.
Have to do more cowbell.
You're right, Ambex selfish.
But the last time I checked, we don't have a whole lot of songs to feature the cowbell.
Yes, what? I got a fever.
And the only prescription is more cowbell.
That's the dumb somkin cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell Cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbell cowbellows
the other day. That's such an awesome mix. Mashup makes whatever you want to call it. Thank you very much. That's great.
Oh, yeah. A lot of people emailed me. Of course, the song don't know much about history.
Don't know much about biology. Don't know much about science book. Don't know much about the French I took.
Was by Sam Cook. Of course. And I looked at my iTunes. I still don't have it. And an email as we wind up
today's show. Just a couple more things I want to hit on. This is from Randall. Is it from Randall?
Yeah. Adam, your podcast was 42 minutes yesterday. My community commute to work 20 minutes.
Yesterday, after 20 minutes of your podcast, I parked my 4 by 4. Shut everything off a continued listening.
A lady parked next to me and proceeded to change her shirt. I got that cool,
Brazier shot. Thanks to the source code. Never can tell what good things will happen to those who listen.
Buying. Yeah. Excellent. Of course, I was looking for the picture attachment, but that unfortunately was nowhere to be found.
And hello, Les Pozen. How you doing? Good morning, Australia.
I had a Les Pozen in Melbourne, Australia. Just to mention it, my first podcast is up there.
It's a suicide podcast, which means I'm looking at research and publications and items of interest in
the general media. I am that psychologists and anyone with an interest in psychology.
The aim is to bring people up to date with their new research and provide them with links on my webpage.
Give the podcast short about 20 minutes. Thanks for inspiration and thanks for your assistance.
And okay, from IT Conversations, this is also an intimate assistance by letting me put up some
short snippets from some of the IT Conversations of relevance. I hope you get a chance to listen.
I'll catch you another time. Thanks for your help.
Alright, buddy. My pleasure. And I hope to get to Australia one of these days.
Because there's a lot of good, good vibes going on down under with the podcasting.
One last thing I promised I do. I promised I'd call Wing Commander William.
My flight instructor about the new Airbus A380. I said,
yeah, and actually I'm trying to hook up with him tomorrow to do a little bit of flying in his new
Sess No 182. Which may work out if he doesn't have a pain customer, right?
Because all I have to do is pay for gas essentially in coffee and sandwiches.
I said, you know, William. So what's the deal with this thing? He said, oh man, this thing is awesome.
So but, you know, it's like, what kind of airfield do we need to land this fucker? He says, Adam,
this plane compared to a 747 has longer range uses less fuel,
can carry almost twice as many people and uses a shorter runway.
God, and I said, but dude, you know, it's like all it has to happen is for one of these things to fall
out of the sky and you know, 800 people get killed at once and that'll be the end of it. He said,
dude, it can only be an act of terrorism. He says, these things will not fall out of the sky.
There's so redundant at these are so modern. These planes are just awesome.
So there you have it from the Wingman, the Wing Commander himself. He certainly would know.
And I was just blown away by the fact that it has a shorter runway necessity.
I said, well, so, you know, what's that? He said, well, you know, airbus, the French, and the English,
and everyone really fucked Boeing. He said, but you watch out, those guys are going to come back
with something pretty heavy with their own super jet. So the race is on.
When I'm in the kitchen, I'll take it up. I'll take it up. I'll take it up.
I'll use the easy listening. I'll make it be loud. I'll take it up.
Morning, noon, and night.
Good night, internet.
That's it for your source code for Wednesday, January 19th. It's just fun.
And I'll gladly see you back tomorrow, probably on a sound scene tour of the Netherlands.
Thank you all for checking in. Thank you all very much for living with me for the past two months.
As I've been strapped down by bandwidth constraints,
living on the motor, we're back on broadband.
It'll probably take until next week, until the easing at Fat Fat Life is up.
But hey, I've got some going now.
So, we'll have to run noon here on Wednesday afternoon. So, I'm going to upload this show
from the convenience and comfort of the cottage.
It's all as comments out of Maccurry.com.
If you got some really big descend, like a big SMP3 file sent that to my Gmail account,
MP3feedback at gmail.com.
And of course, you can always leave a comment on the weblog www.curry.com.
And all the archives of this show available at dailysourcecode.com. We also find the podcast feed.
Talk to you tomorrow, everybody. Bye-bye.