With $16 million worth of airplanes strapped to my ass, then the next generation
radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
They are a Charlie 3-0-2, happy Tuesday everybody.
But I'm Brooklyn in the USA.
They're coming to the ground.
I take my name, got on a plane.
I find a place to go home.
I'm my train in the Westway.
I'm never in the plane, never be.
Look at my mama, my name is a racer.
I'm a farm car, not lingers, I'm a temperful racer.
I'm a man.
Yeah.
I've got my kids with a set of chicks.
I can't want to, until I take it in, I'm never in the trace.
I find a blue one, what I know about it was red.
I got red in the Westway.
I'm never in the plane, never be.
Look at my mama, my name is a racer.
I'm the farm car, not lingers, I'm a temperful racer.
I'm a man.
I get my kids with a set of chicks.
I can't want to, until I take it in, I'm never in the trace.
As I don't do it, nobody will break.
I got red in the Westway.
I'm never in the plane, never be.
Look at my mama, my name is a racer.
The genders, my name is Horatio for this Tuesday edition of the Daily Source Code, everybody.
How you doing?
It's Adam coming to you from the Cottage Curry Cottage and Guilford, the UK.
I got lots of feedback on yesterday's show.
Primarily about the shitty sound quality.
So thank you very much.
Peter was very concerned.
I listened back to him and he was like, oh man, he's so right.
I'm completely reconfiguring the studio here.
I've tossed out that Yamaha digital workstation.
I'm back to the Soundcraft 4 channel.
It has a lot of advantages over the digital workstation.
I'm really digging it.
Although it's kind of cruddy and uses all kinds of semi-professional connectors.
So you get all kinds of buzz and hum all over the place.
Yeah, it seems to be working.
The one thing I changed really is the microphone processing.
I know a lot of you don't like the reverb.
I love it.
I love having a little bit of reverb there.
So it's just ever so slight.
I've put it into the board as what we call an insert.
So I'm going to pull it out and then you know.
So this is without the sound processing on the microphone.
So let me know which one you like better.
Do you like it like this or do you like it like this?
I like it like this because it sounds a little bit crisp.
I don't know for some reason it feels a bit better.
Hey, how you doing?
Working towards Christmas.
Tomorrow we're off to see my mom.
Which means I'll have to have the next door neighbor.
Receive the package of the present that I bought for Patricia.
Now, if you've been reading my weblog, you probably already know what it is.
But I'm not going to say anything because these days,
whether they're on super station downstairs in the kitchen,
she might actually be listening to the show.
It really could happen.
I got some shitty news though about my mom.
It really sucks.
So we're going to see her tomorrow.
So we've gotten touched to talk about schedule
because we're flying over in the Cessna 182.
And now she needs another biopsy.
Oh man, it's poor woman to fucking sucks.
This whole cancer business fucking blows.
Jesus Christ.
What a bitch.
So anyway, and it was a year ago that she was diagnosed for the first time
and between Christmas and New Year's is when she had a lung removed.
So it's just been, it's been one that's not been a very good year.
And she's obviously not feeling very up and positive about stuff.
So we're going to go and send her some Christmas cheer.
And we're going to go hand-deliver it, God damn it.
Anyway, for today, a couple of threads we got going on here
that I want to keep in touch with.
The Metro Sexual Moment, as we continue to talk about
what best shaving implement to use.
Yet another testimonial for this Gillette Mark III Power Razor
as Giles says he converted to it earlier this year.
Can't recommend that enough and his wife agrees.
And here, I didn't quite understand this bit, but I wanted to read it to you.
And on holiday or a weekend away, I take the razor with me.
I lather up, wait a minute, press the power button and shave.
Then leaving it powered up, turn the razor over,
take off the blade, apply the back of it to my wife's button
and wait a minute or two for her to lather up.
Okay, as I read it all of a sudden, I got it.
Giles, man, you're twisted puppy.
But good to know, if you know what I'm saying.
I keep the egg nog feedback coming.
I must have received 30 different egg nog recipes.
I am totally going to going to try and make some this year.
Interestingly enough, Paul Parkinson says,
your plane of cries about egg nog, it forced me into action.
You can absolutely buy egg nog in the United Kingdom.
This is the whole point, you see, is haven't seen it anywhere on shelves.
He says he's always known it by its Dutch name, Advocat.
And I'm familiar with that, but Advocat.
That's not the same thing as egg nog.
It's way different.
Advocat is much thicker.
You can eat it with a spoon.
Anyway, Paul did a little bit of calling on my behalf,
and although Sainsbury's don't have any,
waitrose in godoming does.
This is great.
I got personal shoppers for listeners.
I love it. Thank you.
More egg nog feedback here.
Hey Adam, this is Matt from the Switch podcast.
I just finished listening to the daily source code number 301.
And I heard your comment on egg nog and how you have a hard time finding it in the UK.
I am a Canadian that is now living in Taipei, Taiwan, and I feel your pain when it comes to the egg nog.
I think that an egg nog recipe segment would make a great holiday addition to the source code,
or at least a great addition to the show notes.
I'm going to release a Christmas episode on Sunday featuring only Christmas music from podsafe artists,
and it would be great to have some rum and egg nog in my hand at the same time.
For more of all the podcasts, check out www.theswitched.com.
Thanks.
Yo. Nice ending there.
Okay, thanks, Matt.
And for those of you who have been writing in saying,
where the hell is the Christmas podshow podcast?
This is the thing that I set up at xmus.podshow.com.
So I had a completely tricked out.
I had a folder.
I dropped a song.
I actually had dropped two songs in or a block of songs, which I did have to pre-mix.
It would automatically take it off and post it to the wordpress blog, et cetera.
You know, FTP, the files, the whole thing perfectly set.
And then I started getting all these messages about people saying,
you know, what the fuck?
Where's the xmus.podshow podcast?
And it turns out that what we had a security breach, I guess.
It was essentially there was a file with some information sitting on a server somewhere.
And a couple of nice people pointed out to us.
So we, of course, had to go and lock stuff down and change all kinds of passwords.
And so, of course, my password was changed.
But this wonderful little script I wrote was just failing and not telling me about it.
Because, well, I'm not a great developer and Apple script.
Well, you know, I can only do so much.
So I got to change that and then I'll get back to posting it.
So I do have a backlog of stuff.
And I'm thinking I'll just release a whole bunch at the same time,
just to get everyone up to speed so I apologize for that.
And hopefully, it's 12 past 12 here in the afternoon.
Hopefully, I'll still have some time before the wing commander shows up.
Because the wing commander's coming over with the Charlie 182 today.
And he's going to stay overnight with us and that, oh, you know what?
Oh, man.
I'll have to interview him.
Oh, this is what I've been waiting for.
Did we want to do that last time when flying was when we couldn't fly
because of the inclement weather?
I think I was planning on it then.
It'll be perfect.
So we'll either do it tonight or maybe I'll maybe I'll do it when we fly to Rotterdam tomorrow.
So the deal is, you know, because I still want to safety pilot the fly long.
So William's going to fly with me.
And of course, the machine is still in the Antwerp.
And won't be here at Farrow until you want to tell it's gone through its complete program,
whatever.
Excuse me, sir.
William's going to take the engine out.
Put a black edition engine in whatever the hell that is.
It's going to get all these cool upgrades and tune-ups and new GPS system.
And I'm really excited.
So anyway, then tomorrow I'll have another safety pilot Roy.
He'll fly back with us and he'll stay overnight here.
And then he'll take the plane back the next day.
So it's kind of a long stretch.
But the convenience is still really, really is nice.
It is really worth it.
Oh yeah, you know, if you have a promo for your show.
And you know, want it played on the daily source code.
Of course, it's not a guarantee.
But just go over to promos.podshow.com and drop your promo.
And I've been hunting around.
I think I've played most of the, at least the ones that I like.
You know, if you buy the way four minute promos, you usually don't fly.
Even a minute 35 is pretty damn long.
But sometimes they'll work.
Will you marry me?
How can four little words cause such stress?
Well, if you've heard those words lately, you know what I mean.
Because you're planning a wedding.
I'm Robert Allen, your host over at the wedding podcast network.
The only place on the internet to listen to advice about wedding planning.
We've got podcasts with brides who've gone through the process.
They share with us all of the things they've done right.
And all the things they've done wrong.
We've got podcasts with the top wedding professionals in the country.
From photographers to caterers to wedding consultants.
Our wedding consultants share with us all of the things that are in their wedding
damper to see kids.
Very valuable information.
We've got a podcast with Laura Geller, the makeup artist.
You've probably seen her on the QVC network.
Laura has 25 years of experience in wedding day makeup.
And shares it all with our listeners.
We've got a podcast with Ron Benizreal, the world renowned wedding cake bicker,
who takes us on a delicious tour, and how to choose your wedding cake.
So if you're experiencing wedding day stress,
and you want to hear the low down on what you should know about wedding planning,
then you need to visit us at weddingpodcastnetwork.com.
And listen in as our experts share with you all of their years of experience.
Oh and by the way, congratulations on your engagement.
And we hope to see you at the weddingpodcastnetwork.
Take your Gmail account to the next level with the Gmail podcast.
The Gmail podcast will make you more proficient and teach you features about Gmail.
You may not have known in just a few minutes.
You'll learn tips and tricks that will help you stay organized using Gmail.
If you don't yet have a Gmail account, log on right now to chuckchat.com.
And let us know.
We'll be happy to send you an invite.
Get the most out of your Gmail account with a Gmail podcast available at chuckchat.com.
You've got Gmail.
Hi, Adam.
It's David Straum, former editor in chief of tomshardware.com.
I'm out on the street looking for a job this holiday season.
And I wanted to talk to you about ways that I could help improve podshow.com's website
with my editorial skills.
I know you're a busy guy and you got a lot going on,
but I think I could really add some value and help you do some great things with podshow.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
We're our flank.
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We believe your personal information should be just that, personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We're our flank.
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
This is Jay Donley from madpod.com.
This is how I envision Adam Curry,
making love to his sincere machine.
Uh, commercial.
I remember your time.
Oh, man.
Nice cup of sincere.
First, you put in your sugar.
I use the medium roast pods, by the way.
And also what's nice about it is you kind of give you something to do while the machine's warming up.
You know, you hit that center button to get it rolling.
I don't take a lot of sugar, just a small spoonful.
I remember.
Since they owe machine, and then you get a nice frothy rich.
Then you pour some semi-skinned milk in.
And then coffee with a nice flavor goes down smooth.
It's not too bitter.
You get your cup.
You get your sugar.
You get your milk.
And by the time you're done with that, it's ready to the buttons ready to be hit.
That's him.
Hit the button, baby.
I do love it, man.
I'd be so good for that company.
I have been good to that company, damn it.
Thanks to the guys over at Mad Pod.
I hear my eye chats still open.
People coming and going and making wishing sounds.
I listened to, there was a Mad Pod podcast.
And I'm a little confused if it was Mike,
I think it was Mike.
Last Friday in San Francisco, we did what is known in the, I guess,
the PR marketing business as an analyst meeting.
And what that means is that we met with a whole bunch of analysts,
and analysts are people who research information,
usually to resell it, like the gardener group or forester.
It's a kind of company you got to think about.
But there was also Nielsen was there because, of course,
they, that's what they're in the business of doing is research and talk.
And of course, they're mainly in statistics, statistics that
translate directly into sales for broadcast medium.
And also, let me see, don't they have some kind of metric metrics
or measurement system for the web as well?
I think so.
If not, they should.
They're part of the VINU, actually, which is a Dutch company.
And we talked about podcasting and about our vision,
and pod shows vision for podcasting.
And what we're going to do, and we actually went quite far,
it was, if you will, it was kind of a strategy cast for analyst,
was usually includes a flower point, nice power point.
We kind of liked the spice it up a bit with some audio and video stuff as well.
And Mike, I think he was one of the guys there,
and I'm not sure if he's a part of the mad podcast,
or actually I put a link to this podcast on my,
on my curry.com weblog yesterday.
You should definitely listen to it if you're interested in knowing
what your pod shows up to, and what we're going to be doing in the next couple of months,
and where we're headed.
And I'm not just saying that because the guy was really excited about it,
was extremely positive, but I was completely unsolicited.
And I actually thought that he, I mean, we didn't have anyone sign any non-disclosure agreement,
or tell him not to say anything, but he was, he was actually quite secretive about all of it.
And I was like, wow, you know, that's okay.
I mean, I don't think the art secret that we're out after 100 million listeners
is that big of a secret anymore, because that's really where pod show is headed.
If you're listening to this now on serious satellite radio,
you're probably thinking, what the hell is all this about?
Well, this is pod casting.
It's the extension to your satellite radio,
and you're going to be hearing lots of different shows,
and there's a lot more of us and a lot more out there.
And you can find it, you can go to podshow.com,
find all kinds of cool recommendations.
You can go all the kinds of places on the internet.
Even Google, just type in the type of pod cast that you're looking for.
Google usually shows up with some pretty good results I found,
since the universe of pod casts is still fairly limited compared to that at web logs.
Just saying whatever you want.
Does even, yes, there is actually a knitting pod cast.
I saw someone, I think, post on one of the email groups the other day.
I was like, okay.
Now, you know, we've really got it made.
Let me see.
What's it going to talk about?
I was going to talk about some performing right stuff.
Well, that's really more for podcasters who are listening.
So I'll save that for the second half of the hours.
Anyway, as I said, stars 103 on serious.
We're just one channel away from Howard Stern.
I'm sure that you're waiting for him and anticipating him.
And bumping is in pretty awesome shit here on 103.
After this show, we have Pacific Coast,
the hell way followed by Mad Weinstein, Dawn and Drew.
And I keep forgetting to look at the schedule.
The lineup PW is going to kill me.
Anyway, we're on four hours.
I think we're still on the mornings as well.
They repeated.
I'd love to do to double the amount of hours.
You know, I've suggested this to serious before.
As I've suggested to them streaming.
Yes, come extra blogger.
I hear you.
I've suggested they stream these channels.
But I think they're really busy with Howard Mania right now.
So I'll kind of take in a little somewhat of a backseat, I guess.
But I'll let you know.
We'll keep in touch on that.
You know what?
I was looking through the pod save music network.
And man, first of all, thank you for all the suggestions that you've been sending in.
Some of the stuff was really cool.
And I am saving it up.
And I am marking on my playlist to play.
But today, I really felt like doing like a golden oldie almost.
Although it's not a golden oldie.
It's just damn good music from a dream to thorn.
I'm man, I'm blue, that'll sky.
Rolls is daisy.
Spinning inside my mind.
And as I float through the mist.
Or all below me seems so far behind.
Like again.
Fly, fly, fly.
Nothing seems to matter.
I'll let you hear beside me.
Fly, fly, fly.
When you're with you, I'll feel like you.
And all the cause wouldn't lie.
And motion seems like you could be paralyzed.
And the light inside me feels so bright.
It's hope we'll need it tonight.
Like I can fly, fly, fly, nothing seems to lie.
But today, I really felt like doing like a golden oldie.
Fly, fly, fly, fly.
When you're with you, I'll feel like you.
Fly, fly, fly, nothing seems to matter.
I'll let you hear beside me.
Fly, fly, fly, fly.
When you're with you, I'll feel like you.
And all the cause wouldn't lie.
And motion seems like you could be paralyzed.
And the light inside me feels so bright.
But today, I really felt like doing like a golden oldie.
Fly, fly, fly, fly, nothing seems to lie.
But today, I really feel like you.
Fly, fly, fly, fly, fly, fly.
When you're with you, I'll feel like you.
And there feels so bad
Life, life, life, nothing seems better
You're here beside me
Life, life, life, now you're when
I'm here with you, I feel like
Life, life, life, life, nothing seems better
You're here beside me
Life, life, life, everything
Life, life, life, life, nothing seems better
You're here beside me
Life, life, life, life, when you're feeling
Life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life,
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
Life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life
life, life, life, life, life,
you, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, lives, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, its life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, no way, life, life, life, life, life, that life, life, life, life, life, life, life. life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life and life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, life, lives, life, life, life disease, life, life. life,
I wanted to follow up on some of your thoughts about fees for podcasts which you raised in a recent
DSC when you were talking about blank tapes and CDs. Now in this particular instance it looks like
that idea might not fly but it got me thinking. Sometime ago I was attempting to get an MP3 player
that I could listen to while forcing myself up and down my local swimming pool. Yes that's pretty
sad I know but you know I enjoy the DSC so much I'd like to listen to it while I'm swimming.
But due to the fact that it's almost impossible to rely on reliably here anything whilst doing that
I just gave up. Anyway the point is I was swimming yesterday and thinking about your comments
about podcasts receiving royalties for their content saved to some sort of media. As I went up and
down the pool it occurred to me that public venues such as bars, lifts and yes even swimming pools
have to pay annual fees to the performing rights at society in the UK and I presume similarly
in other territories with equivalent organizations when they play copyrighted music in their venues.
This got me thinking why couldn't you have a business model where Portugal makes
canned genre specific streaming potsafe music available via broadband now to any public buildings
that which actually wanted. The deal is they no longer have to pay the fees to the performing
rights at society or country equivalent but they do pay a modest annual fee to pot show which
then distributes the proceeds to musicians on the potsafe music network. Now using the PRS as an example
if you had just one CD player in a nightclub in the UK and it doesn't occupy an area exceeding 120
square meters yes it sounds strange but that's it then it costs you almost £200 a year to do that
that would be about $350. Now as you'd imagine nightclubs tend to have more than one CD player
they have quite a lot of musical equipment and they have to pay fees to the performing rights
society for all of that stuff. Now you can actually find out some of the fees by the way if people
interested at the PRS website at www.prs.co.uk. But here's what I'm thinking. What if there was a
potential public venues commercial use license with a flat fee on a pervenue basis? I think that
people would go for it I think people and businesses would think find that a worthwhile alternative
one because it's simple two because it's going to be cheaper. Now to avoid creating a top heavy
administrative structure you'd want to run it on an honor system but on the whole most people
or businesses if they know the deal will honor their obligations particularly if it's a saving
over the fees they have to pay to the likes of the PRS or the RIA or whatever a equivalent organization
we're talking about anywhere in the world. Now that might be considered trading on the toes of
the established order but hey we're talking disruptive technology here and no one said that these
people could have them monopoly on music forever. I think that this could be a very popular I think
it may be a great opportunity to also promote pot-safe music and tunes that otherwise
wouldn't get an easy public hearing through established channels. So I'd be very interested
know what you think about that and what other listeners to the DMC think. Okay Ralph. Well I don't know
I have a whole bunch of thoughts on that topic and by the way the reason that I'm just bringing
all this stuff up is because if the rules are changing for the broadcasting industry I think the
rules will change in many other places including all I guess that is also performance right
when you talk about clubs. I didn't know that that's how to work that's how they charge it by
based on the number of CD players that's pretty interesting CD players and space I think it's
different for offices and other you know corporations I do it by head count see the thing here is that
I don't know if I'm necessarily for creating a parallel system that is exactly the same. I think that
I'm not quite sure how but it feels to me like the concept of a performance right fee in general is
I think that that just might have to change. It's already changed in podcasting and you see
what incredible benefit it is to to the pod safe music artists and I think that the reason why
the RIA and all the mainstream music industry you know they really had you know they had the
monopolistic power to go after all these markets but I don't know if it's necessarily good to
recreate exactly that I think that there's many ways that artists can make lots of money
particularly because they don't need to sign up to the traditional system of a record company so
their profit margins will be much much much higher. I'm talking 95% higher
or really of every dollar they'll be getting 90% of the revenue
and what really is the cost of the cost of getting something shipped out you know
so I've got to think about that. I certainly wouldn't want pod show to be that organization
would have to be some kind of independent organization but oh man another crazy organization to be a
member of I don't know I don't know I kind of like it really really simple and so far it seems to be
working okay and I think that getting your music played in clubs is fantastic you know as long
as people have a way to find out what it is and people usually do you know so maybe we need pod
safe music clubs where you know who subscribe to a feed that brings them all the latest maybe
dished out by genre and in return they have flyers in the club or something like that or you
couldn't go online and see what was played at the club you know something like that that would be
cool that's the kind of stuff that I'm looking for honestly hi Adam the finished parliament is
planning to rush through a very scary law by April 2006 writes John Vermont if somebody is found
guilty of copyright infringement in Finland that person can be made to publish and pay for an ad
on a local or national newspaper in which he or she admits his or her fault the craziest thing
is that the winning side is allowed to create the ad. Needless to say this law has already scared
everyone as it is seen as a way for the record industry watchdogs to humiliate people this law
is part of the finished parliament's efforts to rapidly ratify the European Union so called
enforcement directive scary name huh and he put in some original links to the stories um
I'll make sure those get out into the show notes god this is not some man you don't even own your own
shit anymore and then if you borrow something or make a mistake or just share something you get humiliated
publicly come on let's hang people much much better we used to do it it was only a couple hundred
years ago we could do that again hang the fuckers duty from host says hi Adam or browsing
the net i found this info about the Belgian music rights being from Belgium this interest me
a Belgian member of parliament Bart Tomolane has made some comments about the monopoly of saybam
that's the Belgian ask have be am I he says it's a bureaucratic system that sits on a huge pile of
money he's calling for all organizers of parties or DJs to refuse the invoice sabam sends them
Bart goes on they asked fixed prices without any explanation about the bills nor where this money is
going to and they are only allowed to collect money for the artist they represent some random test
show that 15% of the used music on at parties cannot be found in the sabam catalog DJ should
not have to pay for this sabam reply that prices are about the same as our neighbor countries
it's impossible to control the 15% bloody bloody bloody bloody bloody bloody bloody bloody bloody
bloody bloody bloody bloody interesting so there's a lot of stuff happening and it's it's different
at at every single level even though all these countries are within the European Union they're
all doing something different so we're just continue to keep our eye on it and just discussing
amongst ourselves some good comments going on in the show notes which you can find at
shownotes.info or just from the link underneath each podcast at dailysourcecode.com
yesterday I played the first Trinity sound imaging done by Jeff Smith and he was so nice to
make those remixes for me so I'm not going to do a Trinity segment today I'm going to try and cut it
down to one or two a week so I can collect some good stuff and have an ongoing thread about it but
Jeff also does other music has quite a selection up on the pod safe music network and
he sent me a link to his pod safe christmas song so I figured I'd give him a play my own
merry christmas Jeffrey sees Smith the snow is falling down tonight
the carols ringing through the night this Christmas like why who ride outside your door could be singing
one more song for you if I could join them too I would but if there's no other way
then for me to be so far this christmas I can ride a couple words and the tune is my christmas
melody for you go ahead and ride the christmas tree go ahead and hang the mistletoe go ahead and
set another place for me I would be there in your heart this christmas snuggle close up to the fire
the ten that I'm watching it with you though I'm that in miles away please let my own
merry christmas find a way to you to day
oh
so let me whisper in your ear if they want to you like to hear for Christmas I'll tell you that I'm coming home
or I'll be there when you call the turkey true in the tree maybe that I'm big surprise
would better see it in my eyes on christmas
but if I couldn't make it home I could send it in a song you could be while I'm far away
go ahead and ride the christmas tree go ahead and hang the mistletoe go ahead and set another place for me
I would be there in your heart this christmas snuggle close up to the fire
the ten that I'm watching it with you though I'm so mad at miles away please let my own
merry christmas find a way to you to day
oh go ahead and ride the christmas tree go ahead and hang the mistletoe go ahead and set another place for me
I would be there in your heart this christmas snuggle close up to the fire
the ten that I'm watching it with you though I'm so mad at miles away please let my own
merry christmas find a way to you though I'm so mad at miles away please let my own merry christmas find a way to
to day
ah ain't that nice Jeff Smith my own merry christmas sounds like he performed the whole thing live you
find a whole bunch of other Jeff Smith tunes and the podsick music network at music.podshow.com
thank you very much for listening subscribing if you don't know what that's about go to
dailysourcecode.com you can subscribe to the to the show with the iTunes or preferably with the
juice or something like that some open source receiver seems to be something that works a lot better
and gets some more bug fixes put in on time and I'll be back tomorrow and I quite sure what time
the show is going to be up since as you know it will be traveling I'm going to go see my mom so
it'll be I'm sure some version of sound seeing tour interview talk shit whatever will have some fun
with it take everybody bye bye. pod show breaking out of fat sack of the good stuff