Tell us, you're a Charlie, two, five, four.
Please save me from people who've been told what to like and then like it.
In my opinion, if you're over six years of age and you're still getting your music
from the radio, something is desperately wrong with you.
I can only hope that somehow MP3 players and file sharing will destroy FM radio the way
they're destroying record companies.
And even though the air will probably never be safe to breathe again, maybe it will
be safer to listen to it.
I don't see rats.
I'm sorry, information you don't get higher.
I'm Korean.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking greens in.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
And we've hit the hump by friends.
Today is Wednesday, October 5, 2005.
And good morning from Curry Cottage.
It is just barely still morning five minutes before 12.
I was up early, really excited when I woke up this morning.
I just woke up.
I had a whole bunch of ideas and things to talk about, about pot-safe music and music licensing.
And I was really excited.
I started going through the email and how much crap hit me, which we'll talk about, which
maybe has to do with directories in the potter.org and podcastallie.com.
So we will be talking about that.
Then of course, I had something really important, which was go off to the hair salon.
And of course, it's not Sam and Dave.
We're a Tony and Guy.
Whatever the hell those guys named it.
No, I know God too.
I go to Patricia's hairdresser and she goes with me.
Since I have to take my glasses off and can't keep control over what's happening.
You know, I am so lucky.
I am blessed with what I have for 41 years and still a full head hair.
Yeah!
Oh, that enough is just to be happy about it, isn't it?
We've got promos galore.
All kinds of new promos, even from some shows
that have been around a while.
It's nice to see that got some new stuff coming.
And actually, there's a lot coming in now, which is great because if we have a slow day,
I'll know I have plenty of stuff, excuse me, to pull from from the archives.
And it's all about getting exposure for more shows, right?
Podsafe music.
I think I've got probably a time to roll out two of those and some great feedback on this
music licensing stuff.
This is really just hitting me.
I turned everything upside down on the world with a hell of a lot better when I did that.
So we will get into that with a little bit of hiccups from the Mac, which we're still working on.
First though, we have a mashup from mashuptown.com, ArtSent this one in.
Romantic is the new fantastic.
The groove blaster.
This one's feel else to me.
I'm so happy with it.
But you can stay if you want to.
Check it out now.
I've been thinking about this in life.
I might just stay here with you tonight.
Check it out now.
Music
Ladies and gentlemen, this break is made out of respect for the TV fans, our audience.
We're considering to constant interruptions in their programs for messages and sponsors.
We want all you TV fans to see the whole and not forget the thrill you get.
Come on.
How does a girl like you get to be a girl like you?
Black girls.
Not like you're not wicked up to no good.
Have a kill anyone?
Because I bet you could tease a man to death without having to try.
You told him to kiss me.
Ladies, I know he was going to kiss you.
I want to send a boy to do a man's job.
Oh, that's for the man.
You can tell him the job's filled.
Check it out now.
Music
That's like that's nice.
Welcome.
This is the podshow podcast network.
It's the Davy source code.
After this, you'll get Mads Weinstein on a true attention tech.
We've got pdubs, half hour friends.
We've got podsake music all coming up in the next four or four hours.
If you're checking this out on the podcast, well, you are truly wired.
So, as I said, this morning I woke up.
I was so enthusiastic about stuff that I'm still enthusiastic about about podsake music and podsake music network and music licensing.
We're going to get to that.
But first, I want you to know that for the past, I think two weeks now, we have been completely consumed at podshow.
Part of it when I was still in San Francisco and part of it this week with listings in our directories.
Now, just so you know, podshow owns and operates two domains, and I'm saying this very specifically domains.
We have indiepodder.org, formerly known as iPodder.org.
We have podcastalley.com.
Two directories where you can pretty much submit your podcast and have it listed.
Now, there's very distinct differences between these two domains and what they do and what their function is.
Let me start with indiepodder.org first.
This started as a community resource back in the early days before there was actually a word pod casting.
And it's a brilliant system, brilliant.
And I can easily say that because I'm just going to sit down for a second for this one.
I love the stool, I still have here.
The main reason it's brilliant is because it's architected as an open distributed directory based on OPML.
Huge props to Dave Winner for his vision of how this works.
And boy, I'd actually love to hear him weigh in on this.
Although I think that he's going to agree with me.
Wouldn't that be a great.
The nature of a distributed directory means that indiepodder.org really is no more than one page if you.
It's not a database.
There's no database sitting behind that it's one page which is an HTML rendering of an OPML.
That means that there's a bunch of links in that OPML file, which is just a format.
So it's just a file, see it as a regular file with a bunch of links in it.
And those links point to other OPML files hosted on other servers by other people, which are maintained by those people.
Now what's beautiful about this is it's actually a very democratic system because although indiepodder.org,
the main page there and the top level of directory may be seen as the all encompassing top level.
It's actually quite cool because you could take the entire file we make that available for anyone.
Apple did that and other companies and many other directories, of course, have pre-populated their directories with that data.
And we make no claims about that.
Go ahead and grab it.
There's a link right there.
We explain very clearly how it can be done.
But just to reiterate.
Sensei.
Just to reiterate, there's no database, there's no storing of any links other than the links to these other directory nodes.
Now what the system does do and this does add to some confusion.
We're going to work on that is it renders.
So if you say I want to look at the automotive category, you click on that link.
What the system is actually doing is saying, okay, let me go pull in that OPML file from another server.
And I'm going to render that through our rendering engine to turn it into an HTML representation,
which is why you basically get just a bunch of links to RSS feeds, which is many of said is, you know,
that's not the way to do a directory.
Well, it in fact is the way to do a directory because it is a complete resource.
It's just a resource.
Do you hear that?
That's my blackberry.
That's the one thing I do not like about the blackberry is it provides a lot of interference on the equipment here.
The MDA does not do that.
So I have to kind of find the right spot so I can still read my show prep on it and not have that sound crappy.
Anyway, so we are quite happy to point to anyone who wants, that's why you see it's kind of funny.
People say, well, you've got way too many top level links there.
When someone says they have a new category, we bought it in.
Well, I'm happy to put anything in the top category.
If there isn't a category that it already fits in, I'm happy to put it there.
So for instance, we have a politics node right now.
If someone decided they wanted to do an alternative politics node and was different from the one we already have,
they would probably get a top level listing for me.
But again, it's just a link to whatever they're linking to.
So very much like a weblog.
In fact, it's kind of the two different sides of the same coin in a way.
Where I have a weblog and I can point to someone's website,
but I'm not really responsible for everything they link to.
And nor do I have the time to go and read everything.
You would presume that if God damn that really pisses me off.
There we go.
You would presume that no one has time to go and read through everything.
Maybe I would disagree and I could perhaps remove a link.
But the whole kind of idea of the links on the web is that a link is in place and you hope it stays.
And we don't want a link rot and we want it to kind of be in place.
So it's very, very critical to understand.
Crucial really that any potter.org is nothing.
There's no not a database.
It is just a list of links to other lists of links.
That is the nature of the open directory.
By the way, anyone maintaining a node can also.
And that's not only can they.
I hope they do and many do such as the music category.
There's one music maintainer of the category.
And that person has linked in other opium nodes to what I call sub directory.
So there's someone is maintaining under the music category.
Different like the rock music category.
And that's actually that can be someone else.
And it all kind of flows together.
And it's a different system.
It is, in my opinion, the only way an open directory can work because in this case we have over a hundred volunteers.
All of them, you know, so passionate about what they do that they often even hand code these opium
files in like note pad, you know, just to just to get it up and running.
And of course, that also means that we sometimes have breakage, you know, from day to day.
You'll see that maybe a node will drop out because someone's web server one away.
And we usually wait and see if it comes back.
And from time to time, someone will say, hey, this node hasn't been maintained for six months.
I'd like to take over the node.
I think they can do a better job.
Then I'll have an email conversation with the original maintainer of the node.
Most of the times the maintainer of the nodes says, oh, shit.
I didn't even know that, you know, I've been updating somewhere else.
And I screwed up and they fixed it and everything kind of seems to cope with Saturday.
Because the people who usually want to maintain a node are the ones who haven't been able to get listed.
By the way, to get listed in a node on indie potter, you communicate directly with through an email or submission link.
Actually, you communicate directly with that node manager.
So the way the only way that works is that the node managers are responsible for what they link to.
Okay, that said, let's look at podcastiley.com.
The name itself says what it is.
It's the alley behind podcasting.
It's kind of the back end.
It's where we figure where we built, where I didn't, where Chris McIntyre built a community around podcasters.
And the community focus on a number of different things.
You know, primarily how to create shows, make shows, produce shows, create feeds.
I mean, there's a lot of stuff that really the community has created in that space at podcastiley.com.
Now, podcastiley.com does have a database and it has an automatic submission.
So you send it into one place and it basically just all goes in.
It's verified to see if your feed is valid and that's about it.
So what is the issue at hand?
The issue at hand is that a couple of podcasts have popped up into these directories in the past couple of weeks that the majority of people find offensive.
One is a hate podcast and one is a podcast apparently about Peter Felia.
And these both of these podcasts were listed in both directories in indie potter.org.
It was listed in a node maintained by a separate node manager.
And I can't speak for the new issue that is popped up because I haven't been able to find it in any of the nodes yet.
Nor is anyone pointed out to me.
It did, by the way, pop up automatically on the homepage of indie potter.org.
Both of these podcasts were submitted to podcastiley.
Now, as you can understand, again, it's an automatic submission.
There's sometimes there's a hundred to six or seven hundred new podcasts coming out in a day or in a span of a couple days.
And there is no human intervention there, which I think places a much bigger responsibility on the community.
And primarily the people who run podcastiley.com, which is Podshow.
And Chris McIntyre as the spiritual leader of that community and of that website.
So the question that has a risen is, should every single podcast be listed in these directories regardless of what the content of the podcast is?
This is not the official Podshow statement, but I was so emotional about the conversations that have been going on on podcastiley.
Because it's become very, actually hateful and very aggressive.
The way people are attacking Chris, myself, Podshow, other members of the community about this issue.
I think the conversation is just no longer a grown-up conversation.
Let me state right up front that our organization, which is its own little community, a very young and growing community, because we're all just kind of getting to know each other.
We've only been, you know, a company for, for really a few weeks and, you know, new people coming on every single day.
We are very diverse group.
And I think it intuitively, you can probably figure out that not a single person in our organization would endorse any type of hate or any, any crime or violence or anything that would potentially hurt children.
I mean, that's obvious.
This is not, I repeat, this is not a free speech issue. I really thought about this.
Free speech means the right for someone to say whatever they want to say.
That doesn't necessarily mean that we have to promote that or link to it or highlight it or list it.
I'll take it one step further.
Since the podcast Ali.com community is owned and operated by all of us, not just Adam Curry and Ron Bloom or Chris McIntyre, but, you know, it's pod show.
And it's, and that takes significant resources. It takes people and takes money and, you know, there's, there's a, a lot that goes into it.
Chris actually said it very, very, very suit yesterday. He feels that anything on podcast Ali.com basically reflects what we are as people and I totally agree.
Because we do maintain the database. We do maintain what is being linked to, we do maintain the listings.
Indiepoter.org, that homepage, that, that, that top level listing, that reflects who we are as people.
The linking, and this is really, really, really important that you understand this.
The linking to other OPML files, which, in fact, are a little mini directories.
We cannot be responsible for what other people put in their OPML files.
We can't tell a node manager to put something in or take something out.
So, and again, we're going to write this down and come out with an official statement.
And, you know, words are always turned around and I'm not always the best communicator, particularly not when I'm emotional, but I want you to know that the only way to solve this is to put our foot down and say that we have the right.
We reserve the right to not list a podcast if we feel we don't have to or want to.
See, that already didn't come out the way I wanted to sound.
But we reserve the right to not list anything on podcastally.com and on the homepage, the top level of the indiepoter.org directory.
In fact, the, one of the offensive podcasts through automatic script showed up on the homepage of indiepoter.org.
And I removed it because that is my space. That is the space that I control and that is owned by pod show and the community of people who do not want anything poorly to reflect upon us.
Anything else in indiepoter.org should be taken up with the maintainer of that node.
And by the way, we, of course, do reserve the right to drop a node or place it with something else.
But that's where we have to be really, really careful, my friends.
The way we're going to release our policy, if you will, will be exactly that.
If you have an issue with a link on an independently hosted and maintained node, you'll have to take it up with that node manager.
We are only linking to nodes. If nodes are properly maintained, that's all we care about, that the links work.
And that they're updated fresh and that they're, you know, that they're maintained basically and people can get their stuff listed in it.
So I think you will see that the offensive quote unquote offensive podcasts will be removed from podcast alley.
At the same time, we will also, I think, be looking at members of the community who are offensive.
And we might have to remove them because if this has this discussion or what people are trying to call discussion,
podcast alley.com is not the place for it.
Because we're trying to create a positive community that works towards podcasting, creating better podcast.
We don't, I don't think it's the right forum for a huge free speech discussion because it's inappropriate.
Free speech would mean that we tell these podcasters that they can't do a podcast.
Okay? So be very, very, I want to be as clear as possible about the distinction that anything we own,
we reserve the right to remove things and we will.
And I think the reasons will be clear, but we don't have to even give a reason if we don't want to.
What I'm so emotional about, though, is the tactics that have been played out in this without even any consideration for time,
for thought, for the resources, for the consequences that go into this.
And people are blackmailing us, people are sending emails with half truths and sometimes lies to mainstream media to try and quote,
quote, stir the shit up or call us out.
You know, it's a completely wrong way to go about it. It is so incredibly disappointing.
Anyway, how, what time are we now?
God damn, never gonna make this show.
So today at the California hasn't broken up yet, it'll be a few more hours yet.
We're going to publish our policies. You'll see that they'll look very much like Google.
And by the way, you know, threats were made to our investors.
They're very aware have dealt with this before have been giving us some excellent advice on the topic.
And we're trying to be as mature as possible about this.
So we can move on and get on with creating great podcasts, better podcasting and a thriving community that does not yell, shout, and threaten each other.
Okay, now for some fun stuff.
Hi, this is Apocalypse Dahl. I'd like to tell you about my podcast novel, Brace for Impact.
This novel follows the story of Apocalypse Dahl.
Hey, that's me. And Mick Aloha, my arch enemy.
As we join forces to journey across the country for a common cause.
Along the way, win counter truckers, pro wrestlers, robots, ghosts, sex craved middle-aged Japanese women.
In saying farmers, a plot to destroy the internet and midget cowboys.
New episodes come out every Tuesday. You can check out the website at www.freepodcastnomel.com
or do a search for brace for impact in the directories. Thanks a lot.
Hot show. Content that will make you squeeze the dog and burp your mother.
Want to hear something different?
Want to hear how South Africans are doing it?
Well, I'm Glenn.
And I'm Bridget.
A Zedershow.
Come and experience Cape Town, South Africa.
We talk about anything.
But not for cons. It's such an expressive language.
But in Africa, you can't just say four.
Oh, close. Come on, South Africa.
And we talk to interesting people.
Going to break the landscape record for the fastest blind driver.
All I'm going to find is close to possible in the end of the moment now.
So come and join the Zee Cape Townian.
To subscribe, search for the Zedershow and iTunes or go to www.TheZedershow.Zedet.net.
And podcasting all's live and I'm curry.
My pod.com.
And James.
Yes, we have a big interview on Friday show at madpot.com.
Barry Manolo.
That's right. Barry Manolo and madpot.
And I floated down, made it into a ballad.
That's what he was hearing.
Hearing me doing it is a ballad and it was the first number one song for me and for Arespa.
Oh, my singing mandi.
Mabpa.
Doc Call.
Sing mandi.
There you go.
The ultimate mannel L.
And an extremely rare interview.
This is only one of six and ten years.
Mannel L.
Speaks with Shadow Steel.
Regarding his hits, entertainment career and personal life.
Mabpa.
Doc Call.
Hi.
This is Shadow Steel and you're listening to your global audio connection, madpod.com.
Doc Call.
Yeah.
Shadow Steel or whatever.
Baga.
That's a district or trucker name.
I think there are 25 Shadow Steel's running around the country right now.
But it sounds interesting.
I definitely want to hear the Barry.
I like Barry Manelow's stuff.
Let me think what I'm going to do now because I don't think I'm going to happen.
I mean, I'm going to remove the track I was going to play here.
I'll play that tomorrow so we can get into the music licensing conversation.
Okay.
Where to start?
I think the easiest and most logical place to start is to talk about, oh actually.
Yeah.
It's to talk about what music licensing is, how it came about.
And I'm a semi-professional in this area.
I'm certainly not a lawyer.
Certainly not a music lawyer.
But I have dealt with the material long enough to get the conversation.
Going a little bit more.
And this is purely about podcasting and radio and streaming and the digital Millennium Copyright Act.
So historically radio stations have been able to play records on the radio at no cost other than a contribution to Ask Cap BMI.
And if you're in a different country like the Netherlands, it's Buma Stemera.
If you're in England, it's the PMRS, I think it is.
These are all territorial based organizations.
And a little fuzzy on this.
But I believe they have acquired the right from the government to be the collection agency for authors, composers.
And there are actually two separate organizations that I think are in some places.
Well, there are separate organizations that actually got and collect money for the producer.
Of a song as well as for the vocalist of a song.
Believe it or not.
I know this because Patricia gets them.
It's called the Sainat in Europe.
And they actually got and get money for the for the vocalist, even if they haven't written the song.
So the concept behind this is that the record companies who own the actual product.
Okay.
So the product of a song, which is it's the disc that it comes on.
It's the complete, it we call it the master.
You know, basically in 99.9 cases when you have a record deal.
The record company owns the master.
That means they own whatever happens with that physical product and how it is used.
Traditionally, radio's record companies have waived any fee.
I've said, go ahead radio stations.
You can use this because it promotes our product and it helps us in our entire marketing campaign to sell the physical product.
So that's a great hand off and an up until streaming, which I get to in a second.
That was a very cut and, you know, very cut and straight cut deal.
Everyone understood it.
Now, of course, radio stations who play music and music is not just, you know, the number one hit of the week,
but it can also be a filler that you use or some background music during an interview or all any type of music.
Just as with clubs, restaurants, bars, elevators, concerts, anywhere that the music is performed.
Okay.
And by performance, I also mean broadcast.
So it is, it's not that you're just putting a record on and playing it for your friends.
And there's, there's actually some legal language about that.
What constitutes the real performance.
In fact, you've probably seen that there's all kinds of disclaimers that if you buy a direct TV,
satellite dish and you have all your buddies come over and you, if you were to charge money at the door,
if you just let anyone in and a hundred people watching the game, you could get a knock at the door,
and they could start charging you money for that.
But think about it.
You know, if you're in a commercial venture, such as Radio Station, you're using this art,
which, of course, the record companies aren't getting compensated for directly,
but the people who created the song, they need to be compensated.
They're partially compensated through sales, and there's a whole division key of that,
who gets what, and that all depends on, you know, the publishing rights,
and, you know, that's probably a little bit too complicated to go into in depth here.
But that's why there are these organizations, and they've been around for a long time,
like BMI and like ASCAP and PMRS and Bumush Damara.
And their job is to cut deals with all of these places where the music is used in a commercial,
and a commercial venture.
So a radio station will typically pay a percentage of revenue,
I think it's, they based it on audience size and revenue,
but it's all negotiation is what it is.
In fact, we did a trade show recently, that recently, when I was still back in,
at the Curry Castle, for Grandmaster View screens, we did a trade show,
and a guy from the local ASCAP BMI authorities came by and said,
hey, you're playing music here, do you have a license?
And we said, no, we don't.
We thought that was included with the stand and, you know, with our booth.
No, sorry, you got to pay, and you have to pay right now,
or we'll send you, we'll find you.
And it wasn't much, you know, they based upon the size of the booth,
and with the traffic that was going by the booth, you know,
it's all kind of fuzzy logic and math, but it's, you know, it's fair.
We're using music to attract people into buy our products.
I mean, maybe we'll pay like 50 bucks or something per day,
for the week that we were there.
So, you know, it's, it's, it's fair.
It just makes sense.
So, taking into consideration that history will repeat itself,
I think we need to do something similar for the pod safe music scene,
and particularly through the pod safe music network.
Because often, even though often the,
the creator of the song of the product that you can either buy,
yeah, a protract download, or that you can buy as a physical CD,
even though they may also be the songwriter and composer at the end of the day,
when someone is making money, and I've already heard this conversation crop up,
you know, if I'm making money through doing the daily source code,
which I'm not making directly yet, but we will eventually,
there's going to be some kind of sponsorships and advertising,
or so there's going to be some monetization.
And if I'm using music to do that, then the people who created that music
should be fairly compensated, and the people who are selling the product of that music
will be compensated if it's good enough, and it catches on,
and people go and buy the product.
So, I do believe that we have to come up with something for the pod safe music
authors, composers, producers, and let's just say performers, okay?
And that's a huge job to set that up, but it's really going to be worth it.
Let me just tell you how they fixed that with streaming,
because when streaming came out in the late 90s,
radio stations, essentially radio stations in the beginning,
were a simultaneous feeding of their radio station,
so you could pick it up anywhere in the world.
Of course, you were tied to your computer, so it didn't have all the benefits of pod casting.
But this also adheres to the satellite radio,
that all falls under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.
And if you read this act outside of the, you know,
all the stuff about cracking encryption, et cetera,
it was a freaking negotiation.
And it literally says things like,
you can't play a song by the same artist back to back,
because, of course, they're afraid that you'll eventually, you know,
that you could play all 12 of a CDs tracks,
and someone could record that, and then they would effectively have the CD.
It was really a negotiation with people,
with big radio stations who were into streaming,
as well as the then still infant and not even open for business satellite radio operators.
So none of this really applies to pod casting
when it comes to the traditional system,
which means licensed music, which belongs to the RIA,
and of course, the songs themselves,
which belong to the authors, composers, producers,
and performers on the track.
So that's the problem with playing songs that aren't pod safe in your podcast.
The problem is that there is a collection agency,
and their mission in life is to go out and collect money
if you're using the works,
not the physical product, but the works of these artists.
Again, the composer, the writer, the producer, and the performers.
If you're using those works in a commercial venture,
and of course, what's commercial is very fuzzy,
but at the end of the day, if you're making money using that product,
they'll come and collect.
So that's why you see ASCAD BMI coming out with licenses for podcasters.
Because they're saying, hey, this is very clearly defined.
If you have permission to use the master to use the product,
then all we want is we want to fairly compensate these other guys over here.
Totally agree with it.
Of course, the way they've set that up,
the size of the fee, the reporting you have to do,
is nowhere near possible for any podcast.
I can't even do my own frickin' show notes myself.
Let alone do all the work on figuring out.
And we used to do this at the big radio stations before it was all automated.
You have to write down, title the song, the artist, the label it's on,
and then on the record is always stated who's the composer,
and who is the author, producer,
and performers don't apply,
and those rights start to be collected much later on.
So while we could really focus on getting a license with ASCAD BMI,
which is kind of what I was talking about the other day,
I think maybe we should turn the tables and turn it around.
And before I get to that, I want to play for you,
kind of a, it's a promo, but it's kind of a joke,
because, and by the way, it's completely not safe for children's ears.
These guys totally understand the vibe of the record companies,
the RIA, because they would probably sound a lot like this
if they were trying to deal with us podcasters.
We've been checking out this pod safe music network a year.
We like what we see. You know what I mean?
Look, we've got a deal for it.
I think it's going to work out pretty good for all of us.
We really see it, baby.
What the fuck?
Who else is fucking Frenchy in here?
I don't know.
What the fuck?
Joey, take care of the fucking Frenchy for me, would you?
I got it.
Forget about it.
Where the fuck was I before that French fuck in a ruptuous?
Look, we don't let just anyone into the family.
I think it's about time we make an exception.
See, it's a thing.
We got ourselves a business back into Troy.
Go ahead, boat and sing music studios.
Yeah, yeah. We pretty much run the whole town down there.
Joey, shut the fuck up.
Look, we got some talented people recording there.
We like to see if we can make a deal with you.
Go ahead.
You can take a head of that.
Look, we'll get you some good music for your pod safe music network.
And in return, you just tell them where you got it.
It's as simple as that.
What do you think?
Well, first of all, we got the really good shit.
I mean, all this music, top notch.
And second of all, it's a really good fun.
You know what I mean?
The shit rocks.
Forget about it.
Joey, shut the fuck up.
So, what do you think, Adam?
We got ourselves a deal.
Oh, man.
Piece of crap.
I think that was the end of it.
So you kind of get the gist there, right?
So he was my thought.
And by the way, I clearly like to play mashups,
and that's an issue.
And I'd like to pay for that.
And if I want to, and if we can come to terms with AskCADBMI,
or PMRS, or whoever it is,
we'll gladly do that if there's money coming in, of course.
You know, the people who created that work deserve to deserve to have that.
By the way, you know, this is the entire reason why copyrights are extended,
and are extended primarily by artists.
Members Sonny Bono did that.
And Cliff Richard is bitching and moaning over here,
because most of his copyrights are about to expire,
which means basically, you know, he won't get any money
for what he created.
And you know, so that's, I shouldn't even brought that up.
That's a whole different conversation about expiration
of copyrights.
But what we can do here.
Here's what we can do.
Podsafe Music has happened.
There's no doubt about it.
I get emails all the time from people who say,
Dude, I heard, I heard Brother Love on this other podcast,
and I recognized it just like it was a,
you know, a regular radio station
that I'd heard it somewhere else in a,
and it felt like I hit to me,
and I was loving it and singing along,
because it's working.
You know, we are promoting these artists.
It's really, really working.
So I think that I would like to investigate the Podsafe Music network,
being a clearinghouse,
not for the actual product again,
not for the, for the track that's being sold.
If that's played on your podcast,
I feel that that should be, you know,
that's a wash, you know,
it's a promotion for the product,
but we are using the works by these talented artists,
mostly talented artists.
And if you're monetizing,
if you're making money,
then you should,
these people should be compensated.
So I think there's a way to do that
and have the Podsafe Music network
be a clearinghouse for that.
And it will be so cool because it's already happening now
where radio stations want to play
some of this Podsafe Music.
Well, it's not interesting.
You have to cut a deal with the podcasters,
music association or whatever the hell we're going to call it.
Well, the Podsafe Music network
writes clearances.
Yeah, we'll use all the big words those guys use.
So you have to clear it through us.
And guess what?
If you played on terrestrial radio,
you have a different rate,
and it's going to be much higher than on podcasts.
If you want to use it with your film,
then you also have to come to the clearinghouse.
I would love nothing more than to represent all these artists.
And again, not just the author and composer,
but the producer and the performers of the work,
so that when someone uses their work,
whether they re-record it,
it doesn't make any difference.
If it's being used in a commercial venture through a performance,
then I think that should be compensated,
and I think we can do it.
In fact, I got an audio feedback from Adrian Pegg here in the UK,
who said something very similar.
Listen to what he has to say.
I don't know if this is Adrian Pegg.
I was one of the four organises of the recent Podcastcon UK conference.
I was interested to hear about your attempts
to solve the music licensing issues in Podcasting.
I mean, I actually think that Podcast
have found a real niche anyway with indie music
and unlicensed side music,
because that is something that the major broadcast
this content wouldn't want to do anyway.
And it really gives Podcast something different.
But I can see why it would be nice to have
a blanket license of some sort to play a license music
or sign music.
And I think the approach of going to the approach of avoiding
the mechanical rights side of things initially is a good one.
But I do think you could think about taking it
at one step further.
Imagine that you could get the odd small record label signed up
with mechanical rights,
and you were actually acting as a collecting agency yourself.
Pod shows acting as a collecting agency.
You could actually bypass the whole process.
I know it would be a lot to set up,
and it would have to really depend
I suppose on there being significant revenues
to share out.
So that might be a little way off.
But in the end, you know,
what we need really is a global system in any case.
I mean, one of the problems that I have
with things you've been talking about
is that they are effectively confined to the US.
Pod is, for example, in this country,
it would be the PRS, the Performing Rights Society,
that you would need to be discussing with.
And in fact, as I understand it,
these things are territorial based,
not about where the show is hosted
or effectively broadcast from.
So in fact, you know,
your discussions with ASCAP BMI
wouldn't even apply to your own show
because you obviously produce that show
for the most part in the UK.
Or even if you did a territorial blanket agreement
with ASCAP BMI,
you would actually be excluded from it.
So what we need really is some kind of global system
a global blanket license,
so we don't have to worry about territories.
And that's why I think it might be worth
podger thinking about something slightly further reaching
than a deal with ASCAP BMI.
And if that going back to the artists themselves
and doing a deal, setting up a separate
collecting agency even.
And the other thing I wanted to say
was that as far as the million listen to March goes,
I wanted to let you know that he's far too modest
to tell you himself,
but podcast pool at podcastpool.com
who, as you know, is a lawyer in the UK,
and also an organizer of podcast.com UK.
Has been asked by the BBC on Radio 5 Live
to do his pod lawyer podcast
and put that out on National Radio in the UK,
which is also available to international listeners
through the BBC listen again player.
So that is undoubtedly going to be a
good move towards getting more listeners
to podcasting.
And Radio 5 is being very, very supportive
of the whole medium at the moment.
Anyway, thanks again, sorry I rambled
and I love the show.
Keep it up, thanks.
Thank you very much, Adrian.
Really appreciate it.
And of course, congrats to podcast,
Paul, he did tell me that.
I thought I had mentioned it on the show.
Of course the BBC is happy with that.
He's doing it for free.
That's great exposure.
Great exposure for him and for podcasting.
Love that.
So to wrap this up,
here's what I'm going to propose internally at pod show
because I think this is a great opportunity.
I would like the pod safe net
with music network to invest
and to become that clearing agency.
And here's the first steps we could take.
If you're a member of the network,
then I think that the benefit in your podcaster,
the first step we could take is,
okay, we will make sure that,
let me think about this.
We will make sure that the collections are done
for podcasts who are monetizing
and using pod safe music.
And it will be a fraction.
It'll be small.
It'll be freaking pennies, okay?
But millions of pennies
starts to become interesting for anybody
and I think eventually we're going to go
in that direction.
There's no doubt about it.
If a radio station or television station
or some mainstream media wants to use the music,
sure, no problem.
But you have a very different rate.
We're talking dollars there.
Not pennies.
For, you know, ten cents,
ten cents or dimes or whatever.
We'll figure that out.
And it will take significant resources.
It will take work,
but I really would love to invest in that
because I think that's how we fulfill
on George Carlin's dream.
And that's how we turn the tables.
And I'm pretty sure,
if we can succeed at that.
And we really are bringing the listeners in
because we've got exciting new music
and tons of it and lots of diversity
that, you know, the mainstream media
will want to play this.
And they'll want to be a part of it.
I mean, it's there.
It's the fuel that makes radio stations.
Music radio stations run is the music.
They're all pulling from the same
one and a half million songs
that you can download from iTunes
or from Rhapsody or, you know,
whatever other system you,
you may be subscribed to where you buy your music.
Everyone's, and they all say it.
It's a million and a half songs.
That's all that is no more songs than that.
Well, we know that's not true.
So I'm going to work on this.
I'm going to keep you updated.
But I think that as podcasting starts to move,
not all, not all by the way,
if you, if you have a non-commercial podcast,
you should be able to use the music
under almost like a creative commons license
where you don't have to pay anything
for the privilege of using it as long as you report it.
But if you do and people will
and we're helping with them with that
with monetization,
then we're going to pay the artists
who are part of this.
Okay, I'm sorry for the rant.
I didn't get to all the songs I wanted to play.
I didn't get to have the promos I wanted to,
to put before you.
We'll do that tomorrow.
Thanks for listening.
Bye-bye.