Daily source code, April 6th, 2005.
Yo DJ, are you doing mech radio?
Your DJ has only just begun.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do you need it?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need not sticking crazy.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I guess it's about a curry.
Hey, everybody, we're back at the cottage, how you doing?
Once again, it's the Daily Source code.
And we're back on track.
That's right.
Coming to you from Surrey.
Guilford to be specific to Curry Cottage.
This is your Daily Source code, April 6th, 2005.
Oh, man.
It's good to be back home.
Well, do I miss that Miami sunshine?
Of course, we were gone.
It was beautiful weather here.
You know, that's the way it always goes.
My in-laws have been staying here, taking care of the critters.
We still got two dogs, two cats, and all the difference
with the house and apartment, you know, you got to have someone
look after the house.
That's all kinds of shit and happens.
All by itself, actually.
So we got in the this morning, landed around 6.30 a.m.
stood in the immigration line for another hour or so, you know,
big planes, a couple of jumbo's come in.
400 people was shot and takes a little while.
And that went straight to bed once he got home.
Man, I was completely wrecked.
I've been jet lag before, but in this case,
we couldn't get the seats we wanted on the way back.
So it was a little more cramped than that I'm used to.
Certainly on a seven and a half hour flight
so I didn't get a wink of sleep.
It was, yeah, I mean, usually I'm out like a light, you know,
once in fact the minute the engines hit and we're taken off,
that's usually when I fall asleep and I usually get about two or three hours
in that point.
But I'm fresh now, time is 8.22.
Is this Wednesday?
If it's Wednesday, then this must be guilt for it, I think.
So I was thinking what I could do to get the show cranking,
get into the mood and went over to the iTunes Music Store,
purchased something that we could all share together.
I was talking about music licensing again pretty soon.
We could get some interesting feedback
from the Harry Fox agency from Sound Exchange and from BMI.
Looks like everyone's just kind of looking to see what's going to happen,
who's going to go first.
And the meantime, this is the perfect song to get into the mood.
I actually never heard this intro part before.
I'm only, I guess, only played the single version.
But once you hear it kick in, you'll know it is a perfect song for the podcast.
Try to grow.
Do be brothers on your daily source code.
So come to the most limited time.
Have a round of savings.
Take a closer off the road.
Run as fast as possible.
Save up before the stage.
Don't be brothers from the best of the doobie brothers live, that's why I never heard
that intro before.
That's a China Grove on daily source code for April 6, one day before, oh nice, fade out,
nice ending guys.
One day before Patricia's birthday, and I've been forbidden to tell you how old she
will become 56.
So we'll have a little celebration tomorrow.
It's so good to be back and have my own sound again, and be sitting in my office, and
yeah, it's good.
It's really, really nice to be back, and lots of stuff to do.
I'm going back to New York on Monday, and do another blitz tour, let's see where we're
going to go.
It's New York, then we go to Minneapolis, then we go to Colorado, and then maybe all the
way out to the West Coast that kind of depends on a couple of things that got to happen.
So just a little time to turn around, I really want to get this Windows laptop working.
Man, I got a lot of comments about the last podcast, which is the one that I did with
the tablet.
First of all, no, Microsoft did not send me the goddamn tablet.
I bought that myself at the Comp USA, it was at Circuits City.
I thought I actually explained about that.
A lot of feedback, though, a lot of people sending me URLs for great applications.
I have to say that what I really enjoy about this tablet is the one note.
Microsoft Office, one note, whatever, note taking software.
That stuff is really cool, and if you wonder why I'm delving into the world of Windows,
it's not because I've given up the Mac, I mean, no way.
I think I actually said, I want the Mac for content, and I love using the tablet for communication,
for Skype and emails, stuff like that.
Gmail works great everywhere anyway.
Man, it's a great-tab Gmail on all your browsers.
It's finally a great solution for synchronizing email across multiple machines.
Well, that's like, I'm going to just move the microphone up a bit.
So the reason is that, let me see, is it 95% of the world uses Windows, and we're in a business
where people unavoidably use computers.
So we got to come up with some stuff that also works on Windows,
and Mac people, especially when it comes to recording podcasts.
I think we're really, yeah, we're pretty privileged.
I've learned a lot about how the sound system or subsystem, or the fuck you call it, on Windows
works, it's interesting because it's not really uniform.
Each sound card is different, which of course is why the Mac is so great, because it knows
about what kind of core audio it's using.
And Windows, that can differ from machine to machine.
And of course, different sound card that could be used.
So if you want to make a system call, they say the mic mixer, you know, it's not that cut and dry,
you have to kind of like ask the sound card what it's using.
And at least this is the way it was explained to me.
And there's some great software that I've been testing, which is kind of like an alpha stage.
And I'm going to try and use that tomorrow to create the podcast.
So beware, it could be another shitty experience, which has nothing to do with that software.
It has more to do with the settings of the sound card.
I think that somehow loudness was turned on and SLS wow DSP and all kinds of loudness filters,
not write it all, but it's very hard to tell, you know, if you don't have your own gears,
like now with the headphones that I'm used to using, just all my own stuff, you know,
the ambient noise, all of that I'll really be able to tell before it goes out what the sound of the
of the show is actually like. I got a sound scene tour, I'll just play a little bit of this sound
scene tour. It comes to us from Apple iBlog. It's actually, it's not really,
it's more like a virtual sound scene tour. This is sound scene tour of wipeout pure,
which I presume is a game. It was probably like a skateboard game or snowboarding game on the PSP
that's the PlayStation portable, which I thought was interesting, you know, you could definitely do
sound scene tours of software that way. You could, you know, lots of people record their screens
when they're playing Xbox or PlayStation or whatever. Maybe it would be fun if you know,
like Sims or maybe if you're into Doom or some of those, you know, shoot them up games and
you're, and you can record the audio with the participants as well. That could be interesting.
So I just want to play a little bit of it. It's not very, it's not really exciting,
but still, you know, I want to give it a chance there as an idea. And good old Kenster J,
we've talked about Ken before. Ken, of course, has done, was it too now?
We only done two MTV Chronicles. Man, we got to do another one. We keep trying to hook up
up with this, you know, eight or nine hours time difference sucks, basically. So I'll try and catch
him this weekend because it looks like flying is out. There's a huge storm front headed our way
in the wing commander already sent out smoke signals that he probably wasn't coming over to some
training here. Another we can't fly in an inclement weather, but you really can't learn anything
because you're, you know, too busy battling the forces of nature and not, you know, not really
don't have enough time to, to work on, yeah, concentrating on getting the playing down on the ground
or, you know, just all the, all the, all the different stuff, you know, it's, according to the wing
commander, you just don't learn that much. So I'll probably have time to find Ken when it's both
convenient for us to do another MTV Chronicles. In the meantime, if you've never heard it,
the Ken and Squip show has some interesting topics this week. Hello, I'm Kenster J. Please join
Squip and I this week, because I have a god awful traffic accident, Squip undergoes painful oral surgery
and all sorts of famous people die. That's this week, only on the Ken and Squip show,
a dusting my brain.com, KSS. Oh man, poor Ken, that sucks so bad. He's, he is a, he is a real
car freak, as long as I've known him, and probably as far as long as he's been able to drive
over before that. And he's been in some interesting accidents. He does seem to attract them somehow.
Although he'll, of course, deny that and say it's been years since he's had any kind of fender
bender and it's never his fault, but I'll never forget a new jersey. Ken worked at our house for a while.
We had, we, the house was kind of redumbed, but the garage was still, you know, at the end of the
driveway was a stand-alone garage. It was kind of together, you know, it wasn't falling down. So
at the time we had, what do we had? We had a Rolls Roy Silver Shadow, two beautiful car,
bought it from the first owner. And so that was in there. And then, I thought, I'm not quite sure what
it was, but Ken was going to park his car or want to get something out of the, I think it was going
to park his, oh, he was parking his car in there. I think it was that the new, he had like a new
Camaro, maybe that's the one he totalled. So we got the got total, got T-bone. You got to listen to
Ken and Squip show to get the details. We had two doors and one door, you know, they're supposed to be
like roll up garage doors, right, that on a spring system, but it was really heavy,
wooden doors. And usually a park, the rolls on the right hand side, because you had to like push it
all the way up to the bumper for it to fit in the garage. But it was out for some reason. And that was
actually since that, you know, that door rarely opened. That was the broken one, you know, so I
just parked it there. And broken means the spring system didn't work. And clearly recall,
the Ken Park, this new car, you know, opened up the garage. Wanted to roll in and then
freaking door came down right on the hood. We last now, we come to think of it. We laugh then too.
My name is Dave. I'm a Mac guy. Is there an eye Mac on your desk? Is there a power book in your
bag? Is there an iPod in your pocket? Do you wonder what's up with those people who used that
other operating system? If so, you may be a Mac guy. Find out for sure by tuning into the
daily podcast from www.radiomacguys.com. I think I am. I think I, well, if not, I'm coming out of the closet
now. I'm a Mac guy. Sorry about that. I wanted to come home to to see the animals reaction.
Mac cats, you know, we got these two great cats. All of our animals come from shelters or
pounds or whatever around around the world. And cats are so weird, you know, you walk in and
look, kind of look at you for two seconds and look away like, you know, dude, where were you? Yeah.
Like they don't give a shit. So I guess news that quivered through the podcast community the
other day is Paris Hilton's podcast is forthcoming at starts on April 29th in promotion for the
movie House of Wax. Interesting responses to everybody or from lots of people about this.
And I'm thinking, you know, I was a fan of the simple life. When we were living in Belgium,
I was actually downloading the show by a bit torrent a year before the first series aired in
the Netherlands or in Belgium. And even though it's completely scripted, you know, I like Paris Hilton.
I think she's, I think she's something about her that's just, you know, it's just cute.
What else can you say? You know, you don't have to have, you don't have to necessarily be talented
to be cute and nice and likable. And, you know, this podcast is going to be interesting.
I had dream actually the other night about that. It was me, Paris, a hotel room. And for some
reason, Mads Weinstein. Everybody dreams of meeting industry influencers face to face.
So locker room is bringing a few of them to Seattle, Washington for the fifth annual known
decks, a conference for entrepreneurs, smart business executives and tech enthusiasts the world over.
Adam Curry is this year's keynote with a handful of internet leaders joining him in our
single track schedule. I'm Chris Parillo and I'll be your host for the entire weekend,
providing Wi-Fi, a dedicated power outlet in the main hall and unlimited food and beverages throughout
the day for all registered attendees. Swing by known decks.com for more information.
GNOMEDX.com. See in Seattle for June 23rd through 25th 2005.
All righty. Chris, you definitely need to listen to East Radio the most recent podcast
because for the fifth of April, I was listening to that on the plane and Mads who calls you
alternatively Chris Scott and James. You know, I think it's challenging you to a mud wrestle.
I'm not quite sure, but you should check it out. And also, I think Chris is trying to get
Dave Winer out there, which I hope he accepts the invitation. That would be great. So we could
have multiple sides of the podcasting coin and I look very much forward to that.
The Pew ratings is another thing that a lot of people have been talking about. P.E.W.
Let me just see, what does that stand for? Hold on a second. Of course, I'm ill-prepared for
this. Hold on. Let me just open up my browser. Again, I'm using the desktop Mac with a cinema display,
using VNC to control the laptop, which of course is connected to the board to the mixing board.
Let me see. Guess I could just look for this. I'll maybe just get it from my side. Hold on a second.
So these Pew people are essentially they do internet ratings, I guess. They're the ones
that have been tracking. I think the first time I heard of them was when they released a study
on how many people use RSS. Interestingly enough, no one challenged the RSS study.
But the podcasting study, because the numbers are pretty big. Six million people apparently have
listened to podcasts in the United States alone. That's big. Hold on, still. What is wrong here?
Oh, yeah, shoot. The four megabit line was down when I got home, which of course screwed up a
couple of things. I must have gone down two days ago because the in-laws couldn't use the Skype phone
to call us. I didn't know what the problem was, but I guess it's loading now. I guess it's because
about something went down for one reason of the other. So it's a support and email. Luckily we have
the backup DSL, which is a one megabit down. And what is it? 250, I'll present something like that.
So it's not blazingly fast, but it certainly works. I guess there's a way that I could link those
two together with some kind of router or a switch, I guess is what I need. An IP switch, and then
it would automatically switch over to, or maybe it would combine the bandwidth. I wonder if there's
an easy way to do that. If you have two dedicated lines coming in, if there's a simple setup or
do I have to get a switch, or can I just use a router? The interesting to find out. So here I am
Pew about us, who are these people? Basic information about a mission staff advisory board
of privacy reprint and citation policies. What does that mean? Oh, mission. Okay, here we go.
Who are these people from Pew? We want to know our mission. The Pew, I want to put Pew
stands for Pew. Who came up with that name? The Pew Internet and American Life Project produces reports
that explore the impact of the internet on family communities working home, daily life,
education, health care, and civic and political life. The project aims to be an authoritative
source on the evolution of the internet through collection of data and analysis of real world
developments as they affect the virtual world, blah, blah, blah, blah. Okay, so, oh, they have RSS feeds.
Oh, no, I'm going to check kind of RSS feeds. They have, oh, okay. Oh, I definitely need to get that.
They've got RSS feeds for just for the front page, for reports, for the press releases,
or for all them great. Oh, subscribe to that for sure. So the big noises, this is impossible.
Six million people. How can it be? And they had, they took such a small sampling.
200-nate people. So that means there's a margin of error of 7.8 percent. Okay, so that's like,
I'll say 10 percent. That means it could be, they could be off by 600,000. So it's 504,
the 5,400,000 people. And that's still a hell of a lot. And by the way,
who said that's wrong? You know, what's wrong with the statistical sample like that?
This is exactly how ratings have been done for years. Sure, they've got people meters,
but it's still a sample of like, I don't know, what, I know what it is in, in some countries,
it's like 2,000 people. But I'm not sure what the sampling is in the states and companies
are increasingly more using people meters. But for radio, for instance, it's diaries. You actually
fill out a little booklet and tell the arbitron people what you listen to. If you write down the
name of a DJ that you remembered, which could be like, Bubba the love sponge, not like we haven't
heard that on 50 million stations. You know, the station will actually get a credit for that in the
ratings. And then, you know, the extrapolation, it's a great word, the extrapolation of these numbers
is boiled down to Q and, you know, average time spent listening. I mean, it's all kinds of ways.
And all that it's, that that's about is about sales. This is the most powerful sales tool in
really in the commercial world, as we know it today. And no one questions this shit. I think we've
talked about it before that, you know, when you do, well, I've talked a lot of statisticians,
because I've been in television, certainly. And I know that just from the response from people
on the street that sometimes we got a shitty rating, I know that lots of people watched it and
really liked it. And it was, you know, the topic of the day. So, you know, I guess sometimes just
fall into a hole there when it comes to, you know, pure mathematical statistics. And all the
mathematicians tell me that statistics really do work. You know, you, you can fight it. But
I mean, I'm, I'm not a mathematician. I can't fight it with them. So, I'll just have to take
their word for it. The people, I respect for their knowledge. So, you know, how can we be questioning
this and not be questioning ratings? Because it worked. What was that movie? Was there a movie with
who is with the, I'll come on. What's the, what's the little good fellow guy's name?
Ugh. I can't, I can't cope with this name. Anyway, it was like some gangsters and I can't,
why am I bowing on the title of this movie? It's like a movie you see on cinimax. Anyway,
gangsters come up with a TV show or there's a TV show and then the gangsters go and basically
hijack everybody's home who is a, a Nielsenho and they keep reporting that they're watching
that show. And so it's sourced at the top of the ratings. Boy, I wish I could, that's horrible.
Okay, it must be the jet lag. I'm just totally phasing out on what that was. So, you know, no matter
which way you look at it, statistics do work. So, if, I think, I mean, I have a hard time believing
it myself, you know, 200 and eight people that you can come up with a number like six million.
But, you know, if we don't question all the other statistics that we live with, you know,
okay, so five million, 400,000, that's still the hell of a lot. So there's something really
something going on here. And I quite frankly, I find it very exciting. And by the way, when it comes
to statistics, have we ever really gotten over, you know, the fuzziness of stats and unique
visitors and paid views. I was reading in the Wall Street Journal on the plane. I should have torn
in the article out. I didn't bring it with me. There's a lawsuit right now that's been filed
against Google. And I think Yahoo, by one, or I don't know if it was a class action, it was one
of more advertisers who say, hey, you know, your numbers are fucked up. The fraudulent. And we're
paying you too much. And in fact, I think the, and I'd love to hear from some lawyers out there,
I think the case actually states that Google and Yahoo concealed the fact that these
advertisers were actually receiving less legitimate traffic than that they were paying for. So
something to keep our eye on.
This is an invitation to all the Mac OS 10 users in the audience to surf over to podcasttuner.com
and check out a brand new podcasting client for the Mac. Like you, I love free software. But I hate
free software that crashes every time I run it on OS 10 like I Potter. I also don't like paying
$20 for software with a hideous interface like I Potter X. With podcasttuner, you get a podcasting
client designed from the ground up. Now, you know, I was, I played this promo because I want to
give equal airtime to all different podcasting clients out there. I promoted, I was at blog matrix
sparks the other day. Actually, that's on my weblog. But, you know, why would you put out a promo?
And in your promo, you start slagging your competitors that really says a lot about you did to run
fast and stable on OS 10. And podcasttuner does things no other podcasting client does.
Podcasttuner displays show notes without launching a web browser and it can send those show notes
to the note reader of your iPod so you can read them on the go whenever you happen to be listening
to your podcasts. But please don't try that while you're driving. Podcasttuner integrates
seamlessly with iTunes or not. If you'd rather not use iTunes at all, you can listen to your podcasts
right in podcasttuner. And podcasttuner costs only a fraction the price of iPod X. A single user
license for podcasttuner is only five dollars. So if you have a Mac and you're searching for
a better podcasting client, surf over to podcasttuner.com.
Okay. All right, there you go. Actually, download the House of Wax private label branded iPodder.
A little bit of a cold didn't want you to hear that. And I downloaded that onto the Windows machine.
It's cool. It's got all the House of Wax branding on it. Congratulations to the lemon team. That's a
great, great job guys. And it's also cool to see the directories in there and the podcast
Alie Top 10. And so it's really, it'll give people an entree.
Damn airplane air. It'll give people a real insight into the community. You know, not just,
oh, here's the Paris Hilton podcast. And what really slays me is that something that's been
in there since day one of the iPodder clients is the the welcoming message, the welcome message. I love
the fact that left in there. I really appreciate that. That's a way cool. So tomorrow or Friday,
I'm not quite sure which one's going to work time wise. Ron and I are going to do another
another, I don't know if we'll do a full show together or if I'll bring him into the source code.
I'd like to do a full show with him. He's now set up, he's got his setup ready to go at home. And he has
a full blown studio, being a musician and he's built a couple of studios. He has all this gear
left. We still went out shopping at guitar, center, guitar, world, guitar universe, whatever it is.
I've got himself a mixer, compressor. He's got some beautiful microphone, like a noise and microphone.
And we worked on setting up the routing so that's Skype will work. And so we're ready to make some
damn announcements. I'd say the first announcement we're going to make. I will be our strategy. So
be on the lookout for that this week. And as I said, next week will be together for the whole week. So
more coming very soon. And as I got home, all the news here was about Michael Jackson.
You know, now they've allowed this testimony by other kids who say that they've been
molested by Michael. Of course, their parents receive $20,000 to sell their story on hard copy.
Their lawyers are going to press civil charges if I guess if they can or how that works.
And you know, it was a tickling game, but you know, then a tickling game that maybe went too far.
I mean, I hate having to discuss this story. But I just want to reiterate,
innocent until proven guilty. I've met this man. He's asexual. I think he just loves all children of the
world. If I'm wrong, I'll be the first guy to say, dude, I was fucking wrong. But I'm glad we have the
process to make sure that we're right or wrong. And I do believe in the American justice system.
I fucking don't believe in the American media system because, you know, it's just like,
you know, well, okay, the Pope's dead. We're all tied to that story. Hey, let's do Michael Jackson again.
Yeah, this is this man is is half dead no matter what. It doesn't matter what the outcome of the
trial is. This, this will kill just a piece of him. That's what happens. It's when you're a
public figure and this kind of shit happens. And it doesn't have to be about child molestation
can be about anything. And it really hurts, particularly the way the media handles it. It's
assholes. All of you. Okay. Again, if I'm wrong, I'll be the first guy to stand up and say, you know,
totally misread it and misjudged it. And again, it's great. We have this process. But innocent until
proven guilty. Please.
Oh, you go to sleep tonight. Oh, you please.
Oh, you go to sleep tonight.
Oh, you go to sleep tonight. Oh, you go to sleep tonight. Oh, you go to sleep tonight. Oh, you go to sleep tonight.
Oh, you go to sleep tonight. Hey.
You know, it's time
Through the wide mass down
The wide mass down
Down
The woman suffered a rise in the wide awake
She woke with violence started at the side of the world
The two and a half day we were shocked
And since she was full of that activity
Lashed in the battle with the great python
What an order was a blame
She woke her as soon as the sun
Crucially flare around
The room had to be dark
And the candles lit
The windows tally shocked
She moved about naked with a cigarette tank
From the quarter of her mouth
Her toilet was in the bear of the great preoccupation
A thousand trifling females had to be a tent
Before she could so much as dawn and bathroom
She was like an athlete hearing for a great amount of time
My hands start to rust
The hours turn
And to dust like on top of the refrigerator
Indeed
Does an understand
A smile?
In the palm of His hand
Don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough.
Don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough, don't stop to get enough.
Okay, that's different, say a prayer for Michael Jackson, that's sent in by, hold on a second, my screen is updating here, that's sent in by, there's hypno-love wheel.
You know, love wheel, say a prayer for Michael Jackson, that's different, sure, but you might as well.
Hey, Han, you want to do the hit test?
Well, you know, what do you mean by the hit test?
Does she want to do the hit test?
Yeah, hold on a second, no, no, Han, come on.
She's unpacking the suitcases.
I love it when she does that.
The automatic packing and unpacking suitcases.
Do you want to do the hit test with me?
Yeah, the young pull-out hit test?
Yeah.
Yeah, well, I'm recording right now, so, yeah, come over here.
You can have one, you can have one headphone.
I didn't say anything, very dirty.
Right, hold on a second, let me put it in the other ear, okay.
All right, you ready?
Okay, hold on a second, here we go.
Yeah, hold on a second.
Ready, two, one.
It's time for the hit test.
With young pull-out, not for me.
Hey, Adam, this is a hit test made in advance, because probably I'm not available at the moment.
Okay.
If you want to know more about this, check out the hit test podcast.
It should be available right now.
All right, so I don't know what's happening right now, but I have a hit test.
So here's number one.
Here we go.
One, two, one, that is.
It's, uh, came here.
And this is number two.
Two.
No, it's not what we got.
Well, thank you.
There's nothing like no one.
Number three.
Huh?
I don't know what that is.
All right.
Uh, it's hard also.
Sometimes I'm happy.
This is answer number one.
Okay, let's came here.
It's came here and word up.
Remember what the guy was wearing,
from.
He's at, like.
In a red, jux swell.
Teacheroning still down.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Ain't make fification..
Same.
When you hit the car you've got to get it under government.
Get it under government.
It's the trollery.
normally no way you'd say
Cario and word up.
10.
1.
This is number 2.
It's Rose Royce.
This is Best Love.
I am Best Love.
That's a good song.
And now Best Love.
Rose Royce.
And number 2.
This is Answer Number 3.
Oh.
Shack Attack.
This song is titled, Don't Know This.
It's a little bit sweet.
There's a whole philosophy behind it.
Down Under Street.
Answer Number 3.
All music from the 80s.
Man, I love that music.
Well, and I hope you enjoyed this one.
Again, I don't know if I am able to create a hit test in the coming days.
Yes, because I'm not afraid of all.
Well, okay.
We'll just have to wait and see.
See you next time for another edition of the hit test.
Bye-bye.
Oh, very much.
Feedback.
Welcome at hit test at gmail.com.
And check out the hit test podcast at youngvolet.nl.
Bye-bye.
I don't know.
Let me see.
Let me look at his web blog.
I'm here.
I'm off for four days of observation and examination to determine the content of an 18 week rehabilitation
period that is handicapped related and that will be coming soon.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, he has a vision problem.
Oh, yeah.
So I hope he can, uh, I hope that works out.
Yeah, we're trying to get him a grandmaster view screen.
A big one.
Yeah.
Yeah, because he's like, I think he's, uh, he's visually fucked up.
Let me say.
Yeah.
Like, see, here's a little picture of him.
Okay, young.
Well, we hope everything's okay.
Looking new, sunny.
Yeah.
Wait, let me zoom in for you.
Because I have a little bit of a vision problem.
But that's my age.
Uh, he has a little, um, he has a business.
Yeah.
He goes out and fix people's computers and installs networks and shit.
So that's pretty cool.
He has a little, little car.
One of those little mini cars.
Yeah.
Really?
Okay. Well, young.
We hope you, uh, we hope you do.
Okay.
Because, uh, Dan, what am I going to do without a hit test?
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
That would be pretty.
Okay.
Thank you, honey.
I was fun.
Maybe it's a laser thing.
I hope so.
I hope it's something like that.
Yeah.
I hope it works.
Definitely.
And let me see.
That'll just about do it for today's source code.
Yep.
41 minutes.
Love it.
April 6, 2005.
As always, feedback is welcome.
Adamaccurry.com.
And I have two gigs.
So you can fill that up.
For some reason, the MP3 feedback at gmail.com isn't working.
I don't know if it's filled up already or.
I gotta go see what's going on with that.
Because it should have double the space.
Everyone should be able to send at least.
Another problem when everyone already sent one in the past couple months.
Of course, www.curry.com for the weblog for comments.
And daily source code.com is where you can pick up the podcast feed.
Check out the archives and the most recent podcast.
I'll be back tomorrow from the cottage.
Take care.
Bye-bye.
Thanks for watching.