Delta Shara Charley 225
And it is your daily source code for Monday, August 22, 2005.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
We have a new week back at the cottage and a whole new setup.
You're not going to believe where I am right now.
Actually, you might believe it.
I'm in the garage in the new setup since it's too freaking heavy to carry upstairs.
I will definitely take a picture of this because it's just unbelievable.
You know, my father-in-law built me this podcast table, which he built in the garage where we were in the states on vacation.
And he made it out of MDF so that's really heavy thick wood.
And the thing is just absolutely beautiful.
Of course, I've posted a couple of pictures about it or of it on my weblog, on my flicker page.
When we got back, but this thing is so cool.
And I've got new equipment to go with it.
Which of course means that this show may actually not even be recording or it could screw something up.
Well, let me explain what I have here.
So I've got the big setup and today we went to the music store.
We're going to go see if we can get some 19-inch rack rails so that I could put my compressor limiter and all my outboard gear in.
And then we started talking to the guy at the music store.
And he showed me this Yamaha Professional Audio Workstation, which is just beautiful.
And it does everything all in one.
It's got your effects.
It's got your faders.
It's got to hard disk recording built right in.
So we're going to give it a shot and see if we can make it work.
Might as well.
It's a Monday.
So shit's going to break.
This is the right data.
Have it break.
And let's get it all kicked off with a mashup.
This was a mashup town's mashup of the week.
We can trip in too.
Recognize the Beatles in there.
You're going to date this one.
And then we started talking to the guy at the music store.
So we started talking to the guy at the music store.
Well, it was we talked to the guy at the music store,
So new set up, so it may sound a little bit different.
It may not sound a perfect yet.
In fact, let me just roll off a little bit of high in there.
So this new box that I got is something that I actually think I could take with me on
the road, because we were talking to the guy at the music store saying, look, I want
a little mixer, that I want a little compressor, that I need a microphone preamp.
And by the time we got done, if you look at all that kit, all put together, it's like
three boxes, one of which would probably have to be a 19-inch rack size, three power
supplies.
I mean, just all this stuff, and it's like, you know, that's not going to be very handy
to carry with me.
And then you show me this professional audio work station.
It's the AW 16G, 16 tracks.
And I spent, like, with my father and all, we spent, like, at least probably about an hour
and a half, just getting all the information from him, figuring out how to do it, how
you can patch channels, reroute stuff through buses, and then it has this hard disk
recorder.
And actually, you can burn stuff to a CD drive, it's just, it's an incredible machine,
and it has everything all built into it.
Also got a new microphone.
This is, oh, let me see, it's an AKG microphone.
It's something that's very portable that I can take with me.
And I'm still using the computer for the sound output, for, you know, I'm using Megaseg,
and oh, by the way, I'm only, I've scrapped the, what I think was probably the trouble
some fire wire drive.
I'm only using this small portable fire wire drive that I have, where is it not actually?
It was around here somewhere.
Oh, here it is.
It's the, let me see, the fire light, I think it is.
What is it called?
Yeah, it's a fire light drive.
So this incredible podcast desk that my, my father-in-law, John built for me, is still
on the garage because I have to clean up all my other crap first.
And I have to move desks around and have to move, actually, I think we have to take one
door off of the, of the cottage studio in order to get the, get this thing in.
And then when you'd like two extra guys to help me because it's so freaking heavy, but so far
just standing here and, you know, I put the equipment, just kind of in a temporary setup.
While the mashup was running, I took four pictures so I'll be sure to post those along
with the show notes.
It's working, I like it.
It's the right height.
It's, I mean, it's not adjustable, it's my height exactly.
And I've got the mixture in the middle, I've got the laptop on the right, I think this
is going to be a perfect setup.
And on the left, of course, I have my tea and other cool tomals that I need for the
show.
Hmm, we got back Saturday, had a nice trip once again, a fantastic voyage on Virgin
Atlantic.
I actually slept for at least four hours.
The girls, well, Christina slept, Patricia couldn't sleep at all, so she's now completely
jet lag.
She's been up at all hours the night and sleep in during the day.
And feeling much better, it's too bad about the vacation.
It didn't quite work out the way we wanted it to with us being sick in New York for the
first week.
And then San Francisco, it being the coldest week in San Francisco ever.
And by the way, as far as I could tell, actually, I mean, look at my, my weather report
right here.
It looked to me like San Francisco was beautiful this week.
Let me see, London and Amsterdam are going to be horrible.
It's going to be, yeah, San Francisco, they're looking at sunshine every single day.
Oh my god, are you here that?
You can hear the, you can, that's my MDA, making little whining sound there.
So the only thing I don't have here in the garage is Wi-Fi.
I almost could pick up a signal and I'm sure that if I spun stuff around and really did my
best, I could pick it up.
So I won't be able to go through all of my email as usual to talk about stuff.
Actually, I have my Gmail page open here with all my daily source code stuff, you know,
reminders and I guess the, the a couple of things I can see right off the bat.
If, if you hadn't seen it already, the Catholic insider was interviewed on CNN, Father
Roderick, really fantastic.
He was at the, at the world youth day and that was in Germany where the pope was.
And he was, he was doing his thing and then he got a really good spot on CNN, which is
very, very cool.
And, uh, oh, man, there's just so much to do, so much to talk about.
I'm pretty much pretty sure I'm going to be going back to San Francisco next Sunday.
And I'll be there for at least a week, maybe 10 days, just because there's so much going
on.
We've got the new podshow.com that's going to be launching and we've got a lot of stuff
that's going to go along with that.
I think Friday, this coming Friday, we're just going to do kind of like a soft launch of
some stuff.
And then we'll have, you know, we'll start adding on the bits, uh, yeah, bit by bit, literally
but we've got some amazing things that we're going to be doing there and we'll be talking
about that.
And, of course, since I'm back at the cottage and I've got everything all, uh, in close
proximity, I can roll out some of those promos again.
I say, boldly, God, yes, Ambrose, have you ever heard of Rusty Bandar or Rusty Bandar?
Not since I stopped drinking my shan out of a coffee can, but I have, remember, you
would lock your lock, it was yesterday, but I would scarce be so undelicated to bring it
up again.
Thank you, Ambrose.
Not at all, but we got, so what is this Rusty Bandar?
Not what?
Who?
Very nice man has himself a podcast, a podcast, whatever is there, well, I'm sure I haven't
finished idea, but I'm told that you listen to it, where the podcast, this is a podcast
called Strange Brain Radio, yes, I have heard of it really, how did you find it?
It was quite good, I would even recommend it, but bless his heart, well, but what ever
is the matter, he's just not from sound, well, we can all be perfect, how true, how true,
all the men, jula-fambros, well, absolutely, you know without proper medication, I become
quite nervous.
God, Joe, content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
Sing along with a zoo choir in South Africa, swing with sharks and the Galapagos, study
Buddhism in Cambodia.
I'm here on Earth, we share stories that inspire and delight.
We don't just talk about the world, we bring you the world.
Here on Earth, from Wisconsin Public Radio, subscribe to our podcast at iTunesPodcastAlley.com
and here on Earth, our podcast is so much going on in podcast land, there is so much cool
stuff that's been coming out, we were at the office last week and I was just looking at
the ping page, that's ping.indepotter.org, which I think Marcus was also going to map
to podshow.com, so it'll be ping.podshow.com.
But there you can see the most recently updated podcast in the past three hours, ping.indepotter.org.
And yeah, we're just going through this stuff and I was making a whole list of incredible
podcast and I put it into an outliner and I want to feature those on the next podfinder,
which will be coming out tomorrow, also coming out tomorrow, a brand new episode, it was
going to be the fourth and final episode of Spike Lee's Shadowcast of his movie Inside
Man.
But as you'll hear tomorrow on the podcast, Spike was so into it and by the way, we got full
access.
Human Newman is on the set while they're rolling, excuse me, oh yes, we're back and already
the sincere was hitting me.
As I said, full access, so you can hear what's going on on the set, you can hear Spike
directing, some of the actors, you have some, some mayhem that happens on the set.
I'm not going to spoil it for you, but you definitely want to check that out that should
be coming out tomorrow and that'll be in iTunes exclusively, the Inside Man podcast, Spike
Lee.
And because, well, this I can tell you at the end of that podcast, he totally goes
off and says, you know, this is the last one, this can't be the last one, he's supposed
to do four episodes and then he says, please come back again next week, so it looks like
we're going to have five out of four episodes of Spike Lee's Inside Man podcast.
The online community radio show dedicated to moms in every country who are holding the
world together one child at a time at www.monicaest.com.
She moves like she don't care, smooth that film, cool that's it.
Hi Adam, this is Paige and Gretchen from MommyCast.com.
Our podcast is Four Moms, by moms, we've got tips and advice and some really cool interviews
and we even talk about technology with a woman's touch.
Adam, we've got seven kids between us, so we know what we're talking about.
We love your show and we think other moms will love podcasts too.
It's convenient and mobile for moms on the run.
So give us a listen and thanks for introducing us to your audience.
Hey guys, tell your wives about Monikaest.com.
Yousa, I play that promo before, but the Monikaest is a really kick and some major button
people are tuning in and they're even getting all kinds of attention from movie companies.
They do the, I think they did something about the Penguin movie and it's getting good.
It's getting really good.
I also, let me see if I can find that if I had to do my outline.
I came across a daddy cast, let me see if this is going to start out, but it's going
to give me problems here and hold on.
Here it is, what was it, was it, yeah, 101 uses for baby wipes.
I'll be sure to play that piece of that on tomorrow or maybe when's the source code.
It's really quite awesome.
So this whole parent cast thing is really catching on tomorrow.
By the way, be doing a little bit of flying.
The in-laws are going to go back and that means, yes, I get to fly him.
So wink Amanda Williams will be showing up bright and early and the weather's pretty crappy.
I mean, like really crappy.
It's raining and, as I said, rain is expected for the rest of the week.
So I'm not quite sure if I'll be able to go VFR, which is visual flying rules or
if I'll have to go IFR now, I'm not IFR certified, which means you fly an instruments.
But the wink Amanda, of course, is and he can certainly train me on the instrument.
So if we do go instrument flying, then that'll be some great experience for me.
So I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to drop them off.
I haven't quite decided yet if I'm going to stay in an antwerp where the plane currently lives
and then come back on Wednesday morning or from to come back the same night.
That kind of depends on the weather.
But I will be taking my new setup.
So I'll be able to do all kinds of stuff on the road, taking the Yamaha Professional Audio
Workstation.
I got to figure out what kind of suitcase I'll have to be using now because if I use just
the overnight bag, I don't know, I don't know if I'll be able to fit my underwear.
But I'm really, really jazzed about this thing.
And it was cheap too.
It was like 400 bucks and it's got a 20 gig hard drive at anyway.
Enough about all that shit.
Let's see, what else is going on?
I got some pod save music, which I'll play for in a couple of minutes, pod save music
network also doing really well.
I'm just getting recituated.
It's good to be back.
It was good to be back in my own environment, good to have my own bandwidth back.
You kind of get used to the speeds that you have.
But at the same time, I'm gearing up for the next trip because I'll be in the apartment.
So that will be the Kurikondo in San Francisco.
And I guess I'll take the setup with me and be able to use it there.
So that's all coming up.
And this week, plenty of stuff to do, plenty of recording, plenty of production.
Lots of pod show calls, of course.
Back to living the dual time life where I have my normal day here in the UK.
And then around 4 o'clock in the afternoon, people start to wake up, that's 8 a.m. in San Francisco.
And then I have a whole another day to deal with.
Comment a few of the world features me, Michael, an ordinary teenager, expressing his views
an audio format, I speak about issues in the world and what's on my mind.
On the proud founder of the teen podcasters network, if your interest did end during the teen
view, head on over to comercast.tk, don't miss out.
The multitudes went forth and cast their pods in the direction of all who would listen.
And casting their pods in this manner, they were henceforth known as podcasters.
January 1991, the US military goes to war with Iraq, using a media-planet system to control
information.
April, 2003, the US military invades Iraq, reporters volunteer to be embedded.
May 2005, a memo containing proof that the reasons for war were fabricated, is found.
The American Mask Media ignores it.
In that same year, from out of the ashes of journalism, in the tradition of Norman
Miller, Jack Newfield, Seymour Hirsch and Robert Fisk, a journalist appears, a podcaster
emerges.
Exiled in Amsterdam, both Portuguese and the American, he examines the world as the eternal
outsider.
Ignorant and intelligent, angry and amused, critical and open-minded.
He's everything, the mainstream isn't.
He is bicycle mark, and this is his audio-communicale.
Bicyclemark.org.
Bicycle mark, now is a good time to check him out and subscribe, fantastic podcasters.
He's also been known to do some really outrageous sound seeing tours.
But I want to talk about the war on terror and about President Bush, Cindy Sheen.
Now Madge Weinstein went to Crawford, Texas, to get some experiential sights and sounds
from what's going on there, and I've been thinking about this a lot, and I usually don't
try to get too political, but I don't have a political slant on this.
I think a very practical slant on what's going on, and actually having been to Iraq myself
about, was it February last year, so when things were definitely heating up over there,
I met with lots of Iraqis, went to six different towns, really got quite a taste of what
life is like there, and what the people are like.
By the way, pre-Sidam Hussein Iraq really was quite a learned country, lots of great universities,
a lot of scholars came from universities in Iraq, and they say that civilization actually
started there, and I've been to the place where they say that that all began.
So I think that I have some insight into what's going on over there, and when I listen to
what Cindy Sheen is saying, I think that she is absolutely right, if she wants, and by the way,
anytime a mom tries to organize or organize a protest or a march, it's amillated, because women are
really by default, natural organizers. They're already organizing everything with the kids,
right? It's a ballet lesson, soccer, school, other after school activities, dinner,
house cleaning, this is if you're a state home mom, if you add to that, a working mom,
there's a whole another dimension that's going on. And also there's something so
pure about a mom and her child, that's something that no one can deny. Everyone has a mom,
you know, and everyone has that invisible bond with their mom. So when a mom wants to know
what the noble cause is that her son died for, then that really hits home, and you can't
deny it. You can't go around that, and I think that President Bush is making a large mistake
by not addressing this head-on, because he should be talking to her, and I'd like to actually
be able to hear the conversation, but here's what I think that he should be saying.
The war on terror, first of all, is real. And we really started witnessing it full on
on 9-11. That's when it hit home, so to speak. And boy, did it hit home. But the war on terror was
going on before that. Many, many years before that, we had embassy bombings, we had a failed attempt
at a bombing of the World Trade Center. We had a ship bombed in Yemen. There has been a continuous
and constant attack for years on the United States and the United States citizens, but it hasn't
happened at home. It was happening mainly overseas. And I think that you have to realize that
there, when something happens in Iraq, the news media always reports insurgents.
Well, just who are these insurgents? No one ever really stops to explain and take the time to
go through that. Insurgents are not necessarily Iraqi civilians who are pissed off that there
are armed forces from another country in their country. Insurgents are, in this case,
the same people who have been attacking the United States and other countries as well, by the
way, the so-called infidels for many, many years is just they've never done it at home.
For us at home, that is. But for them, home is Iraq, home is Saudi Arabia, home is,
well, it could be North Korea. I can't really speak about that because I've never been there.
But it is the large portions of the Middle East. And that's where these terrorists have been
attacking United States citizens and therefore the United States. What happened is they started to,
well, let's just step back one second. Why are they doing this? This is something that is being
programmed into very young minds from an early age that if you are essentially not Muslim.
And we're talking about radical Muslims here. Again, this is just my viewpoint, but I'm pretty
certain this is what's going down. They're programmed that the infidels must die.
And the reasons for that, hard for me to even start to grapple and grasp how that works,
but it is a fact and that's what's happening. So this war on terror, on September 11th,
really moved into the homeland and heartland of our country, the US. Even though there'd been
some previous attempts. So what the United States government has done because it's not just George
Bush who has sent our troops over there. It's the entire government. Everyone voted on this.
And if they want to change that, I'm sure that they can change that whenever they want.
They basically are protecting the United States and the United Kingdom and other
members of the coalition by moving the front of this war,
there where the warriors are, where the enemy is. Instead of having them come over here and fight
with us on our own turf. That's really, I think, the only practical situation that makes sense
for why we have 150,000 plus troops over there right now. And they are fighting these
extremists who want to kill us. So if you were to pull the troops out,
it is my view that then that front would subsequently move back to the United States. And the
only way to make sure that it would not hit home is by intensifying our borders, security,
which is almost impossible. Already, you know, I guess the best that can be done is being done.
And I don't think it's just a, it's not a workable situation because the extremists want
to come and kill Americans and right now the easiest place for them to fight and fight they will,
no matter what, is where the Americans are. In this case, they're heavily armed and well trained
servicemen and service women. So until we can get to the root of the problem and the root,
really, and I believe that that can only be solved through social awareness. So when you have,
like in the UK, you have imons and other religious leaders condemning any attacks,
explaining that the Muslim religion has nothing to do with violence and that these are
pure extremists that really are misusing religion for something cultural that they have
that has been programmed into their minds. That's a good thing because that's the only way you
can start to change some of that perspective in these young minds is getting that message out there.
And essentially, keeping all of these people that are dangerous, keeping them out of our shores.
So that's a really long-winded way of saying, I believe that that is why the troops are in Iraq.
It is not about oil. And I thought about it and I must say that it's easy to
slip into that thought. But if it really were about oil, then wouldn't we have lower prices?
Wouldn't we have more oil coming in? No, quite the opposite in fact is happening and here's a
little bit of perspective on the gasoline prices. Explain to me, if gasoline prices are now at
record highs, not historically if you translate today's dollar versus the dollar in the 80s or the
dollar in the 70s, but still it's unbelievably expensive by any standards. And now it's
really starting to hit the economy. What is it? I mean, we have these high prices, but then on the
other side of the fence, every single one of the oil companies has reported record profits.
Now profit is money that's left over. After you've already bought your raw materials and
you've got your machinery and your refineries running. So if it's costing us more and they're making
more profit, then the only thing that makes sense to me is that that is literally that money is going
from point A to point B. And it's not because there's a shortage of oil. There may be some kind of
superficial shortage or some make-believe shortage of refinery capacity. That's something I keep hearing.
But it's not because we're in Iraq and now we have this free flow of oil coming in. It makes no sense.
If anything, I think that the president should make a stand against these fuel companies,
because what they're doing is essentially price gouging. I don't know what the situation is that
they're taking advantage of other than just jacking up the price. To me, it smells of price fixing
and price gouging and lots of un-American activity. So that's the second part that President
Bush should be addressing. Now if we got those two out of the way, then maybe we can start to
have a constructive conversation on both sides of the fence, because after two weeks in the states,
this whole red state, blue state thing and they think and they don't know and these,
you know, it's like it's divided. It's a divided country and it's and that's the only thing
that is not, you know, America's great, but this is not right, this division. And I don't
think we should be looking at it black or white or red or blue, because it's just not that simple,
but we definitely need to have a re-explanation of what exactly is going on in Iraq. And the
news media have to start, particularly television news media, it really has to start explaining
better, you know, just saying, oh, there was an explosion, an IED was that improvised explosive
device set off by insurgents. Who were they? Okay, I want to know where they come from, what was
their background? You know, where's the reporting on that? I'm not seeing any of it, because I'm
pretty sure we're going to find out it's not Iraqi civilians. It's any crazy MF from anywhere in
the world, just wants to take pot shots at Americans. And, you know, they can go through very
complicated, expensive procedures and try and get smuggled into into the West and do their damage
on our shores, or they can just go over to where the, where the other guys are with guns. Oops,
what is that? Oh, that was just a text message. And they can go fight there. And so essentially,
that's what's happening. That's, that is the only practical reason I can see why we are in Iraq.
And if I'm wrong on this, then I really don't understand it. But this is what I've seen, and I know
that the Iraqi people don't hate the Americans. They don't like their situation at all. And they
certainly don't like the fact that their country is being used as his battleground, but it is not
the US against Iraq. And if, you know, people would say, oh, you have to, you should be in Afghanistan.
That's where Osama bin Laden is. Again, I'm quite certain that most of the
radical, call them insurgents, but radical haters of the West that they're all now on this battleground
that is Iraq and the Surahams T.C. and Baghdad. What you never hear about, by the way, is the
rest of Iraq. There are at least nine other camps. And, you know, very little is happening there.
So this is a front. It is a war. And I, for one, am very happy that it is not in the United States.
So we don't have urban warfare on our streets. I know that sounds egotistical, but I really do mean it.
And I fully support our servicemen and women who have been sent over. And, you know, there's no draft,
so these are professionals. And I can totally understand how freaked out you must be if, you know,
your family member is called up into service, you know, because they were in the reserves.
You know, it's, you never expected that to happen, right? But that is the deal, you know,
that is the way it works. If you're in the reserves, then you can be activated. And that's just a deal of.
And, you know, it's, it's a bummer, but it can happen. So all of all of these troops who are over
in Iraq, they are really, I feel really are there for a noble cause to keep all this crap away from us,
away from our country, away from our countries. And, and that I believe is what George Bush should be
telling Cindy Sheen and the world if it is indeed true. If he doesn't, if he comes up with some other
story, yeah, then we're all fucked. Anyway, time for some pod save music, I hope that that kind of
came out in an understandable way. It's very difficult material to deal with, but it's been kind of
bubbling up inside, so just had to get it out.
Yes, I'll fill my head and spell my tears in one time, in one time, in one time,
I will see, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, I will see.
I saw time around your feet once, when you see the blink of an eye falling on a cold heart,
seeing it your more can take your place, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time,
I will see, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, I will see.
In one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time,
In one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, I will see.
I saw time around your feet once, when you see the blink of an eye, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time,
in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time. in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in one time, in another one time, in one time, in two time, in one time, in one time,
was actually the garage and the other parts were in the new gear the professional audio
workstation AW 16G which hopefully will let me post this.
If it's accessible this will be my new road kit for sure because it's just about the
right size to take a long on the road.
Okay time right now is 715 going to have some dinner then plenty more to do including
the pod finder for tomorrow so we'll find that on iTunes in the morning again don't
forget to look out for the inside man podcast or Spike Lee that should also be out
tomorrow I think you really like that episode 4 of 5 or 4 or 4 and 5 or 4 of
you next week.
And if it's great calm is where you can send your feedback audio feedback is
also welcome please don't attach any more files when you send them to me because
it's yeah Gmail 99% you know it does grow every single day but it's only like one or
two megabytes it's not enough to keep up with all those attachments and looking
for your promos because we are using them all over the place on the pod show on
serious use them in the pod finder podcast and of course here on the daily source
code send it off to submit at podshow.com if you got pod save music head on over to the
pod save music network that's pod save music network.com or music.podshow.com and
mashups you can definitely send those off to mashup at podshow.com don't forget to
cast your vote to podcast alley that's for this podcast but it's funny when you
might happen to like it all right i'll see you tomorrow where we will continue
tweaking the new equipment on the daily source code.