16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
radio content in my ears, I like to think I'm flying into the future.
From home, don't share a Charlie 3-0-3
Was it hard?
Was it hard to find?
That the notes, that the notes, a your mind, did you take control
With the eyes that you broke, wasn't so hard, good to lose
As a deal, wearing shining new shoes, you said
Was it so hard?
Was it hard?
Did you break it to?
Was it hard to you?
Did you want?
Right to, keep your steps, follow it through
Was it so hard?
Good to lose
As a deal, wearing all the new shoes, you said
Was it so hard?
I'm not afraid of the clothes you wear.
I'm not afraid to join in your mode.
I got the feeling that you won't come around, baby.
I got the feeling that you won't.
Was it so hard?
Selected for your listening enjoyment.
By the daily source code, HotSafe is a network personal shoppers.
Let's leave the echo delta, drop the A for extra assumption.
Was it hard to title that?
Like that very much.
This is exactly the way it should be working.
People sending me suggestions for songs to play off of the Podsake Music Network.
Exactly the way.
Remember, I'm going to write a little letter.
I'm going to send it to my local DJ.
That's what we need listeners.
We need your help.
That's from the Podsake Music Network.
How are you doing?
It's Thursday coming to you from the cottage.
It may be Friday or the weekend, wherever you are.
I didn't do a show yesterday.
I was visiting my mom.
Talk a little bit about that.
I'll see some promos, of course.
Some classic audio on the way from Al Johnson.
We're going to talk a bit about, well, we'll talk about our Metro Sexual Stuff.
I'm about shaving a couple more Podsafe tunes, including a Christmas tune on the way.
I'm having a Trinity and biodiesel talk for tomorrow's show, I guess, along with some blank
media stuff that I've been collecting.
I've been using Omni Outliner on the Mac.
I don't know if you're familiar with that, but it's an outlining program.
It's really convenient for putting my shows together.
Because, you know, my show basically starts at the top and ends at the bottom of the list.
And as I go along, sometimes find myself changing stuff, moving stuff around.
It kind of corresponds with what I'm doing in Megasag, although there's a lot of manual
intervention there, keeping both lists synchronized.
Oh, man.
Wouldn't it be nice if Megasag could import my Omni Outliner file?
Oh, my goodness.
That would be fucking awesome.
Anyway, it's cool because you can basically drag and drop MP3s into it.
Bookmarks for URLs, all this stuff, and it just becomes my console, if you will.
Do you hear that?
I got a, that's the radiator now.
Yeah, at first I thought it was Roger Smalls going through my trash again.
But no, it turns out the radiator at this point has so much air in it that it sounds
like someone's dragging a milk cart in the cross, the pavement out in front of the cottage.
A lot of racking.
I got to find the key to let the air out.
So yesterday, whoa, big, big, big, big day.
Went to see my mom, who, first of all, thank you all so much for all the wonderful emails
that you've sent me emails of support, encouragement of hope of prayer.
It's really, really appreciated.
And I mean, I, I've tried to respond, I started this morning, started to respond to,
to just about everyone who sent something in, there's so much.
I'm sorry if I missed yours, but I really appreciated this.
Well, we'll get to the whole cancer thing in a moment.
Let me take the day step by step because it was quite a, quite a rollercoaster ride,
actually.
First of all, the wind commander stayed overnight, so we had an early start.
Well, when you have two women in the house, an early start is basically leaving within 30 minutes of your estimated time with the part show.
You're doing pretty good.
We drove off to the, to Farrow, to the airport.
We were there around, I wanted to be there around 830.
We're there on 9 o'clock.
So I got everything.
We were already pre-fueled.
Everything was ready to go.
I just went up the tower to make sure we had everything all set.
And our flight plan was filed.
Also just to say hi, you know, it's a small local airfield to kind of drop in and be social for a couple of minutes.
And then we took off.
It wasn't a, it wasn't a brilliant day, but flying at what we do.
We were around 3,000 feet was nice between broken clouds above us around four and a half thousand feet and a cloud cover below us.
Now, I don't have an instrument rating.
I am training from an instrument rating.
So we do a lot of work in, in the plane on these types of flights, the wind commander and I.
And he gives me all kinds of stuff to do.
And now we're not flying on a visual GPS, you know, with a nice screen or anything.
None of that stuff is, I do have a GPS, but it's a very, very basic system.
Just basically with a text read out.
But most of the training that you do for instruments is, well, guess what, flying on instruments, which includes tuning in,
VORs.
So you can basically vector where you are and being able to hold altitude and, and your direction while essentially being in complete cloud cover, which is a very weird sensation.
I mean, that's really, we've talked about this before.
They call it kind of the leans.
Well, you'll be flying.
And if you look outside and, of course, you see nothing but white around you.
You know that you're moving, but you can't see anything.
It becomes like a, a really interesting Disney type park ride.
And you'll think, well, wait a minute, the plane is going right and I should be, you know, and you, your body almost starts leaning left or vice versa.
And you want to turn and then you look at your instruments and you see that the attitude of the airplane is doing something completely different than what you thought it was doing.
Now, we have an autopilot in the machine, but when you're doing these exercises, really, you know, doing it all by hand is what it's about.
So, mostly it was all clear smooth sailing until we got up to Rotterdam where the, the cover was at like 600 feet.
So it was a complete IFR approach instrument flying rules, which I did by hand.
And at the same time, it had kind of a panic-stricken passenger in the back, Christina started to freak out because,
well, both the girls had elected not to wear headsets.
And I think that when you're not hearing what's going on and you're not seeing anything because you look out, you know,
and it's like, you know, think about me having the, the leans, how about the passengers who aren't used to it.
Because you can, not only can you see out the, the left and the right hand side, you can look out in front,
that's something you can't do on a jetliner.
So it's very confusing, Christina was definitely, you know, uneasy, which made me, of course, all that more uneasy.
But, you know, we've vectored all the way down and it was, it was awesome.
I mean, doing it by hand, there's, whoo, there's a lot to it.
Along with the GPS that slaves to the autopilot, I say, but fun to do, really, really fun to just drop out of the clouds and all of a sudden,
boom, there it is, right at AM Airport, right in front of you.
And it's, and that's nicely lit.
It's a huge airport where, you know, big jets come in.
Not 747s, but, you know, vacation like 727s, I think 737s can make it in.
Nice long runway, and so, you know, that was really good.
And completed the landing and went into the jet center, because you can't just land at the airport anymore.
You have to have a handling agent.
So it costs like a 300 bucks to fucking be handled.
Which means they pick you up from your plane with an umbrella, take you into where you pay,
and then shut it out the back.
And if you want, you can get a cup of coffee, big deal.
But didn't nice enough folks there.
So then we went to my mom's house.
It was exactly one year ago this week that I was in Utrecht,
for just before and just after the holidays,
where my mom was scheduled to have a lung removed,
due to lung cancer.
And this was all podcasts back in the day.
Those of you who are just tuning into the daily source code,
and I was podcasting from the hotel room.
It was a weird, a very weird Christmas.
And she survived.
You know, of the 15% of people who survived that,
and are declared cancer-free, she made it.
But throughout the year, she's had another flare-up,
but not in her, quote, crucial organs, but in on her side,
tumor, which was removed.
And now there's some more cell activity going on there.
And if anything, it's fear.
You know, that's what's really freaking everybody out.
It's the unknown.
It's not knowing what we're at.
What we're up against.
And I must say, having all the emails to support really,
really helps.
You feel all of a sudden you feel a lot less alone.
And you also realize how big this problem is.
It's so fucking medieval.
That's what struck me this morning when I woke up is,
you know, to see someone sick,
but actually, you know,
I want to use the word wilting away,
but you can see it.
It's literally eating at you.
And it's like medieval, man.
It's like the, you know,
with all the technology we have,
it's seen so unbelievable that you,
there's no fucking magic pill or something.
And you know, this is really the only case
in our immediate family and friend, you know,
surroundings that we've witnessed this.
And of course, it to be this close is a major bummer.
But, you know, mom's positive.
She really is, but she's really afraid.
And she's tired of it.
You know, she's tired of this fighting the whole year.
And now it just has to continue.
So my sisters and I are,
you know, going to go at it full speed.
Going to support her.
And unfortunately, Tiffany,
my oldest sister who was two years younger than I am.
She lives in Holland.
So she, of course,
is the closest in proximity.
Willow, my younger sister,
who was four years younger than I.
She lives in Italy.
So, um,
now, of course, I'm shuddling back and forth
between here in San Francisco.
So I'm pretty sure that we're going to get
our instrument rating very quickly.
So that when I am back here,
I can just make quick day trips to go and see,
see mom.
Because the broader my airport is really,
it's very conveniently located
to where she lives.
Only half hour by cab.
And actually, we called taxi Eric.
Tea to the E to come pick us up.
And he was there last year when my mom
in the hospital.
So it was a good, good hang.
We had fun.
We laughed.
My sister came down.
So that was a lot of fun.
And Bob, my mom's a new husband.
She got married to a couple of years ago.
Yeah, he, of course, took the day off.
And it was really good.
It was just a couple hours.
But it was, you know,
enough to really raise her spirits.
And so that was cool.
So humbled by all of that.
Back to the airport.
And I wanted to make it back before dark.
Now, of course, we were running a little late.
Now, this was not a problem.
Even though the wind commander couldn't come with me.
We had Roy, who is actually my IFR instrument instructor.
And I'd never flown with Roy before.
You know, we'd done all kinds of other ground classes together.
But he is the absolute king of instrument flying
in the Netherlands and Belgium.
He's just awesome.
He's raided on everything, can fly everything.
And he's a nerd.
He works like Ericsson or something, doing something really high-tech on the mobile networks.
I'm not quite sure.
But, you know, he's got a flight sim at home with multi-screens.
So we flew home.
It was beautiful.
It was, you know, the sun was, we were flying into the sunset,
if you will.
You know, just trying to basically catch up with the sun
as it was setting.
It was so smooth sailing.
It was like we were on a cable car almost.
It was so beautiful.
Could trim the plane, you know, perfectly hands off
most of the time, just looking at the surroundings,
talking with Roy about stuff.
So it was great.
By the time we reached the coast of Dover though,
the sun had set and it was about four PM local time.
And we knew we're going to be making an approach in the dark,
which neither of us had ever done at Ferrox,
which has a reasonably short strip, actually.
And although they're open until six,
and they do have the runway lit.
I think there's a difference between a runway that's lit,
you know, like having seen Rotterdam airport with the center line
is a row of lights and there's just lights everywhere.
You know, it's a beautiful sight.
We actually passed over the airport once
because we couldn't even see it.
Then we saw the runway.
And it was like there had some street lights on,
casting some kind of glow onto it.
But, you know, no center line,
just basically two rows of white lights
and land in the between there somewhere, if you don't mind.
And all of a sudden there was a lot of activity
there were people doing touching goes
and the dark people coming in who were kind of doing the same thing
that we were doing.
I would say probably one of the most dangerous times
at a small airfield or maybe any airfield
is around this time when people are kind of rushing to get home
or maybe they just got caught in the dark.
Now the experience, we had the experience on board,
so I was not worried at all.
But we did, so we actually did one go around
as, you know, we were like,
stirred in row for landing
and the guy right in front of us really
was slow getting in.
We were much, you know, much faster aircraft
and we were hanging everything out
to slow us down, gear down,
flaps down, everything.
And so we actually had to go around
because he wasn't getting off the runway fast enough.
So, you know, did another pass.
That was actually good because then I got
a lot better feel for the situation
of where I was and I could actually recall now
because of course I've done landings there.
You know, what the base and the final leg
should feel like still came in high.
Which is really cool because even though
the runway is lit like shit
and the basic principle of two red,
your dead, two white, your two high
and the white and red, you know,
it's just red and white is just right
or whatever the, whatever way you're supposed to remember that.
So I could pick up the glide path.
But we were going definitely doing 80 knots
that was too fast, put in full flaps
and you know, really when you do full flaps on an aircraft
like that, it becomes a whole different type of machine
and it's almost like you're, you're batman wings
have inflated and you're kind of coasting down
but add to that the depth perception.
We definitely landed about almost halfway
up the runway which, you know,
at the speed we had was really too fast
and the amount of runway we had left.
In fact, I said to Roy, I said, dude,
we're going to run out of runway
and we both started working the brakes
and, you know, that was a tense moment.
It definitely got a little bit exciting there
with, you know, wheels locking up
which of course completely ruins the tires
and you two new tires now but we stopped
before the end of the runway
but it was, it was one of those experiences
that you're glad you had someone really experienced
next to you so that you know
that you're not just an idiot but this is,
I would also sometimes go, I don't know.
I was like, ah, okay, we're back.
So the whole day really drained completely
and so that's why I didn't do a show yesterday.
Anyway, so only positive vibes, ladies and gentlemen,
that's the best thing we've got going for us.
Just a couple more things that I wanted to hit on here
I found, or actually I got a link to a video,
a piece of video from the Hawaiian Association of podcasters
who just had a meeting the other day up
and I don't know where in Hawaii
and it's really cool because the video,
you know, some of the people are talking
and they met at this great restaurant, great food
and they had that all in video
but really what was cool is they were talking about
how they felt to me like is that the podcasters
and Hawaii, you know, finally they're able to free themselves
and spread some of their culture,
which is there is a definite culture happening in Hawaii,
you know, local news, local music
and they're able to spread that around now, you know,
because, you know, really there was no economic model
particularly on the cost side
to get that stuff out.
And it's really nice to see that and I think
we're going to see more of these really locations
that just because the economic model of installing
broadcasting for structure
would never allow that culture to flow out
now that's starting to happen, you know,
I can't wait to see that happen, for example,
in Jamaica, that's going to be freaking awesome.
Thank you all very much for answering my questions
about the television series Lost.
This is low in calling it in from Fresno, California,
home with us, no more podcasters,
no more.lipsen.com.
Just want to let you know from one loss
to another that the show is on hiatus,
like a lot of other TV shows to line up for May sweeps.
It definitely sucks, but that's how
network television people do it.
Maybe when TV shows become podcast,
only we won't have to deal with this kind of junk.
Don't fret, though,
we're only halfway through the series,
so once the hiatus is over with,
they say January 11th,
there should be about 15 more episodes
give or take.
Anyway, just wanted to help a fellow lost out of count.
Love the source code, listen every day,
it's like opening up a Christmas gift five days a week.
Catch you later.
Thank you.
For as Matt Snowgrass would say, Adam,
come on, man, you were in the TV biz.
You know that they're on break of new episodes,
fall like November sweeps.
They'll probably tease you with some new episodes in late January,
and then back full time for February sweeps.
This is also, so the networks can put
out the midseason replacements.
Yeah, of course, during this time.
What are the midseason replacements this year?
I've not been following that at all,
but I definitely missed loss.
It just goes to show that, you know,
what an opportunity here to attach or to first
make the episodes of lost for pay.
That's fine.
Make it a podcast, so I, you know,
it'll just show up.
And if you know this is going to be a two or three week hiatus,
put some melts in there,
put something cool in the feed to tide me over, you know?
God, the needle's in, you pull it out,
you're going to gem it back in.
That really sucks.
Hey, man,
we don't stop at Christmas time.
Shoot.
I mean, I wanted to do this.
Unfortunately, it doesn't work on UK cell phones,
and I only have UK Skype in numbers.
But someone sent me this link.
I'll figure out how to put that together for tomorrow's show.
It'll be great.
Where you can get a phone call from Sir Richard Branson,
which is completely assembled audio based upon what you,
what you entered.
It's really only for travel agents.
And it's kind of like an incentive call from Sir Richard,
and the someone sent it to me,
and I was like, oh, it's interesting.
So I filled out my US cell number,
and low and behold,
then like four minutes at rang,
and it was Sir Richard Branson with a personalized message from me.
I want to get that rolling for tomorrow.
It's just that I don't have telephone recording equipment.
I can do it through Skype,
but you couldn't enter anything but a US phone number.
So let that be a tease for you for tomorrow's
thank God it's Friday edition.
I just wanted to mention some things that are happening on Sirius.
This is pretty much this stuff couldn't happen
on any other venue than satellite radio.
Sirius is a press release that I got from at least Brown,
who's also our press contact over there.
She says that Sirius satellite radio
will broadcast Christmas masses live
from St. Patrick's Cathedral in New York.
And what I like about this is,
you know, there's obviously there's no commercial model,
which is why I don't think any terrestrial radio broadcasts
amass, certainly not in, well,
I'm not 100% sure,
but I don't think they're doing that in New York.
You know, the time has just become so incredibly
precious and every single minute has to be sold.
And here's Sirius who has arguably enough bandwidth
and they're just, what channel are they doing it on?
Let me see.
Sirius Channel 86, what is that normally?
Certainly they have something.
I wonder what channel 86,
maybe that's just one of those channels that's kind of empty.
Anyway, if you're listening to this podcast on Sirius satellite radio,
you've heard me say this before.
We've got a, like a 24 minute and 30 second window
and we're about to close that.
So that we can get on with all the real cool stuff, right?
Which you guys got to tune out.
The podcast continues.
So Pacific Coast,
Hellway is next followed by yeast radio,
followed by Dawn and Drew,
and we take it on up until 10 o'clock with some pod safe,
pod safe music as well.
Still to come here on the podcast.
As I said, we've got some rare audio of Al Jol,
John's, wait, Al Jolson.
Why did I say Jolson? Al Jolson.
And some history there, which particularly this holiday season,
you might be interested in.
We're going to talk a little bit about some more shave.
It's unbelievable.
It's not, I also, I'm the epicenter for all things shaving,
but it seems like there's a lot of different information
and thoughts and theories on what gives you the best,
the closest and the most valuable shave.
And it's not necessarily what the company,
what the shaving kit manufacturers are telling us.
And we've also got two new pod safe music tunes coming up on the way.
So that's, that's still to come.
Man, I'm really beat today.
I feel so incredibly tired.
All right, everybody, do what,
we're going to do the same thing we do every single day around this time.
Raise your right hand.
If you're in traffic, hold on to the steering wheel with your left.
Okay.
And wave goodbye to all those satellite listeners,
so we can get on with the podcast.
Bye, everybody.
We'll see you tomorrow on the Friday show.
And for you, I got some cool shit you can listen to on your own time.
The scenes that show commentary, stories,
using an observation from Ross and Karen.
The sarcastic American and a rye Canadian
joined us in cross border, match and money.
We have friends.
We've got to burn my butt.
What?
I don't like the way that sounds.
Toronto, my hometown, which I miss and loves.
Can we have your hair?
We've got to be sick in him and he's disappointed in us.
I swear like a longshoreman at a hook or convention.
You're just going to show up in his grave and drop trout and let it go.
Just raw meat creep you out.
Ross and I shut up.
You drink wine out of a box and all of a sudden you have standards.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Would you sign my wood?
I'm very much an 80m difference.
Oh my god.
Well, what's our damage?
Well.
And there you go.
That's why we love Target.
Yet again.
And we're not sponsored by Target.
No.
Am I the only one or is Bob the builder kind of pornographic?
I like the Union suit.
I think it's cool.
Well, by the time the cops got out of Tim Horton's and made it to our door.
The ZNZ show.
We're not carrying cancer here.
We're just podcasting.
What do you want for nothing?
ZNZ.blogspot.com.
Beyond Science Podcast.
Dot com.
Species exploration.
The European Space Agency sent some light guns in the space.
It didn't kill him.
There are no more phenomena.
It's called the coming great dissension or the Luciferian angien.
Nanotechnology.
And carbon nanofibers or nanotubes.
Make a cable that can literally reach tens of thousands of miles.
Alienly.
Obduction.
The alien gospel simply this.
That way the aliens are your progenitors.
Journey into the unknown.
Travel through time.
The past.
The future.
Unleash your mind.
Beyond Science.
Beyond Science Podcast.
Dot com.
Hello.
Can anyone hear me?
This is Captain Corval of the United Defense Force.
My ship's been disabled and I'm adrift in the shadow of one of Neptune's moons.
If anyone is receiving this transmission, please get it to UDF command.
In front of presence of tar-that invasion forces, currently inbound to the homeworld.
And they are not tipped towing in.
Their ships number in the hundreds.
And they're impossibly huge.
I don't think you're coming to shake hands people.
They're loaded to take us out.
Our homeworld is in ruins.
Our future is in doubt.
This will be a battle unlike any in our history.
And it's outcome will decide who are the chosen ones.
We are all children of creation.
But which of us are the children of the gods?
Join the fight for survival and children of the gods.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
We are a flank.
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We're a Earthling.
We believe your personal information should be just that, personal.
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We're a flank.
Make this smart choice.
Visit earthlink.net and discover what our internet experts can do for you.
Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
Okay, so I don't have a partner on my show where I talk about our sex lives.
I haven't taken a dump and talked about it.
I haven't dumped in my tank to get my car to run.
I haven't put my grandma on her tank.
I haven't talked about how I'm going to shave tomorrow.
But I have talked to many great independent musicians in southwest Ohio.
Where they talk about their songs, their music, and what it takes to get their stuff.
To get their stuff to you.
Join us on the Miami Valley Musiccast.
MiamiValleyMusiccast.com.
And our promos are under 30 seconds.
Excellent rich thanks.
Hey, about that Earthling spot.
Oops, when I just got, oh, hold on a second.
That's so crystal.
Almost second.
And then show.
I don't have to do them.
Belly.
That's my PA, my Dutch PA, who now lives in Switzerland.
And we had a talk scheduled for today.
Okay.
Go a crystal.
Great. Thank you.
About the Earthling spot.
Now, I personally think we're under such an, yes, crystal.
Okay.
I personally think we're under something really important here.
It's something really good as we work on changing what advertising means.
I have three different user-generated commercials about Earthling.
People who actually like their service or have used their service in the past.
And I really want to use those instead of the cookie cutter, like 30 second commercial.
And unfortunately, now with Christmas time is very hard to get a hold of people.
But I am really working on, I'm getting together with this, with this advertiser
and talking to them about the possibilities and hopefully being able to, you know,
get some trials going and track some of this stuff.
And I do believe that it's much more powerful to have your customers make your commercials
than it is for you to make the commercials.
It's just a thought, you know, by the way, even though they were completely produced.
That's what Apple did with their, what is it with their switch commercials or whatever.
And you know what, so people start to parry to them, too.
That's great.
Anyway, so I'm working on that, just so you know.
There was one, there was a promo that didn't get, didn't get into that lineup for some reason.
Actually, I know why because I put it in the wrong place.
But this is something that we talked about the other day on the source code.
And already there's a promo ready to roll.
I think that it's a piece of art that you're going to like to listen to this Christmas.
Hey, everybody.
This is the seed of Chris daily.
I want to welcome you to the feed for the upcoming podcast Christmas Carol.
I have come in.
Oh, shut up.
Oh, man.
I really messed that up.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to say shut up.
But I just got really frustrated.
Okay.
That was the seed.
We don't want the damn seed.
Where is it?
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
I'm never going to be able to find this.
It's the, what I'm looking for here is the podcast Christmas Carol.
Maybe I can, I shouldn't have subscribed to that feed and iTunes.
Oh, here it is.
Podcast Christmas Carol.
Don't tell me.
I have to.
Isn't that the one?
Is that exactly what I just played?
Let me try it.
Hold on.
Hey, everybody.
This shit.
Maybe it comes later on.
I don't know.
This is what it gives story.
We have final to cast.
Blow me.
Okay.
Let me go look for that.
I want to play a song.
And while that's playing, I'll go look and see if I can find the right
audience.
It was a great fucking promo too.
I can't believe that.
I'm just placed it.
Wait a minute.
Let me check over here.
Shit.
Okay.
I don't want to take up any more of your time.
An email that came to me from my partner and co-founder Ron Bloom.
Turns out, well, let me read the, what he sent to me.
Al Jolson, the star of the first talking movie or talkie was a famous and infamous
artist.
I don't know if he can be famous and infamous at the same time.
He was originally a canter and then became a Vaudeville pop singer and starred in the first
talking picture of the jazz singer.
He's a bit of history for you.
Now, it turns out that Al Jolson is Ron's cousin on his mom's side.
And she circulated an email, bless her heart.
She circulated an email with a file to a whole bunch of members of the Bloom family.
This is where he sings the Israeli National Anthem.
As Ron writes, he was later also ostracized for being a white person, quote, in parentheses
a Jew, playing a black person in black face.
So Ron thought it might be interesting to give the suspense going along with the following
article, so that he encloses article from the American film Institute about the jazz singer.
And it really is a fascinating story.
What's really fascinating is the change that the industry underwent.
And actually the movie studios tried to build a cartel to check this out, to lock people
into certain sound formats so that they really had a doopily on talking movies.
And how people laughed and said it would never happen.
And it wasn't worth it and people weren't interested.
That's just fascinating reading.
So if we can't get a link to wherever that information is from, I'll drop the whole piece
into the show notes.
And again, can I just thank everybody for maintaining those show notes, man.
Wiki's really do rule in some cases.
So check this out.
It's some pretty rare audio.
It's about three minutes of Al Jolson singing the Israeli National Anthem.
Hello.
Oh.
I am pardon me, I am pardonable,
I am pardonable, I am pardonable.
I am pardonable, I am pardonable,
I am pardonable,
pardonable,