Delta CR-Charlie 2-0-2 Something remarkable is happening here Radio is springing free
of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear since radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
I'll be my wife checking in, I'll hold on a second.
Hello.
Yeah.
I'm in the middle of the show, how are you?
Hello.
Jesus.
Here's me.
Here.
Don't worry.
Whoo.
He's going away.
Don't worry.
Yeah.
I'm strong.
Don't worry.
Hmm.
There we go.
Where was I?
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
There's been the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need us.
Thinking crazy.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Fantastic.
Yes.
I'm curious.
Hey everybody, it is July 3rd.
This is your daily source code.
Hello.
Yeah, it's been a while.
But we're back.
Oh, my goodness.
I do apologize for the radio silence.
Or should we say the pod silence?
It's been a crazy ass week.
I've got lots to talk about.
Let's call this the catchup podcast.
Your daily source code, which light there are 2005.
Oh.
It's got mashups.
Got, uh, pod safe tunes.
Got plenty of promos and plenty of stuff to talk about.
I mean, Miami right now.
Or actually, it's still officially say it's South Beach.
Miami Beach, FLA.
Sitting in the lovely Lowe's hotel.
It's a never state app before, but it's actually quite nice.
And outside, it's about 152 degrees.
It's crazy.
The time now is 1015, local time, PM.
It is the eve of July 4th.
It's Sunday night.
And we got a pod cast going on.
The last time we spoke was a dating source code episode 201.
And man has a lot happened.
The iTunes launch would be the top of the list.
iTunes, of course, featuring pod casting.
It has really opened up the tremendous amount of opportunity.
A tremendous amount of discussion and shit loads of bandwidth.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to tell you about some of the things we've been doing regarding the bandwidth.
And lots of cool fun.
So I've got some stuff lined up for you.
This is brought to you by Cast Blaster.
We're talking about that as well.
The public beta now officially released.
And I wanted to start it off with a mashup.
It's DJBC who has been doing some awesome mashups and submitting them to us.
This is his crazy 80s.
Of course, that would start off with a little bit of dire strain.
We're talking about some of the things we've been doing.
Fantastic.
I could tell you that DJBC, I don't know what he's doing.
If he's doing drugs he better share some of that because he's got some great stuff going on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm gonna steal it, I'm gonna do it, I'm gonna go
But you're going to want me, but you don't say no
to me
you hear me, this my old friend
does pick up all the floor
you're going to take your yıl
just search the dead
yeah
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey hey, hey, hey, hey, hey hey, hey
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Let me stay with you like a lover's boys
For the mountain side
Stay in the light
In the big country
Let me stay right here
We've got the lover's boys
Let me stay in the light
Let me stay right here
Mighty New Year mythin'ора on the free knee
I hear a rainbow here is a me chance
I got silly reform to set a shit
It's all you're suffering from the day
Easy to feel like a fool
Here we can ask for water, we can leave y'all mad.
We can ask for water, we can all y'all like the mine.
As long as we have the hell of a loser never think of a hell of a fight.
I see you, we can ask for water, we can leave y'all mad.
We can ask for water, we can all y'all like the mine.
We can ask for water, we can all y'all mad.
We can all y'all mad.
Oh man, DJBC is out of his mind. Crazy 80s. That was probably more a mega mix than a mashup,
but I loved it so much during all those tunes one after another. It's really, really cool. Nice to hear
my bit in there from, well I mustn't have a couple weeks ago when I played a DJBC mashup,
so let's definitely hand out a Boeing to DJBC. My goodness, okay, let's just bring it down a
notch or two. Let me rewind to, and by the way you can hear the air conditioner rolling in the
background, which is very necessary right now. It literally is like 110 degrees. It's cool down now,
as I said, it's like, well, after that DJBC mix, we're 10, 25. So I flew in from,
came from Portland, so let me back up, you know, this whole, well you probably wrote
on my weblog by now, and that I got my, my PPL, my private pilot license for fixed wing.
I kind of did it backwards, where I started off with helicopter. I've had a helicopter license
for two years, and have flown 700 or 800 hours on helicopters. And most people, you know, go for
fixed wing license first, so regular airplane, and then go to helicopter kind of as an add-on, so
I did it in the reverse manner. And this is something that had been planned for, oh God,
eight or nine, at least six months, we're probably closer to eight months, that we go to Portland.
We do a couple days of, you know, training on a Sessner 172, which is the four-seater
150 horsepower, single-engine light airplane, and I basically been training on the Sessner 182RG.
We know what that stands for, don't we? Yes indeed, you're tractable gear. And I just felt,
you know, as things were drawing me, I didn't know that the things would heat up, and
podger would heat up, and that the iTunes launch would be right upon us. I didn't know any of that
stuff, of course, when I booked this entire trip. And as that all junior and drew closer together,
and I knew, and I couldn't talk about it, because we were sworn as secrecy, which I think
it's unfortunate. I couldn't talk about the release. I knew that it was going to be on the 28th,
but I'd promise not to tell anyone, because Apple wanted to do a big launch, a big surprise launch.
In hindsight, I think it would have been better for everybody if we had kind of known about it,
because the deal was, and this is something that I had agreed with Steve Jobs, I would create,
you know, this pod finder podcast, which you're probably seeing now in iTunes,
which will be a weekly feature. We're leaving it on for about, you know, up until next week,
I guess, because so many people still have to upgrade, and you know, slowly all the new iTunes versions
are coming online, and the whole intention of this of the pod finder podcast is to kind of be like,
I modeled it quite honestly after a bit after talk soup. Remember that talk soup? The red
canier was doing on E, not so much the dry humor, because I don't have any of his humor. I think
the gray canier can be a very funny guy in a very cynical way, and of course, he's a great actor,
it turns out. But when he's doing talk soup, you know, you talk about what was on a show,
and then play a clip, and so that's exactly what I want to do with this and try to highlight
anywhere from 15 to 20 pod casts a week, and the deal that we made was that, okay, what we'll do
is we'll feature all these podcasts in the 30 to 40 minutes show, definitely don't want to go
over 40 minutes. We know that's a great time, you know, for a complete podcast. And thinking that
the way it would work, and of course, the way it does work is when you're looking at it in iTunes,
the artwork chains will change as long with each podcast I'm talking about, you click on it,
and then you can go to that page within iTunes, and then preview the show if you want to or
subscribe to it directly. And so, you know, we approached everybody that I wanted to feature,
you know, everything from the GM podcast to father, road-rick to a couple of our own pod shows,
so just, you know, all kinds of stuff in there, and we approached everyone and said, look, you know,
we want to feature you, but we're thinking that the bandwidth is going to be a pretty big deal,
so we have to help you out, and we'll, you know, put your shows on a on a server temporarily,
and we had come up with a agreement that at least for the first six weeks, while, you know,
we don't have a content or didn't have a content delivery network, or certainly just about
had enough bandwidth for the pod show, for the pod squad, that Apple would optimize them,
so that they would have a guaranteed delivery, and would be a good experience for everybody,
and that kind of got messed up through no, you know, just through a whole bunch of circumstances,
so we got caught with our pants down when the new iTunes was released, and everybody,
and the grandma started trying to get the pod gas off of our server, was just when my
collapsed almost immediately, we couldn't even if we tried to restart it, it would come up,
and a million hits and requests were becoming in simultaneously, so it would just freeze,
you know, we couldn't do anything, so we were scrambling, and, and this was happening,
it exactly the same time when I was, you know, supposed to be training for my flight,
and the only way to get my pilot's license was to train incessantly and just go add it over and
over and over again, I think I flew in, in four days time, I must have done about 15 hours worth
of pure hardcore training, and actually by the second day, it all clicked, it all clicked
to my head and just like, you know, like I am in a car or in a helicopter, I had total control,
it felt good, and then it was just a matter of getting the experience and just going through
procedures, really, is what it is, because once you can fly an airplane, it's pretty amazing,
it's not that hard, it really isn't, you have to, you know, there's a lot of stuff that has to be
just automatic, you know, particularly emergency procedures, and so all this was going on,
I really had to focus on it, boom, you know, iTunes is exploding, and luckily we have,
we have a couple of people working for us now, which is great, Brian Longus, that was doing most of the
work, and my God, poor guy, he just had his third kid, he's moving to a new house, and he was,
he has been doing all the infrastructure stuff for us, so, you know, he had to get servers in,
and the secondary and tertiary, 100 megabit pipes, and setting up stuff with Akamai at the same time,
just a handle of a load, and so it was really nasty for about two or three days there, and it seems
to have, we have a handle on it, we have a control on it, so the, the podcasts are now downloading,
and the sites are up and running again, and it was just, what a surprise, I mean also,
we had worked with Chris McIntyre podcast Ali to make sure that basically anything,
anyone who's registered with podcast Ali would automatically have an iTunes feed that you could then
use to submit into iTunes if you weren't in the directory, and, of course, we met our directory
available, just so much stuff, and, you know, it's going to take another few weeks to shake everything
out, and the directories, you know, it's, we need some cleanup, you know, so we're working on all
that now as we speak, so it was just the timing could not have been worse, but I was so happy
that everybody basically covered for me, and just let me go and do my thing, which I really,
really appreciate, because I'm no scholar, I, you know, I went to college for exactly 2.7 months
and learning anything for me is, you know, particularly when it comes to the book work, and if you
look at the, you know, the stuff you have to know, there's some, some real learning that has to
take place there, and it was just, it was cool to be able to do it, and man, when I do something,
I like to take it all the way, so hey, I'm really excited, and as I want to thank Frank Harlow,
of course, who was our instructor at Willamette Aviation in Portland, also want to thank John
Strauss, who did the mock check ride, boy, he really put me through the ringer, so essentially,
you know, before you get your real check ride with the official FAA examiner, then, you know,
you go up and you get a pretend test, oh boy, you know, all kinds of wacky shit, at the put on
something they call foggles, which essentially gives you only a view of your instrument panel,
so if you should run into real inclement weather, it's kind of a precursor to your instrument flying,
which is a whole other add-on to the license, which of course I do want to get, but, you know,
let's fly a little bit in the, in a nice weather first off, emergency procedures, you know,
all that stuff, and you know, really have to know all the systems in the aircraft and know a lot
about the aerodynamics, and then the FAA examiner came up, and, you know, coming from a country
where the, or from the continent, basically, in Europe, where you either have the CAA and the UK,
or you have the, the RLD, which is now the I, what is it, what are they, the, uh, for Kirswantza,
I can't remember, uh, whoever the FAA is, and that one's I'm spacing on it for a second, you know,
those guys are really hard noses, and they come in with their, you know, the three-piece suits,
and, you know, this guy Lee, he was, he was just fucking cool man, you know, he came in,
and he asked me all the questions, but he made me feel really at home, and, you know, comfortable,
and it turns out he'd been to Woodstock, the first Woodstock, so we chatted about that,
and, uh, so we went up to the check ride, it wasn't by far, uh, the best flying I've done,
it's certainly, my landings didn't deserve any beauty prize, but that's kind of what you,
what you can expect, you know, it never is your best flying your check ride, um, and, uh,
but it was great, you know, so I got my ad on, and I couldn't be happier, and it was cool,
um, I think at three o'clock, uh, we landed, and we're just finishing up the paperwork,
three, thirty Doug K, from IT Conversations called, you know, Doug and I flew from, uh,
from Seattle to San Francisco, and his bananas after nomdex, and he knew that I was doing the check
ride, he called me up and it was really sweet, and so he wanted to hard-gone, and it was, uh, it was cool.
So that, uh, was, oh, and of course, in Portland itself, um, I hooked up with Ken Clark,
who you've probably heard on the MTV Chronicles, if not, on the Ken and Squip Show, another fine podcast,
you'd want to check out, uh, Ken used to work at MTV for many, many years. He was my personal assistant,
then ran a major portion of the operations at, uh, at the previous company that Ron and I had called
thinking new ideas, um, and he's now, um, selling real estate in, uh, in Portland, and he's also an active
member of the Portland Podcast Association, and I really wish that I'd gone to the meeting,
which was on Thursday, last Thursday, which was also Ken's birthday, which of course I'd promptly
forgotten. Uh, so I do hope to come back again, spend some more time with Ken also go to the Portland
Podcast Association, because I was blown away. I was really, uh, importantly, it's beautiful, um,
the surroundings are beautiful, the people are beautiful. Uh, it's great to, you know, just to see
the scenery where you have Mount Hood, and then, of course, there's Mount St. Helens off in the distance,
and I really do plan on going back. If not for my instrument rating, definitely to go hang out,
so it was good seeing him again. It was kind of funny, um, with all this going on, I hadn't really
paid much attention to, uh, to live eight, and when I was at Ken's on, um, was it Saturday, uh,
he was going to take me to the airport, uh, I called home Patricia and Ken knows Patricia very well,
because he worked from, uh, office in our house for, uh, for a couple of years, and they're really
good friends, and so he was talking to her, and she said, oh, you're not watching live eight,
because, you know, of course he was in the UK, so she was watching a much earlier, and I got to tell you,
this may not be a very popular, uh, um, position that I have on this live aid, but it doesn't feel
right to me, you know, I think that, here's what I say, you know, the, the problems in Africa
are not just because it's warm, and, you know, it's a jungle, you know, there's, there's some
serious economic issues, and yes, this was awareness to get the, you know, the G8, the big eight,
to pay attention, and saying that we're not going to take it anymore, but I think that we have to,
you know, it somehow just felt like a big eighties reunion show to me, you know, and, and, you know,
maybe if, if half the people who performed wouldn't wear diamonds, you know, that would solve a big
portion of it, and, you know, I don't know, I just have very, very mixed feelings about about
benefit shows, and yes, it may make you, and I feel good to feel that we're doing something,
but I just really have to wonder how much we're really doing. It's not about money, you know,
it's about how money is spent, how it's appropriated, what happens with it, and also economics,
you know, what are the, what are the sanctions, what are the trade tariffs,
certain goods coming from, from African countries, and also you can't see it as one country,
you know, it's a whole mess of countries, a continent, there's a whole bunch of countries with
different leaders, and there's like many countries, there's lots of corruption, and, you know,
Shapoban hats off to Sir Bob, and everybody who did that, but, you know, I think that we really
have to make a political move, a very political move, you know, we can get Bob Gold off to be
president of some country, you know, then maybe, maybe we can, we can make a difference, but
as I said, you know, when I hear all this, you know, it's about, oh, it's a cool pink
Floyds reuniting, and the Spice Girls aren't new reuniting, and status quo can't get on the bill,
and who is on the bill, and I don't know, it's just, I got some mixed feelings about that, but
it doesn't matter. So, not a goodness, I have so much more to talk about, let me talk about
Casplaster for a second, because the same day that I did, daily source code episode 200 as the
closing keynote for nomdex, Casplaster, the public beta was released, you can go to castblaster.com.
This podcast is being recorded on Casplaster, as we speak. In fact, I even have the, an older
beta, which is, this I think is beta number 16 and beta 17 is the public one, and you're free to
use it, for as long as you want, as long as your podcast, I think, is an over 10 minutes,
that's the restriction we're putting on, and by the way, you do quite a podcast in 10 minutes,
and so I think that'll be, be freely available for as long as you want to use it, and if you want to
upgrade and buy the full version, which, of course, will also entitle you to the 1.0 release.
It's a 50 bucks, you can order it right online, and I'm getting a lot of great response,
people seem to really like it. I love it. I have my Mac here, and I don't have my regular setup.
When I'm at home, I like to have my compressor limiter, I've got my big honk and microphone,
I've got the preamps, I've got everything all set up, and then I use Megaseg to line up the show.
But on the road, just to get stuff going, you know, a cast blaster is great. I'm using the
lava layer microphone, but it has the built-in compressor limiter that we've talked about before,
and I'm really digging it. If you just want to make a podcast, create an MP3 file,
and actually you can configure it to automatically FTP it up to whatever server you choose.
I think it's a great product, and let's you do all the tags you need, the picture, your artwork
gets put in there. There's even a spot for show notes, and the next step, of course,
will be the connection to the pod show services so that when you hit publish, it actually creates
your show blog from your show notes and creates your podcast feed, which is an RSS 2.0
within closures. As the enclosure uploads everything and you're done, so that'll be the next version,
and you can look forward to that castblaster.com. Give me some feedback. Let me know what you think about it.
Okay, so by now, of course I'm trying to get home. I had to take two flights from Portland to
get to Miami. Ron is back in Miami. He was out in San Francisco for four weeks, the reason for
which we'll be able to make some damage announcements about, if not at the end of the week, the
beginning of next week, and we plan tomorrow, which will be July 4th, we'll do a strategy cast,
and we'll be together and we'll have some time, and we have done plenty of strategy. He was
living out of a suitcase that was packed for like five days, it was there for four weeks, so we've been
really going at it, and working hard, and it looks like we're going to set up pod show headquarters
in San Francisco, very excited about that, so I'll be rackin' up plenty of frequent flyer miles.
In fact, I was trying to get home, and really no flights available, as you can imagine for
today in tomorrow, so I was able to get a flight on Virgin Atlantic for the fifth, which was
a Tuesday, and it's funny because you can't pay for flights if you're in the States going anywhere
from the States to any other, well, if you're flying in the States, you cannot use a credit card
that has a building address that is outside of the U.S., which is a, quote, security measure,
to me, it's like fucking lame, so you have to take the extra fee of using the phone service,
and you don't get your 750 free miles for using the online service, but okay, so I'll live with
that. So I called up, and I talked to a nice young lady who helped me out with the reservation,
and at the end of the conversation said, I just have to ask you, you, the Adam Curry from MTV,
and I said, yeah, that would be the one, but that was a long time ago, she said, well, you know,
I'm old now. Yeah, indeed, thank you very much. She said, you know, I just got an iPod,
and I saw, you know, your podcast thing, your pod find your thing, and it looks really cool,
and I'm really excited about it. I was like, wow, you know, it's really spreading. The virus is a
spread. Hey there, I'm Big Rock, it's a measure of walkie-talkie for a moment. I'm not crashing
my editing software. Oh yeah, we got some pro action. Let me play another pro. I got a couple
of them here, so I just wanted to run through some stuff that I'd found. Let me see where's the other
one I wanted to play. It was this one. That's not the one. I'm sorry. It was this one.
Hey, this is Barry Coral, and I've got a new podcast, Call of Confessions of the New
New Girl, and I'm going to be talking about my cleaning record, Confessions of the New
Girl, and my novella of the same name. You can subscribe to it at BarryCoral.com. That's
B-A-R-I-K-O-R-A-L. Thanks for checking it out. Wow, we'll soften the volume there, Barry. Now, Barry Coral, of course,
we've played on the source code. We've played some of her pod safe music, BarryCoral.com,
and she now has a podcast. It's great. It's catching on. It really is. I think that there's some
stuff that we can do. There's a lot of discussion about how iTunes is doing podcast. I think we have
some cool hybrid things that we can do together. By the way, just so you know, there's a new version
of iPod Element, which is out, which is version 2.1. It's got a lot of awesome features
that you definitely need to check out. It's good to see that we have support from developers
on all sides of this. When I get back home, so that'll be Wednesday, so either probably Thursday,
I want to start talking about how we can use Bitcoin to solve a lot of these bandwidth issues,
because I saw so many podcasts go offline within two hours just because people have,
they've got accounts where you get x amount of gigabytes transferred per month as all kinds of
quotas, and you get a whole bunch of people. And by the way, subscriptions through the MF and roof.
I mean, it is just outrageous how many new listeners have come in. We talk about the 100 million
listener March. It is definitely, definitely on the move. So I think that, let me just tell you
the way I think it should work. And then hopefully, as I wade through the the shitloads of email that
I have, I now have officially 6,261 red messages. If you send something to me, you haven't heard
from me in like a week or two, you're going to have to send it again. That's going to be this
smartest thing. Unless, of course, it's an MP3 file for a podsafe, music, or a mashup, or a promo.
As always in the show notes where I link to anything that's been played or anything that we've
talked about, the email address is to send off your program is submit at podshow.com, podsafe
music tune instead of the podsafe at podshow.com and mashups off to mashup at podshow.com.
That also, by the way, is where you can submit to be on the serious show, which is going great guns
getting amazing feedback from from lots of serious satellite listeners. So there's another
area where you can promote your podcast, which actually will cost you no bandwidth at all.
Last get over to tardthumbs.com. He's at little tips and little tricks you're looking for.
Let me tell you something, Charlie George, he's going to tell y'all about these things.
He keeps up with gaming and gaming news and all things you want to know.
Charlie's going to talk to everybody and ask him what the little tips and tricks are that they know.
If it's actually into, he'll tell y'all about it. He'll talk to people that are all into.
So you get your game playing honey and those without a tardthumbs.com.
Hey, this is Richard Tyler at the fruit. You'll see you.
Yo DJ, are you done? Next time you're.
Your DJ has only just begun.
It's a gift from me, but it's all right. Yeah.
Wow, shit. Hold on a second. I messed that up.
Oh my god, I was so perfect home. Let me, let me reload that.
Let's try that again. You took it from me, but it's all right. Yeah.
Well, you took it from me and I'm feeling bad, but it's all right.
Yeah, well, the love that you give. Yeah, girl, my goodbye.
Oh, you're dressed that I pay. Yeah, hey.
We're little too hard. Wow.
When I go up, I wanna be a fucking stroller.
When I grow up, I wanna be a fucking stroller.
And I go up, I wanna be a fucking soldier
Baby, I'm ready to get from me
It's alright, yeah, yeah
Yeah, all that you give
Yeah, girl
And I can buy, I can buy, I can buy
The price that I pay
Hey, hey
A little too high, no too high
When I grow up, I wanna be a fucking soldier
When I go up, I wanna be a fucking soldier
When I grow up, I can't be a fucking soldier
Anything music on the source code
When I grow up
I want to be what was that at the very end?
Almost second.
That sounded like the end of the source code.
Hold on let me just cast Blasters so cool for this.
Let me just drag that to the end.
Let me see what the end was there.
That's right.
Thought it was.
Fantastic.
Three, two, one.
It's time for the hit to go.
With Y.
Hey, I'm.
How you doing?
I was just hit just 46.
Boating the public better of cast Blasters better number 17.
Excellent.
And this hit test is a themed version.
So I guess you'll figure it out.
Okay.
Number one.
Oh, of course.
Oh, Yon.
Oh, so right on, man.
Oh, what Yon doesn't know is that I'm a big fan of this guy.
This is Luther Vandross, man.
This is a theme of Luther Vandross.
That is any love.
I know that.
Oh, my goodness.
He passed away.
And this is number two.
Hey.
I interviewed him a while ago.
I'll talk about it after.
I know all of them.
Yon, you could have known that.
But that's here and now.
I know every single Luther Vandross song known to man, I think.
And third and final one.
That's stop to love.
I'm just going to shut up and listen to the answer because it's such beautiful music.
Well, if you haven't figured it out yet, this is a theme version as a tribute to Luther Vandross
who died last Friday at age 54.
This is answer number one.
It's any love.
I speak to myself sometimes.
And I say no more.
In a lot of ways you're a little kid.
And if anybody's there.
Well, if anybody's there.
And if you don't.
Any love. Luther Vandross.
And this is answer number two.
Also, it's my Luther.
This is here and how.
One, look in your eyes and bear a seed
Just what do you mean to me?
You and I are promised to love faith for me
You and I are promised to be one with me
Beautiful balance
Luther with here and now and this is ancient number three
It's stopped to love
You and I are promised to love faith for me
Stop to love Luther Vendros and there's one answer missing and that's the answer to one of the bigger hits
I couldn't use it as a clip because I used it already in hit press number four
I think it's never too much the biggest hits he's ever had Luther Vendros never too much
And now and this is from New England
I just don't want to stop all my love
I'm new young days in your mountains and your clouds in your eyes
I just don't want to stop that never too much
And this concludes my little tribute to this great singer, songwriter, producer and performer
That is going to be made certainly by me
I think I've got almost every album ever released by him
So I went to two of his concerts in the Netherlands here in Rotterdam
And way back when I heard a R&B and soul show on local radio
I played a lot of his songs so it's the influence of my...
Yeah my thing with music a lot
And of course I was also shocked by his death because he's only 54 minutes of shame
Well I hope you enjoyed this hit test
I guess I will be spending some time on this topic in the next hit test podcast as well
You can find information on it at youngpolettes.com
That's J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T.com
And of course the regular address
Usual address for feedback is hittest at gmail.com
Well thank you for listening
And see you next time
Well I guess hit test number 47
Bye bye
Thank you very much John
Perfect
It's interesting because I was thinking about doing a little tribute to Luther myself
But you know, didn't quite know how to do it, you know, can you play?
Obviously you can't play a licensed song
I figured it'd be okay but I was so happy when I heard this kick in
I too
No just about every single Luther Vandro song
And that is my background when I was a disjockey on decibel radio and Amsterdam Pirate radio station
That was in the early 80s man
We played and of course we were playing records back then
We played those records until they were gray
I'm telling you
Great loss
I met him a couple times in the past of the interview
Just the sweetest guy
Very down to earth
Very low key
He hasn't been healthy for a long long time
Of course he had a stroke and he had diabetes
And hypertension and had a lot of weight issues
Up and down, up and down throughout his life
And he will really really be missed
And God damn 54 man that is way too young
Kind of put you in touch with your own mortality and with reality
Okay 45 minutes
That will definitely have to do it for this source code
Thank you all very much for tuning in to this source code for
July 3rd 2005
Just on the cusp of independence day here in the United States
I'm happy I'll be able to
To be here for the celebrations
Since well as you can understand
It didn't do a lot of that in the UK
I think they celebrate the opposite of that
If you're new to the daily source code
Thank you very much for checking us out
You may do this thing through this on iTunes
Just hit the subscribe button
If not, you can head on over to dailysourcecode.com
And you can
Copy the link from the white XML, white and orange XML button
And paste that into your iPod or lemon
Or whatever other iPod or you may be using
And if you want to know more about podcasting
I suggest you go over to podcastvalley.com
And that's where you can vote on your favorite podcast
There's forums about podcasts
People recommending podcasts it's a great community
You have some time
Send us a thing back
Audio feedback is welcome
You can send that to www.artowaker.com
We're just a drop me an email
As I mentioned before
You can submit stuff for this and for the pod share
I'm serious side by radio
At submit at podshow.com
You've got some podsafe toms
The podsafe music network opening
Any day now
Send off your submissions for this show
To podsafe podshow.com
Or of course you can head over to
A go over to CC Chapman's podcast
Axon Hashtag
Check out what he's playing these days
And my weblog www.curry.com
Everybody I will be back tomorrow
Probably with a strategy cast with Ron
If not with a daily source code
Thanks for tuning in
Thanks for staying subscribe
And have a great fourth of July
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear