Daily source code 123 2005, what do I do? Do I press pound or what? Is this thing on?
On ground casting with Adam Curry. Hey everybody, it's a special weekend source code.
Right on, sitting up here in the lovely office at Curry Cottage. Hi everybody, it is Sunday.
It's late afternoon. Actually it's almost the evening. It's a 615.
As promised, in lieu of Friday show, this is the weekend source code.
Well, good news is, got back from Amsterdam.
And the bandwidth was still here.
So this is going to be kind of a little mellow show today.
Since, well, I haven't really prepared much. I think we just listened to a couple things.
But, you know, every once in a while when I come across an MP3 or a podcast or something that I like.
I drop it into a folder on my desktop. And then when I get ready to do a source code, then I just tell my application here.
My production suite to go scan through all the new files.
And it pulls out all the ID3 tags and makes a little shortcut in my outline.
But I can then copy and paste into a rundown.
Like, you care how I do that, right?
Anyway, so I hadn't really organized any stuff specifically to play today.
But I found a few things. I've been playing around with Net Newswire.
As, you know, I try to get my hands on everything eye-patter.
Everything that looks, smells, feels like an eye-patter.
And I'm actually in the throes of ordering a Windows machine.
Specifically to check out a couple of eye-patter's that just won't run on a Mac and thought.
So, playing around with Net Newswire, which I have to say, does eye-potting extremely well?
Yeah, it doesn't have the vacation feature, any of those things.
But it does do multiple concurrent downloads.
But downloads, I think it's default setting is for eight files at once.
Well, with a pipe that I've got now, I didn't even notice that it was downloading all these shows all over again.
So that wasn't too bad.
I-patter, the Lemon Edition apparently has come out with their beta.
There are two-point-o-beta-one.
I couldn't get it to run on my Mac. I submitted a bug report.
Something with, I looked at the console log, something about, I don't know if there's some error that's wrong.
But, of course, it's beta, so that's what it's supposed to do, right?
So, you're supposed to be reporting errors and helping the development team out.
Looks pretty good though, the screenshots are beautiful.
I've really- I started to notice that there's really two main approaches to iPodders.
And I guess the thing that- it really tip me off when I was looking at Net Newswire, like, wait a minute.
This is- this has a whole bunch of features that I really like.
And of course, that's an aggregator. It's been an aggregator since day one.
And it does a really good job with just aggregating and, you know, putting stuff away, downloading special times, filtering through
different types of fields. I mean, it really does have a lot of excellent options and rules settings.
And yeah, it's a Swiss Army knife of Macintosh aggregators.
Although, I do not like the three- pane approach.
I hate having an indicator. That's what I don't like about Net Newswire.
Now, there's an indicator in my- in my doc that says that, you know, has a little satellite icon for Net Newswire.
And it says, it has a three on it right now, meaning that there's three new pieces of information.
Now, I know that I'm only subscribed to podcasts and Net Newswire.
So the place I go to look for new shows is in iTunes.
And that's where it kind of came through, and it's like, well, wait a minute.
There are also some iPodder developments out there that are focusing from the player side.
iPodder X, by the way, I think, is looking a lot more at the player, although,
I think they're pretty much using all the quick time components.
But really, a combination of the two is what seems to be like the sweet spot.
And I don't know if anyone's quite hit it yet, but maybe on some of the windows version that just haven't had a chance to check out.
So definitely looking forward to seeing some of those new windows things as well.
But Net Newswire, I'm going to try it out for a little bit more.
And I believe that there's also an iPodder X, 2.0 beta on the way.
So I'm excited. This is the second round of iPodder development of the first two big teams.
So let's see what we've learned. I am really, really excited about this.
Let's see, Sunday afternoon, early evening.
It is, by the way, the 23rd of January 2005.
For the first time in a long time, I looked at my calendar, and it was absolutely nothing in it for the coming week,
although now it's filling up with the phone interviews and a couple of people want to do a photo shoot.
Particularly now, because, well, the hair is ruined, right?
And notice by the way that I haven't posted any pictures of that, there is good reason my friends believe me.
And in the mail, I received, while I was an Amsterdam, I received two CDs from Dynamo's River Maces.
You remember we talked about them, also played a track or two.
So I actually got this from one of the band members.
And I will put a link once again to their site in the production show notes for today's show.
But now I have real good quality recordings. This is great stuff.
Hold on, let me just get the, let me get them hot.
There we go.
Oh, shit.
Okay, this is Dynamo's River Maces. This one is, I'm not saying, I'm just saying.
Okay, but basically they do all these great versions of classic songs.
Like, addicted to love dancing in the street, hit me with your rhythm stick.
Born to run, see what a jump, ace of spades, hajo, my generation.
So all pod safe music and obviously stuff that we'll be playing for, well, I think about 24 tracks there.
I can play a lot of this on the source code for the next coming shows.
And every single one is a hit, done just a little bit differently.
I think you'll like it.
This is a classic by Queen brought to you my Dynamo's River Maces.
Tonight, well, I'm going to have myself a real good sign.
Because I feel alive, man. I feel alive.
Like, I can take the world.
I'm just turning inside out, baby, and floating around in ecstasy.
So don't stop me now.
Don't stop me, man.
Because I'm having a good sign, I'm having a good sign.
So I'll leave it to you to start.
Like, I can talk a good, fine, long, gravity.
Today, I'm a racing girl.
That's in by.
I hate to get that vote.
But I have to know, no, no, no, no, hold in me.
But it's straight through the sky, yeah.
So hundreds of degrees are by the communist firing heights.
We're driving at speed of light.
We want to make it super sunny, man.
I know you.
Yeah, dude.
So don't stop me now.
I'm having such a good time.
I'm having a vote.
Stop me now.
If you want to have a good time, give it a call.
But don't stop me.
Have a good time.
Don't stop me.
Yeah.
Because I'm rocking too.
I'm on his way to Mars.
I'm a collision course.
Like satellite.
And I've control I'm sexy.
Great to reload.
Like an out of bomb.
I got the boom.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's low.
I'm shaking the sky again.
So hundreds of degrees are by the communist firing heights.
Driving at speed of light.
I want to make it super sunny, man.
Of you.
Yeah, dude.
So don't stop me now.
I'm having such a good time.
I'm having a vote.
Stop me now.
If you want to have a good time.
Give it a call.
But don't stop me.
You have a good time.
Don't stop.
Say it.
I'm having a good time.
I don't want to stop at all.
So don't stop me.
I don't burn straight into the sky.
Yeah.
So hundreds of degrees are by the communist firing heights.
Driving at speed of light.
I want to make it super sunny, man.
Of you.
Yeah, dude.
So don't stop me now.
I'm having such a good time.
I'm having a vote.
Stop me now.
If you want to have a good time.
Give it a call.
But don't stop me.
Have a good time.
Don't stop me.
I don't have a good time.
I don't want to stop at all.
Man, I'm like a refugee.
But don't wait a month.
I'm a collision cause.
I'm like a satellite.
You've got an out of control.
I'm a refugee.
Ready to do reload.
Not good at bomb.
I got a, got a, got a, got a man who got his vote.
I burn straight through the sky.
Yeah.
So hundreds of degrees are by the communist firing heights.
Driving at speed of light.
I want to make it super sunny, man.
Of you.
Yeah, dude.
So don't stop me now.
I'm having such a good time.
I'm having a good vote.
Stop me now.
If you want to have a good time.
Give me a cough.
Don't stop me.
Have a good time.
I don't stop me.
I don't stop me, you're just my little girl.
Time, don't stop me.
Have a good time, don't stop.
Don't stop.
Don't stop me.
Have a good time.
Don't stop.
nào lead good time, don't stop me.
I don't take good time.
No.
I don't stop me.
I don't take good time.
Don't stop me.
Have a good time and don't stop, don't stop me.
I don't take good time.
Don't stop me.
Stop me.
It's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me, it's not me
Bloody record, the usual city
First time I heard that it did freak me out. I was like oh shit, something stuck
There was a future tense that came through the other aperture through that out shit. That was stupid
There was a future tense that I was talking about the record scratch and that even though the record scratch that
That's you know a needle being dragged off of a record even though that's one of the most used sound effects in advertising today
Seeing if I still have it somewhere here
They did a survey and they asked a whole bunch of kids if they knew what that sound was they went
Yeah, that's from the commercial they had never heard of it actually scratching on a record
Let me see if I have that it was
I bet you don't have that anymore shoot
Future tense. Oh, maybe this is it. Hold on. It'll be great if I still had that one. Let's check it out first
Libraries get hip to really simple syndication. No, this is future
That wasn't that shoot
Shoot, let me just check iTunes for a second. I bet you I tossed that out
Okay, I'm probably get the yeah now it's gone darn
That would have been great to play for you right now
It was on the media anyway. I'll look it up for you. Okay, it was it was a podcast. That's for sure
That I do remember here's something that came across I think open podcast.org it showed up in my iTunes
And it's almost like poetry, but it was pretty good. It's about it's called Dead TV
It's done by Jenny Gillespie Gillespie
It speaks it speaks for itself. Let's sit back and chill. It's about two and a half minutes, but you won't want to fast forward because it's it's good
Life TV is an even live TV. It's so dead to me. So orchestrated so seamlessly so perfectly. I'm telling you it's dead TV
Our perfect people they brush their teeth before they go on the air someone somewhere counts down from five to one
Making their colgate smile shine on like the sun and over their paper props and coffee mugs painted a stylish navy blue
They deliver us the news with delicate creases and their dry clean sports jackets and their neat little bundles of free striped telecast packets
They have appropriate faces and tones for all their heart wrenching recitals with a rather catchy title that rhymes of course
About some golden retriever dancing for the sick kids that we who and we are over because you know that stories vital
But not so urgent so meaningful so necessary that we can't lay our heads down on our pillows and sleep that night leaving behind us the senses sympathy
We like to portray to star new day where no one else matters but ourselves
But those people from the news God damn they have it's so great
They're everyone super hero everyone's best friend our favorite face on our cable access station
They're so trustworthy so reliable. They have that that chronic dedication
They have the stuff that it takes to relate 45 minutes worth of truth and nothing but
Okay, maybe there's a bud there's you know societies buy a certain in there to spice it up a bit
But I mean they have plastic hair like burvey dolls and spray paint and make up it's fucking impenetrable
So what's the new fat in the news today politics or politics and when it comes down to it we could care less really
We want a generic black man with a sought off shotgun running rampant and someone else is suburban streets killing him some
Blonde hair blue eyed chair leaders so sweet. We want the story. We want it concrete
Who cares about the sources or if the you know facts are incomplete?
We'll put it on repeat on every fucking channel until everyone from the Pope to your grandmother wants to donate just 50 cents to the cause
So the informed public will raise you up in a plus the thank you being a great aid citizen
That's simply just a perp
Great stuff, huh? Yeah, first time I heard that I was like wow
That's good Jenny Gillespie don't know anything about her. I presume she wrote it herself
But don't like that very much when I heard it
A lot of people pointed me towards this podcast from what is it?
This show has no name is the name of the podcast
I pointed to it in the production show notes
It's got a home page stop macadress
So it shouldn't be a problem if you want to download the show
Because I know that sometimes when I mention someone's podcast and we get it like a little mini slash dot effect
Not that there's so many people that I'm sending over your way, but
Because the files are so big
Anyway, I listened to it and I was like wow, you know
Here's a guy who listens to the daily source code every single day and a second tired of me
Finally, I'm sure there's more out there
But he put it in a podcast something I totally, totally appreciate
And I thought we'd listen to it together because there's some interesting things in here that I'm sure other people are thinking
They're maybe a few misconceptions and some things, I think he's probably right about
A couple of the things I want to talk about is that I want to make it official now that I'm pretty much sick of Adam Curry
Okay, I'm glad you made that official, that's a good start
I'm sick of him in general, I'm sick of his podcast
Even though I listen to it all the time and I'm relatively addicted to it
And there's some couple things that I'm really bothered by
And mainly because, you know, everybody's pretty nice
And he seems like a nice guy, but it's really his podcast, it's kind of bothered me more than anything
Okay, I've seen like a nice guy only when I'm podcasting, which is the only way he knows me
That's not starting to bother me
And it's just that not that I want to be sour grapes or anything
But you know what, drum cadence suck
Okay, let me just put that out there
There was maybe one or two that was pretty good
I understand that he's having a hard time because you can't get any good RIA
No, no, that's not true. No, I'm receiving more drum cadences than any other music period
That's why I think playing so much of it
Actually, I haven't played a lot in the past week and a half to be free music and that's running
But the drum kids, just they just got to go
I mean, really, you know
Dude, fast forward, that's all, he'll show you how it works
So the 10 that's a drum case
That's not that cool, I'm sorry
I found myself just skipping through the whole thing
Right, this thing is just that
You know, I'm so sick of those serious bitties
Maybe he's got some sort of a financial thing
He keeps saying that he is a businessman
And I think that people keep forgetting that in their days
Oh, hold on a second, hold on a second
First of all, I have absolutely no financial arrangement or any type of deal
whatsoever with any of the list of his bitties
Except they have promised me a big hug when we meet up in New York
That they have promised
Because believe me, dude
I think that's something I would have to disclose
Right, like tell you about
Believe me, I would tell you if I had any financial gain
But yes, I am a businessman, absolutely
And I love it when I see people who are already doing business
Like those serious bitties
Do more business because of something really simple
Mainly people who like their music or play in their music and podcast
So I see that as a good thing
That's a ties by the fact that he's going to find a way to make money
Either this podcast and thing
He's going to milk it for his good
Oh, all right, okay
And you know what that's probably what they said
Well, okay, yes, of course
Of course, I'm going to milk it to death, damn it
Oh, wow
If you know how
Please put that in your podcast so I can start milking
And I think that's something that people should be very aware of
And understand that the reason he's so pumped about this
Because he sees a monetary opportunity there
Okay, first of all
The reason this all got started was out of frustration
Because I wanted to get pod cat or MP3 files onto my iPod
It was no absolutely no fine
In fact, I tried to pay people to do that for me
But I have to admit
That there's totally
A lot of interest from the business community
From the financial community
A lot of people are saying, hey, how can we monetize this
Am I looking, of course I'm looking
To have ideas, of course I have ideas
Of course I do, is that wrong?
Apparently
It's reminds me so much of
When I started out
With something I called cyber sleeves
And I was promoting that on my radio shows
And it's actually this was before mtv.com
And I remember that all the, not all
But the, the quote community at the time
Was very against the commercial internet
It was like, you know, commercial was bad
It's not going to happen
It's going to fight against it, will hack you to death
It sounds like the same thing, you know
It's like, of course someone's going to
Commercialize parts of pod casting
I heard someone say, I don't know where it was
I think it was maybe it was a pod cat
I'm thinking, I'm going to say pod cast brothers
Because it was a brilliant analogy
That whenever there's a, there's a gold rush
The people who always make the money
Are the outfitters
So that's the people who supply the horses
The wagons, the donkeys
The shovels, the spades, you know, the tents
Whatever, of course
And we really don't have a pod casting service
Yeah, do we, this is one of the things of course
That we've been looking at
And what does that entail?
I think the number one place to make money right now
Is helping people make pod casts
I don't think there's a lot of people making money
On their pod casts right now
Nor is it clear if they will
I got some ideas
But yeah, of course I'm looking at ways to make money
But I'm not hiding that
I'm not doing the source code
Because I have some genius plan
That's going to make me billions of dollars
Through that show alone
I like doing it dude
And don't be lulled
Into thinking that this guy
Who is now
God, I've seen it now on
In a macadic magazine
I've seen it in New York Times
I've seen it on ABC
I've seen it everywhere
Because they all call me up
And ask me for interviews
It actually takes a lot of time
And I don't have an actual job at the moment
We'll talk about that in a second
I'm sure
So I could make time
Which I think is also help
Propel pod casting
For good or for bad
He's going to make money off of this
Oh, I can't wait
And you and me are probably not going to do that
You and me presuming me the listener
The way to me
You just told me I was
But as a listener, I'm not
Mainly because we're probably a really well-versed
And making money off of something like this
Dude, I've never made money off of anything like this
Let me tell you how I made my money
Okay
I might be good
I started
Actually, it did start a content company
Called OnRamp
And we had actually Metaverse.com
And we had cyber sleeves
And we had a whole bunch of cool sites
This is around the time that addicted to noise
It was also a
Some of you might remember that website
That was purchased later by MTV
And we were making content for
Re-box for Budweiser
For continental airlines
For Procter and Gamble
Hey, we did tampax.com
The website you'll want to visit more than once a month
We haven't fun
And we just started going more and more into the service side of stuff
She's going to be providing services for companies
At the time when you could charge $40,000
For what I knew eventually
And what now are indeed tools that cost $40
And so we did a good job
We worked really hard for about five years
And we sold the company in 1999
Always made a profit
At the end of our tenure
There I say ours, my partner Ron
We had a pay roll of $65 million
And we always made pay roll
And we were profitable and we had
Happy clients
And we did good work
We were advertising agency basically
And I made money on that
But the real money I made came from lucky investments
And the real money I lost by the way
I also lost a lot of money came from unlucky investments
But that's his goal
And I think...
No, no, sorry, that's so my goal is not to make money
My goal is to...
Well, to have fun doing whatever I'm doing
And if possible
Make the world a better place while we do it
And fuck yeah, I'd like to get paid
Doesn't everybody?
I mean, everyone has bandwidth bills
Has, you know, your time is worth something
And either you say this is 100% hobby for me
Or you say, hey, I'm going to try and make something out of this
Not in wrong with that
Yeah, as much as he would like to be
Befriending all these other people
Well, no, I am actually befriending people
Because I make friends pretty easily
And I would pretty good track record with friends
You can look it up dude
And whether it's he wants to be the little
Sivius Bitties Manager or whatever that
I don't...
I wish, God damn
I'd love to be their manager
Hmm, I think they have that all sold up
I actually, I was talking to Leon
I've got you such an angelic voice
Even on the phone she sounds so, so pretty
And she was telling me about, oh, we just shoot in the shit actually
And I said, well, you know, because they were interviewed by CBS
For the CV, I don't know when this piece is going to air
But it should be reasonably soon, I guess
And I was so happy for it
And I said, you know, you're going to get calls pretty soon
And stuff's going to happen, she said, oh, we, you know, we have had such a luxury over
They've been doing it for like seven or eight years
They really have all their finances, their legal stuff
It's all, I mean, not that they have a lot of finances
But it's, they have that all set
And I said, anything you need, let me know
Dude, of course I'd like to be their manager
But that's not why I'm playing their songs
Because I'd like their songs, that's why
But I think that that's something that is
Is true in call speed of speed
You know, and any...
You know, he's, he's alluded to that
He said, you know, hey, he's a businessman
He's the most big money, there's nothing wrong with that
But don't be low than the thinking that
He's just this super nice guy that's just trying to
Really help everybody out
Yeah, I actually believe it or not
I mean, I'd be a super nice guy
But I do like to help everybody out
And I think that by helping each other
We'll be able to figure some stuff out
And actually maybe, you know, work together on some things
That could be fun to work on or could generate revenue together
Or kinds of stuff, but I'm not like
Something like job and life to go around
You know, sucking up to people
And getting to be my friends
And then go make money off of them
Which of course we haven't established exactly how to do that
I think in a lot of ways you may be
But I think in the back of his money he's going to say
You know what?
I kind of think money at this
I mean, just look at the sound scene thing
Hey, baby
Hey
I'm doing a podcast
New?
Umm Hmm
How much time would I have?
Are you ready right now?
Okay, what should I do?
So till the audience, or I've put them on paws
Or should I put its good stuff right now?
Should I put the audience on paws?
Yeah
Alright everybody, you're going on paws
I'm going to have dinner
Come back and we'll continue
Do do do want
Right, okay
So I'm back
That was two and a half hours ago that we last spoke.
Okay.
You get the fast forward.
I get to hit the pause button once in a while.
And actually it's pretty good because I was thinking,
but after dinner, Patricia and I were watching,
we were watching, and Tiggs Roadshow.
Love that show.
Of course, it's not really about the antiques or the objects that they display.
It's what's worth.
That's the game, right?
Okay.
I think that's going to be worth about,
and probably about 3,400,
and then once when you get the 10,000 pound valuable item,
whatever.
And then Patricia Files sleep, so I went to clean up the kitchen.
And I was thinking about the comment about the Sylvia's Bitties.
And I was thinking, you know, what is it that I like so much?
And I thought back to the early 80s when I was just really getting into top 40 radio.
It was, you know, there was still an opportunity back then to actually play a song that you thought,
and I think it was like once an hour in most formats that that I worked with,
at most radio stations.
Not really in the, yeah, it was very early 80s.
At least had one song an hour that you could kind of, you know,
fuzzle around or legally play as one of your own picks.
And before that, you know, we used to just, you know,
bring whatever, whatever the hell we wanted to play,
but of course those weren't very commercially successful radio stations,
which will tell you a lot about, you know,
what needs to be done to become commercially successful.
But, and it could be anything, particularly in Holland,
where I started my radio career,
and Bruce Springsteen never really caught on big in the chart.
And I say chart because back then, you know, there was a chart,
it was the top 40.
And then, of course, we got the, the top 50,
and then the top 40 album and singles and airplane.
And these days, you have the top download chart.
So there's no real authority, you know, it's a,
but that used to be very simple.
It was compiled based upon actual sales figures.
But also, some audience research was put in there.
And it was, it was a, it was a good chart.
And you could get it, you know, and if you played a song
and then some of the other DJs from other stations
or your own station would also play that song,
then it could get some momentum, you know,
and then you'd break an artist.
And that was something that we were proud of, you know,
it's like dude.
And I've actually broken a couple artists in Holland
that people will attribute to me.
I laughed because Renee Froker is probably,
the one that became most famous after I,
I broke him as an artist.
It sounds weird, doesn't it?
It's like a real industry term.
I broke you, boy.
He's kind of like the Dutch Engelbert Humperding.
So that's why I'm chuckling.
But anyway, I digress.
I was had a joint after dinner.
I forgot to mention that.
So that's why you get like.
Okay.
So, but it really was all about, you know,
it was just pride.
And then it would be even better if that artist went on
to get a gold record.
And, you know, somewhere down the line,
you would actually be presented with something like that,
like a gold record or platinum record or whatever.
And it says, you know, thanks for your thanks for contributing
to the success of the album or the artist or whatever,
depending on what your contribution was.
Literally.
And there was no money that passed hands.
You know, this is just a part of a thing that happened.
And it just started to roll and snowball.
And, you know, and something would catch on.
And then the audience would catch on and it just goes, right?
But sometimes songs need a little bit more.
And you know, I guess they're more complex or something or whatever.
So, as I was saying, Bruce Springsteen was something that
buddy and I broke in Holland.
It was dancing in the dark.
It just wasn't catching on.
But there's been, you know, lots of examples like that.
And even at MTV in the very early days when I was there,
which was still the 80s, you know,
you could still kind of have some kind of influence.
But it just went away.
And also, the gold record started going to everybody,
like the sales guy and, you know, the station manager,
and became more cheesy.
And, you know, more like production work, nothing,
it used to be that you could actually play these records.
They would be the, they weren't really, well,
they were dipped in gold, I think.
But most of them, the original records that were given to, you know,
given to the artist based upon huge amounts of sales,
were the mother or father masters when they were still pressing records.
And you could actually take them out and play them.
You have to play them backwards, though,
because it's a reverse of what you'd actually have in the vinyl.
And Patricia has a lot of the original type of gold records.
And one time by my radio show, we took one out of the casing
and played it backwards.
And it actually was the real record.
But I never got the casing back together the way it was intended to be.
So I'm not allowed to demonstrate that anymore.
I've been banned from touching the gold records and rightly so.
But anyway, it's nothing about, you know,
about wanting to do anything more than just have that feeling.
That's a great feeling when it works.
And that, I guess that's what kind of, what,
what, that's what the kick is about that.
I get out of playing the civvies, bitis, and bitis,
and hearing people catch on and like it,
and watching them get famous.
You know what?
I'm tired of this.
Let's do something else.
We do live from your headphones.
It's asked Uncle Know It All.
Hello everyone and welcome to this week's edition of Ask Uncle Know It All.
This week's question comes to us from Sex Kitten, who asks?
Dear Uncle Know It All.
I'm writing because I'm wondering, what's the deal with the cowbell?
Thanks so much.
Hugs and kisses.
Love you.
Sex Kitten.
Well, Sex Kitten.
Sometime ago, VH1 aired a documentary
of the blue oyster cult in studio recording their hit song,
don't fear the reaper.
While they were recording, Bruce Dickinson made comments
about how he loved the cowbell sound
who, done by one of the band members.
Now, this caused something of a stir in the current music industry.
And as a result of this footage,
next March, Virgin Records is releasing the cowbell collection,
which is a collection of both old and new songs
featuring Greg Groups on cowbell.
Now, if managed to secure an advanced copy of this CD,
and I'll be playing a couple of samples for you.
Our first sample is,
Stip Tiffany's recorded by Deep Blue Something.
This next song was recorded by Metallica,
entitled Enter Sandman.
And last but not least,
we have gin and juice,
courtesy of Grandmaster Rapa, Snoop Dogg.
As you can see, or rather, here,
the cowbell can be used with a variety of different music styles.
In fact, there's only one style of music that the cowbell
cannot help.
It's not that easy.
As you can see, or rather, here,
the cowbell can be used with a variety of different music styles.
In fact, there's only one style of music that the cowbell
cannot help, and that's country,
because nothing can help country music.
Now, inside sources also tell me that
P. Diddy will be releasing a new album entitled
Cowbell in the Hizzles,
which features remakes of every song
on the Cowbell collection.
And that about wraps it up for this week.
Don't forget, send me your questions,
your questions, make the show.
You can email Soundclips or just type the question
if you prefer.
The email address is Uncle Know It All at gmail.com.
Thanks.
On Cowboy Casting with Adam Curry.
Say it again!
Nothing gives me doubt.
To do how to talk.
To seem to talk to Rahan.
Maybe I know.
Just how to feel.
Let's say you got bro-o-o with a budget
to get to what's real.
We can't see instead of here.
We've got the back of your gaze.
We're breaking the sheet.
I have the rest to see.
We'll be able to see what I mean.
Well, you might as well jump.
Go ahead and jump.
Man, I'll say jump.
Hey hanger.
It's you.
Go ahead and jump.
Me and I said jump, jump, go ahead and jump
I said jump, jump, go ahead and jump
People I said jump, jump, go ahead and jump
Hold jump the whole time
Hold jump, go ahead and jump
Okay, you can see it was down here, got the back against the rain from the sheet
I have the words you've seen, maybe see what I mean
Hold jump, go ahead and jump
Oh, they're a classic difference
Say you might as well jump
You're head and jump
Come on and jump
Go ahead and jump
Man I said jump
Come on, now jump
Time is rhythm and sense
And then all I know for today's daily source code
Actually, this special one we can make up for this new source code
How's the difference?
Yeah, I've got to play more of those guys.
I say rock.
All right, everybody, that's it.
Have a good weekend.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Or maybe you're just getting this.
And it's already Monday morning.
So then you have another source code on the way later on.
I'm going to leave it for this for now.
Of course, comments.
I don't have to worry.com.
If you've got an MP3 comment,
send it to MP3 feedback at gmail.com.
And of course, comments on the web
longer, always run.
Some power.
www.create.com.
Thanks for watching.