Delta, share a Charlie 2-4-Zero.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Transmidders?
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking, can we?
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Welcome to the Curry Kondo. It's the 15th of September, 2005.
Well, brand new acoustics, everybody.
How you doing? Welcome to your daily source code.
It's been a few days.
If that all kinds of stuff going on,
why do you have explanation of your, uh,
you'll understand once we're getting to it?
The very first show coming to you from Curry Kondo.
This is your daily source code.
So, um, apologies first and foremost for those of you
bummed out that I actually haven't had more than one show up all this week.
Because now Thursday, international,
jet-ro-sexual, man of mystery,
traveling all over the globe.
That'll definitely screw up your, uh, your source code schedule.
Take that and some DNS and transfer and delivery
issues and all kinds of crap, but I'm here.
It's been my first night at the Kondo.
I've got lots to talk about about our adventures in New York.
What's going to be happening for the next two weeks in San Francisco, California?
Okay, just to set the scene a little bit, um,
I'm in the Kondo.
Uh, of course you have no idea what that looks like,
really maybe you seem wanted to picture it on a weblock,
but, um, I have a bed.
I have a couch. I've got, uh, table. I have no chairs.
Uh, I have no cups.
Uh, apparently, JC Penny did deliver a whole bunch of stuff,
but when I got here last night, after the plane ride, uh, from hell,
there was nothing here, so we're just kind of making
do with what we got. I still got to figure out where to get some breakfast.
Uh, yeah, it is 1045. Um, I'm going to break it down and, uh,
give you a full rundown of everything that's been going on. All good stuff.
As, uh, we roll out a kind of, I don't want to do,
like a jazzy source go today, kind of just mellow and, uh, kind of ease into it.
I found, um, from mashuptown.com, very interesting mashup.
Titled, even your jazz is not safe from the mashup,
and it's, uh, a little bit of, uh, was it take five in there?
And, uh, well, you see if you can, uh, figure out all of the different jazz songs.
Enjoy this while I, uh, get to put some on my feet.
Yeah, well, jazzy, uh, jazzy undertones to kick off the daily source code, uh, for this, uh, Thursday.
So you can hear right off the bat, there's a way different acoustics taken place here.
I'm also in the, uh, uh, in the living room slash, um, well, there's an open kitchen.
It has, uh, oh, second. It has, uh, it has a bar, uh, and so I basically put everything next to
the sink. I've got, uh, got the power book here. I've got, uh, the digital audio workstation. I've got, uh,
I got the new mic, uh, which I have, uh, there's a little flight case that comes with this new,
AKG mic, so I've actually stood that on its end. And I'm still leaning over, of course, so I don't have a podcast
complex up here, but I have different ideas for how I want to set stuff up here. Also, um, you could tell that, uh,
it's just empty. Uh, I've got the most phenomenal view here. Um, I can see if, now, I have, what is it, uh,
three, two hundred, two hundred, like two hundred, no, I don't have two hundred,
see, I have to go from there. Well, yeah, I almost have like a hundred and seventy degree view. I'm
almost a hundred-dated degree view. I guess it's depending on how you look at it. Uh, corner, um,
corner apartment that kind of hangs out over the building. So it's really cool. So I, to the right,
I see, uh, the skyline, the city, um, ahead. I see, uh, the hills. And if I were to look left, uh,
actually I'm right across from the Bank of America building, uh, and the clock's not working.
On the last night when I came in, it was working, and then at midnight it went off, and it hasn't
come back on yet. I wonder if it only, uh, if it's only on at night. And of course, there is the, uh,
the up ramp, the on ramp to the, uh, uh, was it, uh, to the Bay Bridge over to Oakland. So I've got
to really quite an, uh, an amazing view, although there is a huge yellow crane, almost, uh, almost at
my, I level here, and we're up on the 24th floor. Uh, and I don't know how long the construction
is going to go on, but, uh, let me see, where should we start? When we last, um, when we last spoke,
I was on my way to New York, that was Tuesday. Yeah, I was going to do a source code on Tuesday,
but then we had all kinds of DNS issues and all kinds of stuff, uh, basically just blew up,
and so I was able to repose Monday source code, uh, thanks to Apple putting it on the dot
Mac, and I may even have to do that again today, because we're still having all kinds of DNF
stuff, DNF stuff, but this is, you know, this is what happens. Uh, luckily we're all just kind of
getting back from somewhere vacation. So we're working all the kinks out and, uh, Brian and Marcus
and, uh, Chris Rockwell, we're all moving servers, uh, over the past two days they've been up for,
for just nights on end, get everything all set up because, you know, yeah, um, I love it when
people say, oh, you've got all that money. You're so well funded and you shit didn't work. Well,
that's exactly what we've got it for. So, you know, give us a little time to play catch up if you don't
would really work on it. Um, so I didn't do the show on Tuesday, even though I had a kind of plan,
so I have a few of the elements, uh, for Tuesday's show in today's show. Um, flew, uh,
of course, Virgin upper class loved it as always. It was funny. The, um, the entire crew from,
orange county chopper was that, um, a chopper is born. Is that, uh, no, that's not the tide
love it. Uh, maybe it's called orange county chopper. I don't remember the name of the reality
show where they build chopper motorcycles. It's, uh, basically, you know, the big dude with the, uh,
with the kind of like the walrus mustache, the whitish walrus mustache. So he and his, uh, I guess
four, five of them were all, uh, uh, on my flight. And it was pretty funny because he and, I guess
it was his girlfriend or maybe his wife, I don't know. Um, uh, so they had two of the middle seats.
Now, these are like the, the sweet seats that they have. So you know, we've discussed this where
you've kind of got your own little world there. And there's a divider if you're in one of the
middle seats, uh, one of the middle two, um, there's a divider right down the middle of the
plane, so that, you know, your seat mate basically, you know, doesn't bother you. It was so funny
because, you know, it was clear that, um, he wanted, uh, I should figure out what his name is.
Uh, he, he clearly wanted to be kind of closer to his wife. And so out came the screw drivers and
they just dismantled the whole thing, the whole divider in between these two seats and basically
created a huge double bed, which was hilarious because I'm like, yeah, next time I travel with the
Trish, I'm going to do that. He's got to bring my, uh, um, my compass and rubber knife and we'll
get it all all fixed up. Um, the flight was, uh, reasonably uneventful, although we did have, uh,
I'd have to say about four, 500 miles worth of clean air turbulence, um, which isn't, you know,
dangerous per se. Uh, usually nothing really happens. And, you know, the airplane is,
can well withstand, uh, the shocks and jolt, but it's very uncomfortable, uh, for, uh, for the
passengers, um, and it was kind of hard to get to sleep. And I actually, it gave me a little bit of a pain in my neck,
just because of all the, the bouncing and jolting must have gone on for, uh, um, yeah,
probably about an hour, 45 minutes to an hour. Um, and then I got into New York, um, and the United
Nations, uh, as you probably know, uh, or mate might have heard, have their 60th, uh, general assembly,
this week in New York. There was not a sin, and of course, a fashion week just ended. There was not a single
hotel in the entire city that had one single room, not even at the airport. And I'd foolishly
booked myself into, uh, into Newark airport. And the hotel we wound up getting was, uh, up, uh, in Westchester,
like near Rye, New York. Uh, so I had a fun time, like two hours from the airport getting up there,
because it was nine, nine, nine, 30 at night. And for some reason, of course, the George W. The
George Washington Bridge was completely backed up. It was, it was a nightmarish. And, you know,
so got in and we had to leave the hotel at 7 a.m. the next morning to go in and, and present. And we,
and we did two, uh, two presentations, uh, to two groups of media buyers, um, and media planners,
uh, so these are the people that actually buy radio advertising and, uh, internet advertising. And
I think we did two sessions and we had about 50 people in each one, I'd say, very, very enthusiastic.
Lots of really good questions and some, and nice to see some very creative thinking going on about
how we can do, um, different types of advertising, uh, in podcasts. So, uh, that was, uh,
I was actually quite delightful. And then, um, so that was, of course, Wednesday, and, you know,
I had no time to do a show, um, and at quarter to three, the car picked this up and my, like,
was a 23rd street or something like that. To go to JFK, took us two hours to get the JFK,
the flight, which, of course, was fully booked. So, there was, uh, Chris, who's our, uh, VP of business
development, and we were both together. So, we were sitting in the back, like, row, uh, 39,
or something like that, because there was, you know, no other seats available, no upgrades available,
or anything. Uh, and then we sat on the tarmac for about two hours, and then, of course,
the six and a half hour flight. So, by the time I got in, it was, uh, it was a court like a 1230
quarter to one, and we had literally been on the road for 12 hours, and so I was just completely wiped
out, and I basically threw the sheet on the bed that Patricia had, had nicely packed into my, uh,
into my suitcase, and, uh, and hit the hay, and I must say, I had a great sleep, uh, I didn't
wake up for anything, really, uh, just kind of awoke all by myself, uh, to, uh, well, unfortunately,
it's kind of a gray foggy day, um, foggy day. I can see, uh, when I can see the other side of the day,
so it's not all that bad, but the hills are still, um, uh, the crests are just, uh, enveloped
in fog, is that what I, is that, what it is, and enveloped? Uh, that's fog, okay? It's just a fricking.
You don't want to fly there. Let's put it, not without your instrument rating. Let's put it that way.
Also, it's something that I had to queue up for Tuesday, from the across the sound podcast,
was, uh, a topic that we discussed, uh, with all these, uh, media buyers and planners and advertising
agency people, and they had actually discussed some of the sound advertising stuff that I had done
on their show, and I just wanted to play a little snippet from that for you. I think that's interesting,
actually, what's, what's, have you heard about what Adam Curry is doing? He's got a neat experiment.
He, he, he, he, he, he's up there talking about a coffee, a fan of his coffee, or if it's a coffee
maker called Senseo. Um, and what he does is that is that he says, stop what you're doing right
now when you're listening to my podcast, and remember where you are and look around you and
you and focus on one object that you're looking at while you're listening to this. And I'm going
to say the word Senseo. And I guarantee you that every single time you look at that object or
or item, you're going to remember the word Senseo. And in he says, gee, I wonder if there's
something to that if there's some sort of advertising model from that. And so for me, I was actually
sitting outside of Starbucks listening to his podcast when he said that. So now, whenever I see that
the Starbucks logo, I'm thinking Senseo, which is kind of a weird kind of a weird thing. And
you know, maybe maybe I may start to move away from Starbucks towards Senseo. So I think that
that's kind of neat. Um, one thing that the funny thing is I, what I happen to when you said that
I happen to stare at at my pocket pegs, uh, the screen coolments, uh, oral catch strips. And,
you know, I guess with coffee breath, uh, that would come into play as well. So for for some reason,
the the object that I happen to look at had that contextual rid of and see as well.
Uh, so it's a very, it's a very cool idea. I don't know what you do with it, but maybe you can
maybe if there's some like day part advertising or a pod part, uh, advertising. So that people
can sponsor like a minute. And, uh, and I don't know, maybe there's some somebody holding up some
way to capitalize on that. Well, I think it's, I think it's going to be probably the most expensive
slot to advertise on. That's what I think. Because you can't help yourself if you're listening and
someone says, okay, pick a spot. You don't, you know, you can't not want to do it. Because you're
already programmed. But the minute I say the minute you hear, I say, okay, pick a spot. You're already
lost, you know. Um, I think we actually have a conversation with the sense say, oh, people pretty
pretty soon. I'd love to do this with them because it does work. Um, if, well, I'm not going to do it
today. I'm not going to do it right now. Um, one thing was really disappointing. You know, I got this
great MDA, this T mobile, um, now I'm a T mobile customer and I pay monthly and they can direct
debit my account and all that. And they still have me on probation because I'm a new customer. I'm,
you know, so, um, if you go like 50 or 50 pounds over your a lot of budget or some shit like that
for your, you're, you're, you're predicted monthly build and immediately, uh, they stop outgoing calls.
They stop, uh, if you're roaming in a different country, uh, you can't send any outbound text or SMS.
You can only receive. And, uh, so this happened when I, when I arrived really late to Tuesday night.
And so I said, oh, I'll just hop on the website, um, and, uh, and, you know, top up my account there.
And of course, so the website didn't work. It was broken. Called the number, um, uh, they're open from 7 a.m.
So, you know, a UK time, 7 to 10 or something like that. So, I had to wait.
And really, it just pisses me off, you know, this whole, I guess they have no incentive to really
make it work, you know, this by this phone and you can travel the world and you can use it everywhere.
It's, you know, it's not true. It just doesn't work everywhere. You've got to continuously be in contact
with your, um, with your network provider to, to make all the bits and bytes, uh, gel at the same time.
And it's, uh, disappointing is what it is. Uh, what else did I want to say? There were a couple of,
oh, yeah. Um, so on this, this flight from hell that we had yesterday, they played,
since we were so delayed. They played five, five, count them five episodes of,
everybody loves Raymond. I don't love Raymond anymore after five episodes of that. But then they
played a movie in Chris and I looked at each other and I went, oh, man, this is going to be a real
chick movie. It was um, sisterhood of the traveling pants. I don't know if you've seen this, uh, this movie.
Uh, but it was a 100% chick flick. And, uh, and what I hated even more is it maybe cry.
It's just like, oh, man, it's a chick flick and I'm crying. This is, this is wrong. This is all wrong.
A little bit of pod save music now, although I realize it's actually it's not pod safe.
But I think I can get away with it for this one time. It is when the pod save music
network, Carmen Tyler, who has a couple of really, really good songs up there. This is a classic one,
kind of staying in our, in our Jazzy vibe, which, uh, well, the ASCAP BMI payments will take care of it.
But it's not pod safe every pod cast. It's summertime.
Summer time, and the living is easy. Fish on jumping, and the curtain is hot.
Your dad's rich, and your mama's good looking.
So hush, little baby, and don't you cry. So hush, little baby, and don't you cry.
One of these mornings, you're gonna rise up singing. Then you'll spread your wings
and you'll take to the sky. But till that morning, there's enough thing
I can't hold you. And death, you mama, standing by.
Summer time, and the living is easy. Fish on jumping, and the curtain is hot.
Your dad's rich, and your mama's good looking.
So hush, little baby, and don't you cry.
Man, who is that girl? Carmen Tyler. K-A-R-M-Y-N Tyler with a Y as well.
Summer time, she also got a great song called The Guilty, which I'll be sure to play for you here on
The Daily Source Code. A couple of the things I wanted to mention. The podcast music network
where you can also pick that song up has a really cool new feature, which I just noticed earlier this
week. When you add a song to your playlist, and then you report it as played, it pops up a little
window that will automatically send an email to the artist who song that belongs to. And you
can edit the email, what it basically says. Hey, the Daily Source Code played your song in episode,
and of course it puts in the episode number that you tagged. And it sends it off to them, which is
it's a part really, it's social networking, which is great. And I've been playing a lot with
social networks recently. There's a lot of amazing stuff going on. We say so easily, you know,
social networking, but it's really just small little features that make it work so incredibly well,
just like that email that is sent off. And of course, it has a link back to my podcast page.
So it's really, it's very, very cool. Also, yeah, I wanted to thank the multitude of people
who have their Wi-Fi networks open. You know, my Wi-Fi networks have always been open all over the
world, wherever I've lived, and I've enjoyed using them, and coming into the Curry Condo with no
phone, no cable, and no internet connectivity. I must say absolutely phenomenal to see 15 open
networks just sitting there waiting for. We've of course, I'm up really high, so you have to be kind
of careful, because you can kind of get reflected bounces, you know, a car all drive by, and
all of a sudden you'll get five new networks, because, you know, the signal just bouncing off of
its straight up and through all the glass into the into the, into the pad. But I guess there's
a couple of people, what I must be, several people in the building, who also have Wi-Fi, and I've been
totally vibing on this three-com network. So anyone who has the networks open, thank you very much,
again, it's so much appreciated. You have really no idea.
Hey, yeah, this is hit, there's number 58. Hey, I'm on airplane.
I'll go back to the 1767 somewhere halfway, yet Atlantic, cruising at a speed of 500 miles
an hour, and the altitude of 33,000 feet. Young clearly has a hundred million dollars worth of
airplane strapped to as asked where today's hit does. With a lot of noise, cramps in between two
seats right in the middle of an airplane. So I can hardly type, I hope and confine to the function
keys to start everything. But there is a hit test, so here we go, this is number one.
Well, that's, I think it was certainly within the first hundred record I ever owned,
Deon Warwick, heartbreaker. And number two.
Another one I should know was the first video of the year, the very first video of musical
awards, Don Henley, was the summer. And the final one is number three.
I recognize it. I do recognize it, but no. And times up and here are the answers
from a seat. What is it? 33 E in a 767. This is answer number one.
It's a start from 1983. It's Deon Warwick. This is a heartbreaker.
Love is really, but you and dad, I can't love you in your dreams.
Why do you have to be a heartbreaker when I was being but you are a baby?
It's got to be a dream that I love the moment.
It's past me love. It's a new world.
I'm going to New York, New York, New York International Airport.
And see number one, Deon Warwick, heartbreaker. And this is answer number two.
From 84, Don Henley and the boys of summer.
Yeah. Saw that dead head sticker on the Cadillac.
And this is a third and final answer. Also sung from 1984. This is We Are Deon.
We Are Deon.
Then Hartman, We Are Deon.
The third and final answer in today's hit test.
From Continental Flight 71 to New York International Airport,
somewhere in the middle of the plane from the economy clash,
the packaging between my trifling companion and a total stranger.
Yeah.
I have totally no idea when I can mail you this one or upload it to the server.
I suppose to have me having free Wi-Fi at the hotel.
So, feedback is still welcome at hittest.gmail.com.
And the website, yonpolit.com is where you can find some info about the hittest and the hittest
box catch that's janpolyt.com. Well, thank you for listening.
Don't expect me to know when the next one will be.
I hope somewhere in the coming days. If not, you know why.
I'm having a good time in New York and I'm trying to do some nice things here.
So, until next time, bye-bye.
All right. Yonpolit from 37,000 fees.
Sort of C33E is what it was on his way to Newark New Jersey.
Great Yon really appreciated.
Glad we could finally fit that one in.
Okay. So, that's it. Almost 35 minutes a little longer than I wanted to go.
I still got to do some production work. Then I'm going to head over to the office.
Which will be fun. And we've got two days of some hard work ahead of us. We've got some demos.
We're doing. We've got some folks coming into town tomorrow morning.
So, it's going to be pretty busy. Thank you very much for tuning in.
As always, dailysourcecode.com. I don't know. This may have been hosted not on our own podcast
delivery network, but maybe maybe I put it back on God Mac or something. So, hopefully,
this all arrives in good shape. We'll get everything fixed. And I can't do my signature sign-off
because the TSA Homeland Security confiscated my lighter. So, I can't click out of here. So,
we'll just leave it at this. I will see you tomorrow on the Daily Sourcecode.
Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.