Daily source code for March 25th, 2005 you're DJ you're DJ has only just big transmitters
We don't need no stinking transmittance
Autistic it's that I'm curing. It is Friday. Thank God
Everybody how you doing? Welcome to the Daily Source Code Friday March 25th, 2005
It's another beautiful day here outside Curry Cottage in Surrey and the UK
The once again I can see all the way to the rising
Just a few scattered clouds and full sunshine
Okay, that was my DJ a bit for the day
One down the week
So it's been a pretty busy one and today almost felt like Saturday of course it's a holiday for a many around the world
A bank holiday in many cases where I believe
Which means the bank's your clothes, right? Or it's definitely something like that
Got the email is over which is always find an entertaining
It's fun explaining podcasts to them. You know what they get it that was the coolest part of
Talking them last night
Got a couple of things we'll be doing today. Let's see a
New podcast theme song not for this one but for another one I'll play for you
Pete to pronounce checks in with another edition of Ressweb audio
We've got another aviation podcast for listen to of course you don't pull it with a hit test
I will be taking a look at the g bag
Which is the new name for my
Gmail overload and we'll pull somebody email out of that
And it was another one of those days where the weather was just so nice
You know and you kind of come into yourself. I thought oh I wouldn't be a great song to play for you
But I just share with my friends listening to the daily source code so I ran over to iTunes
Looked up sure enough there it was I was able to buy it online and share it with you
Hopefully doesn't mind lovely hurts with that you baby
Run around town like full and you think that it's good and bad
You give a smile of a guy
You give to the eye. You don't get love at the community
You say it is fun and you embrace so much
It's like me
But don't you know you're turning me home
And all that's wrong
But I can't stop
Hey, it's time to be very nice
Never really had a suit like you love really bad suit like you
And it's breaking my heart for what you do
But I never really had a suit like you love really has to run
Oh
The way that you love
You really
With a sweet guy
But
So give me a sign
But the hell do you use
And I am signifying
Love really hurts when I hear
And it's pretty long
No one can help you
Love really hurts when I hear
And it's pretty long
No one can help you
Love really hurts when I hear
And it's pretty long
No one can help you
Love really hurts when I hear
What Can I put it's really hard to put it
Telehotion
Love really hurts when I hear
Without you, babe
Baby-sourced cold Fridays, song of the day
purchase done iTunes, played for you, one time sharing deal only, of course, does not
condone doing that in your own podcast. I wish someone would send me a song just like
this, you know, nice and happy and, you know, a real good Friday feel that was pod save.
That would, I should talk to CC over at AxonHash and get him to send me a song for the
day or something. I just, it's was good, you know, when you can play that, Billy Ocean.
Interesting guy, met him a couple times back in the 80s on the TV shows,
smart guy too, but I have no idea what he's doing now. What is Billy Ocean up to? He's probably
producing other people and making tons of money, something like that. So it's actually the sun just
kind of started to slip away. It's a 430 in the afternoon here at the cottage. I've got my cup of
Senseo. He laws a real coffee drinkers. So the thing is just doing overtime. You've got the double
bagger in there. There's a little, uh, there's a little cup that you put your coffee pod in. And if you
want to sit in more than one cup, then if you want to make more, if you want two cups, they have to
put two bags in unless, you know, you like really watery coffee. Um, and so you have to put another
container, they're different, uh, a different cup holder basically for two pods stacked on top of each
other. So the thing is just, uh, it's working. And, uh, I wonder if there's a, a life span on a machine
like that. I wonder if it just breaks after a while. It's good, though. I was listening to, uh,
I should drip some coffee on my pants. I was listening to, uh, yeast radio this morning, uh,
Madge Weinstein. I'm trying to open up this note in my outline. I'm doing it via VNC, which is
like a remote screen application. There we go. And, uh, um, there seems to be some confusion, uh,
he was interviewing Eric Rice, and Eric, uh, was retelling parts of the story about how, uh,
Dave and I were a Dave Weinstein, and I were confused about, uh, Madge Weinstein. And we talked
about that on a trade secrets. And for some reason, Laura has become that we didn't know that Madge
was, I can't speak on, uh, on behalf of Dave, obviously. Um, but the law or somehow has become that
I didn't know that, um, Madge wasn't a woman. It's like, you know, dudes, duh. No, um, what, what
had surprised me at the time was that Madge, uh, was actually a character created by someone else.
I thought, you know, it really was a Jewish transgender, or, uh, gay man, 50 years old,
living in Chicago. Um, that's what surprised me. Um, and it's interesting because I told Madge,
uh, that personally, and, uh, she didn't defend me. Damn lesbian, what can you expect?
I was actually pretty funny is I listened to, uh, most of the podcasts on my set-up here at home
through the speakers. And they, you know, I said, basically run it from iTunes right off of my
Mac, and that I run that through my board, and then run actually, I do it a little differently.
If you don't mind, if, uh, just indulge me for a moment, I'll tell you exactly how it's, I have it set
up. Um, so I have an older power book on my desk that, uh, is connected to a cinema display.
And the, this display, the screen of that laptop broke and I just, you know, didn't work out
from me to send it away, and so I never did, and so I just used it on the external screen.
It has a kind of noisy fan that's starting to act up a little bit now.
But essentially, I, uh, that's sitting on the desk, and that is, uh, I don't really run any big
applications on that. Um, there's three accounts, Christina, and Patricia can log in, because
this is an eye, an eyesight connected to it, so we use that for video conferencing when any of us are
on the road or away. Yeah, when Christina's on our world tour, right? And, um, I use this program
called VNC, which is really cool. It's an open source application. You can get a server for it
and a client. And the server, you run it any computer that you want to grab the screen and grab
control of. And of course, you use the client to do, to do that, perform that act. But it works on
Mac, Windows, uh, Unix, Linux, and on the Mac, it's cool. I haven't installed on most of my Macs.
I can just, uh, SSH in, uh, and issue a command line VNC, and it'll start up the server,
which I can kill later for security purposes. Um, and, you know, as a basic, I can control any
machine on my network that way. And it works on Windows as well, except you have to really have
a server running in the background. They don't have a easy command line way to do it. I'm not that
I'm not that I'm aware of at least. Um, uh, so I control, uh, my power book, which really is my,
my workstation has everything on it. I have the audio out going into the board that comes through
a channel. The audio in is actually the monitor bus. So that way, if I want, I can send audio to someone
who's listening to me on Skype, and I can record them at the same time without they're being this
loop, and, you know, it, uh, basically creating havoc and feedback. Uh, I can route two microphones
through it, and then I have a, uh, a record out on the compact four mixer that I have. And I run that
to my M audio fire wire device, and that actually goes right into the old laptop sitting my desktop.
From there, I use a program called Line In from Rogamiba, um, and I just select the, uh,
M audio device. And now I can route anything I want to the beautiful Harman card and, uh,
uh, speakers that are attached to my Mac. So I hope that made sense. Um, when my microphone is
uh, switching on a little bit. Let me just tighten that up. Oh, uh, here we go.
Fair, perfect. Um, so, uh, I'm, I listen, I was listening to, uh, to Magic and Eric Banner
away, and I'm like, I keep, keep looking around. I was like, oh, it's someone's sending me
to Skype instant message. Like, yeah, but it was actually, uh, coming through from Magic's computer,
and I tell you, it, it's happened a couple times. I was listening to a podcast where people are
doing something on Skype and chatting with each other, and I'm looking at, you know, who's
Skypeing me now. I don't see any windows opening up. That's kind of freaky when, uh, when that happens.
Uh, let me see. Oh, uh, remember yesterday I was talking about, uh, actually I read the email about the,
the pilot, uh, who listened to the daily source code at 37,000 feet, and he had this beautiful email
that he sent, which is, it was, it was virtually poetry. Uh, you got to love this podcasting stuff,
man. It came back to me today in a little different form.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass than the next generation radio
content in my ears. I like to think I'm flying into the future.
It's Adam Curry.
Damn, I love that. That should be my new opener. I'm going to use that. That is, so I'm in this
day one more time. That was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass than the next generation
radio content in my ears. I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm just kidding. It's Adam Curry.
Ah, that is so awesome. That is great. Hold on a second. Let me put that up, uh,
the top of my outline as a part of my opening sequence. Fantastic. Love that. Thank you very
much. That's cool. That's what's so great about this is, you know, podcasting is one thing,
but how we are able to, you know, remix and rehash and mash up all the stuff we're doing
amongst each other is just an amazing amount of creativity. Speaking of which,
I've talked about Father Roderick, who is the Catholic insider, the Catholic priest from the
Netherlands who has been doing podcasts and sound seeing tours of the Vatican. He's gotten Vatican
radio to podcasts. And this guy is a total pioneer. It's great to listen to what he's doing.
And he has a new, I don't know if it was my, my iPod or what happened, but I guess I hadn't
caught a few episodes or maybe he just doesn't do him as regularly as he was when when the Pope
first fell ill. He recorded some beautiful choir in the Vatican. I've just blown away by that
and the quality is really beautiful. But he also has a feature on this show which tickled me. I'm not
going to play the whole thing, but just the the imaging of it, the sound staging and the topic
itself. Last year when I actually, I think I reviewed Dan Brown's Da Vinci code on the source code,
probably played played a little bit of the audio book, which is the way I quote Reddit and I really
enjoyed it immensely. I love the voices and yeah, it was just it was a fun listen, totally all in the
car, of course. And this is a very touchy and very controversial topic and what's taking place
now is that the church is, the Catholic church has taken to heart mission to debunk some of the
myths that are portrayed in this book, because and I have to agree with them there, just like the
Eric Rice story, you know, not Eric Rice story, but the mad story with Da Winner and I, before
you know, it that becomes like a lore and it's no possibly not true, right? So the new feature here
on the Catholic insider which I really love check it out. Investigating the Da Vinci code,
facts and fiction.
And it's time to look at some of the claims of the Da Vinci code that I mentioned in the
previous edition of the Da Vinci code investigation. And remember the reason why I think it's
important to separate fact from fiction is that Da and Brown continuously claims that his book,
although fictional, is based on historical facts and a lot of Christians and non-fiction believes
even some of you wrote me that after reading the book they didn't know what to think anymore about their
faith. The claims in the Da Vinci code go against some of the core beliefs of the Catholic church.
But is done Brown indeed using historical facts? Let's look at the first three claims.
Claim number one, the nightstumper existed. This is a fact.
Claim number two, according to the Da Vinci code English poet Alexander Pope spoke at
Isaac Newton's funeral. This is incorrect. Pope just wrote the epita that appeared
on a monument to Newton in West Minster Abbey erected years after his burial.
So you definitely should listen to that. It's a continuing episodic feature on the Catholic
insider, Catholic Insider.com. Very, very interesting. Of course it's, you know, just for Father
Roder to say true or false. It doesn't really give him any more credit than Da and Brown. But he
has some facts to back it up in some scripture and some writings. But on the end, you know,
even if Michael Jackson is actually a quitted of all claims he'll be that, you know, child molester.
That's just kind of the way folk lore goes. Looking into G-Bag, G-Mail,
um, interesting comments. Hold on, now I'm trying to, I'm trying to open up the comments themselves.
There we go. Let's see, this was, it's an email about Christina. Oh yeah, from David Banks and
Hi, listen to your tale of Browning Christina. This is the whole thing about her mouthing off and
having lack of respect for stuff and other people stuff and I didn't let her go to the good
Charlotte concert, which she'd been planning for three quarters of a year. She said, like a thank you,
David says, like the thank you for setting a good parenting example. I've got a 12-year-old boy
and it's difficult to raise kids nowadays, so many parents seem to feel that they have to be their
kids best friends instead of being a parent and setting limits. Hard to do throughout the years,
but it sounds like you are raising a great kid. Hopefully, when she's 20 years social,
appreciate it. Thank you, David. Banks and thanks David. A great email. Yeah, you know, we don't
talk about that enough, really, I guess, about parenting. You know, the one thing you learn
when you're first starting off in computing is read the fucking manual and of course,
you know, there is no, there is no stank in manual, which makes it that much more interesting.
Speaking of that concert, a good Charlotte concert that Christina did not get to go to,
that was at Bricks in Academy. Derek Peters pointed out that there was a shooting at the
NAS concert at Bricks in the Academy that the day after we were there, she says, yeah, I know
it was a different show from good Charlotte took place after it, but it might make it a bit
easier for your daughter to get over not going to Bricks than it can be pretty rough. It has
pretty amazing gunfire and mid-performance at the NAS concert in Bricks in Academy. It's
what is the world coming to? The cops don't even have guns hardly in the UK, but NAS's fans do.
Got a lot of email from people about acid. Yesterday, I sent out a request for explanation.
Basically, it's a popular looping and music editing software from Sony, says Michael Ridley.
DJ Danger Mouse used it to produce the now infamous Jay-Z Beatles Grey album,
but does not have the ability to do what was described. This was Michael who
excuse me, damn, since so. This is Michael who came up with I think is an ingenious idea to
send control files out for mashups instead of the mashup themselves so that your computer essentially
will assemble the mashup because you presumably have the files necessary to create it and then the
mashup, you just get those control files and your computer, yeah, it basically does all the
mixing for you, which I think is a great idea. You know, this is somehow I can't get the control buttons
to work properly on VNC. I'm trying to open up, there we go, trying to open up different nodes
here in the outliner. Another email, let me see from Michael Oster, in your 321 source code you mentioned,
wanting to know if others are using the I-river with an external mic, yeah, that I did ask about that,
because I'm basically using my receiver of the wireless mic set as a kind of a preamp,
which explains a lot of the great sound. Michael says, I just got the I-river 899, which is best
by his version. Same as the 7-in, 99, and the same price too. Okay, hooked up a set of stealth microphones,
which are installed in a common headphones set. I record stereo through an 20 kilobits per second.
Sound is really nice, especially for sound-seeing tours, completely stealth, and he has a couple of
links there where you can check that out. Michael Oster, and of course you can read about all that
in the show notes for today. And then finally, this thing that got a lot of press over here
in the UK, the day it came out, but then it almost went away overnight. The PSP, the PlayStation
portable, if you've been hearing about this, this is, it sounds like it's an interesting device,
because a couple of people sent me a link to information about it. Yunky Dunk, from Gamers Radio
podcast, sent me some information. I see about the PSP portable video device, perfect for
my podcast, he says, because it's designed to be a portable gaming system, but you can also use
it as a portable audio or video player. This will allow for video gamers to listen to the audio
podcast and watch the video podcast between games that are on them when they're on the go. Right.
So we're doing anything but concentrating on being on the go. The PSP releases Thursday the 24th
in the US and has been delayed for Europe until the summer. Okay. And he has a couple links in there
as well. So I guess the big question is, can you record with it? Because that's what I'm still
looking for. And I think the I River, I got to tell you the I River really has a lot of machines
beat so far in the MP3 space. I mean, all the recording options they have just fantastic. It can
also record regular FM radio, you know, which there's still a lot of value to that. But yeah,
it's a great device. It is, it truly is a one and all and it's quick. If you just want to
listen to some stuff and you don't want to deal with playlists and just want to jam something onto
it. Boom, you know, it's on and it's basically in a file system so it's easy to understand where you can
find stuff. And there's more information on curry.com. Oh, blatant commercial plug, there's a link
there. I'm an Amazon associate. So if you buy one, I get a little hit from that and it's much appreciated
because it just proves that, you know, we can like make money with podcasting.
Hi, Adam. This is another hit this. I am very fresh for time. So we're going to do it
very quick. Number one. I want to say Scruti Politi and Absolute, but I'm not sure. This is number two.
I know this one. I know this one. Is it sheena eastern? You've got the look?
I think it is. Yeah, I think it's sheena eastern. You've got the look. Pretty sure I got that one.
And the final one. Number three.
Nope. I got a pass on that one. I'm sorry, young. Times up. This is answer number one.
It's senderfold. I'm a trader. Oh, man, senderfold. Another fine Dutch trio.
Okay. It was guys also produced some of Patricia's hits. You can tell it's the same kind of
actually it produced this band after they did Patricia's stuff. Remember,
flysmart for time. We're talking about on the VPP podcast.
Number two. In today's hit test.
It's Prince. Who's got the look? Why do I think it was sheena eastern? I know. Damn. I know
the Prince wrote it, but I'm just an idiot. And now I saw like a real
door. Oh, she's sang on it. There you go. She's singing with it. That's it.
Remember?
Prince and who's got the look? Number two in today's hit test.
Oh, no way. Was that for her?
Oh, a tough clue, man. And this is answer number three. For her, say you will.
I can't sleep. I can't dream in a blue blue blue blue hit deal.
Make up your mind to now.
Oh, that voice. Whoo champ.
You want me again.
The third and final answer in today's hit test, foreigner and say you will.
Well, I really got to go.
So, let me say very quick that you can send your feedback to hittestingmail.com
and the only information about this hittestin hittest podcast
can be found at jompolet.nl, this JNPL80.nl.
Well, Adam, see you in a couple of days for next hit test.
I think after the Easter holiday, so see you later, bye-bye.
Thank you very much once again, great songs.
Just like now, I feel like I got to run over to my iTunes music store
and go buy some foreigner tracks.
I'm pretty amazed by the experience I have to say of iTunes music store.
It really is pretty damn cool.
I mean, you can't have better show prep.
It will be so easy for these guys to license it for extra money.
You know, we could totally come up with a fee for that.
You know, just make a podcast button and then, you know, that would be it.
It would be, oh, man, I would love that so much.
Okay.
By the way, Jan, how did a young one over and look at some of the grandmaster view screens
to company have an investment in.
And he was looking for something very specific.
You should let us know how that is, Jan.
Make some commercial noise here for a little bit of my companies.
It's turning into the real commercial show, isn't it? Oh, my goodness.
Aviation talk.
As if we haven't had enough geek stuff.
Now it's aviation stuff.
So the concept of sound seeing tours and aircraft is great.
I love it.
I'd love to hear some other types of aircraft.
If you're pilot, send a send me a link to your podcast where you, you're in the cockpit.
I used to love that by the way.
I think it's Delta United Airlines.
I used to have Channel 7 from the flight deck.
And unless the captain turned it off, which some of them did by the way,
you could essentially listen in.
And I remember one time being at Newark, flight to San Francisco.
And it was one of those days when Newark was backed up.
Three hour delays.
Finally got on the plane.
And you know, as a taxi was just, well, that knows the tail literally.
So at least another hour just getting out to the taxiway to get to a runway.
And I was listening to the cockpit and the tower was, you know,
well, ground actually ground control was actually going pretty bizarre.
Just trying to figure out who was who, and I remember saying, like,
United 65.
He just flash your lights.
So I can see if that's you.
And that was my first clue as before.
I was a pilot.
My first clue that not everything is as controlled as you'd want it to be in aviation.
But you know, it's a lot of really hardworking people who don't get paid a lot of money
by the way, pilots or other staff, other aviation workers.
There's not a lot of money in it.
Some people make a lot of money from it.
But in it it's very hard.
You may not think that often about what goes on in the control tower.
But there's a lot happening there as well.
It's, you know, it's been very glorified by television.
But, you know, there's a lot to be done.
You know, there's weather updates.
There's basically making sure planes don't bump into each other on their approach, helping them out,
helping them in, making sure they see the airfield.
I mean, it's a lot less automatic than you think it is, or then you've been led to believe that it may be.
I mean, there's people, very skilled people who do this, who transport you from one place to the other.
And after the aviation podcast in the past couple of days,
Misha Masjar, I hope, pronounced that kind of close, who has Misha's minute podcast,
sent in his most recent one.
And it was just enthralling.
I couldn't stop listening to this.
This is the Mike has been a podcast for March 20th, 2005.
5 star 122.
Congratulations, visual approach from way 25.
Clear to land runway 25 remain this frequency.
1, 2, 9, or 0, at 9, or 0, at 9, or 0.
How's everybody doing this evening?
This is the tower admission of the Mike's minute podcast.
And right now, we're looking everything compliant over the tower.
Right hour tower, everything.
One person showed the student, which is our standard practice on Friday Saturday.
We're going to be a gigare.
I've been for 4,55 here at Charlie's, that you want 11,000.
Here are 45 five stars.
Charlie Toledo, approach out, 103, 0, 11,
103,000.
Expect the visual approach runway 25.
3,000 is 25.
So the frightening thing is actually understand exactly what he's saying there.
But it's great.
And in between talking to different aircraft as they're on their approach and he's helping
him get into the airfield, helping the metacopter get out and assisting them with the in flight
change of flight plan.
He's doing the podcast.
It's amazing to listen to this.
Even if you're not interested in aviation,
it's good to know how that works.
It's funny because at a certain point,
I don't have it cut up.
There's an American eagle flight that's coming in.
And this is, so this is how you'll love this.
The American eagle flight says,
you know, hey, we didn't really burn off all of our taxi fuel,
wherever they're left from.
Because this is all calculated right down to the gallon.
You know, they know or pounders, they say.
They know exactly how much fuel they need for each flight.
Because if you know, the more fuel you have, the heavier you're going to be.
The less efficient you're going to be flying.
I mean, this is all.
Aviation is a total spreadsheet business.
So I guess they didn't, you know,
they overestimated the amount of taxing fuel.
The fuel they need for taxing at their departure airport and whatever they need at the,
at the airport of arrival.
And so the pilot says,
you know,
we didn't burn off all our fuel.
So could you give us a, like a long final,
which basically means instead of coming to the airfield,
you know, hang in a, a right,
in this case, a right turn,
and then another right to land.
He would get it like a 10 or a 15 mile final.
So you'll be all the way out, 10,
15 miles,
and then you can just burn off some excess fuel straight into the airport.
It's funny, you know,
they could have also opted to have given everybody a little refund on the way out, I guess, but.
And that also, by the way,
is not just for the purposes of finances,
but I think actually in this case,
they were pretty much up to their maximum weight.
So, you know,
when you load passengers on and baggage,
and then you've got your,
your fuel,
no, that way is something.
And you expect that to diminish after X amount of time.
And they were very close to the maximum landing weight.
Probably for the length of the field,
they were landing at.
So just to burn off a little of that,
we'll give them a little more margin,
a little more safety margin there.
So that's really what that was about,
but it's just funny to hear how all that works.
This is the daily source code,
in case you'd forgotten and tuned out and came back.
And of course, you had to start
all over again at the beginning,
because the iPod won't bookmark anything,
and MP3 files are hard to bookmark.
Except, by the way,
did I tell you that on the creative labs,
the one I got it in Redmond,
it bookmarks.
You can actually bookmark an MP3 file, which is very cool.
And here's Pete,
our buddy, Raster Web,
the more sound sings the web audio,
more of 2005, low 3, 23.
Well, if you heard our last podcast,
we did a, we tried to do a mobile podcast.
I don't know how it worked.
You know, what it was, it's retarded.
I had to kind of yell,
because I don't have a portal recording device,
but I've got some new equipment today.
And I think this will actually work a little better.
Check out Pete's equipment.
I'm going to start right now.
I'm going to have to run,
because I don't have a lot of time.
Okay.
We're running upstairs.
One, one second.
Let's go.
Okay.
We heard that last time.
Here's the dining room.
Where we got four chairs and stuff.
We have a,
sorry about that.
I like going.
We have a front door here.
I'm going to close the door.
You can also hear what that sounds like.
We go over here.
There's the living room.
Then the television here.
Turn it on.
Let's do it over here.
Next slide's turn that off.
We'll probably get, probably get soon by the,
I hear some of that.
The more stuff.
And there's a door right here.
I can hear it.
Turn it on.
Close the door.
It's another bathroom.
Water.
We got water in this bathroom.
We got running water in the house.
Still, so that's pretty good.
Come on in.
And, you know, the bedroom.
Where all the action happens.
My action there for you.
We're actually, mostly overnight.
So, sorry, let's go to the bottom again.
That's about it.
That's the rest of me.
Don't sing normally, simply.
And back in the dying room.
There's, oh no.
There's, there's basically a turn.
Looks like we've got a broken string though.
That really sucks.
Okay.
Well, hold on.
And we're going back down to the basement.
Here we go.
Okay.
I almost fell down the steps.
But it's okay.
And that concludes this sound saying tour.
Thank you.
And good night.
Figure dick.
But even, you know, it kind of backfires because even though it was done to the walkie-talkie,
I still immediately had a visual of your house.
You know, it was probably a combination of houses I've lived in or been in.
But I had a total visual.
You know, it's just, it's crazy.
It doesn't, the quality doesn't even matter all that much turns out.
You kind of get used to it too.
It's like you get used to AM radio after a while.
My favorite girls, the list of views, biddies have been doing the bitty cast for a while.
It's great.
Like 15 minutes.
They're on the road.
They're all in four chicks with instruments in a hotel room.
And it's at bittycast.com as we can pick up the podcast.
Bittiesforever.com is their website and web logging where you can buy their CD.
Great music.
And of course, if you do a podcast and you're, and it's about a group about what you go through in a band.
And life on the road and life at home and life studying and life working to make ends meet.
And life about podcasting while doing all this in a podcast thing.
You know, you got to do your own theme song, you know?
But I'm written in the IQ who just can't say the name.
But believe me, it won't matter to you when you've learned to play the game.
Sitting and snapping or singing along.
Favorite bitty or favorite song as long as you like it.
It's okay with us.
And if you don't like it, get back on the bus.
And if you stay put, then your loss will be us.
We can only pray.
Man, I love those girls.
The CBS bitties check out the bitty cast for sure.
Another great episode to listen to.
Let's see, what are we doing for now?
We're doing for time.
Let me just check the trusty eye river.
Beautiful 36 minutes just time for a final match for the day.
Jimphew sent this in.
He says, hi, excuse this direct approach.
Couple of guys that get your bootleg on.
Said it might be an idea to send you links to tunes because you do a very popular podcast.
We're piled shirt here.
What does that mean?
We're piled shirt, piled shirt.
There you go.
Here's our take on Ravelle's Bollero classic.
And the clapping song with Ursula 1000 in the engine room.
All right, trying to get up.
Get those here, bud.
Pump the never body.
Clap the roll.
Clap.
I'll be so drunk, I guess I'm so drunk
I'm not sure you can find me, I'll rob that guy
She's a friend of mine, she's a friend of mine
And that was the freaking end of it all
I was so drunk, I'm not sure you can find me, I'll rob that guy
I was the freaking end of it all.
Oh man, what a bummer.
Didn't quite get the whole thing.
I don't want to be in this.
Oh, it's all in the world.
Kind of anti-climactic there.
All right.
That's it for your daily source code for Friday,
the 25th of March 2005.
One more day tomorrow we're at home.
Helping the emulsives figure out the navigator at the car
so they can get the supermarket.
And then Sunday, we're off a vacation to the lovely South Beach, Florida.
The power of the door is close.
Can't wait.
Sunshine, pool, beach.
And my podcast.
F.E.3 player.
We got the sound scene here all night.
You know what?
I'm going to go golfing.
When does somebody can whack them?
Figure out how to freaking golf.
That's the sound scene to what we could do together.
All right.
Comments item of curie.com.
We've become it on the weblog www.curie.com.
Let me source code.com.
We can pick up the archives, the latest show,
and the podcast feed.
I'll see you on Monday for sure.
Everybody take care.
Bye-bye.