Delta share Charlie 2-3-2.
You're DJ.
Your DJ has only just begun.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
And it is August 31st, 2005.
I almost want to do a Spike Lee there and say it's August 31st.
In the year of our lower 2005.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It's Wednesday for the Daily Source Code.
We've got a real pressure cooker going on here in Gilford in Curry Cottage.
Not only the Convair, but now I have additional redundant backup fan running as well.
It's like 31 degrees centigrade today.
It's too hot.
It is 10 minutes before 3, so my timing of course is excellent.
It's always got a record in the afternoon when the sun is shining right through the bedroom window.
The studio Cottage.
The second bedroom course.
That's all because once again, not a really smooth night.
Patricia has this bronchial infection.
It's the same thing I had in New York where she kind of skated through it.
She's got a bad man.
But she's got Panicillin.
So it's just a little bit of hacking and coughing at night that keeps us away.
So we slept in and it was nice.
I think we woke up around 9.30pm until 10.30pm.
Of course we're still enjoying the fact that Christina has vacation from school.
She starts on Monday and she's enjoying it as well.
She's laying out in the backyard, sunbathing.
It's kind of cool because she's been going into town almost every single day.
And she said, you know what, guys, I'll stay home with you today.
I'm going to sit in the sun.
Yeah.
We'll have some more parental teenager talks today in the show.
Amongst other topics of course.
Because you've been sending a lot of interesting feedback.
We'll continue a bit on the bio diesel stuff.
And as I said, the teenager conversation.
Promo's coming away in a nice and mellow pod save tomb.
And to kick it off today with the mashup.
This is one that art from mashuptown.com sent me a couple days ago.
I've heard people talking about it, but I hadn't actually heard it myself.
But I picked it up, I was like, oh yeah.
Yeah, I'm digging this.
The doors take a walk down Sesame Street.
Mashup by Pilsher.
And of course brought to you by mashuptown.com.
Just listen to this man.
Totally gonna love him.
See you tomorrow.
But I know that I am a vet...
We are beating...
But I know that I...
DIE!
Hey, call me my guy tonight
It's the boy face, baby, you'll win now
They all want me, you'll be dead as me
So they're awesome, that's me, that's me
I'm not the boy, I'm not the boy, I'm not the boy
I'm not the boy, I'm not the boy
I'm not the boy
Ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready
ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready
ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, set, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready to finish, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready, ready,
street, uh, piled shirt. So that's the doors, uh, the Menamanagai, which, of course,
as universal goes back to my youth, you can pretty much stand in a street corner anywhere
in the United States and go Menamanagai. And someone will go,
t t t t t t t t t t t t t t t little macaroni and a thrown in. And as an experiment,
uh, today, I'm going to put in links to, um, the originals that are heard in the mashup,
and in the hit test as well. We have a hit test today, y'all pull that, uh, sending a man every
single day now. Um, I still haven't been approved for iTunes music store to be in a
city, so I put in, um, links to yesterday's hit test from Amazon. And of course,
I've been doing a great, almost this young palette sending me an instant message,
uh, y'all doing the show. I'll do the show back to you later. Um, I've been doing
great business with Amazon with the, uh, with the senseo coffee makers. I'm telling you,
I make about a hundred to two hundred bucks a month on selling, uh,
selling senseo. Um, so I'll put that in the extended outline of the show notes.
You notice now that I have, um, uh, show notes that just do the top level
notes of the outline that are embedded into the weblog, which, of course,
also become the description for the RSS feeds so that that pops up in iTunes.
And then it has a link there if you want to, uh, go to the full outline.
And that's where I'm going to put, uh, the links in to the, uh, to the music.
And I'll see, I'll, I'll let, you know, exactly what I'm selling. If anyone
clicks on those. Because these, of course, are CDs. You know, uh,
some of them second hand from Amazon. So it's a little different than purchasing an
iTunes music track. But I'm sure that eventually I'll get approved. I would
hope. Uh, as a part of the continuing, um,
experiment that is the show notes. And this, I'm, I'm totally
living in outlines these days because there's so much to do. I've outlines for
Pod Show. I've personal outlines. I, I just keep lists everywhere and try to
merge them all together because I'm always coming up with ideas for the source
of some other show or anything. You know, so just I got to keep lists all over the place.
Kevin Crossman, uh, as did many other people sent me an email. He said, uh,
didn't like the new show notes form at it first, but I do like seeing the text of the email.
So, uh, net positive at this point. Uh, but then he goes on to say,
it wasn't a big deal for me. A podcast was email address all over the net,
but those, uh, others might object to you posting their email addresses in the show notes.
Um, and, uh, I didn't even think about it. I mean, I,
my email address is so out there that, uh, although I must say spam has gotten pretty
good. Gmail is doing a reasonable job for me on that. Maybe only ten or
twenty a day, but, you know, nothing out of the ordinary. Uh, but yeah,
if you do leave your email address out, it can get harvested and can get
spammed. I hadn't even thought of it that way. I thought maybe just pure privacy
issues. No one really seems to have much of a problem with that. Anyway,
I've taken, uh, the, uh, the most safest, um, uh, track in this,
and I've just deleted all email addresses, uh, from the show mode to show notes,
but I still like putting the, the actual emails in there. And of course,
any links that are, uh, contained in that, um, do show up. So we're going to,
keep it going this way. And also I'll put in a,
a link to a real opium alpha. I link to the MP3. Okay.
It's Wednesday. Um, and,
and yesterday, we just touched briefly on, um,
the damage that Hurricane Katrina has done.
And already today, the podcast community is responding,
and I think it's important that we talk about this.
Hello, it's me,
which you talk about the first. Hey, know what?
Nothing's funny today.
Has caused that hurricane to head down there.
Oh, here's bad. Now, now you're saying it on the news and stuff.
And there's a bunch of people down there, the lies is tore up.
They ain't got an ass to live in. Nothing to eat.
Nothing to drink.
Ain't got no nothing.
No clothes. They don't need some help.
They really are. Now, if you be so kind,
it's a go like to the salvation army and give some clothes.
Some old clothes or your shoes and stuff.
Now, if you go red cross dot org,
and it's given some money or some time and years,
that'd be so good.
If you could do that, you'd just be precious.
Because they need some help.
And I think we ought to just lean into it and give them some help.
I'd really appreciate it.
And I know they would. Do you know what?
You would do.
Now, this is Richard Tolberat.
I've heard him as scenes.
All right.
Thank you very much.
Richard Tolberat, the third from the five minutes with
Richard Tolberat, the third podcast.
And Richard Tolberat and I've had a kind of an offline email
conversation.
How stupid does that sound?
Offline email conversation, email conversation,
but not being podcast yet.
His idea is to do some sort of podathon
for the victims of Katrina.
And he says, you know,
we can pull the serious satellite into.
We can do stuff there.
And I've, you know,
I've just been thinking,
what can we do with this?
Because we do have a great community of podcasts.
I might, first of all,
I think we have to establish at the best place right now
to lend your supporters to the American Red Cross.
It's red cross dot org.
And of course, I have a link to that in my show notes.
And if you,
you can either help out with your own time.
I think donating blood is,
is a useful option from what I've understood.
And definitely donating money.
And I,
I don't know if it's going to,
I don't know how we'd put a podathon together
because the whole asynchronous nature
and not live nature of podcast.
Doesn't really lend itself so well.
But maybe if we all just really promote
the red cross dot org and,
you know,
given whatever you can,
a couple bucks,
anything that you can offer
will make a difference.
If there's other organizations
that we should be aware of,
then let me know,
just send it to atamaccurry.com
and we'll start plugging them.
I think that the best thing we can do right now
in,
in the podcasting universe
is to make these kinds of public service announcements
and just to disperse them
so that anyone with a podcast can just easily
pick up an MB3,
play it,
and we'll be helping out.
I'll be happy to make some myself as well.
I just really like to know,
what is the best thing we can do?
What is the,
what is the best way that you can help?
Particularly if you're just sitting in your easy armchair
and don't want to go down,
I tell you,
if I had a helicopter
and I was in Louisiana,
I know what I'd be doing right now.
That's for sure.
But in this case,
I guess donating money is the best way to help.
So if there's other ways,
let me know,
and then I think we should start cutting promos
and distributing those far and wide.
And if you have any ideas
of how we could do something
with all the podcasters
and with the serious satellite radio,
and we should probably do that next week.
So after the Labor Day weekend,
and you know,
by then lots of the relief efforts
and the news were probably have been moved on
to the next horrible event in the world,
but the money and relief efforts
will still be needed.
So I think there'll probably be a great time
to do something and a happily
offer up the serious radio time
and I know which at all will as well.
So just drop us a mail.
Let us know what we can do.
And just to prove the point
that people are thinking about this,
a couple more hurricane relief
public service announcements.
We're all concerned with the disaster
from Hurricane Katrina.
And here at radioenergywx.com
and hurricaneproject.org,
we are going to help with the efforts
to get people affected
back on their feet
by donated to the American Red Cross.
Please visit our websites radio.nacwx.com
and hurricaneproject.org
and click on the Red Cross Manors
to make a donation directly.
We will also be donating
any funds created from the purchases
on any of the sponsor manners on those sites.
Additionally,
radio-nacwx will match the funds
created from you clicking
on the Google ads on those sites.
The radio-nac donation drive
will last through September 30 of 2005.
So please visit radio.nacwx.com
and hurricaneproject.org
and click to make a donation.
So we all can help with the long recovery
from devastating hurricane Katrina.
Thank you very much for your support.
And thank you for listening.
Pod Show
Content that will make you walk the dog
and kiss your mother.
This is Dave from the Dave's Lounge podcast
at Dave's Lounge.com.
The devastation brought by Hurricane Katrina
along the Gulf Coast of the United States
is torn apart countless families
and left hundreds of thousands of people
with no homes, no livelihoods,
and little hope for the future.
The American Red Cross
is now undertaking the largest disaster recovery operation
in its history.
And now more than ever,
this organization needs your support.
The Red Cross currently needs money
for rescue boats, power generators,
search and rescue equipment,
drinking water,
and other supplies necessary to save lives
and rebuild towns.
Please go to www.redcross.org
to donate to their hurricane 2005 food.
If you are unable to give money,
please consider donating blood.
Contact your local Red Cross chapter
for information on upcoming blood threats.
Please help the victims of hurricane Katrina
because in times of crisis,
all we really have is each other.
Thank you.
And that, by the way, is the American way.
That is what Americans always do
we're always pitching in to help our neighbors.
I'm not saying that other countries don't do it,
but it's the strongest in the United States of America.
So two great public service announcements there
and I agree, I think the best thing you can do
is just send it off us and off your donation to the Red Cross.
I'm pretty sure you can even do it with PayPal.
I got a check.
I haven't made my own donation yet.
I just want to make sure that I'm donating to the right organization,
but it seems like Red Cross is the way to go.
I was going to say.
Yeah.
I really, at the pod of thorn,
you know, keeping totals of how much you raise
that seems so egotistical.
You know, I just want to bypass everything
and get everyone focused on going to one website,
Red Cross.org as the best example I have now
and donate money.
Okay.
Right.
I got to say after hearing that promo,
I immediately went to the pod safe music network
and got a really mellow tune for today.
I just had a real mellow vibe and so hot.
A little more on bio diesel.
I'm talking about this,
that I'm turning into a big fan of bio diesel
where you just take a crap in your tank and your engine runs
or something like that or you throw your old vegetable oil in there
and it's all kinds of ways to make bio diesel.
My cross of news is free.com wrote me.
It says about the current state of oil supply,
there's this thing called tar sands,
basically oil,
which was not trapped under a non porous layer of rock,
so the liquid and gas part is evaporated,
leaving only tar in sand type soil.
Okay.
I've seen that before.
I've had it on my feet.
Loads of that in Canada more than in Gulf,
apparently, in the Gulf, I guess.
And we know exactly where it is.
Getting the oil out of that is expensive though.
You can't pump it.
It's more like mining.
We've cost about 45 bucks a barrel.
But with the current price of oil,
it wouldn't be economically viable.
Of course, this means more oil related to pollution
for a longer time.
Bloody bloody bloody bloody brown.
Okay.
So that's just a little bit of info.
And of course, I'm posting all these in the show notes.
So you can read them without email addresses.
Great link from Tom Schuuring.
He maintains my old radio days website,
which I really appreciate.
He recently sent me,
you know, I think I told you about this.
I sent him a whole box, a huge cardboard box
to Australia of old cassette tapes of all my radio shows.
And he digitized them all, put him up as a podcast.
And he sent me, I think, four or five DVDs with my entire,
you know, just or a large bit of my radio career archive.
Which is so incredibly nice.
So he has a great link to a pizza shop
that uses their excess oil every month for their car.
Using that as biodiesel, just dilute it a little bit,
drop it right in.
Oh, this one's in the wrong spot.
I don't want to have that one there.
And then this was interesting.
Paul Clark says this may sound stupid.
And you can dismiss it if you like,
but I've been receiving numerous emails about a rumor
that a not a drop day will be held on September 1st,
not a drop day convincing people to not buy gas
forcing the oil companies to lower their prices.
You live in the UK.
You pay a lot more for petrol than we do here in the States.
If you feel it's a notable cause,
maybe give a little leap out to your viewers,
while listeners then this case.
I don't know if that helps.
I really don't.
I mean, it's this whole thing.
It was pointed out to me through listener feedback
that the price of oil is determined in free open markets.
And it's supply and demand.
And it's just clear what's happening.
There's worry for the demand and for the increasing supply.
So we've got some problems.
But I guess at some point we're going to have to give up the SUVs.
We got to give up the Hummer.
I know I'm getting rid of this Audi.
I think I can get rid of it because I least it for three years.
And I want to get rid of it as soon as possible.
It's way overqualified for our mission.
As I said, I want to diesel.
I want something I can just throw some junk into the tank.
You know, not necessarily.
Well, yeah, just a proof of point, I guess.
You got to start somewhere.
Right.
We talked about the Cessna 182 versus the Cirrus SR22.
And Nigel says, we're just listening to your show.
You mentioned the SR22, my pals at test pilot for it.
And I went up for a test flight with him.
A real test flight?
Or was it certified by that?
It's actually a great plane.
Don't knock it.
You also mentioned the plane is destroyed after shoot deployment
and landing.
Not true.
The landing gear only needed replacing in several tests
performed in Minnesota.
Besides, it gives a crap about the state of the plane when you survived.
You know what it is?
I think with the Cirrus besides the entire wing construction.
If you ever see a Cirrus SR22,
ask the owner's permission first.
But stand on, go to one wing and just jolt it up and down like
like you were having turbulence.
And then listen to what the sound to the sound the wings make.
It just it freaks me out.
Now, this plane is beautiful.
It's got the full glass cockpit.
You don't have a yolk.
You really, well, you have a stick right on the left hand side.
Very much like an airbus does to control it.
I think I'm just one of those old fashioned guys.
You know, I was taught in the old fashioned by old fashioned pilots.
The wing commander, of course.
I, you know, I really like, I really like the old avionics.
I mean, yeah, of course a GPS with autopilot.
Of course, that's wonderful.
But just for the pure flying of it,
I really love, you know, getting the VORs and getting,
and picking up ILSs and but doing it on the old.
You know, kind of like the World War II is,
I feel much more in touch with the actual flight than doing everything
through a glass cockpit.
And I'd like a yolk much more.
And I think that really if you compare the two aircraft,
the SESN and 182RG and the CRS SR22.
And you want to take, you know, take four full grown adults and baggage.
I think you're going to want the SESN out,
particularly with the black edition engine that I'm getting put in.
So I think I think that's going to be a better utility plane.
Now if you want to pick up chicks, the SR22 is, of course,
completely the way to go.
A little bit more on the teenagers conversation.
Rishub Kumar, who I think emails Christina a lot.
He says is a big difference between teenage guys and girls.
And he says, it's just me as a scene that more than 95% of advertisements
on television are directed at girls.
Girls seem to do almost nothing, but talk about fashion.
And guys, well, advertising is in my opinion,
turning today's girls into fashion zombies.
And you got to read this.
This is a, okay.
The more I read feedback from teenagers who are listening to the source code,
the more I realize that, well, this two parts to it.
One is, yeah, this is exactly the age when you are emancipating.
And I could see it with Christina.
And she wants to be all grown up.
And we're sitting here watching TV, watching the news,
seeing what happens to kids and all kinds of crazy stuff from,
you know, drinking to murders, you know,
and you just get freaked out.
You know, kids can certainly understand that.
And of course you think, ah, nothing's going to happen.
But it happens to someone.
And this is it.
For Patricia and I, this is the kick, the bird out of the nest stage.
And it's, it's, it's definitely, it's complicated.
It really, obviously.
Honor you up here.
Hi.
I want to get Patricia back on the podcast.
Because I think it's great when she comes in to roast me.
She has some always has interesting things to say.
And I wanted to talk to her about this on the show.
You know what, I'm going to see if I can, well,
if she walks upstairs, I'll pull her in.
And Field said that he saw my show notes yesterday that I was going to talk about the MTB video,
musical awards.
I guess I didn't, you know,
did he, of course, the artist formerly known as PDD hosted the show.
And, and I, it's finally dawned on me.
He doesn't really have any talent.
And I think that's what really brought the show down.
I mean, I've been going to video musical awards,
and it've been in the minute of co-hosted them for a long time.
And, you know, first of all, the video,
there's supposed to be a lot less slick, you know,
and you always had to have someone beating up on someone else
for, you know, going out with their girlfriend.
We haven't had any of that.
And, you know, so now it's the bad words, you know,
it's like the fox and the shits and the whatever and the mother fuckers.
And so that's like, and it gets applause.
It's unbelievable.
You know, if that's the only thing you can do to say,
hey, we're bad.
We're, we're anti-establishment,
which MTB clearly isn't anymore.
And Peter, you know, he had, he had some,
what he does well as he surrounds himself
with very talented people, which, by the way,
is the right way to go.
And so he's got, you know, he had a couple of great dance routines,
which he didn't do too much of the dancing in,
but it, you know, it's surrounded him,
and that was really good.
He didn't really have any great jokes.
Okay, so he gave away his watch, you know,
he gave away probably a 40 or 50,000 dollar watch, you know.
Okay, so that's this thing,
but he wasn't particularly funny.
There was no real writing done for him clearly.
And that's, that's tough.
You know, hosting an award show,
I think it has to be more than just an image.
You gotta, and I think really comedians are the way to go with that.
And, and those are usually great hosts of great shows.
So, there was that, and then it did seem very,
very R&B hip hop, rap oriented,
and I don't think that reflects
the state of the music business.
You know, we had a,
what do we have Green Day?
Green Day was kind of a rock song,
and we had the Gwen Stefani.
Oh, Kelly Clarkson.
She, I mean, she was something went wrong with her.
She was like, first of all, I don't think her,
I don't think her monitoring was right.
She couldn't, she didn't have the right sound
in her ears, because she was adjusting the audio pack the whole time.
She was really off-key, and just yelling,
and the whole idea was cool,
but I didn't pan out the way I think she wanted it to.
So, little disappointed by today's video music awards.
And the other day I was talking about,
you know, how, if you look at MTV,
and you see the videos,
how it seems to be pretty much centered around being in the club,
and everything's happening in the club,
and we're going to the club,
and we're successful,
and I'm drinking in the club,
and that's what all the songs about in the club.
We're totally welcome to picked up on it.
He sent me this little ditty.
Yo, what's up? This is Chris Rock,
and I'm on my man, little John,
and we stay in the club.
We live in the club.
We die in the club.
We get our car washed in the club.
We go to school in the club.
We go to the cleaners in the club.
We never live in a motherfucking club.
We go to church in the club.
We do everything in a motherfucking club.
We pay our taxes in the club.
We go to library in the club.
Yo, I think he's onto the same thing I'm on to.
This is in the club thing.
We got to stop with that.
And we talked briefly about MP3 licensing.
Drew sent me some feedback about that,
and I've gotten this,
received this same recommendation from lots of other people.
There is a format out there,
the Aug Form at OGG,
which is comparable to MP3,
but doesn't have any of the patents on it.
From time to time,
we'll get a whole slew of people asking me
to release the source code in the format like that.
I don't think it's proliferated,
but when it does,
we should seriously consider it.
Just keep in tabs on it.
Congratulations to Donna Drew.
Drew Domkis now,
a full-time podcaster.
He's given notice that his day job.
And so he'll be living the day.
He'll be living the day.
He'll be living the dream.
He will be podcasting and producing podcast full-time.
And I congratulate both of them.
And let's hang out soon, y'all.
And finally,
Sergei,
he says,
the title of his email,
TV screen brain melting.
Remember, when I was a kid,
my parents used to say,
don't sit too close to the television.
And don't watch more than an hour a day.
A friend of his been using computers for as long as he can remember.
It's his job.
He used the first PCs with a green and black screen.
The TV screens and computer screens are basically the same thing.
But the computers just sit close.
Anyway, that's at least what he says.
There are some extremely low radiation monitors out there.
I don't know if they're they're useful or not.
But he's been sitting front of monitors every day day after day for years.
Now,
and now he's bald.
And he started getting less hair in his early 20s.
And his early 20s,
known as family has ever had problems with that.
After some research from medical websites and books,
he found out that the freaking screens made the problem.
We just back off a little bit here from the Power book.
I don't want to get any kind of problems.
This is the TV Talk podcast.
I'm Davis.
And I'm Mary.
Every week from most part,
we chat in chat about the latest and greatest TV shows.
Discuss the latest in TV news.
And we compile our own weekly top 11 lists.
Like for example,
our favorite TV characters,
favorite theme songs,
and favorite TV villains.
Every week we have a new one.
And thankfully,
we try to avoid an annoying,
funny voice stick that plays so many other podcasts.
We try to keep it real,
so to speak.
Murph and I live on different coasts.
Me and San Francisco,
and Murph and Delaware.
We go on the phone,
and talk it up right now.
If you'd like to surprise us,
the key to our deadwood,
24, the shield,
lift up, survivor.
The amazing rate.
Big brother.
Over there,
Kirby and Suzie has them.
I'll eat.
Find something else,
tune in and subscribe.
You can find us at www.tv.podcast.com
or on the iTunes music store.
Under the name, TV Talk.
Hey Adam.
This is Eric Bergen from Green Room Radio.
The Arts and Entertainment Podcast.
Located over at greenroomradio.com.
I just wanted to sendo for a brief,
promo type thing,
just to let you know what's coming up on the show.
Today,
we actually just put up a new show dedicated to the Muppets.
You know,
season one was just released on DVD,
and it's some pretty exciting stuff.
I mean,
where else would you get to see Connie Steven singing
with Faussie Bear?
So yeah,
so check that out.
There's some great stuff on there.
Also coming up soon,
we have an exclusive backstage interview
with Julia Merney,
who is in that new Broadway musical
Lenin,
based on the life of John Lenin.
Many people think it's actually
based off the life of the Lenin sisters,
but that's not true.
So yeah,
where we talk all about what it's like
to be in a Broadway show
that receives harsh criticism
and all that.
So it's really, really great.
We've some great stuff coming up.
I also wanted to wish you a happy sweet
16.
I know it's your birthday soon.
And, you know,
sweet 16s are a big thing.
Don't get knocked up if you can prevent it.
Lastly,
well,
I don't,
if you just indulge me for a second.
You know,
you've had that,
that song recently on your show
by cruise box,
heard it on the podcast.
And I,
and I really think that that song
has one of the best messages I've heard
in a long time.
It really truly is about the future.
And it really just shows you
what kind of a revolution
this podcasting thing is,
is doing.
Here's the thing.
I'm a singer myself
and I just think,
well,
I just think I could do a better job on the song.
Just,
just on the vocal part.
If you just indulge me in a second,
I just like to try this out.
I heard it all the podcast.
Fucking,
radio,
you want it.
You got it.
Now,
if you just got up.
And I heard it all the podcast.
Yeah.
Oh,
I just like it.
No.
Okay.
I tried.
A fantastic.
We need that.
We need a whole cover version,
done just like that.
That's fantastic.
Why shouldn't we?
The lyrics,
the melody.
It's all great.
Let's do a couple different versions.
Do you hear that gap
by the way,
between the first and the second promo?
I got that crime scene evidence screen again.
So,
let me see.
Where does that happen?
It happens.
It's the podshow disclaimer jingle.
But whenever I play that,
I get,
I get the,
the whole,
whenever I play that in Megaseg,
the whole screen goes blank.
Or black,
I should say,
with huge white letters,
it says crime scene evidence.
Let me just see if I can replicate that.
Hold on a second.
If I go back to this.
This may be talk podcast.
I'll just move this forward.
Let's see if it happens again.
Or on the pictures music store
on the name TV talk.
Yeah, crime scene evidence.
And then the Adam,
this is,
and from green room radio,
the arts and entertainment podcast.
How is that all right?
Remain,
Oh man.
OK.
So, it's clearly,
it's the podshow idea,
and has now been labeled as crime,
let me,
let me just go back.
Let me do the,
I'm going to take a screenshot of that.
You won't believe it
what I'm seeing here.
Hold on.
Let me just do this podcast.
Or on the ideas music store.
or under the name TV call.
Got it. Got the screenshot.
This is Eric Bergen.
Amazing.
Okay. So we'll have to look at that.
I was telling you about,
Wait a minute, I have something written down here before I get to that.
Oh yeah, Nintendo is going to start,
is really going to start a push into podcasting it appears.
They've started their own podcast,
the link to k9cast.com.
But Walter wrote in to say the timing of this is interesting because the play,
young MP3 multimedia add-on player for the Nintendo DS and GBA.
I have no idea what that is.
May see a US release date in late 2005 according to Wikipedia.
Wikipedia is now more than in cyclopedia apparently.
Nintendo could, it's a rumor mail.
Nintendo could be planning to turn DS and GBAs into podcast players.
With over 50 million Game Boy Advance units sold,
that's a lot of listeners. That is very interesting.
I got to find out with the DS and GBAs are,
but it sounds interesting.
And of course, the other question is,
will people use the device for podcasts?
Use it for gaming and stuff like that.
And a lot of people are hacking into their PSPs.
But if there is an audience there, that's a big number.
That's for sure.
And then finally, JPDane Castro says the other day I was driving in a car,
listening to the daily source code.
And I went under an overpass.
And for split second I thought to myself,
oh no, I'm going to lose reception.
And then I remembered.
It's a podcast.
You can't lose reception.
That's the beauty.
So I told you I was gotten a real mellow mood after I listened to the Hurricane Katrina PSA
from Dave's lounge.
And I remembered I had heard this particular song
on accident-C-C Chapman's show,
as he got back from San Francisco to Boston to the whole mellow show.
It's a Zach Ashton.
Tonight, I cry alone.
Tonight, I am forgotten.
For I run to you, run to you, run to you.
But I know, I know.
It won't be home, no, no.
Tonight, I'm asleep alone.
And you're voice-in, so familiar.
Tonight, I am so old.
I want to have you.
But feelings anymore.
Tonight, I am so old.
Tonight, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I want to have you.
Tonight, I am so old.
Now, once you have been feeling any more, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now
Now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, now, znajd memorial and porch,
The other way.
Hold on a second.
Do you have both channels now?
Yeah.
I don't hear both channels.
I don't hear one channel.
Oh, hello?
Okay.
Who's works really well?
Not.
You hear me in both ears?
No.
both ears? No. Only in one, right? Right. What's going on here? Why don't you
use to that? No, but I don't want that, I have it's supposed to oh shit. Okay, I
have it in two, wait, I can hear it in two. Do you have it in one year or two
years? No, I'm, yeah, last two years. Okay. All righty two years? What do you
think of that song? Nice. What do you think of that song?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, not like very special. Oh, okay.
Did you think it was better? I like it. Yeah, it was kind of mellow. It was sweet. Yeah, it was
very sweet. So I finally found Patricia. I was doing the garbage bags. Oh really?
Yeah. What does that mean? Also if people, if a glimmer is people, need to do
the garbage bags. Well, you don't need to do the garbage. Well, there are people
don't have to do it. Yeah. But I did that for a while and that was actually very
boring. And I'm misdoing the garbage bags. Oh, yeah. You mean you misdoing? Oh,
you mean you had someone do it for you. And then you, and now you, I was actually
missing doing, you know, the normal stuff. Really? Yeah. I didn't mis the garbage
bag part. No, you hated. I know that. It's, it's, you keep thinking about when
you were young. My parents always need to take out the garbage. I had, I was trash man.
He trashed. He trashed. I swear to God. And my, my dad would always do this. Oh, it's
Tuesday night. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no trash man. Really? Oh, they made it
you know, fun. Very irritating. Very irritating. Extremely freaking irritating. Well, it was typical.
How old was I then? I was probably 14, 15. You know, I've been talking about teenagers,
parents. That trash boy. It was trash man. It was trash man. Yeah, that's true. So they were trying to make me feel
good. Okay. I was just saying how teenagers now, you know, they, they think they know it all.
And then we're parents who don't want to push the bird out of the nest yet. Yeah, but we, we thought we
knew it all too. It was exactly. But not so extremely as the kids right now. What do you mean?
Yeah. Well, they, they, they, they, they exo mature. Yeah. Well, it, it looks mature, but it's not really,
but you know what I mean? They want to what they want to be mature. I don't know. Well, because they
see all those videos, those, those music videos. You think that's it? It's all because of the club
the 16 and 14 year now. I really sound old. The 16 and 14 year olds that are in the
clip density, because they're very young. Yeah. Yeah. I think they're very. Yeah. And they just,
they look like all dancers and, and yeah, that's true. Yeah, that's true. Yeah, that's true. Yeah.
And just, you know, it's sort of the street fashion. I'm so torn. The high street. And I don't
know, I think where is this going? Everybody's naked. I'm so torn because I like looking at it,
but I don't owe my daughter participate in it. And you know, I, I am always, I was always the first
one to hang on the pole. Not to hang on the pole, but you know, to do dairy things and, and being,
you know, one of the first that was wearing, actually before Madonna wearing those, underwear
things, you know, those bus jays. And, and, and I did, and there was quite sex. You know,
we thought that was quite naked. And I'm from the 70s where we showed, you know, we had those,
hip-hangers. Yeah. Very low. Right. But now it's going up, up, up, up, up. You know, and there's hardly
any t-shirt there. What's like the video music awards, everybody was, was pretty much naked. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, go go on. With your swimsuit, who cares? Yeah. You know, next time, don't wear your,
your suit, just your, your swimsuit. And our Kelly was grabbing his crotch a lot. Yeah, what was that?
Is that our Kelly was doing? Yeah. I know they do a lot, and it's sort of a thing that
goes with it, but yeah, but he was doing it a lot. Hey, let's play the hit test.
Are you ready? Yeah, I'm ready. Okay.
I suppose you think you know, we're gonna use it.
What do you mean, yeah?
The hit test.
Young polehead.
It's a general polehead.
Hey, Adam, this is another hit test. I'm not feeling too well, so I hope I sound bit better than I am.
Can I feel? Oh, I sense. Don't want to be in the throwing up all morning. Oh, no. We don't do that.
Pretty soon, but um, I still wanted to make a hit test for you. So here we go. This is number one.
I know what it is.
Yeah, yeah. So Ray Parker Jr.
Because of woman. Yeah. And this is number two.
Do you know that one, don't you? Yeah. What's that? Come on.
It's from your time. I know. For people rolling stones start me up.
Yeah, start the final one number three. I thought I was thinking about it.
She was just thinking.
It sounds like Terrence Trent Darby.
And it's time for the answer. And this is answer number one.
It's Ray Parker Jr. and Ray now.
And the song is titled, a woman needs love.
I remember all that.
See, I know. I know my head.
Hey, you got to sing along.
Answer number one.
And he doesn't number 54. He's going to hurt all. Junior.
Answer number two.
Ray Parker Jr. and radio. And woman needs love as answer number one.
This is answer number two. The rolling stones.
This is start me up also from 81.
Any has a small teeness? Yeah, I heard that. It's an all the newspapers here.
That's horrible. We said that. Is it Keith Richards saying that?
Keith Richards.
One of his best friends.
All the English newspaper.
When he was all balls. What is it? What is it?
All balls. No power. No power.
I'm going to make the show.
I'm going to call. Answer number two. The rolling stones.
Very good. Start me up.
How do I have been recording this, um, um,
hit test with, um, what is it? Gas blaster?
Beta version number 30 with all new sorts of additions.
Oh, I don't want to go 20.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Draw it up. Answer number three.
Charne. Smooth.
That way. Ray.
Yeah, I know. I, you know, you're here.
Do you think I know that?
But then you can't say it.
You're colleagues.
And so number 3 in today's latest, Sharday and smooth operator.
Well, this concludes hit test number 4.
So, as always, to end this video, hit test a Gmail.com for feedback.
And, youngpolettes.com for info about the hit test and the hit test podcast,
the TTA and BOLET.com.
I always love getting those feedback messages.
I got a lot of them about the train hit test, recorded on a train,
and I also got one from John Lason, and he states this.
I was listening to the daily source code on my iPod at work,
and when I heard the first couple of notes from on the beach,
I shouted out the title, which invited more than a few curious stairs.
From people's side of a beach.
Hit test at Gmail.com.
Is there something else to mention?
Well, not really, I love the fact that the hit test is creating sales at iTunes
or other music, offending sites and stores.
I still haven't found a good way to monitor the links to every song on the site
because it really takes a lot of time.
Well, it's not important when you look at the amount of work
that you have to do to get the link on the site.
Okay, well, that might help you enjoy this hit test.
Yeah, you've been doing it for 55 until then.
Bye, bye.
Thank you very much.
Feel better, young.
Yeah.
What a trooper, eh?
Nah, if you calculate.
A few could choose.
You're speaking Dutch on, just saying no.
Yeah, I know, but I'm Dutch listening.
Okay, all right.
Think about that.
This shows me no one for 15 minutes.
I got to stop him.
All right.
Okay.
Will you come by tomorrow again?
You know, maybe.
It's just the walk out of your bedroom, take the first left.
You're going to talk a little louder.
But I wasn't feeling well, you know.
I know.
Okay.
Yeah, but it's better.
I got to do something like the headphones.
This is something.
Yeah, be people.
Very old fashioned.
Yes.
Okay, hon, thank you.
Okay.
Love you too.
Okay, oh shit.
There we go.
That's it for today's source code.
Hello.
Hello, hello.
I just respect the other headphones here.
Hold on.
Okay, much better.
I got that.
That determines it.
I need to hit so now.
I need serious headphones amplifier.
amplifier.
They got the microphone part for the guess worked out, but not the, uh, not the headphone
amp part.
Okay.
Feedback out of McCree.com, please do not attach your MP3 to the email, put up on a server,
put the ID3 tags in there, so it shows up like something I can recognize, and other people
can use that information that sent it to Atom McCree.com.
Anything else?
Promo's Potset Music mashup Submit at podshow.com, of course the feed for the show is a
daily source code.com.
So make sure you check into the expanded show notes to find out more about the hurricane relief
for Hurricane Cortina Katrina.
I'm pretty sure it's going to be redcross.org, but give that a look.
And, uh, let's see, uh, leaving for New York, definitely on Monday, uh, but coming back
on the couple days later, you're leaving.
Thank you very much for listening.
Stay subscribed, talk to you tomorrow on your daily source code.
Another podshow podcast, stick it in your ear.