Okay, testing one, two, one, two, check one, two, three, hey everybody hold on, I don't think
it's just right yet.
Let me crank that up a bit.
Okay.
Is that working?
This is the daily source code.
It's Wednesday.
It's the ninth of March, sorry, April.
No.
March, 2005.
I'm trying out something entirely new, which is so beautiful and elegant.
That if it actually does work, it'll just be a breakthrough in sensing, podcasting, and mobile
podcasting, you can tell I'm missing around with my microphone right now.
Okay.
Shoot.
This is not going the way I planned it.
Hold on.
Put the mic there.
Okay.
It's a little hard to tell if the mic quality is up to speed.
Hold on a sec.
I'm now outputting as much as possible from my wireless setup.
What I've done upon the recommendation from a couple people, as I was on a continuing
quest to find the perfect mobile mixer, said, why don't you use one of those splitters
that people use for headphones?
Hopefully, so one headphone out jack turns into two headphone out jacks, both stereo,
and reverse the process and use that for your input.
Combining the input from my microphone, I won't say.
And the input from a portable player, such as an iPod, and combining those two through
that splitter, and then, you know, just basically it's a one-to-one mixer, and you control
the volume of the audio on the...
Whoa.
Okay.
So I just turned the iPod on.
I think that really...
Well, that's probably the answer to the question, will this work?
Wow.
That was pretty weird.
Let me see if I disconnect the iPod.
Whoops.
Wow.
Hold on.
That's...wait.
Wait a minute.
That's not...Oh, of course not.
I'm not doing it right.
I'm not doing it.
Am I doing it right?
Holy moly.
I'm so confused.
Hold on a second.
I'll put your impulse while I try and think this through for a second.
Okay.
I think you're on pause, by the way.
I think I figured it out.
So I have the splitter going into the microphone jack.
The one part, so I'm using the...
What normally would be the out as the...
Is the in part?
Oh.
Man, that sounds so confusing.
And now I'm going to connect...
Bitch is going to do the same thing.
This is probably why you need a mixer,
it's because when you...
Just connect basically the two wires together.
Yeah.
You get that shoot.
That's not really going to work.
At least I don't think.
Unless...
Unless I really...
Can I crank up the volume anymore on the microphone set?
I doubt that, too.
Hello, hello, hello.
Hello, hello, hello, hello.
Okay.
So that's like maximum.
But that could even be overmodulating at this point.
I cannot...
Literally cannot hear myself to the headphones.
So let me just...
See...
I'll just play something sort of...
I have something really...
Short here, don't I?
I've sounded of the day.
Let's play the see what happens.
Okay.
So I can volume down and talk over the music.
And then...
And then I can...
Put it up.
The sound of the day is...
The singing of the music.
Well, there we go.
Watching machine.
All right.
So the question is...
What's the level of the microphone?
Like, it doesn't sound like it's going to be very good.
So I have to say this test is...
Not good.
Not to...
Successful.
Well, let's say the test was successful.
Just the outcome is not what we wanted.
Okay.
I'm going to listen back to this and then we'll start the show.
It's kind of working.
Hey, everybody.
Hey.
Welcome to the Daily Source Code.
It's Adam Curry coming to you from the Curry Cottage here in Guilford.
And the lovely...
Was it...
Suburb of Surrey and the United Kingdom.
All mobile today.
The power of the Lord is coming.
I'm trying out the set up.
You just heard me basically set up.
It's kind of interesting because I control the volume of the background or the tune in this case.
Just by twirling my thumb on the iPod wheel.
But I used a headphone connecting wire for the microphone.
Which means there's a little volume control right on the wire.
And I can start to turn that down.
Because that's one thing when you're playing a mashup.
You want to be able to mute your microphone.
So that's now possible.
And it's kind of working.
So we'll give it a shot.
But essentially, I'm doing something that should not be done by any...
Electro-technical...
You know, means or terms.
Because this is exactly why I need a mixer.
You don't have these basically these two outputs just connected to each other.
There's all kinds of crap that's going on.
I'm sure you can probably blow something up doing this as well.
That wouldn't surprise me at all.
But all in the name of science, my friends, all in the name of science.
You know, I didn't...
Oh, man, I didn't even grab my show notes.
Normally I have that all set up because I record direct onto my power book.
So here we go.
Wow, this is kind of cool.
Oh, is it already starting to sound crappy now?
Is that?
Well, we'll just go through the whole show and then see where we wind up.
How about a mash-up?
Ooh, how about the D.J. skills?
This can skip me to the next track on the iPod.
This is a mash-up.
This is the saled-y-said.
The Beatles vs. Paul McCartney.
It's the Bradmix on the source code.
When it's too late, it's me.
Who buys money?
When you pay the rent?
Think you think that money was heaven's end?
Friday night, the rise without a surrogate?
Sunday morning, freebing like a nom nom nom.
On these dollars, learn to tie his food base.
T.E.R.B.R.B.
Lady Madonna, baby at your rest.
One does how your man is to feed the way.
The Beatles vs. Paul McCartney.
Well, that's kind of disturbing and really cool at the same time.
Say Lady say the Vietnamese just one of the many nice workshops I got received.
Well, over the past couple of weeks, it seems to just really pick up a lot.
A couple of things I want to talk with you about today, let's see.
One of them I received an email from, we'll just call this person, DJ Ultra Violet,
and I hope this is sounding okay.
I can hear kinds of crackling and shit.
And she's a lawyer.
And basically, she said, hey, if you have any questions about this music licensing stuff,
why don't you let me know, and then I said, well, very simply, is there a way for me to pay
to play R-I-A-A licensed music on a podcast, and how much is it?
That was the only question.
And I think one of the problems is, shit, I'm sorry, that's the crackling.
There we go.
And that's literally all I wanted to know.
And she actually came back with some very interesting thoughts and ideas,
which I can't publish in the show notes, because she checked it with her law firm.
And obviously there's no one need the aggravation of having to check all this stuff.
If she could say that, or if I could podcast it, but sound exchange, sound exchange.com
is the royalty collection agency for digital music webcasting.
And so the question now, of course, does podcasting belong in the webcasting category?
I don't think so.
It seems like just about everything would fit within their license.
But let me see, I'm reading here, yeah, because podcasts are basically archived,
and not, you know, streamed that could be a problem.
And it's also, it will be $500 a year.
Oh, oh, that was interesting.
Crap, of course.
So the iPod switched off.
And then it automatically gave control back to the microphone.
This may not be a very handy way of doing this.
I'm going to have to pay attention to how this is going now.
Okay.
So sound exchange.com, you know, I'm going to be reading through it and see if there's anything,
that might actually work, and who knows, maybe someone over there is listening,
and they can help us out.
Email from bicyclemark.
Oh, yeah, he was doing something interesting.
I wanted to tell you about.
And just go to Google and search for a bicycle mark, the bicycle mark communique,
or, of course, you can go into the iPod directory at iPod about org.
And you can pick up there under sound seeing tours or sound seeing tours.com.
You can find bicycle mark almost anywhere you want.
But he's done a reverse sound seeing tour, as it were.
Remember, he did that cool thing with the flicker photos,
which is not really catching on, where he plays a little tone.
And then you click through the flicker slide show.
So now he's actually doing it like Uncle Stan's slide show.
You know, when he comes over and boars the whole family,
only it's not that boring.
And he's doing the audio commentary after he photographed the slide show.
God, this sounds horrible.
Oh my god, you know, I'm just going to check this and see how this sounds.
This is, this is starting to become worrisome.
Yeah. So, you know, kind of as I thought it doesn't sound too hot,
but I'll just leave it for now and we'll just use it as an experiment.
So, hey, all I really need is just a mixture between those two inputs.
One little mixture, and with, you know, with a way to pot down the microphone,
which I think I've already found. I mean, that they were almost there.
Okay, so that was bicycle mark.
I had to, what is this? The next track I wanted to play,
mouse pad report. I think I know if that was a promo or not.
It's, uh, I compiled this, uh, the day before yesterday, so I'm a little fuzzy on exactly what we're
going to do. Let's check it out. Adam Curry, the pod father, our father in pod.
Oh, yeah. King Curry, give my love to the queen, Dawn.
I got to save the queen. This is a promo with no production value.
Uh-huh. Who why what else do we need? Me, you, the mic, we got everything.
This is a three-ring pod cast. WWEW.3ringpodcast.com.
It's about life, the universe, and everything.
No more pod cast about nothing. Who wants to listen to that?
We're about everything. So, come on. Show some love for the new boys on the block.
We were down with the mashups and the hit test. It's all good. But come on.
There's new boys on the block. We're not getting any. We're not getting any love.
Lightly from you. Spreading love. It's a more promo. It's all right.
I discovered some of my favorite pod castes through your show. So, let's go.
One or two a day. Won't kill you. Never one will love it. So, come on. Jump on my train.
We're having a good time at the three-ringpodcast. Check us out. Thanks.
Late. Oh, is that it now? That's the new thing. Late. All right, bro. Late. Cool. Uh, absolutely.
So, um, the mixer that I would love to have is, you know, it runs on like a, um,
it runs on like one battery, right? And it just mixes these two input signals. And that's really all it
has to do. Um, and it, but it has to, you know, I'm sure radio shacket has something like this.
I just got to go visit one. I get to find them. My nearest radio shack. You know that in America,
I think it's every American, almost every American lives within 15 minutes of a radio shack.
Yeah, we pitched their business once. Didn't get it, but it was fun pitching. Learning about radio
shack. I was like, I kind of grew up in radio shack. So, obviously, you know, it's kind of silly.
I'm sitting here with a, uh, you know, 350 dollar iPod. I've got a, uh, it was a $250 dollar, uh,
I river. I've got my wireless set, which is not necessary, of course. But that's, you know,
the only, uh, love microphone I have. I can kind of walk around with. So, it's an expensive solution,
but still even those two devices. I mean, it could easily be combined in the one, just put the
input on the box. And, um, and kind of, uh, yeah, this playlist, uh, what ideas I just, uh,
compiled a little playlist on iTunes of the stuff I wanted to play in today's show. And, uh,
and, you know, I scroll to that in the iPod, and there you go. It's, uh, uh, it's basically,
I'm trying to keep it from popping off. So, they're setting for that, actually, let me see.
So, they're setting, oh, man, iPod is not great. Let me see, shuffle repeat.
Does it have a timeout? Has the backlight timer, but that's, hmm, interesting. So, I guess you
can't set that. All right. I go back to today's playlist. Ah. Um, now I had something written down
about podcast alley. I know that podcast alley has changed its voting system. Um, to, what is it?
And I think you can vote once a month. That's interesting. I'm talking with the Chris from podcast
alley. It's a very interesting guy. He's got some fun stuff going on over there. But I think that
we can do, um, there is a real ratings component to, uh, podcast, and that I haven't really looked
at that much, but I hear, uh, lots of people talking about it. And obviously, I think what we're looking
at is, um, because the mainstream media really loves, um, you know, easy, easy ways to show
their readership or their viewership or listenership, um, you know, what is going on in a certain
community. It's really easy to, to pick something and say, oh, well, here's the top 10 of anything.
And so, and, and that's actually not that bad. Um, but, you know, the, the gripes are that, you know,
it's the top 10 of why. There's kind of like having a top 10 of web logs. So maybe if we define
it a little bit better, and we made, uh, I, I think we can do something with this voting. I guess that's
what I'm saying. Um, and we should be able to convert that energy into something really good for
everybody. So I've been thinking about that thinking about it a lot. Um, and, uh, who knows what
else, uh, you may be you're out there thinking about some things as well, um, because it's just
amazing to see this happen. It's really cool. Um, to have all this fury flying and then you're
here, uh, Don and Drew talking about, oh, no, we were not, we're not going to talk about it anymore.
And, uh, and Madge Weinstein over East Radio, um, you know, has, has her take on it as well. It's just,
it's, uh, it's been interesting. And this new podcast that I found, and I, at first I thought I was
going to be repurposed content kind of like the Pepsi Max, um, what they call that Pepsi Max is doing
a promotion. It's a, I think they do it on UK radio stations. And they're basically just repurposing
that in a podcast, which is, it's cool, um, although the, ah, shit, did it again. Although the, um,
uh, what is it? The humor is, it's very British humor. So, you know, it's a, a wind up, that's what
they call it, a wind up is where, you know, basically the prank phone calling people. Um, but this
podcast is something that, uh, I think it can actually get into. And once I get my life a little bit,
you know, more structured, uh, just been a lot going on as you heard yesterday. I'm still traveling a
lot and, uh, and tying up loose ends all over the globe. Um, I'd like to, you know, get back into
the habit of, uh, walking or, you know, more regular exercise, uh, I've threatened Patricia that
we're actually going to, uh, uh, you know, go to the gym one of these days and get that started as well.
And we will, uh, but this podcast is from Marina and actually, uh, it's, uh, it's what you want,
you know, you want a daily fresh mix of exercise music with someone, very motivated about helping
you exercise. Here's the first of the podcast by Marina. This is Marina and you're listening to my
high energy fitness, sing off the pound. If you work out all the time or you never worked out before,
we're going to have a great time today, burn lots of calories. Whoo! You see, it doesn't matter what
kind of workout you're into, walking, running, spinning, aerobic fans, as long as you never stop
moving. So come on, let's have better times. Yeah, okay. Let's work out. Let's have better times together.
And then I thought it was like, oh, this is just one of those exercise tapes, but then somewhere
I heard the word podcast pop up, probably around here somewhere because, I don't think I could
listen to this music for a very long. But, uh, is that her singing? No. And mine feet. That's interesting.
It's a 10-minute, you know. So it's the perfect, uh, perfect length, too. It's not one of those,
you know, really long ones that you're going to pause midway anyway. We see if I can pass forward.
I knew there was something about podcast. I knew it's that.
All right, wait, it must have been that piece, hold on.
You're doing a great job. Thanks for being with me today. On the part.
There it is, you see? Yeah, that's cool. All right, let's go everybody.
Okay. Oh, baby, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Okay.
Okay, all right. All right, all right, it may be way too early for you for this
crap. So I'll turn this down. You know, I'll keep it on in the background so I can use that as my
don't turn off the iPod mechanism while we talk a little bit more.
Well, I discovered something interesting. The gaming guys out there, I got an email from, uh,
was it Aaron? And, uh, we starts off as email, which I will put in the show notes, you know,
by saying that he received started playing Grand Theft Auto, Vice City, uh, as Xbox after,
you know, finishing it months ago. It turns out that there's a lot of stuff going on with Xbox
and Xbox Live, and basically the gaming developers who I think use the dot net infrastructure,
or, or, or, I'm sorry, direct X, God, I know nothing about Windows. But they are, uh, creating
some really cool audio tools. Uh, in fact, you can, uh, you can listen to different radio stations now
while you're driving the car in the game. And they're also this Xbox Live stuff is, you know,
it's, I've been looking into it. I'm not a gamer at all. We have an Xbox, uh, Christina has an
Xbox. I don't even think we unpacked it, you know, we're just not really gamers. And, uh, but I was
interested because this stuff obviously runs in, uh, in Windows, and there may be some really
good slick tools that can be made from the gaming community. So I'm pretty excited about that,
and I reached out to Larry, remember we played Larry's promo, he's from Microsoft. He's from the
Xbox division. So, no, we'll see if we can get any traction with that. I just thought it was kind
of interesting that all this activity is going on. And, and there's some, uh, gamers now Xbox,
I don't know if their developers are just gamers or both, but they are also doing podcasts,
you know, about gaming. So there's something going on. I'm definitely going to try and figure
out where the community is and, uh, and, you know, introduce myself and see if we can connect
something here, because I think there is something going on for sure. And now, cue the next track.
Oops. Oh, that's just from my buddy, P.W. Fenton.
Oh, Adam, and welcome to the geriatric hit test. We have a doozy for you today. So what do you say?
We get started. We get out three great songs for you to identify. So what do you say?
We get started. Rock and roll. Oh, you said that already. Oh, I did it. Okay, then get
ready, Adam. Here comes number one. Oh, what was that? It's a neat little drop.
Okay, what a wonderful song. Yeah. Okay, let's begin with number one.
Grandpa, he did that one already. Look, we're 21. We have two. Oh, we're two.
Okay, then here comes number three. Oh, number three. Nice bumper.
White Christmas? No.
Now, here comes the answers. Okay, we missed number two. Number one was the Pentalvania
Polka by Miron Florian in his accordion. Oh, okay.
And the Pental. Okay, I should have known that actually. Patricia would have known that one.
Number two was when the we do number two. No, you didn't. No, grandpa. You skipped number two.
Well, he answered a number two would have been when the moon comes over the mountain by Kate Smith.
Oh, sorry, I didn't play. In finding number three.
Freak grandpa. Uh, it's getting me. Number three. Number three.
Oh, wait, I could find it. Wait, number. Number three was tenderly by Rosemary Clooney.
Another one Patricia would have known. I'm sure.
They've never seen it before.
Oh, yeah.
Let's ramble in trees and brace the brain.
Okay, well, that's today's hit test. Where's Nan? Lunchtime yet.
We already had lunch, grandpa. Go tell Nan. It's lunch time and we're ready for lunch.
I think yeah, that is from my buddy Peter. It's great creativity, my man. Thank you very, very much.
Oh, boy. Um, let's see. What else we're going to talk about? Have a couple of things written down here.
Um, a lot of, um, these are really, I prepared, as I said, prepared this the day before yesterday.
And I'm not quite sure what I was thinking at the time. But I wrote down to talk about the death of
radio. And there is a discussion as a conversation going on now about radio. And I think the
wired article really picked up on that or wired magazine, you know, looked at different angles.
Uh, I think that even the cover says the death of radio as we know it and they looked at
different types of broadcasting and distribution methods really that are taking some hold.
But more importantly, and I think that that's really where the conversation should be going is not
necessarily about the distribution. But, um, I think that we have a whole generation of people growing
up and we've talked about this before who really just, you know, are not interested in what radio
has to offer. Um, and, and the, uh, I don't know if you remember the, um, the podcast I did
with Christina when I took her to school and I said, you know, what, what radio station do you do?
Listen, the radio, I think I said. And she said, yeah, listen to, uh, the eagle. And in the same
breath, she said, because you can go up there to the studio and hold up her request in front of the
window. And I'm like, yeah, that is exactly what this whole new generation that grew up with messenger
and, uh, and, you know, so MSN and hotmail or Xbox, you know, that's exactly what they're used to,
you know, it is feedback, direct immediate feedback where something happens, you know, a way to
be a part of the process, to be a part of, um, of the creation of the output of the product. And that is,
I think a big part of what weblogs, uh, are about, uh, or met many whoop, holy crap. This is just not a
good way to do it. Um, uh, wait, can I put on? Let's, uh, let's find a track.
Wow, this really screws it all up, doesn't it? Oh, man, why do I shouldn't have done this way?
Hold on. Well, now I'm committed. We find something from the 70s music been, uh,
oh, man. Okay, we'll just put this in the background. Really, quietly. Okay.
Right. So I was talking about, uh, yeah, that Christina really liked being able to be a part
of the process of what is happening on that radio station. And of course, the fact that her friends are
listening to it because it's local. And that's when radio really does work best. And I think that's what
radio has proven throughout its history to do incredibly well. Um, is within a local community. And,
you know, that is a little bit more than the local temperature and the local traffic conditions.
Granted, those are probably, you know, 70% of the information people need from their local
radio stations. But, you know, there's a lot. And whenever you hear that, you know, uh, the community,
bullet board or whatever, uh, whatever the, that particular segment may be called, which is basically
run as a PSA public service announcement. That's important. That's an important part of, um,
of what radio broadcasting is about. And it's also a part of the license of these stations and
obligation, uh, to work for the community. And that's for a reason. And I think part of that
reason is because that's what radio really does extremely well. And then you're using, you know,
the public airwaves to their maximum benefit. Wow. Um, so if podcasting is, uh, going to follow
that model or any type of, um, uh, communication audio communication, maybe I should call it,
that is mobile. Because that's real important, right? It's very important that this stuff is mobile.
Because that, that's what, you know, part of the big revelation of radio was, is that, you know,
this could be, um, enjoyed anywhere. Notice it didn't say receives, but it could be enjoyed anywhere.
So, um, podcasting, whether it's, uh, I guess any type of content really, but let's just, you know,
look at audio because that seems to be happening will work really well in smaller communities.
The, uh, the thing that that we're then going to bump up against is, well, you know, it takes
a time to do this. And, uh, some people not all, certainly not all, probably only a few,
really on a grand scale, will want to make money, um, by doing this. And to me, it's, it's all
down to the content, you know, uh, you can be just as funny as John Stewart, and you're going to have
just as much opportunity, uh, to be as successful. Um, you know, it's take away the TV show part,
but, you know what I'm saying? Uh, because those barriers are coming down and it's, and it's only
going to come down to who can move fast, who can be the best. It's going to be quality, uh,
over anything else, which is going to make the playing field incredibly level and very,
very interesting. We'll be able to see the battle much better when there are no hills on the
battle field. And I'm looking forward to a lot of that. Uh, so in the background, you've been
listening to Food Rotten, fell in love, uh, Elven Bishop with, um, it was a Mickey Hart who, uh,
who's saying on that particular track. Uh, and now I'm going to move over to a bit of cadence,
which we haven't heard in a while, and I thought I'd play one for you. Uh, the Leland Standford,
Jr. University, marching band. Here's the incomparables.
Yeah. More than just a cadence, actually. And the crowd goes absolutely wild.
Roundabout, the Leland Standford, Jr. University, marching band. Uh, here on the daily source code.
Actually, I'm, I have about, uh, what is it? To 10 more minutes, and then I'm going to do a Skype call.
It's almost 2pm here in the UK. So, uh, I'll be 9 a.m. people on the East Coast waking up.
Um, and, um, may I just say, although I'm always a bit wary of complimenting technology too much,
because that's usually when Murphy goes, ah, pound of fuck with you. Um, Skype really is rocking.
I mean, these guys, they have it. Stay ahead. It's great. I love it. I totally love it. I,
can build a virtual company using Skype. You know, it is, it's just outrageous. The conferencing capability.
Certainly now they're available on the Mac. You know, a conference in two, three people who are on Skype,
then conference in someone just by calling a phone number. Um, and, you know, make no mistake.
Skype is the phone company. This is what's going to happen. They, uh, they already have,
what is it? How many people are online right now? So, 2.2 million users online,
a percentage of them has Skype out. I think it's like 900,000 of them have Skype out and are using that.
So, you pay 1.1 euro cents a minute anywhere in the world to make a phone call. As a little bit more,
if you call cell phones in the Netherlands, for instance, but still it's a great deal. It's good
to deal. You're going to get almost anywhere else down to pennies. Um, so everyone's kind of used
to this combination of free-foning and then using Skype to make phone calls because it's incredibly
cost-effective. And next, they give everybody Skype in, which means you can have a phone number
wherever you are, wherever you want it to be. And then they're the phone companies, as far as I'm concerned.
So, excellent. I really love what those guys are doing. And that is, that to me is ground-breaking
stuff. Um, congratulations to the former Cazard dudes who served their shop once in Amsterdam. Very cool.
Okay. So, finishing it off just following on some questions or some questions that
were raised during one of my, I think, Mr. Mom Podcast, Terry Wogan Show on BBC 2 on Radio 2,
runs from 730 to 930. Um, and that's according to an email from Jonathan, who goes through a
little more detail about Terry's show. So, if you want to find out about that, check the show notes
for today's podcast, which is March 9th, 2005. And also, it says something very interesting about
dish washes. I'm going to, because I'm saying, I'm not a big fan of dish washes, because basically
you're handling the plates twice, you know, putting a minute taking about. And here's what Jonathan
said, and I like this. He says, there's a school of thought that holds that you need two dish washers
and no cupboards in your kitchen. Start off with one dishwasher full of clean crockery and cutlery,
which means plates and so forth. As items are used, stack them in the other dishwasher. When
it's full, run it, take the clean dishes, as needed from it, then stack them in the first one,
and so on. I'm like, dude, that's like totally a great idea. I'm really digging that.
Two dish washes. I think that we have stumbled upon something really, really, really big here.
Right on, the official one. Well, hello Adam. This is hit test number 20. Right on.
And if you're ready, we haven't done this one yet, have we?
Wait, this is number one. Okay.
And one more time.
I'm Genesis.
Time. Time.
Second time.
Fan. My being. I can't walk. I can't walk.
This is number two. I can't dance. I can't dance.
I can't dance.
I can't. I can't.
I can't.
Yeah.
I know this is, that's Jenna Jackson and Nasty, and you're playing all those songs that I guess that we're wrong.
And this is number three.
Yeah, one more time.
Right over that is.
That's the guys who remind me of my horrible hairdressers, Tony and Guy, there will be
salmon Dave and hold on. I'm coming.
And these are the answers. This is so man, so man, so man.
I'm a soulmate with Genesis.
I can't dance.
Genesis.
And so number one. And this is answer number two.
It's Jenna Jackson.
Nasty. Yeah.
Nasty.
Jenna Jackson, Nasty.
And this is answer number three.
Well, hey, everybody, it's Tony and Guy.
And salmon.
That's not bad.
Thank you.
Well, that's what you call stereo.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
salmon Dave and soul man.
Well, this wraps up here to us number 20.
And I hope you're still enjoying the hit us.
Yeah.
If you don't, please let me know.
And if you do, please also let me know information about the hit us can be found at
www.yumplelet.nl that's J-A-N-V-O-L-E-T.nl.
And feedback is welcome at Hit us at gmail.com.
Well, Adam, see you next time for number 21.
Bye-bye.
No, I mean, and do, I totally love this.
I mean, I'm wondering, are it is Yana use sending me a message that maybe you're
getting tired of it? Is that is that possible?
I mean, I think it's amazing you do this thing.
And obviously, it doesn't fit in all the time when I'm on the road.
Although, if I have this kind of setup and it didn't sound like crappy and it, you know,
well, you've heard the things that are going wrong, but it feels very powerful to actually
sit here just be holding the iPod and controlling the recording of the show or basically
all the elements of the show through it.
It feels great.
So, no, Yana, I totally love it, totally.
And, you know, if I skip one, don't worry about it, you know, you can skip one too.
I should not be a problem, really.
One more thing I wanted to mention, and then I have, you know, what we're going to do
another mash-up just to end it off today because I feel, well, no, should we do another mash-up?
No, we shouldn't do another mash-up. I happen to make this phone call too.
So, let me just get the final tunes queued up here a whole lot of a second.
Can I still pause that?
No, no, no, pause. Okay. What that work?
Shoot. Okay, so there's some interface stuff we go to think about here.
No, what I, I just want to final thing,
continuing what I told you about yesterday about this new company that I'm really excited about.
A big part of this company will be about
creativity, content, and the people that produce that.
And in the next few days, I'll be talking to you about a couple of names that we'll be working with,
and I'm very, very excited.
And that's it for your source code for today.
I'm going to leave you hanging at that. If you have any comments,
it's adamantcurry.com. You can get the new shows and final the archives at dailysourceco.com.
Of course, that's also where you can find the podcast feed.
It's RSS 2.0. And that is my weblog. That's www.curry.com.
So I'm going to do some some calls, some Skype calls,
enjoy every moment of that. And I'll be back tomorrow.
Who knows what we'll do. We'll find something fun. I really do want to say thank you all very much for the
wonderful emails we've received about the Patricia Pi podcast. We will definitely do more.
And I'll also thank you for sending in songs. I mean, people are sending us MP3s that Patricia
didn't even recognize that anymore. So if you've got cool stuff at home, let's see if we can
stump her with her own stuff. All right, everybody, take care. I'll talk to you tomorrow. Bye-bye.