Daily source code 1-24-25.
Transmators, we don't need no stinkin' transmitters.
There are wums as a fellow in curry, who's do need high cause and to worry.
Technicians installed 6 maga bit balls, that we get some stuff off in our hurry.
Yeah!
My name is Adam Carey, thank you for your time.
No, no, it's Gilford. My name's Adam Curry for the next 40 minutes. New podcast and pot save tunes.
Or as Dr. Floyd would say, it's fun making a show about nothing.
Man, normally I have a show full of all kinds of stuff because I did saving it up over the weekend.
Yesterday, of course, we did a special make make do or make up or make good podcast.
So I thought that I wouldn't have that much to share with you today until I check my Gmail account.
This is the MP3 feedback at gmail.com, man.
Clentio. Clentio MP3 is coming in there. Lots to look at.
Actually, a very calm weekend. This is my first full weekend that I had the fat pipe or at least the
interim fat pipes. Still no word from easy net. I don't think that the four megabit
despite what you heard in the opening there. It's not sex makes six megabit, but four megabit pipe.
I don't think it's connected yet. I'll have to check the router later on.
Or as they say here, the UK, the Ruta. It's not a router. It's a Ruta, everyone.
It's a Ruta!
So, I said yesterday, almost the entire week is clear on the calendar, which means plenty of time for
well, particularly downloading podcasts, checking out new stuff, maybe I've actually thought about
hacking a little bit of code, doing some creating some stuff that hasn't actually, I haven't been
able to find out there. We'll talk about that in a second.
Something that I found last night was, actually, I was really, really happy. Remember that
the lascivious bitties were on coverville, and they did a Brian from coverville,
an interview with the bitties. They were New York, he was up in Canada, and the interview was done
by IChat AV on Macs, and it was really a shame because the quality was just so fucking poor.
And this was, you know, actually, insert Skype, Skype mentioned here. Hello Skype, can you make
recording easier, please? Can you make it easier? Will use your stuff? I swear to God.
So, now there's a director's cut available, which in the DVD world means something a little
bit different than in the podcast world. In this case, what happened is Ben from the bitties,
Ben is not a bitty, or maybe he's the fifth bitty. He's their production manager, and I
does a lot of stuff for the bitties. He also set up the whole interview on their end of the conversation.
I guess he sent a recording of what they did in New York over to Brian, and he cut everything together.
And now it's really an excellent, excellent interview, which I encourage you to check out.
It's the director's cut of the cover real podcast with the lasivias bitties. You can find it
at uh, I guess cover real dot com. That's where uh, that's where I always find it. And then, of course,
you can subscribe to the podcast there. If you're looking for other podcasts, by the way,
we have a great categorized listing. It's a directory. It's called ipodder.org,
and you can find most of the topics there, and podcasts associated with it. This is also the
directory, by the way, that that flows through most of the ipodder software. We're having a
product problem with ipodder lemon. And this is a really complicated one. It goes a little bit
while it goes way above my head, really. It seems that in technology, we've been able to agree on
a whole bunch of things, except how we encode dates. I think is one. Although there's multiple agreements,
but the hardest part is character encoding. If you've ever seen this uh, you know, ietf-8
whatever encoding crap, that basically is, it's been explained to me. But I guess what your software
needs to be if it's creating um, uh, files that work all over the world that has to be double bite
encoded, which essentially means you have to have, you know, double the amount of code is what
sounds like to me. What's going to explain to me. Um, so what happens is if someone adds a
um, a podcast with a name that has special characters like one of the French podcast or Portuguese
podcast that are also listed in the directory and the languages, um, it can basically break a
reader that is parsing through that OPML file, which is no more than XML, really, and it's trying
to, uh, departs out the information. Uh, so I haven't been able to fix that on my end right now.
I'm kind of going through it. Also, I don't maintain the entire directory, right? Only maintain
the top level at iPodder.org, and everyone else is pasting in uh, uh, sites along down the the
hierarchy of the tree. Um, so it's been breaking the directory in uh, iPodder in the lemon version.
And um, I'm desperately trying to figure out how to make that better, but uh, probably the the
the easiest fix right now would be for um, people on the receiving side to filter out crap characters
as they come in, but it's a problem. Uh, definitely working on that on my end.
Hey, they're Adam and name Scott, and uh, but checking out your podcast for a couple of weeks,
believe it or not, as much as I say I'm into technology and actually my title is technical evangelist.
I have just discovered podcasting really enjoying it. My first podcast was your sound scene tour
of Miami, and I thought that was just the coolest damn thing. Now, I'm experimenting, um, and
and thinking about doing a podcast, my own. I've got to watch it because I am in commercial radio
and actually I was talking to my partner and I said, hey, we could do a podcast and we can do like
an uncensored show where I could look at you and say, hey, fuck off. And uh, and we could get away with
it, but you know, I've got away with those things, so I'm sure you understand that. But anyways,
I heard you doing the name that song, and I thought I would uh, send you over a few. I know I
love playing it myself and being a dishjockey in the 80s, 90s and still today.
Hey, everybody. I enjoy playing this game here in a couple seconds of a song and I describe
you're not going to, oh, man, what the hell is that? Okay, this is indeed something that I've
really gotten into people sending in intros of songs and trying to stomp knees. Actually,
it's turned out to be relatively easy to stomp me. Uh, so let's see what this guy has lined up.
So, uh, the differences I've added and being a radio guy, I'm sure you can appreciate this.
The audio prisms. I've simulated the gender audio prism actually. The excellent. What
is talking about here is the processing that that we used to hear. Well, it's still here
it on a lot of top 40 radio stations that really compressed tight sound and everything's breathing
really quickly. And well, you'll hear it. I'm sure when he plays these songs. So he's not only
going to give me the trivia of 80s and I guess 90s songs or whatever, I'd actually, I'd prefer
50, 60, 70s and 80s. 90s is just shit for me. I wasn't paying any attention. Let's see if I can guess.
Hex are the original ones. Yep, to the music. Uh, so hopefully it'll have that pure 80 sound. So,
here we go. A quick couple of songs. Um, let's see if you know him. All right.
Oh, I give up on that.
All right. I know the song, but I just don't say I won't. Okay, go west. We close our eyes.
I can figure that one out now.
Oh, I sucked to the wish. I don't know what this is going for. All right. It made
thanks for checking it out. I'll let you know if I have a podcast on it. You know,
maybe I'll have to go underground. I was working on a couple of names. Maybe 88.1,
which was the frequency of my first, uh, Mr. microphone, or maybe I'll just call it Mr.
microphone. All right, Adam, enjoy the podcast and I'll keep subscribing. See you. Yeah. Okay.
That's, uh, ABC's look of love you're playing there. Oh, man. I sucked on that one.
Hope that you'll send in the answers or anyone, or someone will send in the answers to, uh,
to those trivia questions. Shoot. Oops. I thought I'd do a little bit better.
I talked about, uh, maybe working on some code. There's one thing that, uh, that I've been
looking for, and I've found different versions, but I couldn't get them to run, which usually
makes me want to go and make it myself. I'm looking for something very much like, uh, what was it?
Andrew Grummit made this dirt to RSS. We're basically you throw MP3 files into a directory and then
it automatically creates an RSS feed. Oh, a second. I actually had something here that
someone who has done something very much like it, uh, let me see. Is it up here? Yeah.
So what I want to do is I want to create an RSS feed of just random files that I,
that I collect because there's so much stuff that doesn't make sense to excerpt on the daily
source code because it would just be too long. But I think that, you know, I could pretty much
make a feed that would be entertaining to listen to. If you just subscribe to that, you'd get,
you know, podsafe music, you'd get, uh, a full podcast of, you know, the ones that I've enjoyed. So
I wouldn't automatically subscribe you to, uh, Don and Drew, however, um, you would maybe get
one or two really great episodes or ones that I liked a lot. And the interface for me would just be
dropping it into a folder on my desktop to be uploaded to a server and automatically, uh, create an RSS
file. Don't even need an HTML file really because I'll put all the show notes. Uh, and of course,
when you drop it into the folder, um, it should, uh, this program should, uh, scour through the,
uh, MP3 tags and create each enclosure and each item, um, uh, within the podcast feed based upon what's
in the ID3 tags. And then this morning, as I was taking Christina to school, actually, in the way back,
I had this on my iPod, uh, loaded up, uh, and was playing it through the i-trip on the car stereo.
And this sounded very much like what I'm looking for. Hi, this is Kim and Ken from Shakespeare
to Flay and Homeschool Habitat to podcast we do. Ken has made a fabulous program that he would
like to tell everyone about. It's called podcastmatic and, uh, basically what it does, it's a
pro script that will generate your HTML index webpage and your RSS feed, um, and it bases the, the data
in those files off of your MP3 tags. So tag up your MP3s with your comments and, uh, all that
good stuff and, uh, you can generate the webpage and the RSS.xml feed automatically. Auto magically.
And just for what, like, 20 easy payments of $20 a month? Nope. Not even. How much?
Only zero cents and zero dollars. You're doing this for free because you love mankind.
I love. Okay. And also, if you must pay us back, pay us back by becoming subscribers to our
podcasts, um, Homeschool Habitat and Shakespeare to Flay, where can they find your program, Ken?
They can find my program at Bradley. Chicago dot i-l dot u-s slash projects slash podcast
and you can find our podcasts at, uh, a very similar website, Bradley dot Chicago dot i-l dot
u-s slash h-h for Homeschool Habitat for SS Shakespeare, so Flay. Yep. So I downloaded the, uh,
the pro script, um, and it, it looks like it does exactly what I wanted to. You can set parameters
so it can run locally in a, in a folder, um, but it'll know that it's updated on a remote folder.
So I had it all set up and then I tried to run it. Remember, I'm the guy who, who didn't get
much further than Apple script. And I immediately threw an error asking for an XML module. Now,
I learned that on OSX, um, or at least the install that I have, if you're going to terminal and
you type in CPAN, which is kind of the, uh, the central repository for, um, uh, for all these
pro modules. Uh, and then, uh, space and then you type the name colon whatever. So it was like, uh,
XML colon colon, uh, death or whatever. I can't remember what it was. It was actually in the, uh,
in the read me file. Then it downloads all that, um, and it starts to install that module. But then
it broke because for some apparent reason, um, on a Mac, the pro install is not standard, um,
let me see if I can, uh, tell you what it says. Excuse me, um, what happened when I was
installing. Yeah, here's what it does. Um, it gives it throws this error about at at sign ink.
And then it basically says that, uh, uh, let's see, it's something with the Darwin thread multi-two
level, because it's not installed in the right place and then what happens is, uh, it fails on
comp, compiling these, uh, these, uh, these C-pan modules that I bring in. Clearly not something that
is going to work for people who just want to drop something in the folder, I know how to medically
create a podcast feed. Um, so I decided, uh, after about an hour, I said, fuck it, I'm not going to
try and reinstall Pearl because I know I'm just going to screw everything up. Um, and I actually
had asked Marcus to, uh, to hack something up in front here for me, front here or radio, whatever,
do something in user talk. And I don't know, we actually went through, uh, a list of stuff that
would that I would want it to do. And so he's probably working on that. Um, but, uh, well, if, if you
see a feed show up, then you know that I got something working. So that's just to call out to developers.
If you're, um, if you're working on anything very similar, that, uh, doesn't necessarily need some,
some install that won't, of Pearl that won't work on my Mac. I'd love to hear about it.
Okay, uh, let's see, uh, from pod castematic. Oh, yeah, you know, when I was in Holland,
taxi Eric, uh, who's the cab driver who I've, you know, used for years now for, for almost five
years since we've been living, since we've had a house in Amsterdam. He's kind of like my getaway guy,
you know, it's like my robber bank, I'm calling up him because he'll drive me to safety.
And, uh, and he, he really takes care of a lot of stuff for me and for, and for the family,
when Christina was, uh, when we're living there, you take Christina to school and it's just these
to great guys, part of the family. And he was, you know, he was, he read a lot about podcasting. He's
heard a lot about it. He hears me on the phone in the car. He never really understood it. And then I
said, you know what, Eric, why don't you just tune the radio to 88.3, which is what I have my
eye trips set to. And then I played for him the jet lag edition of the Rock and Old Geek Show. This
is the one where Michael Butler just got back from the two-week European tour. It is fucking hilarious.
And it's an English. And of course, Eric speaks English because he actually used to be on an oil
rig, uh, fly out two weeks on two weeks off. So he was exposed to lots of English. And of course,
his customers speak English. So his English is above average for a foreigner. And in the Netherlands,
most people speak English anyway, but he was, he loved the Rock and Old Geek Show. He was cracking
up, particularly the way Michael Butler was, you know, kind of explaining the scene with the girls
and, you know, girls and Sweden and which girls were cute or the ones in Sweden or Denmark.
And hey, wait a minute, take a picture of me with the big cans of hyenic. And it was just, it was
beginning to end. It was hilarious. And in that Michael also does a driving with Butler or
boating with Butler, which is kind of like a sound scene. Uh, only he narrates it a little bit more
and interviews people and sticks the mic in their faces. And all of a sudden, Eric got it. He was like,
oh shit, this is what you're doing. Said, yeah. And then as he said that, I press pause. He said,
what'd you do? I stopped the radio show. He said, you can do that? No, and of course, he's not an idiot,
right? He understands very well what MP3 players are. His daughters have an MP3 player. He's got
cable motor, and a PC at home. But just to have all those bits connect and to actually
hear it on the radio, he was completely blown away, which tells me a lot about where we have to go
still with podcasting. We have to make it easier still. I think I was talking about that yesterday
where, you know, we're kind of, no one is really quite hit the sweet spot of a player and an
eye potter at the same time. You know, most eye potters are good at getting podcasts, but they're
not necessarily the best aggregators, because, well, I think quite frankly, you know, it takes a while
before you figure out what your aggregator has to do and what you need it to do. And it's also,
none of them are really great players. A lot of them are using the internal quick time players,
or some other player that works on Windows. So, you know, we're just trying to hit the sweet
spot of moving away. I don't know if we can move it away. I mean, currently,
eye potter talks to eye tunes. You know, so we have two listings of files in eye tunes and an eye
potter. And the same thing with net news wire that I'm trying out this week. So, just stuff to think about.
You're almost really want to have, I don't know, in Eric's case, you want to have just a box
that can, you know, maybe the eye pot shuffle with an eye trip, you know, maybe there's a combination.
I mean, maybe we just need a very small storage device with a transmitter on it. Optional headphones,
of course. But one that really just gives you one or two podcasts a day, which will pretty much
be the limit of the, of the eye pot shuffle. That you can just grab with you, put it in the car
and place the two or three shows that you always listen to on your commute. Maybe we have to
think a lot smaller before we think bigger. And I do believe that we, we totally have to get much closer
to this all happening on the device. I had another idea, by the way, since I've been playing with the
eye river, maybe instead of having eye potter copy files over to eye tunes, we set up a way.
And I don't think this works very well on Windows, but if you plug in the eye river or any other
USB storage device on a Mac, it pops open pretty much always, I think it's always, it always has
the same name, a granted that name is often untitled, but it will mount on your desktop. I guess we
could make an eye pot or look for that, you know, if so, if you basically plug it in and all
of sudden the new volume mounts, which is titled, I, I, F, P, 799 or whatever, the then all the
downloaded podcast should be just basically copied over. And in that case, you know, we kind of
route around iTunes, which I think, and also Windows Media Center, which I think we're going to have to
do. It's going to, you know, either we have to incorporate it into those players or we have to
route around it. So maybe another thing that we could look into is a plugin for iTunes. That's something
that Madge Weinstein actually suggested when I, when I, when I called her a while back from
Miami. So anyway, just shit, there's one thing in my head today. It's a Monday, so, you know,
shit runs freely, podcast, tell you, okay. Hi there Adam, thanks very much indeed for playing the
promo on your show, how few days ago. And but a week and a half Adam, I've had 12,000 hits,
which has been brilliant, so thanks very much for that. It strikes me Adam that the UK is the
poor relation. And that's, uh, we over here in the UK, really should have a podcast conference,
podcast con, UK, I'll be speaking to a number of guys who are doing podcasts over here,
uh, dot com, post dot com, uh, hoxfm.co.uk. And a few of the guys as well, and in fact, we're,
we're looking probably at putting a meat together. And, uh, I've put a link on my site, podcast,
Paul.com. Um, so if you go to the podcast con, UK, uh, sites, it should take you through to, uh,
a page, tell you a little bit about it. I'm also going to put a pay weblog. I'll be a couple of
authors myself, uh, rarely, uh, Richard, they put a place I've just mentioned to you. And I'll send
you a link as well, Adam, um, so that we can contribute and put things on there. But, um, any
UK listeners do send me an email, please, or, uh, puts something on the weblog, uh,
enjoying your show as ever, uh, Adam, I get really frustrated when you don't do one, because, um,
I feel like I have to film a time with something else like work or something. I think I may,
thanks very much, indeed, all the very best. And do email. P, I podcast, P, dot com.
P, podcast, podcast, wake it, wake it, wake it, wake it, wake it, wake it,
I love it. That's great. Podcast Paul. Okay. There's also, um, uh, there's all kinds of podcast,
conferences and stuff that people are working on, which is pretty exciting. Um, working on some
in the states. I think there's one being considered for Minneapolis, um, about midway through the
year, uh, I believe there's, you know, some stuff in the UK. Yeah. Yeah. Of course, I'm being invited
to every single one. I don't think I can actually make it to every single one. Hey, how about some,
uh, some rock and tunes? How about a mashup here? I'm ready for a good mashup. This is a mashup
of one of my favorite podcasters. If you've never heard yeast radio and you don't know who
Madge Weinstein is, then beware. The following mashup is not safe for work.
Hello, everybody. This is Madge Weinstein.
I'm so sick. Okay. I'm 40. Do you realize what's going on? These people are fucking crazy
and have no business running the country. You meal concert and serve it at 80 years.
You know, let's say your husband comes home and he's like, stinks like pussy and you say,
we used to be good with somebody else and then a husband says no. And then she says,
I don't believe you. The husband goes with me. Are you calling me a liar?
Fucking bullshit. What ever the fuck you are? People that I hate.
Fucking obvious. El Presidente says fucking fucking fucking self.
President Bush, it's about the fucking roof, what you said.
Okay, now explain to me.
Did you listen?
Fucking obvious.
How can you tell me that these people have any business running a country?
It's blandest. Please, she's got balls. Madge Weinstein in the mashup.
The ACDC mashup featuring Madge Weinstein Eastradio.com. I was going to call
Madge over the weekend. We've been trying to hook up for over a week now. But the time difference
is a little screwed up. And Madge actually was off to VloggerCon in New York City and was interviewing
people and calling stuff through an openpodcast.org. And yeah, just some some good stuff.
Again, Eastradio.com is where you can find all things Madge. And from one end of the spectrum,
all the way to the other one, it comes to podcasts. Here's something about an educational use of podcasting.
Cole?
Hey Adam, my name's Cole Campbell. I'm a faculty member at Penn State University and director
of the IST Solutions Institute. I'm a podcaster. I have been for a while, have my own podcast.
But that's not really what I'm here to talk to you about. What I really wanted to let you know
was, is that I'm part of a group from not only Penn State University, but for other universities
around the country, part of the Apple Digital Campus. And two of us Penn State and the Missouri School
of Journalism got together with Educaz to make sure that all the sessions are a good number
of them were podcasted at the NLI annual meeting being held at New Orleans starting today, Sunday,
the 23rd, and pushing through to a Wednesday. We're doing some presentations on a whole lot of
other stuff. But the really cool thing is we convinced Educaz to set up blog spaces, to set up
enclosure hacks that work with the RSS feeds and everything. And you're able to go ahead and get
all that stuff downloaded to your iPod or whatever MP3 player and listen to it. What I thought you'd
find interesting was the fact that we're taking some of the work that you've pioneered
and we're moving in an education in a way that I really think is going to make an impact.
Some of us have even been doing it in the classroom and our students actually really enjoy it.
So I'm going to include the promo piece, maybe you want to play that, but other than that,
have a good time, enjoy it, and I'll catch you on the other side with the URL.
All right, let's play the promo then. All right. Hi, my name is Kyle Palmer and I'm a student at the
University of Missouri Journalism School in Columbia. I love keeping up on the news and I always
want to know about the latest things happening in the world, but sometimes I can get busy, you know,
class gets in the way. So I may miss the news on radio or may not be able to get back to my computer
to listen to NPR's webcast. But a new technology called podcasting may help me out.
So all I have to do is download an audio file of a newscast and interview our speech on my iPod
or MP3 player and go. That's it. Here during the NRI conference, you'll have the chance to use podcasting.
Over the next two days, you'll be able to download audio files that include conference presentations
and stories about some of the biggest topics we're talking about, like the balance between a
multi-tasking student like myself and faculty members trying to grasp the technology that I've
grown up with. Well, tell you, you know, this is this is totally right for education, by the way.
I know we've talked about this before. I'm so happy to see this happening. And wow,
what an opportunity for someone to really set that up right and make it work and come up with
some packages for educational institutions who are just looking for an easy way to disseminate
information. Isn't that kind of what teaching is about going from one to the next,
passing information on from one person to the next, sounds like podcasting to me?
I need a black star ship, racist through the time and space stream with one mission to make
as much havoc as possible. This is the ship of the evil mastermind Dr. Steven is suck shaped
assistant fidget. The reviews are written fidget. The radio adventures of Dr. Floyd podcast is a hit.
Yes, look at this. Five stars from podcastbunker.com. Four and a half stars from podcast reviews.net.
Tracks of the tree calls the Dr. Floyd podcast laugh out loud funny and says it'll make a dreamer
out of anyone who listens. PLPH radio says Dr. Floyd is good for all ages and delivers the
good. Well, yes, apparently one of a few podcasts that's fun for the whole family. You
know, safe for kids, fun for adults and all that. It's even become a syndicated show on godcast.org.
There's only one problem. Well, none of these reviews mentioned how absolutely fantastic I am.
So I guess I'm going to have to ramp up the evil then. The kid gloves are off. It's time to put
the evil pedal to the metal and it's several other cliches that mean. I'm going to become even
more evil until the reviewers stand up and take notice.
Oh, no, Dr. Steve is just one. It's to become even more evil than he already is.
We'll Dr. Floyd and his rag tag bunching heroes be able to prevent Dr. Steve from causing more trouble
throughout history. The only way to find out is to tune in each week to the radio adventures of Dr. Floyd
brought to UVA podcast by Dr. Floyd.com. That's DOCTORFLOID.com. New episodes of podcast every Sunday
subscribe now and set your imagination to fund Dr. Floyd.com. That's DOCTORFLOID.com.
I'm actually pretty hooked on the radio adventures of Dr. Floyd. PW Fenton puts that together.
It is a completely family safe show but it's weird and it's twisted and it's it reminds me a lot
actually of peel. Jump peel. Jump peel. I think it's jump peel, right? The the famous English DJ
who you see if I'm right about that. P.B.C. Peel. Jump peel. Why am I thinking? Yeah, jump peel,
right? He passed away just recently but he had kind of those those types of shows. A little bit
twisted, a little bit weird but cool. Definitely check it out and subscribe to it. And I got an email
from who was this from a young bullet. He's a Dutch guy. He said, you know, I've been listening to
the Daily Source code and I've been listening to all the songs you're playing including the
list of the obvious bitties. He says, now I heard this song you don't own me by the bitties which I
played and he said, it sounds to the T just maybe maybe one or two bars off and you know if you
twist and time stretch a little bit they'll actually fit together very well. He says it sounds just
like this song from 1982 by Dutch guy called Andrey Hazes and the song that he did was called
the Sechmannitsmeer. So just listening to the two titles I immediately could put them together
and because I know both songs the Dutch one from 82 now was Sechmannitsmeer and the bitties
says, you don't own me. So he actually sent, he mixed these two up. It's not really a mashup.
In fact, you'll go, huh? They're like, what the hell is this? But you can hear that it's basically
the same song. He also sent this mix to the bitties and Leanne is so crazy about it. She wants
to now record the Dutch version of the song. So let's listen to this mashup of the bitties and
Andrey Hazes. On broadcasting with Andrey. It's separated left and right for your convenience.
Okay, so that was, if you're listening on the headphones, I probably trip you out. I think they
are actually one octave higher than Andrey Hazes. But same song. Very, very cool. So we'll see
if the bitties come out with a Dutch version of that anytime soon. Thank you very much, Yon,
for being, yeah, for being on the ball there and actually taking the time out to mix those
dude together. Let's see, 36 minutes into the show. Actually, 32 minutes. Oh, we can just have some
time here. I had put these set these aside. Didn't think I'd have time for them. A couple of
geek podcast promos that I wanted to play for you because, well, I'll shoot. You know, I listen to
my like them. Hey Adam, this is Craig Shumaker from the Polymorphic podcast at drs75.com. That's drazz75.com.
I heard on your show today that you said you need to figure out some dot net stuff. I'm a dot net developer
and my podcast is about software development and the dot net environment. So if there's anything
I can do to help or if you need, you know, anything at all. So please let me know. Thanks.
Okay. Well, when I get my windows machine or let, you know, I have no idea what this dot net
stuff is about, but I definitely want to try out the mixed cast live stuff. I wonder how this
going? That was a dot net application. Haven't heard anything about it. Who was that? Oh, that's
Patricia. She's just rolling up into the driveway. Another promo for you. Hello, Adam. My name is Jeremy
and I'm from linuxquestions.org. We have a new podcast that I thought some of the daily source
code listeners might be interested in. The LQ podcast focuses on Linux and open source related
issues, we're also working on a live Linux and open source radio show called lq radio.
Both the LQ podcast and lq radio can be found at lqradio.org. Thanks. Adam. Boyo.
Yeah, pouring back at your melody. Okay. Time for some pod save tunes here on the daily source.
Code. This is from Andrew neatly. I think was reported in his apartment in New York city.
Check out Pretty Girl on the daily.
source of code
Oh, wait down to my song, yeah, you do
And there's nothing, it's going to change where I feel the table
Just want to tell this to you
Hey, right at your home, you walked this way with me
Oh, we're not gonna ever need you a strain
Oh, we're not gonna ever be able to move this way
But we're not gonna ever need you a strain
Hey, right at your home, you walked this way with me
Oh, we're not gonna ever need you a strain
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Every world can step in together
We're headed to call the black market
We should just stay
Ready, go home to walk just where you're coming
Stay and I'll set that for now
You'll be too late
Pretty girl and do kneesley on the daily source code
Could you mind coming in for a second because we Patricia just came home and we were actually
It started off. She just walked into the studio and she said I was ring the doorbell
Yeah, you didn't hear me. I'm sorry
We haven't talked to the daily source code listeners about my hair yet
Do you want to they have not seen a picture? Would you like to explain what happened?
They don't want to see a picture. Oh, thank you. Yeah
Well, you needed a haircut
So you didn't tell them at all that you needed a haircut. Of course I did. I said it that we went to salmon days
Tony and guy
My sister said who used to live in in London, you know Tony and guy. That's it hip
Salmon day if you look inside the that Salon you see those
Sort of goths, you know very hip people
Let's let this be a warning if you see a barber shop or hairdresser with with Gothic looking people that are you know black clothes black shoes black hair
Beware they are the stars
Yeah, you can see that we're hip we know you know what kind of hair you need so the two of us
Went in and ask for one of the books, you know where you see pictures of all sorts of hairdo's and we pointed out
One hairdo. May I say that you pointed out the hairdo?
We knew exactly because you had it before so I said this is what we want a little bit
Longer in the neck a little bit of hair on your foot thicker on top longer in the back, please
And and some hair on your rod have a high forehead with all the brains in it
So cover of the brains a bit and
So is it this is it? This is exactly what we want so I dropped you off
This was the mistake. I never should have let you never let my mom just drop me off you should have stayed there with me
You like watching my back. I didn't have my glasses on like a good mom. I dropped you off, you know trusting these people
And you trusted them with your child damage. I child we made the wonderful the gorgeous hair
You know that you have who's penis is bigger than David Bowie's and one point out
All your hair is short enough
If you had to choose
What between short hair or
It doesn't man. It's not it's not it's all in the knob
No, no, it's not it's not it's a combination of things of course
Hair and arm no, no because our people would know hair at all so you can and which which bald guys do you find sexy
I am three
But um so I dropped you off and
I went shopping remember and you came home and I said to my sister Ivn who stayed here
I said well, I'm so curious about his hair. I thought it's gonna be lovely. I mean one of the best hipster
hair salons there there
so
So when we come home you were hiding behind the door which was of course
a bad sign
And I said so how is and I still thought you were joking so and when you just
When you open the door and I looked
Behind the door I could not believe it you were a sort of a genre dog
You remember that
It was just like the rats were eating on it and
Nibbling on it and yeah and
One side was even shorter than the other side
That's hip baby. No hair on your forehead. It was so short. They thinned it out
Now have you ever if you have wonderful hair. Why would you? Did it look at all like the picture?
Absolutely not and I am afraid to go in there because I'm gonna kill her
I will make such a no really because I don't want to go in there every time I see that store
When I pass a bite it's a the seven-day store
I just I can her name was Eve
She gave you a car. She was really nice. Yeah. She gave you a car like oh
I'm Eve so remember that well we we we will remember that
I could kill her really and thank god hair grows but
You're I know you know don't laugh because you're laughing now. Why I know you're very unhappy about it
You're in terrible fall mood from me
Bullshit you're in a fall. Don't don't wink at me. This is a podcast baby. You got to be honest
You have to be honest on the podcast. I know why I know you're very unhappy about it
I'm not happy. Let's put it out now. I mean how does it look like? Well, I don't know. Do you know there's those things that you
Get cobwebs with it's on a stick
That's how it looks. I thought I'd look more like a chia pet actually. Yeah, now it's just unbelievable
She didn't even look at the structure of the hair or the type that you are you're tall you are
So how long do you think before I can present myself to the public?
Wow, but you were say today wants to do a photo shoot this week
If you get a reward right now
reward and a reward
reward
That would be the reward I get for putting you in jail. Yes
In a war or anything don't go
Okay, baby. All right. Thank you. I feel so much me on myself a steam has raised just just inches after this conversation
Thank you, baby
That was a nice way to close up the Monday source code
Addressor right now
the appointment and they they knew about the complaints
I'll really they'd heard about this about Sam and Dave. Okay
All right, everybody that's it then when I'm in the kitchen
All taken of that
You're easy
All right, that's the source code from Monday, January 24
And we'll see you back again here tomorrow saying time saying you are
Of course the time is completely up to you right whenever you decide to check it out
That's when you can get the latest show if there is a latest show of course
It's a daily source code. We're here every single weekday and today was the show for Monday, January 24 for 24 to 2005
My name's Adam Curry
Comments of course, welcome Adam at curry.com or if you're gonna send an MP35
Please send it to mp3feedback at gmail.com
And if anyone has daily source code at gmail.com
Let me know. I'd love to take that to gmail address. It was no longer available
So MP3feedback at gmail.com
And of course, you can always be the comment on the weblog at www.curry.com
I'll see you tomorrow right here for the source code take everybody that bye