Delta Sierra Charlie 215
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear since radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
60 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
July 27th, 2005, it's the source code.
That would be your official daily source code, it's...
It's the show coming to you once again from back home.
That's right.
Just got my butt off the plane.
That was about 116 million dollars worth of airplane.
I had strapped to my ass.
We're back at the cottage.
And guess what?
It's raining.
That was a mind-bender from a week of just absolutely beautiful weather in San Francisco.
By the way, it was really nice here as well while I was gone.
Of course Patricia says,
It happens every single time when you're gone and it's beautiful weather.
There you have it.
So it's chilly.
It's like a high 50s right now.
It's dank and damp and a little bit musky.
But I had a good sleep on the plane.
I slept in aggregate about four and a half, almost five hours.
So I figured I'd put together a source code.
See, we can keep it daily as the name of the show implies.
So once again, Virgin Airlines has done me justice.
Although the TSA is not done me justice.
I'll talk about that on the show.
You know, that's the homeland security, transport security authority, whatever it is.
And I've got some awesome stuff lined up for you.
Actually, not a half-ass show.
I've got hit test number 50 in today's show.
Youngpalette.
Of course, that's worth the celebration.
I've got a couple of promos lined up for you and a mash up as always.
But to kick it off, I want to play something that Abe Dove art from mashuptown.com.
Send me.
When I first heard this song, I got to tell you, I got like a lump in my throat.
You know, it wasn't quite that I wanted to cry, but I kind of did because it's
just so amazing to hear and listen to the lyrics of this song.
And I'm a sucker for big power ballads anywhere.
Power rock songs.
Check out Cruise Box.
You'll dig it.
Do you remember way back last summer?
When mainstream radio was such a fucking bummer.
No ending music.
Nothing seem funny.
Cleared channel motherfuckers didn't bother money, but somebody heard it wrong.
Now you can have it all right.
I heard it on a podcast.
Rock and fucking radio you wanted.
You got it.
Just download it and plot it on a podcast.
No one's gonna stop you telling MCC to stick it big in for revisions.
Oh.
Do you remember your first computer?
That piece of shit was like a freaking roller-roader.
Now we've got Wi-Fi.
Downloading files fast.
Listen to everyone who's ever done on podcasts.
Listen to me.
Now you're seeing each and every nation.
Radio is got to prove it's our imagination.
Need that song.
Sing a loud mash it up and exit.
Breathe.
Fucking loads you.
Now I'm gonna fix it.
I'm so bad.
I heard the call.
Now you can have it all.
I heard it on a podcast.
Rock and fucking radio you wanted.
You got it.
Just download it and plot it on a podcast.
No one's gonna stop you telling MCC to stick it big in for revisions.
On a podcast.
Rock and fucking radio you wanted.
You got it.
Just download it and plot it on a podcast.
We know I was gonna stop you telling MCC to stick and kill you.
The relevance of ours.
The relation of ours.
You're the machete.
Tell the FCC to stick at kick and cruise box.
I heard it on a podcast.
Oh, man.
I must have played this song 20 times since yesterday.
I got it on email yesterday morning.
I'd already recorded yesterday's source code did that late the night before.
And I was like, oh, man, I can't wait to get up.
That's really, this song was the motivation for me to do this podcast today.
That is such a kick-ass song.
I think I'm going to have to mash it up and mix it and create a new opening for myself
with parts of that.
And it's not just because I mentioned in the song, which, of course, I'm completely
fucking flattered.
But wow.
I mean, it's a great song.
It's just cranking.
I played it for Ron.
We were waiting in line at the bank and I had it on the MDA, which, by the way, I've
found out now is called the Blue Angel.
That's the official product name for it.
The manufacturer thinks it was an HTC or something who makes it.
And we were just vibing in the bank and I came home, played it for Patricia.
She's like, wow, that's a great fucking song.
And I can't get out of my head, man, as I heard it on a podcast.
Love that.
Love it, love it, love it.
It's a total fucking anthem.
Fantastic.
So, let's see.
We got lots of stuff to talk about, even though I'm a little bit out of it.
But, of course, I have something I've been missing for a week.
Yes, it's right here.
So, my sense, say, oh, you know, you can get, you can owe deons in, say, oh, but, man,
I still kind of missed it, you know, it's like that perfect combination between not quite
a cappuccino, but not quite a regular coffee, and you can make it within seconds.
And I'm not getting paid by the company, by the way, for saying this.
I've sold a shitload of them through my website, but that's just people I hope are sharing
the experience of a sense, I'm making at least 300 bucks a month on selling these
things.
So, but I really do like this product, that's great.
And so, in the curry condo, which is now official, like half an hour before my plane, or
before I'd to check in for my plane back, we signed for the condo in San Francisco, where
I'll be spending a fair amount of time for the foreseeable future.
And so, there's a couple of, you know, it's an empty apartment, right?
So, we're going to have to, you know, get furniture and stuff like that, and oh, man,
lots and pans and forks and knives and plates and you name it and chairs, and, and of course,
they'll have to be a little studio set up.
And I need a goddamn San Seo machine, otherwise the home was just not complete without
it.
So, boy, oh boy, let's see, let me just tell you about, oh, the flight back, so Virgin Atlantic
once again, great service, God, you know, it's so perpendicular, 180 degrees, the opposite
of Virgin Mobile.
And, of course, we went through that, how poor that service is.
It's almost as if they heard me talking about them because, you know, it was just fantastic.
There was actually, the plane wasn't completely full, and, you know, Mr. Curry can
we make up, but this bed next to you, so that all you have to do is just kind of snuggle
up, and they have a nice little sleeper suits that you can jump into, and it was great.
Unfortunately, I've seen all the movies by now, so I hope that changes every month.
You know, I literally have said, and they have a huge selection of movies and television,
and I've seen most of it.
So, you know, landed, you get, yeah, I've gone through this before, right?
You get your fast track, a little purple card, which means you go home straight through
a special line for immigration through customs.
My suitcase, it was there, walked right out as a part of the upper deck service.
There's a limo waiting for you, the guy knew where to take me, it was perfect, perfect.
And on the right home, the cell phone rang, the driver's cell phone rang said, Mr. Curry,
excuse me, it's Virgin, on the line, like, man, I probably left something on the plane, you know?
No, we just wanted to check and see if everything was okay, if any suggestions to make
our service better, like, well, yeah, change the movies, but otherwise, I'm very happy.
Now, what pissed me off is, you know, I bought this, was it two or three trips ago.
I bought this great new suitcase, this two me suitcase, which is indestructible, and it has,
and these, it has a TSA lock, you know, because if you lock up your suitcase, they'll break
the lock to go through it if they feel they have to search your lock.
And that's okay, I understand that, particularly my bag, it's all kinds of crap in there that
shows up up and scans, you know, I've got the craplet always travels in my suitcase and
chargers and you name it, but as a part of this suitcase is a really nice, expensive TSA
lock, and they fucking broke it off, you know, and until that's a plastic, what's the,
I have to say, we didn't know it here, and they put it up a little plastic tie on, it says here,
you know, to protect you and your fellow passengers, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
passing your screening, blah, blah, blah, as a part of this process, your bag was identified
for physical inspection. If your bag was locked using non TSA recognized locks,
C-A-S, what a C-S, a covenant aviation security, may have had to break the locks,
but the fuck, you know, this like a $20 lock that they broke, and of course the lock is gone,
so, you know, I guess it makes no sense, you're going to have to buy one of those locks,
it's just a scam because they broke it and it has big TSA letters on it, so
that was disappointing, but it didn't matter because I was home and my god Christina opened the door
because I didn't have my keys with me, and for like a split second I was like, who's this woman?
I swear to god, I got two chicks at home now. I'm believable, so the condo was approved,
Patricia Doria, I sent her some pictures over email and we already agreed that this was the
place that we should get, but I taken some video and some pictures and some details shots and the
video was really important because you can get a layout for kind of what the apartment is like that
you can't get from photographs and we now had to look quick by to eat and so yeah it's all good,
it's all good home fries, I did use the MDA, the blue angel to write down a couple of things I
wanted to talk about today in the show and by the way I am definitely liking this device and
apart my return I have ordered a new clip on carrying case, a hard case, so you can clip it on
your belt because I'm just deathly afraid that I'm going to drop this fucker somewhere, I've already
dropped it actually, it has a little ding in it, but I also, it's a little inconvenient, it's just
right on the edge of being too big, it's not too big to slip into your pocket but it's a little heavy,
so this has had a great case to go with it with a quick release, so I can look nice and geeky and
yet get to my phone quickly when it rings, extra battery which by the way is not a luxury because
it does last the day a full work day but it doesn't last the day in an evening, so the secondary
battery is necessary, there's still working on it and I got to say this is Windows Mobile 2003,
it's still, I'm not going to say it's buggy but particularly Wi-Fi stuff, it's still not quite
there yet, I find myself getting a little bit frustrated, probably one of every 10 times and just
hitting the reset button so that I can connect to a Wi-Fi, but I'm happy with it, I really am,
it's my life is now in it and luckily it synchronizes with my Mac, because of course I've synced
it up to the Mac and the crap-let it works both ways, so I got this great pocket Mac program which
doesn't, it's there's some things that aren't working in tiger yet but excuse me,
let's send sail moment, but I took a couple of notes because I listened to a ton of podcasts
on the flights about 10 hour flight, I listened to the bitty cast hadn't heard the girls in a while
and they've got a kind of the format down for their show while they're on the road,
they put plenty of live performances in there now which I'm digging and there was something really
interesting that I heard they were talking about that I didn't know about the U.S. Highway System
and I guess it was, I forget, was it Eisenhower? I think it was, oh and I forgot what they said,
I think it was Eisenhower who installed the U.S. Interstate Highway System and this is something
I did not know that the even numbers go from north to south or south to north and the odd numbers
one while I'm saying it the wrong way around, the odd numbers go from north to south
and the even numbers go from east west to east, so Highway U.S. one is all the way in the west
coast and of course 95 is all the way on the east coast and then 80 which is kind of like in the
middle, I've been even number that goes from east to west and root 66 of course goes from east to west
and I thought that was fascinating that I didn't know that that grid system was build up that way
and I kind of felt stupid because it makes so much sense and you think that that's something
I've driven a lot in this day something that I would have known but learn something new thanks to the
biddies, hey Adam Scott here for MapleAllRadio.com, I want to tell you about my podcast called
American cliche, producing our studio in Santa Barbara, California, I'll take you on a trip through
weekly headlines, bizarre news, odd safe music, that's right in the pod safe music network
and end this other amounts of pop culture dribble. During the podcast you hear great features
like the dirt bag of the week, listen a rant of the week and now that was a funny 911 call.
You can subscribe to the podcast by going to feeds.feedburner.com or slash American cliche
or you can just do a search and iTunes in the podcast directory for American cliche.
And don't forget to check out a ballradio.com for show notes and such. Beyond that it's also a
pretty cool independently run internet model rock station. The website again is a ballradio.com
that's the number eight B-A-L-L radio.com. You can also draw me an email at the American
cliche at gmail.com. Thanks for your time out.
But we also have some fun with a word association game called celebrity square root and then we turn
the tables with Ask Bill 3. That's where you as a guest get to ask me three questions about
anything you want to. You are the guest wants to share with the world your opinions and because of
that it is completely dependent upon your participation as a guest. For details on how to be a guest,
just go to our website at www.youaretheguest.com. Thanks for listening and I hope to be talking
to you on a future edition of You Are The Guest. All right. A couple promos there for everybody.
So here's what the schedule looks like for the next week and a half. Recuperation today
after I'm done with the show and I almost don't feel like doing the show notes but I will
am going to force myself. So I'm going to do a pretty tomorrow, plenty of calls lined up. You know
who call me Charlie Rose? That's cool. I definitely want to be on the Charlie Rose show. That's
going to be fun. So there's lots of interviews and lots of stuff that's lining up. Then Friday,
I'm sure we'll do some pod show business, everyone. We had some great meetings in San Francisco
so part of the small, at this point small core team that we have all flew out and we talked a lot
of strategy and I was it was good. It was really really good but particularly because San Francisco
just it has a good juice, you know. Then this weekend the wing commander who's birthday to us today
unfortunately he's going on vacation and I really want to get some stick time in so he has a
backup pilot. His name is Yamp and Yamp is not an instructor but of course I'm officially licensed
now so I can you know I can fly and he can go along with the safety pilot. He's going to pick up
my in laws at Rottenham Airport Saturday morning. He's going to fly the 182RG which is still
located in Antwerp because you know the wing commander won't let me have the plane. It might
position until he thinks I'm good enough to fly across the the channel all by myself which is a
good thing I believe. Then Yamp is going to take me we're going to fly around for an hour or two
and he's going to fly back and so the in laws are coming then Monday Patricia and I are going to
go to London we're going to stay overnight in London. We're going to go to the we've been invited
to the Playboy Party UK so I'm looking forward to that and I've been approved to do a sound
seeing tour. I have no idea what this party is about or what it's like but I think it'll be kind of fun
and we'll turn it off after the party because you know as I said we're you know dude we get to stay
in a hotel just the two of us hey that's going to be fun. And so the in laws will be here and then
Friday we're going to leave we're going to go to the States it's vacation time so I think I've
gone through the schedule more or less but the idea is first we're going to go to New York
stay there for a couple days go to Jersey look up the old neighbors hang out a little bit in the old
neighborhood you know it's just to see some folks in New York remember now it's vacation so please
don't go emailing me like hey let's hook up let's talk with me I'm trying to have a little bit of
vacation then we're going to go to San Francisco we'll stay in hotel for a couple days and we're
going to start furnishing the apartment we're probably going to stay in San Francisco for a good week
then we're going to go to Vegas which is going to be a shitload of fun and then from Vegas probably
go back to San Francisco and fly from San Francisco back depends on what the flights are from Vegas so
it will be a two week vacation and I got a lot of good response about the idea of having
members of the pod squad and other podcasters take over the hosting duties for for most of the
shows guys actually there's a lot of stuff that we're doing other producing so we have four hours
of day on serious I'd love to hear match wine scene do a day or dawn and drew you know and rock
will geek and so that's going to be fun it's a Steve Gilmour should do a day too you know and so
I I really want the the pod squad to take over I don't see see Chapman whatever you know
well there's plenty of time for people to take over the duties in those two weeks
speaking of duties maybe yeah we can get Chris from from the daily download to do it as well
I'm thinking that maybe even the we could do something fun with the pod finder as well
because it's just a lot of work and what I don't want is to be on vacation if say okay well I
got to go back to the room now because I've got to go record something I will do the daily source code
and of course that'll be vacation source code so we'll we'll see if we can break the format up a
little bit do some do some cool stuff let's see also on the way back I was listening to the
rock and roll geek show Michael Butler had a great interview with Tim Ferriss of in excess I know
those guys pretty well when Michael Hutchins was still alive they did a couple of concerts that I
hosted I've interviewed them before I think I when I we just moved to New York in 87 and we saw them
at the beacon theater which was although I really liked the band I was disappointing because that
a lot of tape running there it wasn't definitely was not all live that we were hearing the drums
were for sure they were on tape and he talks about there which I have not seen yet he talks about
there the reality show which is kind of like an American idol type show I guess where they're
looking for a new lead singer it sounds like it's cooler than it sounds and Michael Butler is
now a fan of that show so it was good interview and some good insight into the show and I actually
want to check it out now that I've heard that interview and along with that comes a mashup that
that just kind of appeared serendipably it takes a new sensation
international note but I'm also like the microphone because I'm a school and I mean I
ready to stay with me because I take this to all the way and I don't know if it's up to be
let's see if what I choose or leave is down and I don't know if it's up to all the
comments and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the
I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the way down and I don't know if it's up to all the
this.
It's the end of the world
yeah
Yeah, sticking your ear
You know, if you have zero energy level, this shit doesn't pump you up.
It takes a new sensation mash up on your daily source code today also a special day
because we have hit test number 50.
Let's say, uh, it's time for celebration, of course.
But before we get to that, we've got backtracks podcast number four lined up four, backtracks
podcast.
So you think, you know, your hits backwards and forwards?
I like to think so.
Yeah, right.
You're listening to the backtracks podcast exclusively on the daily source code with Adam Curry.
Hey, Adam.
Hey, how you doing?
Let's get right into this week's quiz.
I'm a little flush ready.
Yeah.
Are you ready, Adam?
A little fuzzy today.
Okay.
Here we go.
Alright.
Number one.
I love you.
Oh yeah.
It's amazing how you can hear it.
Uh, uh, we got the beat, the gogos.
Uh, time's up.
Number two.
I know this one too.
This is true.
Definitely, uh, uh, uh, men at work down under.
Time's up.
Number three.
Oh, sorry to see.
Okay, I don't know that one.
It panps up.
Okay here we go.
Okay. Here the answer.
Number one.
Are you.
Yeah I got this red grain.
Number one.
Let me find you.
We got the beat.
And here's number two.
Pretty sure I got this one right.
That's right, it's down under.
And now number three.
I have no idea what that is.
After the love is gone.
So how did you do Adam?
Two out of three.
Hope you enjoyed this week's Backtracks podcast quiz.
You can visit Backtracks podcast on the web at Backtrackspodcast.com.
Catch you next time.
Backtracks podcast.
Spin it back.
Man, the production on that is amazing.
It's like a wall of sound that just hits you.
Cool guys.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate it.
This is your daily source code.
Listening to the cinecast.
I don't know if you've heard that podcast.
It's a really good movie review podcast.
Sometimes a little bit too long for me.
But they always review at least one movie that I'm interested in.
And if you would ask me what is one of my most favorite movies of all time.
I'd have to say it's Willy Wonka, Charlie and the Chocolate Factory with Gene Wilder.
And there was something about that movie.
I can watch it over and over again.
I really really enjoy it.
And I've been looking forward to the remake, which is Tim Burton.
I think Danny Elfman did the music.
I think he did the music, right?
And of course, Johnny Depp as Willy Wonka.
And apparently, and I take these guys' word for it, it sucks.
And the part that sucks is the Johnny Depp performance that he really just somehow, from what I was hearing from the cinecast guys,
really really missed the mark on that.
I don't know what you're feeling is.
You might want to let me know if you've seen it or not.
But I'm afraid to go see it now because I've such a good feeling about the original that I'd hate for it to be destroyed.
And then I think, well, you know, maybe I should give it a chance.
But I got to tell you.
Uh, I'm thinking I'm going to take my boys off.
My husband has been hunted, but he doesn't know it.
He holds a secret in a power that could change the world, but he doesn't know it.
Setting this Scottish Highlands Tom Corbin appears to be a symbol tail of a lost boy in his growing attachment to his rescuer.
The beautiful Catriana.
But for Tom Corbin, the rabbit hole is a grave and a dead have something to tell him.
Created by Paul Story, Tom Corbin is a world's first novel written for podcasting.
It's family friendly and enjoyed by young and old.
It's a little different from most sci-fi and deliberately sets a thoughtful pace.
It takes you from a tiny corner in Scotland to events at Span the Universe.
It's yours free at www.podilbooks.com or www.dreamords.com.
Most of our high spots were coming to us now by TV.
But not this one serious 148 Adam Curry's odd show.
Experience the unexpected.
Tell the world.
Tell us to everybody wherever they are.
serious central 148
Portland Jazz Jams.
Pod shows are profound and powerful in their propensity to perfectly portray the
The personification of jazz through the medium of sound.
We're glad you came around as we lay the ground for the new technology we found to bring
jazz through the medium of sound.
Hey everybody, welcome to my promo for Portland Jazz Jams.com.
You can check out the pod show at podshow.portlandjazzjams.com.
For the hippest, the coolest, the grievous, the swingingist.
I'll have jazz Jams sessions from the local area and beyond interviews with hot artists,
Q&A sessions, instructional materials, and so much more.
Come and check out the website and check out the pod show.
Let's know what you think.
Thanks Adam.
Alrighty.
Very lean back podcast that is.
And definitely subscribe to that.
Message to Ray, message to Ray.
Stephanie would like you to pull those plugs out of your ears.
Hey Adam, it's your hit test number 50 already.
Wow, this has gone really fast.
Okay, I know you're on the road, but let's have a bit of fun with this hit test.
Three intros and this is number one.
Alright, kick and surprise.
Okay.
I'm already starting.
I'm going to blow number 50.
I can't believe it.
I'm sorry, Yarn.
I have no idea.
And number two.
It's either we are family or rockwell.
And the final one is number three.
Hey.
Triple mine.
Don't you forget about me.
I wouldn't dare, Yarn.
And times up.
And this is answer number one.
The first one and hit test number 50.
This is Mr. Ferris.
You are my one tattoo.
I never would have guessed it.
If you're fine.
You got it all and you're not the same.
Good song.
You are my one tattoo.
You are the one I've noticed this goes to.
You're honey into.
Alright.
You are my one tattoo.
What the heck was that for two?
Give me the thrill that I'm addicted to.
Look for a sensor and this hit test.
Let me see if Ferris.
And this hit test.
I got it.
We are family.
This is sister sledge.
Sorry.
We're together.
As we walk.
Come on.
We are family.
Go ahead.
I got all my sisters with me.
We are family.
Can I never find it?
And some number two.
And this is a third and final entry.
Hit test.
Number 50.
The simple minds.
This is don't you forget about me.
Won't you come to your memory.
I'll be alone.
Dancing you know it's just me.
Won't you forget about me.
Don't don't don't don't don't.
Get up.
Get up now.
Answer number three.
Don't you forget about me the simple minds.
Well, I'm this concludes hit test.
Number 50.
The next time we'll be number 51.
So I hope you enjoyed this one.
As always.
Two addresses.
Hit test at D-Mail dot com.
And J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T dot com.
See you next time.
Until then.
Bye bye.
All right, y'all pull that.
Thank you very much.
The 50th hit test, he is looking to 50 more buddy.
Thanks again for your contribution to the daily source code.
It really makes a big difference.
That's it.
We're moving up on 40 minutes, time to quit.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
So I will be back tomorrow.
I'll be a little bit more awake, promise you.
And I'm also going to promise you.
I'm going to play that FCC here on a podcast song.
Again, yeah, I really tripped me out in love with it.
That's it.
Your source code for July 27, 2005.
DailySourceCode.com as we can subscribe to this podcast.
You can also just search for it on iTunes, if you wish, check it out on IndyPotter.org, our podcast
to Ali.com.
And now we've got so many full places where we've got to go on on www.curry.com is my web
blog, servers getting better.
You can actually get to it these days.
I didn't get to all of the feedback about the sound seeing touring San Francisco, got a couple
of the emails.
I'm going to save those until tomorrow.
When will return with a daily source code?
The power of the door to the door to the door to the door to the door to the door.
Feedback is very much appreciated at amacurry.com.
You can send an audio feedback if you.
So wish, I'm kind of skating at the 98-99 percent on my Google
Gmail.
The size of Gmail is increasing, but not as fast as we've seen it increased before.
So I'm still just on a very verge of having to start to the lead stuff.
Hopefully I won't have to do that.
So Adamacurry.com is where you can send that off to.
And we'll meet again tomorrow, right here on the source code.
Stay subscribed to everybody.
Thanks for checking us out.
Bye-bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.