Okay, this is, hi everybody. Welcome to a special edition of the Daily Source Code. This is for Tuesday, February 15, 2005, which it really is.
It's just that here. I'm in the lovely town of Utrecht in Holland. It's 10 minutes to one in the morning.
Tomorrow, I'm leaving it eight for a conference where I'm speaking.
It sounds really funky. It sounds kind of shitty, actually. Anyway.
I don't know what you're doing there, Ken, but you're messing up your intro dude.
It's Ken Clark, everybody. You made me laugh.
Hey Ken, how are you doing? Have we haven't talked in like two or three weeks?
I know we were going to try to do this more frequently, and then life caught up with both of this.
I liked it. Life got in the way. I have been working.
Yeah, we're supposed to meet this morning. I got up. I was on the computer at like 7.45 and you're like, where you been?
Yeah, exactly. I was just about ready to leave because I'm, so I have this thing tomorrow.
I was going to have to be this early, so I took the 930 easy jet flight.
I love fucking easy jet Ken. I don't know if you can.
It's an easy jet. It sounds like a disposable jet plane.
Yeah. Well, it's a budget airline. The service is Europe, but it's just, it's so perfect.
Everything about it is right. I bought stock in the company. I love it so much.
So it's like a European jet blue.
Yeah, I don't know. Probably. I don't know. It's something about the attitude though.
They're whole four minutes right. That's very, very good service. Good attitude as well.
But this has no service. They promise you no service. So anything you get you love, you know,
and even the little smile from the flight attendant is just like, oh, I love you.
You know, and that's, that's the guy flight attendant. I'm telling you, it's crazy.
I don't know. If my voice, it sounds like I'm like I'm coming through triple on this.
I don't know what's going on. Anyway. If you sound fine, I'm okay with that.
Yeah, but I don't know what I hear is what everyone else will hear.
Well, whatever. I don't, actually. Yeah. Who knows? It doesn't matter.
So Ken, last time we spoke, we were catching up on the 37 different MTD air talents that you worked with.
So here I had forgotten. You reminded me of a couple like Trixie and Trixie.
Yep. People I had completely forgotten about Wendy Westbrook.
But so I had somewhere around 30 mids, some that we talked about.
And we barely got to, to when you and Julie both got hired.
Oh, Jesus.
Wait a minute. But it wasn't like four people at once.
We talked about Kevin Seal. How he got us auditioned.
There was only much college campus.
Yeah. I mean, I mean, we stayed on Thursday, by the way.
I'm having dinner with him with Steve Leads.
Oh, cool. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, that's right. You're going to New York this week.
Yeah. The big, the big US trip, baby.
Well, tell Steve. I said hello.
Yeah. We'll do. Okay. I'm sorry. Interrupted you.
Well, I was just going to say JJ left and Julie came and then Nina left and you came.
Right. And then Carolyn Helben.
Carolyn Helben came shortly thereafter and replaced somebody.
Mark or Alan.
Hmm.
And then Kevin Seal. Alan. Alan because Mark was one of the last ones to leave.
He was still there when I was there.
It was like really weird.
Nina was actual. I'm not Nina. Martha Quinn was the last of the original.
And she came back. She kept coming back. Yeah. Yeah.
Once you got hungry.
We got a funny piece of mail after we did that last show to remind me that she had
had the dubious honor of playing Tracy Brady Bobby's wife in the 1990s TV movie.
That's right.
That was great.
It was an adult drama or it had Brady's in which Bobby is ever called
a quadriplead.
It's horrible.
Instead of, you know, Mama was said never to play ball in the house.
They were dealing with topics like Bobby's erectile distance.
It didn't really make it.
It did all right though, didn't it?
Must have done pretty good on DVD.
I don't know.
I did.
I watched it.
It was hilarious.
And Martha was cute.
Even though in person.
She's a little bone. She's too bony for me.
Of course.
Very, very teeny girl.
I mean, that's one thing we've never mentioned.
Martha's probably what?
Four foot eight.
Yeah.
It's like 90 pounds.
That's right. It's snappled like a twig.
Well, I feel tall next to Martha.
You're, you know, six and a half feet tall to begin with.
Yeah.
But she had like a putter beat my beer right on top of her head.
Can was beautiful.
So that was a horrible show in the show.
Bro, basketball player came in at one point.
And she barely came to his waist.
I think that was shack.
It was shack, wasn't it?
I think it was.
Look, I barely count the shack's waist.
I hugged him one.
I said, excuse me, Mr. Shack.
You know, I'm tall in my world.
Like, can I hug you?
And he was like, yeah, that's cool.
That's what the reboc.
That was great.
You know, we've already, our digressing,
but it made me think,
didn't you do a photo shoot with Michael Jackson one time
whereby he had to stand on a box?
Oh, yeah, I've told that story many times.
Yeah, well, I've been on a whole Michael Jackson support rampage,
you know.
Oh, I have nothing.
I, I, I, I withhold all opinion.
I really do.
I mean, I've met this guy.
If anything is asexual, you know, he just loves hugging people
and loving people and he's a kid, you know?
Oh, I, I, I, I don't, I would like to think very much that
it's not true.
I do think that perhaps he has a screw loose
from being too famous and too protected
for too long.
But no, you know what, even that's not true.
I'm telling you that even that is it's all just media
and what they've made him.
He's played to it, of course, but dude,
this is like a really well rounded, nice,
well brought up human being.
I'm telling you.
It's, it's a, it's a big joke.
And we just, we, we don't want to see it.
We don't want to believe it.
Well, I tend to always, you know,
I sure they're a little, the whole family's had a fit
with us.
But, you know, it's just back to the end of time.
I hear an allegation of this nature against anyone
that, you know, money is often a very motivating factor.
Fuck, I, I, I tried it with whole chess.
Yeah.
Well, you should watch that Haraldo thing.
It was pretty good.
Haraldo did interview and, and some of the pieces of it.
Yeah.
I haven't seen the whole thing.
You know, speaking of interviews, I saw,
we talked a little bit about Daisy Fuente's last time.
She came.
Well, she did fill in work there for a while.
She was the weather girl on a channel,
something or other, right?
Tell him window.
My new jersey.
I've got to see if I could turn you up any louder.
You're really soft.
You got to talk to me, you're like,
Oh, my mic is strapped to my face.
It's strapped down.
Maybe my mouth is strapped down.
Is it strapped down?
Oh, it's strapped.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's better.
Daisy was doing the weather at Tell him window.
Channel 49 or Channel 47.
She was the, the Latin weather babe.
Oh, I love his team.
And Steve Leaves was there because I remember watching the tape
and thinking that there was something interesting about her.
But, you know, she was just at the time.
MTV was very, very milk toast and Daisy was very exotic.
Yeah.
And that just wasn't hip at the end.
Jungle fever on the channel.
So she went and did MTV int on the nasty one.
I mean, not till now.
That's right.
And she could barely speak Spanish herself.
That was hilarious.
Yeah.
She, she, she, she.
That's great.
Something about Daisy this week.
I was going to say, I saw a great interview show with her.
But I didn't know that Daisy had lived in Spain as a child.
Yeah.
She was Cuban.
But I think she had lived in Spain before moving to New York.
And what's the difference, really?
But yeah.
She, she, Spain, New York.
Spent most of her time speaking and learning to speak in New York.
Cause Daisy had quite a mouth on her.
But Daisy was on Rachel,
got the chick from the food network that's got that new talk show.
That's a variety of nice, Rachel Ray.
And network showers on the food network.
Food network.
Okay.
And that's pretty happened.
That's just like, right.
Yes, it is.
And Rachel does this Friday night talk show where she interviews celebrities.
This last week with it was Dennis Franz from NYPD who last week.
We before was Daisy went this.
And they were in her apartment in California.
Making some kind of Daisy was showing her some Cuban dish.
And it was a really cool interview.
So you should, if you happen to catch it, you should.
It was like a cool to.
I remember how with Daisy and see what she was up to.
She was just engaged or getting married again to some.
Guy was my star guy.
Yeah.
English pop star guy.
That should be up in your London then.
Yeah.
Actually, that is true.
She said she was spending quite a bit of it.
She likes going to London because people don't know her.
Right.
And he likes coming here because people don't know him.
What is he going to find out who it is?
Can.
All right.
I've got to get a name.
I remember one time was coming.
I remember that I saw it.
Right.
I remember one time was coming down.
The corkscrew into the, what do you call that?
The corkscrew into the Lincoln tunnel.
You know what that's called?
On the Jersey side.
Yeah.
Can't remember.
They had some cute name for it.
Yeah.
And there was some.
Remember I had the roles.
We talked about that.
Right.
You were waiting in line in the 12 booth.
Yeah.
Well, it was kind of like on that ramp going down towards the toll booth.
And it was before easy pass.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So I had to pay four bucks.
Maybe it was still 350 there.
I don't know.
And I was like this.
Hongken next to me.
And I look over on this.
This little white little Japanese thing.
It was no way.
It was a Daisy had a hot.
This is funny.
She'll be embarrassed.
Daisy had a hot.
Pontiac Fero.
Oh, that's right.
It was a Pontiac Fero.
Right.
Yeah.
That's right.
It was white.
That was.
That was her weather car.
Yeah.
Moved up.
Right.
So.
And then she rolls down the window.
And I'm in the rolls.
And I rolled down my window.
She says.
Pardon me.
Do you have any gray proposal?
She thought she was being cute.
Yeah.
Well, she was.
And then I reached over to my dashboard.
Yeah.
And I pulled out some gray proposal.
But of course.
That's what made it all the funnier.
She had a jar of it.
Did there.
Did you do somebody was going to have to say that to you sooner or later?
All right.
So from Daisy.
From Daisy.
Carolyn Healthman.
Yeah.
She was supposed to be the the chicken eggs door from Colorado.
She came and went pretty quickly though.
She was there for two years.
And that last year was a constant argument between her and the powers to be.
Yeah.
But it was horrible.
I felt so bad for her because she had thick legs.
And big hips.
I'm just being honest.
You know, she was beautiful.
She was a beautiful person.
She was very cute.
She was big.
She was big bone to can.
Now that they wanted.
They wanted some glam chick.
And she wasn't.
No, that's not true.
They wanted.
That's not true.
They wanted to have a girl next door.
And that's totally what she was.
But then.
Then they wanted a glam chick.
And instead of just saying, hey, we want a glam chick at the fuck out.
They told her like, oh, you know, don't wear this.
Cause it, you know, you look too fat in it.
I said, I tried to make her into, they wouldn't let her wear her glasses.
She had to.
I felt so bad.
That was because I, it was kind of happening as we were just getting there.
And it was, I got a whiff of that.
And I was like, man, this is fucked up.
She, uh, she was a Colorado girl.
I was like Carolyn.
I think she went back to Colorado.
And last I heard and last I saw an interview.
She was producing.
Local television.
Really sing, not on camera.
Colorado and was married and had kids and is an avid ski bum.
Yeah, of course she is.
Yeah.
Good for her.
Excellent.
She came in, did her thing and got out.
And that was it.
Yeah.
A New York was not for her.
It was killing her.
Really cared for New York.
Hey, look, I only spent a year in New York.
And then moved to fucking Jersey.
I do remember a young, smitten Keanu Reeves, though,
showing up at the studio and hanging out with Carolyn.
Really?
Yeah.
Keanu had a crush on Carolyn, helping.
But during that first year.
Really?
Oh man.
It's happened to think of that.
Forgot about that.
Interesting.
He has a new movie out doesn't he?
Keanu?
Keanu.
I don't know.
He was at the, uh, at the Baptist, the British Academy film awards.
And he was being like, I'll trippy.
I don't know what I make of him.
Sometimes I say movies and I really like him.
Sometimes.
Sometimes I say movies, but in real life he's kind of weird.
We talked about Kevin last time.
I think Kevin, the whole thing.
And he's back in Seattle when he's married.
And I think pursuing engineering.
Right.
He was being built, nuclear, a nuclear facility or a bridge or something.
Your facilities are bridges.
I can't remember which.
You know, I was waiting for easy jet.
They, of course, they were delayed with that's part of the charm.
Not like, I tried to record it with myself.
I didn't catch it.
Like, three times they announced, will the atomic physicists translate
Amsterdam on easy jet?
Easy, why?
If I won one one, please contact our company.
You could use some assistance.
Like, will the atomic physicists?
He was trying to figure out how to tighten the rubber band back up.
It must have been a joke.
They do it three times.
It was great.
That was great.
All right.
Back to MTV's slime.
This is a part two.
We're the way boon units.
Oh my goodness.
Yes.
We've got about very regularly during that period of time.
Dweezle and moon unit.
Right.
Oh, they were really nice.
I always really liked moon unit.
I dug moon.
I thought you was really cool.
Dweezle, I can't say I didn't like.
Dweezle was just so...
He was out of his mind.
He was in New York.
He was in the chicks and drugs.
And he was totally living rock and roll.
My mic sound.
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
He's only where he was at the time.
No.
He probably did.
And it was during that same period of time that China can't.
They're gray slick and Paul canner's daughter.
Guess VJ every summer for like three years there.
Yep.
And remember China?
I do remember that.
Because I know it's probably 14, 15 years old when she first walked in the door and started
doing summers.
And the thing with China, first of all, her mom was nuts.
China was a sweet, relatively unaffected.
Yes.
Yeah.
But her mom was nuts.
Her dad was nuts.
And they would cross by.
All up all the time.
And I got to talk to Grace.
For hours.
You were talking to Grace Slick for hours.
Love Grace.
She was wacky.
She was out of her mind.
Yeah.
But she was very sweet and very nice.
And kind of like they're both like Drew Barrymore kind of people.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
She ended up a potty mouth.
Yeah.
And she had Steve.
Now, Kain and Littman were the George Michaels managers at the time.
And this was big fucking, you know, shaking your butt.
George Michael, mega, mega fame days.
And she was all his hanging out with George Michael.
So how he was pretending not to be gay.
That was the big secret.
I think last week you asked me about Bernsey, who first.
The number of years answered the phones there at the MTV studio.
Yeah.
George Michael, we want your sex was the I want your sex hit of the week.
I want your sex.
Bernsey got in trouble on numerous occasions by the management for picking up the phone
and saying hello.
MTV.
We want your sex.
Those are the days that we do before John.
And he had to.
Yeah.
Had to.
Of course.
Somebody got that complaint.
Those were the days.
When I look at MTV now and I see that studio overlooking Times Square.
It's not somehow, you know, the whole vibe of sitting in the fucking basement, which really was,
even though it wasn't a basement, we were next door to it.
We were on the ground floor.
Yes.
In the balls of a big brick building.
Right.
No signage out front.
Next to Sally Jesse Raphael and all her degenerates walking down the hallway.
On 57th, we had CBS Street.
Yeah.
No one knew that that's where MTV was.
That was a great thing.
We had the biggest rock stars in and out of there.
No one ever knew.
No spark.
Nobody knew where it was.
And no one was that.
The only thing that was near there was the Rolls dealership, which is how I got trapped.
There was nothing to him.
What was the name of that dyno?
We'd always go to it on the corner.
Oh, God.
No.
The oldest grace.
The great.
The flame.
The grace was by on Ram.
Yeah.
Wasn't the grace?
Wasn't that.
It was the flame.
I don't remember.
And there was a way.
But there was Tony's Delhi.
It was next door, right?
Tony's Delhi was the little.
Yeah.
I wonder if he's still there.
Tony is.
I think not.
I haven't been down that block in a long time.
But you'll see.
When was the last time you were roaming around Manhattan?
Dude, it was before 9.11.
You're going to trip.
I mean, if you just go anywhere near like the whole time square 42nd Street.
It's Disneyland.
It's like a whole new city.
Is it like Disneyland?
It's cool.
I mean, I'm like Tokyo.
It's like like Tokyo.
I go back as frequently as I can.
But yes, time square is is, you know, when I first got to New York in 84 times square
was, you know, prostitutes and drug dealers.
That was cool.
And it was cool.
And then Patricia and I would walk in the middle of the night to light FM to go see
Rick as she flash your boots, which was a right on time square.
We do that at like one o'clock in the morning.
You remember when Rick was, was that when Rick was DJing there?
Yeah.
He probably still is somewhere, right?
You know that he's, he's Rick come on the audio guy.
He was basically any light FM station you hear with that guy in the middle of the night.
That's Rick.
Well, and the funny thing is Rick didn't sound like that in person.
No.
And you could do anything.
You first guy and he'd get in there and it would be like the light at the end.
Yeah.
And you could do anything.
You call him up.
You call him up on the hot line and you be talking right.
And like, and you go, you have to go, I'm smoking a joint.
No.
Yeah.
We got to set coming up here.
And then we, WLTW, let FM.
Yeah.
He would never crack.
I was fucking great.
Then they put in that whole computer system.
Like the entire day was wrapped up automatically and computers.
You didn't have to do anything but sit there and talk every few seconds.
And enter the beginnings of the need for podcasting my friend.
Exactly.
I haven't heard the new kind of in the script show.
By the way, haven't heard it yet.
The Valentine's Day show.
I did hear the Valentine's Day show.
I did.
Half of it.
I've heard.
Okay.
It went this morning.
And you know what?
We were stationary.
We didn't travel anywhere.
Nothing complicated.
No.
I heard the promo.
Okay.
Yeah.
Just a little.
I just want to curse Don and Drew for a second.
I have to curse them.
Because I got the today show.
And I, you know, it came in just as I was leaving for the airport.
Right after I skype you, like, you're a fool.
And.
730 in the morning.
And so I'm.
So yeah, this is like three.
It's like 430 my time.
And so I'm ready.
You know, the taxi's almost in front of the door.
Toon is home.
I'm leaving.
Sorry.
And.
So I'm listening to Don and Drew on the way to the airport.
And, and I hear them say, like, well, you know, because it's show number 68.
We want to do 69 on Valentine's Day.
And you have to take, it's a brilliant idea, by the way.
You have to take the survey on the site.
And then you get the secret hidden link to show number 69, which is.
Completely foul mouth just weird ass.
But, you know, so I'm sitting on the plane the whole way.
I think, and we had a delay.
Like, oh, man, I could have been listening to show 69.
Swallow.
Baby, where are you?
And so I curse you.
You actually like the idea of having to go do a quiz.
Great idea.
I was blown away.
And it's all these questions.
Like, who do you love more?
Don, Drew, myself or God?
Yeah.
It's like perfect.
That was a great idea.
Those guys are smart and talented and funny.
I love them.
Okay.
So, we've got to do some more here.
Who else do we have?
Andrew Datto.
The great white hope from Dan.
He was very cool.
Very oblivious to everything that was going on.
He just came in and did his thing.
Andrew was very cool.
And I think only there for what a couple of years.
But there was friction between him and I.
There was friction.
It wasn't between.
It wasn't because, you know, we had a problem with one of the other.
But I never knew that.
Yeah.
There was a little bit of friction.
But it wasn't really like, um, not that we didn't like each other.
It was friction like because they, they'd fuck around with everything.
Okay.
Now, let's, Andrew's going to do headbangers ball and then he'll do this.
So he's basically doing all my shows.
Of course, they were testing him out.
But, you know, it was weird between the two of us.
He knew it was going on.
Trying to shake things.
Oh, God.
Because I haven't my list of people that came in around that same time.
Were the pair of Jonathan Solomon and Lisa Edelstein awake on the wild side.
Oh, my goodness.
With the fucking with the breakfast set?
Yeah.
Several set pieces of which still grace my living room and everybody always comments on them.
Dude, do you remember?
Okay.
Here's one for you.
So in the early days, I'm talking 88, 89 from me early days.
Okay.
That's when Sam's set we still had, which was like the Sam's diner.
Sam's diner, right?
And then we had the the booth.
Right.
And then so this was this theater seats.
That was a stairway.
That was a really cool set.
So this is the height of MTV exploding creativity.
We were just breaking through on the 40 million households.
Cable was popping wide open.
It was a big deal.
And all of a sudden, all these idiot motherfuckers would come through and change everything.
Come with this great new concepts to shake things up a little bit.
And at one point, we had this set designer who for an exor,
I'm sure was an exorbitant amount of money created the sand set.
Oh my god.
Let's just bring it back.
Everybody come to sleep for a second.
Do you remember that dude?
Well, it was a nightmare.
But I don't remember what happened.
Didn't it involve sand and like gallons and gallons?
That's glue.
And it was sand.
Everything.
It was like a couch and a chair and all covered with glue.
It was sand.
Totally.
Forgot that's right.
They covered all this furniture.
They like dipped the shit and glue.
And then just cut off the sand.
So stupid.
Oh, you'd sit on it.
No, this sand and shit was.
That's right.
And that's right.
You would have to.
And it was like, I think at one point, Julie revolted and would know and refuse to sit on
sand set.
I'm not sitting on that fucking thing.
Yeah.
The sand might get a lot of hair and kiss me puns.
We're like too old.
Whatever.
I think of Julie yelling out of the make-up room.
They'd say, we're ready for you on the set, Julie.
And you'd hear her yell down the hall.
Right.
I'm just rinsing me, no need.
Just rinsing me.
Oh my goodness.
Oh my.
Yeah.
So there's a great period of time.
We're Julie was dating Billy Idol.
That was fodder for all sorts.
That was.
Yeah.
That was pretty funny.
That was Billy was big on MTV at the time and he was up there.
He was huge.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, boy.
Billy had the best work.
There was some great.
And Julie wasn't that big apart really.
No.
I think had to put up with some serious shenanigans.
Let's see who else is on my list.
Well, Ricky Rackman, who came in when you stopped doing head bangers.
You were just doing.
I think dial MTV and the top 20 video count down at the point.
Right.
Rackman came in to do head bangers ball.
I think people liked Ricky as well.
Well, the reason what happened was that tattooed Narlie had been.
Right.
Well, no, but at that point at that point in time, he was a co-owner.
I think of the cat house in LA.
Yeah.
And that was where Guns and Roses or specifically Axle Rose would hang out a lot.
And so he was buddies with Axle.
And that is pretty much what got him the gig.
And honestly, he was right in the middle of that scene.
And he was kind of right for the LA hairband rock scene.
But not for what he was pretending to be.
I mean, I was, even though I was a fucking poser and had just a whole bunch of pretty
leather jackets and attitude.
I bought it for leather jacket.
I really was always into the music.
You know, I really was.
And in the beginning, I know a lot of guys that would come on on the head bangers ball
and go like, oh, dude, like, you really care.
I was like, yeah, I'm totally into this shit.
But I could also digs in the other stuff.
You know, but we're friends with like the guys and deaf leopard and stuff.
And Ricky was hanging out with Molly crew and Guns and Roses.
And it was a period of time when LA, you know, that metal scene was all that.
And Ricky was right in the thick of it.
So years later, when we had the office in Los Angeles,
Ken, I bumped into Ricky Rackman at the airport at LAX.
And he was, say, it's what you do, man.
And he said, wow, you know, I took my company public, like, fuck you,
Rackman.
Like, it's like my company public.
And I'm like, fuck it.
It's some set man.
Look at me.
I'm wearing a suit.
Yeah.
And, and Ricky's like, yeah, you know, this is a manager now.
I'm managing her.
It's like porn star.
And at that point, I thought, man, your job don't suck.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
But I mean, you know, what would a former metal people do in LA?
Yeah.
Hook up with porn stars.
It's Molly crew was not back together in hot again.
Yeah.
What the hell would Vince Neil be doing?
Right on.
What was he managing a strip club or something?
See how I'd do that until they're getting fat.
There was a TV show on this year.
It was a riot.
I can't remember what channel it was on.
It may have been like the learning channel or something.
But it was a complete physical makeover.
And every week, I don't, it's usually not a celebrity, but they were doing it.
It was probably about four or five, six months before Molly crew announced they were back together and going out in the road.
And it was a complete physical makeover of Vince Neil over a period of, like, four or five months.
Really?
And he had, like, plastic surgery.
He started drinking.
He got a personal trainer.
He went to vocal coaching.
Freaks.
Style is hair cutters.
I mean, they fought.
They filmed the whole thing for reality show.
Oh, yeah.
Totally.
I mean, he looked like hell when he walked in the door.
It was like, that's Vince Neil.
Oh, my God.
And by the time it was done, he did it.
He was doing a solo set at the hard rock in Vegas.
And he had a shit together.
It looked like Vince Neil was totally back.
And then he was a few minutes after that.
They're crewing out.
They were going back on the road.
So unfucking believable.
Although I'm not sure about the drinking because he's already been arrested once on the tour
for pounding the daylight side of somebody.
He is a baby party and just a little bit of a kid.
I can't imagine the crew on the road without partying.
So let me see.
Do you remember curry?
You know, I really like curry.
I really did too.
I, you know, I liked her.
She was cool.
And then when she got her breast, she was even better.
Well, she came from remote control.
Curry started on remote control with Ken Ober.
Ken Ober, Colin Quinn.
Curry were Adam Sandler.
Yeah.
Dude.
He was on the channel all the time.
Yeah.
I mean, it's amazing.
He got a lot of support from a TV.
But yeah, curry was really, really funny.
And went on to make a bunch of pretty good.
Well, she made a bunch of like, big, great horror movies.
But they were like, good, big, great horror movies.
Yeah.
She'd like really got maimed and killed and stuff.
It was good.
But she was sexy.
You know, she was played like a scientist too.
Yeah.
I wanted it.
Well, you had to take the glasses off and the hair just comes full swing down.
Chumbling down.
Yeah.
My librarian.
That's, that's what Curry were.
Is it?
Typecast librarian.
Sexy librarian.
Who was Steve?
Steve Trikas.
We almost forgot Steve Trikas.
I forgot.
He was the dad.
He was the Paul Schaefer of remote control.
And you know.
Sorry.
Let me finish all the coughing at once.
You can then edit it out.
No.
I'm editing nothing.
This goes out like this.
You never fucking lazy.
No.
Why?
It's all the, all the, all the, all the fun stuff.
And you know what?
Let me just say something.
You guys, you edit that too.
Someone's editing on your show.
I wanted to edit it.
Don't edit it.
Well, I want to hear when you fuck up.
Each show would be an hour and a half long.
Well, started timer, you know.
Then you started timer.
I know.
You, you pull out shit.
That's not interesting.
Then you have an, an interesting conversation.
Yeah.
Typically you record for an hour and a half to two hours.
And you end up with.
You're kidding me.
And it's of comedy.
It's some five good editing.
Good editing.
Yeah.
Think of it as audio theater.
Oh, I do it.
See it to the mind.
All right.
Now I listen to a two secret,
Lissiveous bitties.
The bitty cast.
One of, it's a fucking great.
One of them is in the van.
It's van talk with the chicks on the road.
Dude.
I'm like.
I love it.
Bitty cast.
Hey.
On Wednesday, Joe's pub or Joe's cafe.
Fuck, I can't remember what it is.
At nine thirty that they're premiering the bitty cast.
I'm, I'm so there.
And in the big apple.
Mm-hmm.
That is the debut bitty cast.
That's the debut.
But anyway, so, you know, I think,
Deedra, she keeps saying, well, we'll edit that out.
You know, and I don't know who did the, who did the bitty cast.
But it's in there.
They left it in.
It's great.
You're like, don't even say.
You have to say that it's boring.
It's not boring.
It's fun.
Well, I leave certain things in.
You know, some weeks like this last week,
the Valentine's Day show.
Very, very, very little editing.
Because we're getting better about coming in.
Right amount of time.
Right.
Sometimes we just get carried away and also,
and you're like, holy, shit, we recorded an hour and a half.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, so that's, so that's,
all right.
Speaking of which, let's do, uh,
good about ten more minutes, eight more minutes.
Let's do couple more.
Okay.
All right.
I was going to say before I gagged before
who is Steve masters?
Cause he's on my list of people.
Steve Masters, of course, and by the way, I found out his real name. Steve Masters was running MTV
and was eventually fired and replaced by John Reardon.
Yeah, I remember John Reardon.
Yeah.
Hold on a second.
And then he went off and he started the E Entertainment Network because it was the movie channel.
Yeah.
And he was, Lee was a pretty interesting guy.
He looked like he had been in like a Columbia drug cartel.
Well, him and Bob Pittman.
Oh.
Bob Pittman always used to scare me.
Bob Pittman was pretty cool.
When we first got to New York, we're still living at the Mayflower.
Mayflower Hotel.
Yeah.
Well, who ate?
No, one of the cats.
Somebody was either a dog or a cat.
It was the cat.
I lost in the Mayflower Hotel.
Stop.
But, um, and it was where we were still there.
And he said, come on.
We'll go to John Cook and Melancham show.
We went to, you know, it was cool.
He picked up a pick up in the limo.
Went to the show.
Went backstage, hung out with John Cook there.
And, uh, he was nice.
But he was definitely like a major league mover and a shaker.
He was like, Bob Pittman.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Big time.
No.
Yeah.
I mean, I, I worked at the channel for almost 10 years.
I met Tom Preston so many times.
It's not even funny.
I, you know, 20, 30 times over the period of time.
I was there.
And every single time Tom would come to the studio or something.
He'd come into the room and he'd say, hi, Adam.
Hi, Julie.
How are you?
Yeah.
He was good at that.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
And how long have you been here, son?
I would have been every time.
And they'd say, this is Ken Clark.
He's the, the VJ talent manager.
You know, you remember him?
You met him two years ago.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Fine.
Guarantees, six months later.
He's good.
And who are you?
You know, well, you know, but a cloud follows Tom Preston in my book.
Hmm.
Oh, yeah.
There's a cloud that follows him, boy.
I think I know what cloud we're talking about.
Johnny Abbott.
Yeah.
Well, let's talk about that another time.
I don't want to talk about that.
And I was going to say that's a sad story because Johnny's
somebody that I really, really liked and got a bit screwed over.
I loved her.
She was, she was beautiful person.
She committed suicide is basically what happened.
But that's for another show.
That's a teaser.
Ken, that's a fucking clip.
I was MTV's fault.
Yes.
I totally blame Tom Preston.
I said it.
God damn it.
Well, all right.
Ken Ober and Colin Quinn.
We glossed right over him.
I don't know what happened.
I'm going to cover Colin Quinn's done quite well for himself.
Finally, there was a long dry spell there.
But then he wasn't through HBO.
He started to make some shit for HBO.
And then he hooked up with Ted Demi.
He was also passed away.
Yeah.
Yes.
Unfortunately.
And then it's Saturday Night Live for a few years.
Colin Quinn did the news, right?
Right.
Well, that was also because Beth McCarthy,
who was a director at MTV for a hundred million years,
wound up directing SNL.
She probably still does.
Oh, she does.
Yeah.
Beth and I were interns at the same time.
She actually worked for Steve Leads for a little while.
That's right.
Production.
We have a lovely relationship.
Beth and I.
And then she went into the control room at one point.
Is it?
I can't remember.
You know, she ended up a assistant director and then later a senior director
and has now been at Saturday Night Live for a couple of years.
Maybe five, six.
More than five, six years.
And primarily, I think they brought Beth in because she was really good with live music
and MTV.
Saturday Night Live's.
Yep.
Music performances had never been.
But she learned everything from Milton.
But that's a.
From the Lage.
Yeah.
No, it was the King of Ditty.
DV.
I mean, it club MTV, baby.
So wait a minute.
So there's a great connection.
So club MTV.
There was this big thing.
It was Milton.
Lage.
And he was, he was Greek, right?
Wasn't he Greek?
Yeah.
And he was.
And really cool Greek.
Yeah.
And he was like he was smooth and slick.
You know, like, you wanted to hang out with him because he was kind of cool.
And he was, you know, who would laugh, kind of like that Mafio so way.
And very calm.
And he was direct.
Yeah.
But when he was directing, he was like boom boom boom boom.
But he was funny about he wasn't an asshole.
He was a boom boom is right.
Right.
Because he was doing club MTV, which was basically that was Julie talking about
some music and then, you know, tits.
That's a best in angelating bodies.
And what was the club?
What was the club?
What was the name of that?
We used to shoot that at the play team, the play team.
Right.
Down on 14th.
It was for real.
And it was all the, it was like club MTV.
And, you know, then once a month they do four days of club MTV.
I think it was once every six weeks.
They would run out there.
Yeah.
And for three days.
And awesome.
Yeah.
And they would do back to back to back.
You know, all day.
Yeah.
Believe me by the 8th or 9th show.
Julie's Waba was dragging.
Yeah.
It was out of baby.
But anyway.
So there was this one chick.
And she was kind of like the leader of the dancers.
And her name was Camille.
Camille.
Yeah.
And Camille at one point.
Doing well for yourself.
Yeah.
Wait.
I'm getting to that.
Don't blow.
I'll let you do the punchline.
I'll let you go.
And she had.
She had plastic surgery done on her face.
She had her breasts.
It just blown up to enormous proportion, which, you know, Milton totally egged on.
And once she first had her cheekbone implants put in.
She hadn't taken out later.
She looked like she couldn't.
Yeah.
It was awesome.
It was really bad.
But, you know, she was endearing somehow.
And actually, boy, was she because what happened to little old Camille, the club MTV dancer,
Ken.
Oh, she married Kelsey Grammar.
Fucking crazy.
And she's now.
Isn't she hold on?
Wait.
She is a lead spokesperson for, um, it's something disgusting.
And I have to do it with your butt.
Like you're at a bolt irritable bowel syndrome.
What's he's posh now?
You know, and she shows up in these people magazine pictorials.
Oh, yeah.
They're California mansion.
They're mans.
Right.
And you know, and Kelsey Grammar is, of course,
Kelsey rolled his brand new Viper over, pulling into the driveway.
That's wrong.
He's, but he, you know, he's having a good time.
He's got that English accent going.
So you think, like, you know, he's all proper and shit.
But he's like drinking and he's boozing.
And he's, you know, and he's having a good time in Camille.
Oh, please.
At the time, he, he went out and bought a brand new Dodge Viper when they first came out.
Rolled it over, pulling into his own driveway.
Oh, yeah.
She did quite well for herself, didn't she?
That was nice.
Oh, Lord.
Well, you know, we're at, like, 40 minutes.
So we should, we should leave.
You know, we got to cut it short.
We need people to keep coming back.
For more.
So we're going to do more on the, on the mysterious Tom Freston cloud.
Okay.
I got to talk about that.
I really feel bad about that one.
Well, shit.
Yeah.
I want anybody to have a think I'm making light of that situation.
No.
But, you know, I've only written Camille.
Yeah.
It is quite a scandal.
And it got buried.
They got buried.
I don't know.
Well, big media company.
We should pop the car for that stuff.
Yeah.
We should pop that one.
We don't have a scoop.
All right.
Well, we can talk about that one another day.
It's 130 here.
I got to go to bed.
And you've got a big day tomorrow.
Big day.
And then I'm going home flying home.
And I still have to listen to the Don Andrew Show.
Number 69.
And the Kenan script show number.
What it is.
Oh.
It's the Valentine's Day special.
We don't number him.
Yes.
Indeed.
Okay.
And I can just hear Patricia saying, Oh, no.
Not a Valentine.
Exactly.
You said you had to fly up there.
Yeah.
Well, happy Valentine's Day.
Thank you.
You too, counting me.
Okay.
I will speak to you soon.
It's always fun.
Chanting.
It's good to remember old time.
Good times.
It is.
And talking to you and doing this.
Always remember things that I had long since forgotten.
So it's good.
Okay.
So you got your plugs in, right?
Yeah.
For the Kenan script show.
Dusting my brain.com slash KSS.
Every Monday, new show.
Okay.
All right.
I'll talk to you soon.
And another daily source code tomorrow.
Y'all.
Bye.