Hey everybody, this is Adam coming to you with the daily source code for Tuesday, March
8th, 2005 from the restaurant area at Skiple Airport in Amsterdam, which is outside of Amsterdam.
Got myself some McDonald's, I looked at the healthy stuff like the walk place, but it looks
shitty. It's 820 PM, and oh man, today has been ups and downs, rollercoaster all the way
in all aspects, by the way the sound quality is because I'm doing this on the iRiver recording
on its internal microphone, so whenever I basically move my hand on the casing it creaks
and scratches, but in general the quality is not bad, I found, so where to start off, today
was supposed to be a flying day, and literally flying day, getting up really early, 415 to catch
easy jet to Amsterdam, where taxi Eric was waiting to drive me to Antwerp about an hour and a half,
to do some serious flight training with Wing Commander William, and when you're crazy about
flying like I am, and you got one of the best in the business to train you, you'll do almost anything,
and of course, driving back up after that, and taking the 955 flight home, which gets me
in almost exactly the same time, 10.05 since we gain an hour, flying back in time from Amsterdam to London.
So, I recorded some bits in the car, and I was going to do a much longer recording in podcast
on the way back, but I'll get to that in a second, why that didn't happen. But the easy jet flight
was actually great this morning, left on time, 7, 6, 25, got in on time, and we were able to land
on not the fifth runway, which is the one that's like 15 minute taxi ride away from the terminal,
and literally the plane has to taxi for 15 minutes, so we about 10 minutes early, taxi Eric wasn't
even here yet, so it waited for like 5 minutes, he showed up, and then we started to drive down,
and as I promised him, I brought along my iPod with the I-trip and his favorite podcast,
Rock and Roll Geek Show, so here's a bit of our ride down to the airport.
Okay, we're in the car right now with taxi Eric on a way to Antwerp, this thing is in Rock and Roll Geek!
Hey, how are you doing, buddy? I'm very good thank you very much. So we're off for some flying lessons today.
I'll crank it up Eric, let's listen to Rock and Roll Geek Show, Mark's got the I-trip cranking
wild parts, the theme song is Cheers, nice to opening down for there, thanks a lot for joining me, I really appreciate it.
So I'll be checking in a little bit later on, right?
Oh, and this is a here, really pretty unbelievable, we're sitting here listening to Michael Butler,
trying to think of Cheers.
All you think is, I'm just showing them his trio with your GPS, and it actually seems like he's working.
You can't listen to that person anymore, you are, and we'll give you driving directions,
and it tells you how fast you're going in the car, what do you think about that?
Oh my god, that's amazing!
He is so nice!
Oh, thank you, man.
All right, have it.
Like I said, chicks dig guys with GPS equipment.
So, and speaking of GPS, so I, oh no, I give a positive review to the
map-opolis navigator GPS for the trio 600.
I'll put a link to Michael Butler, you know what I mean?
Okay, well you guys were listening to that, I polished off one of the two burgers I bought,
from Mickey D, and I got my large fries here, and, you know, they don't give you free ketchup,
or as they like to sell here, the free sauce, which is the French fries sauce,
pay for that extra, a little, a little bucket.
I remember the first coming to Holland, see people eat French fries with mayonnaise, and it really
grossed me out, because you know, that's you eat that with ketchup, right?
Kits up.
Well, I'll tell you what you get used to it that for a while.
I'll actually start to like it.
I'll go on to something here to use Dutch guys.
So, we got to the airport, Antwerp Airport, which is where the wing commander has his hangar
in his operation, and we went up to the back gate, and Nick, who you know, because I've
flown with Nick before, came up to the gate and said, you know, we actually, the gate won't
open, because they just called a strike, so here I am, I've been traveling for a couple hours,
to do some flight training, I'm really psyched, and now the fucking airport sounds strike.
And actually, that was the last recording I made of the day on the spot.
So, here's us discovering the strike, and Nick trying to smuggle us into the airport,
and not succeeding.
So, we're at the Antwerp Airport, and I can't move the foot, I can't move the foot.
And guess what, there's a strike here.
So, we can't get onto the field itself, this is a, this is a relatively small airport.
There's only one airline that flies in on it here.
V11, the Flam-Soulet-Fartmaster Bay, which flies from Antwerp to London City.
Not really convenient for me to land here today, because London City is a real long haul from
our house, whereas Gatwick and Heathrow are pretty close.
So, we're now in the main hall, and there's a whole bunch of striking workers, and it's only an hour
long strike, so let me be done in about 20 minutes. Nick came out to pick us up, I remember Nick
flew the mooney with him. Oh well, it was months ago.
And so, now we just see if we can get onto the field before the strike is over, if we actually have to wait
until everyone's back at their posts for them to let us on.
It's shitty, it's shitty, yeah, it's especially after, you know, the day started for the death.
Yeah, I got up at what time, I got up at like four or fifteen this morning.
Yeah, I used half-fosh five, and it started for the death, and then we started very bad.
Oh, I'm mooney, I'm a white Brazil.
Oh, that's your life.
You had a big flu.
Okay, yeah, I'll pretend I got out.
My daughter had a tooth.
I don't want to end the tooth at there, you know?
Yeah.
And I'm, uh, be had this wonderful ride all the way.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I really cleared up with the rock road.
Each year.
Yeah, how did I start this?
I started smiling and then I did, yeah, you know, and I defrost.
Yeah, totally defrost, and then I come in and I'm fucking pissed over again.
Okay, well, that's all right.
Of course, we can do a fly.
Yeah, we're gonna fly.
I'm gonna fly.
What's the deal?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm gonna, I'm gonna fly.
Okay.
And all the way, if we come, we'll jump to the next.
Is it a restaurant?
No, it is.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're gonna back.
See if you want me to go to the next one.
Okay.
It's good, Nick.
Thank you.
Okay, it's a Nick person.
I have a comeback.
Man, this guy's gonna sell me an airplane.
They will be back.
Boys in the desto restaurant.
Yeah, they will be in the same spot.
Three.
Yeah.
Well, this is kind of interesting.
Interesting start of my training lesson for today.
A training in human relations.
Okay.
Now we're going into the training a little something to work here.
I'll have a cup of tea now actually.
Yeah.
You can go.
Okay.
Can be closed, man.
Okay, let me introduce more.
Well, haven't you seen my interview?
I once related the intro of this video.
Um...
... right...
When you went to our club?
What do you usually love?
Yeah.
You would like here?
It's a competition in Boston.
What?
Yes.
Thanks.
Good start.
Good spot!
Okay.
And I do another audio check.
See how that came out.
So it didn't sound too bad.
It's a high river.
It's amazing to me every single time.
So needless to say,
we got in.
The weather wasn't great, but it was actually more than good enough.
And kind of cool to have a little bit of wind and turbulence to work with.
My touch-and-goes.
And we did some pretty extreme flying for a bit.
William took the wheel.
Then it shows me how the Cessna 182RG, which stands for a tractable gear.
Fly is just like a fighter plane.
And poor taxi Eric was in the back getting greener and greener.
And then we'd ask him like, you know,
you got big shoes, man, because you might need to use it.
But he was okay.
He, Eric has been on the helicopter.
He went to the, excuse me, burger.
He worked on the oil rigs in the North Sea for seven years.
And so that's like, you know, two weeks on one week off.
And you're always transported by big helicopters.
So he's had even had some water crash training.
So he was okay.
But still, when you're doing touching-goes,
it can make you pretty crazy in the back.
But we did that for like two hours.
It was great.
Wonderful plane.
Really really really like that machine.
Fast too, man.
Like a hundred and the cruising speed, about 150 knots.
You know, you can go up to,
this thing can really move.
It can do like 170, 170 miles an hour.
So really quite quite a nice machine.
Of course, the gear retracts.
So it's, that's where it gets some of the better aerodynamics from.
It's definitely a machine I'm looking at.
So I got really excited.
You know, we're kicking the tires around the hanger.
And it was two crappy after a while when we got back to take a helicopter out.
Well, certain do that another time.
And then I got a phone call.
You know, so first we had the roller coasters in the air.
The ups and the downs.
And I got a phone call that a legal proceeding that I've been
up to up in for like two and a half years.
Finally is being settled.
And I'm getting almost everything that I obviously deserved
about two thirds.
So in a settlement, you got to give a little bit right.
But it was just getting crazy.
Two and a half years worth of crap.
So I was very happy about that.
And all men with planes started looking more attractive to me.
I tell you.
I was like, you know, what would it be like to own one?
And so, you know, we had some coffee, hung out,
and you just talked to a guy stuff, right?
Which I really should have recorded.
I apologize.
But I was kind of sucked up into the moment.
And hop in the car to drive back to Amsterdam to the airport
and my phone rings.
And it's a whole other proceeding that just, you know,
these things like the courts here, it's crazy.
But I don't even want to go into it.
So it's like, you know, where one door opens,
another door closes, or one door closes,
another door opens.
That's definitely what happened today, man.
Just continuously.
So close the door on one proceeding,
and open the door on another,
which was not a good door necessarily to open.
And I'm just trying to cut loose from this country.
And I just want to get all my assets out
and just be freeing clear everybody and be done with it all.
And just when I think I'm out,
they pull me back in.
Well, that was a shitty impression.
So I spent most of the ride back on the phone with lawyers
until about, not just about three quarters of the way.
And then I actually got another boost of a call.
We've, I've finalized some important agreements
and stuff, which is called stuff for now,
for a new company that I am co-founder of.
And I'm really excited.
So this is where another huge, like,
they loading doors opened up for me today.
And now, don't think that, oh, you know,
this is Adam's podcasting company,
because it is going to be a part of a podcast
and that is, will be a part of a much larger idea.
I think is extremely exciting.
I'm going to be talking about it in the next weeks.
Maybe even days, talking more about what I see coming
and where we're going.
And podcasting is a big part of what's coming.
It's probably just the tip of the spear.
And it's taken quite a while to figure out
where I might want to fit into all of this.
And I think I've done them on to something.
So what I'm going to do is, I'm just going to presume now
that my flight back is going to be uneventful
and everything else would be fine
and that there are no more doors opening and closing today.
And tomorrow I will be back with you from the cottage
with a full source code.
When you've been saving lots of bits over the past two days.
Of course, we had the Patricia Pi Podcast,
so I kind of left that run from Sunday over to Monday.
And tomorrow, we know, first day,
really back behind the mic with a full outliner stacked
with clips and stuff to talk about.
And who knows what else we'll be mentioning tomorrow.
Now remember, all of you are under the no-dam announcements rule, right?
All right.
So in closing, I'd just like to say,
that isn't an amazing, but I'm sitting here in airport.
They're the McDonald's talking into a piece of plastic,
which is being broadcast to all of you.
Elroy Jetson signing off.