Delta Chericharly 2-3-7
They are your secrets!
I information you don't get out of them!
Adam Curry
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass!
Done the next generation radio content in my ears!
I like to think I'm flying you to the future!
And it's September 8th, 2005!
Welcome to the Daily Source code!
The Power of the Lord!
Yes, Surrey Bob!
Shit lagged!
Oh boy, the honeymoon is over between me and Virgin Atlantic!
We're talking about that today!
Just stepped off the plane!
From New York, I'm back in the cottage in Gilford, Surrey, the United Kingdom!
It's good to be back home!
We also have to talk about some of the connectivity problems that
Basically, with help me from even getting all of my show notes up on the server
Properly, that was a major hotel snafu!
I must say though, I'm very pleased with the Yamaha Professional Audio Workstation AW16G
It's an unpacked, beautifully in New York, performed perfectly!
And came back through open suitcase, which was not checked by TSA this time, right?
At least they didn't even have a friendly little note behind me!
That'll have to wait!
I can't even go home and shit starts ringing!
Ah, there's a Skype Upgrade!
And now, that's got all kinds of cool features that are ringing off the hook!
I've got plenty of email to look through!
For the next, I'm going to try and keep it in 30 minutes!
This will be your Daily Source code!
You've got brand new Podsafe music coming up from Rob Costlo!
See, I've got a couple of promo for you!
And as I said, some stuff to talk about the trip to New York!
And obviously, some email that came into the Gmail still skirted at 99%.
Kick it off though!
We've got a mashup!
Team 9!
This was actually from mashuptown.com.
This is the perfect mashup for after a long weekend, such as the previous holiday weekend!
Baby mashup!
Belinda Carlisle and Graham Coxon on the Daily Source code!
And then it's supposed to...
What the hell is that?
Oh, that was lame!
How come I didn't work?
Let me see!
That was really weird!
I thought I had an old program!
Okay, I could start the show over, but this is...
I'd say this is too much fun!
Oh, I see!
You know what?
It really helps if you put the mashup in the lineup!
We've got a lot of fun!
I'm out!
I remember one of that Ballina Carlale song, and saw the video came out with that inflatable
blow.
It was quite a rock jam though.
I remember that.
I mean, a team nine gets you going after the long weekend with that mash out, Ballina
Carlale, Graham Cox, and sorry for that, it's a very unprofessional moment before we
rolled into the song.
Let's just chalk that one up to the jet lag.
And of course, as always, and when we have bandwidth, I'll be uploading everything in the
show notes, all the links, all the MP3s to the promos, and of course this came from
a mashuptown.com.
I found out that AWSart from mashuptown.com is Dr. Art.
How about that, huh?
It's always the doctors and your dentists and your next-door neighbor, lawyer, who's doing it,
all that legal stuff.
Okay, I mentioned the honeymoon was over with Virgin Atlantic.
Yeah, I mean, it's not entirely over, but I was very disappointed.
Told you on the way over what a great trip it was in the upper-class suite and completely
lined flat on the bed, and a nice little note, personal note from Sir Richard with the
email address.
I'm definitely going to email them now, because here's what I did.
I thought, you know what I'm going to do.
I'm going to take the 1110 PM flight back from New York, so I had some time to hang out
with a couple people, and I went over to Sirius, Sirius Radio, and it's been mostly
the afternoon there, and I definitely want to tell you about that.
And I thought, you know, what I'll do is I'll have dinner with the Steve Leeds from Sirius.
We've talked, it's Steve's been on the show before.
Rock and roll in radio, legend, Steve Leeds, and you know, then I'll head off to JFK, and
then I'll get on the plane, and I'll go to sleep, and then I'll get up, and it'll be like
11 o'clock, and I'll have to head a short, but a good night's sleep.
And I got on the plane, it's like, wait a minute, this isn't, this is not a Boeing, this
is an Airbus A340, I think it was a three, yeah, A340, and like, whoa, hold on a second,
these seats, although they do recline, this is the old model.
This is what they used to have before, and it's far from the suite, the bed doesn't recline
completely flat, it kind of goes down on an angle, it's really weird sensation, it first
that the chair goes down about about a foot into its encasing, and then it kind of goes
down, but your feet kind of touch the floor, well, it just didn't work for me, I had my eyes
close for most of the trip, but I don't think I was in a very deep sleep at all, I had
been a nice little sleeper suit down, that was kind of cool, and everyone was very nice,
and they all understood that it sucked, I think if, you know, if you're going to pay the
same amount for a flight with a, with a, with a sleeper suite, then if you don't get
the sleeper suite, it should be cheaper, that's all, so I'm, you know, I'm going back
to New York Tuesday, I believe, and so that's the big trip, right, the big trip for the
rest of this month is New York, then on Tuesday, then Wednesday, to San Francisco, then the
Tuesday after that, back to O2 Chicago, then back to San Francisco, then to New York,
and then back home to London, so it's going, and that's going to take me through the rest
of the month, so it's going to be, it's going to be pretty busy, but I've got the workstation
with me, and the actually, before I left, even before I went over to Syria, satellite radio,
I went to Sam, Ash, music in New York, legendary, any musician, it's ever been in New York
or it's ever heard of New York, and knows of Sam Ash, it's, what a great store, and I was
really looking for a similar set up, a similar mixing board, as the Yamaha, but I wanted to be
just a tad smaller, and I had like five sales guys, and of course there are musicians and gear
heads, and so they were totally into the whole concept, and it just doesn't exist, not on a
smaller scale, this Yamaha is the best I can do for now, because you can get the, you can get
mixers with built-in hard drives and effects and processing and dynamics, but then it only has
two inputs, which means you can either do a stereo signal, for example, from the laptop or you can do
two mono microphones, but you can't do a mic and have a stereo signal on any of them that I saw
that were of any smaller size, so that's too bad, but as a holding a market, you know, a whole
by the way, the cast blaster fills up just very nicely on the software side, hold on, you know what,
I just mentioned that, I better put a link in the show notes there to cast blaster, perfect,
and then let's see, so I told you about the meetings we had in New York, those were all great,
but on a pawn checkout, and I didn't tell you what hotel I was in, I was in the
St. Regis Club at XSX House on Central Park South, which was an expedient offer, and so it looked
like a really nice hotel, and you know, it said, some rooms have Park View, I got the partial
Park View Room, I think I've mentioned that, and you press your nose up against one of the windows,
and it kind of looked at the right there, and then you could just see the Park, but it was great hotel,
you know, the price was very affordable, like $250, I think $270, of course you get tax and all that
crap, and you know, room service or whatever, and so the plan was, you know, check out around
noon, one o'clock, and then I was going to head over to to serious, and I was going to walk,
which I did with my, oh man, like, I've so much, it's so many things, I'm gonna tell you about so much,
but the checkout, so I, I was going to check my bag and leave it there and come back, let
you know, around 8 o'clock when I was going to go to the airport, so I go to the cashier,
and it's just beautiful black woman, it was helping me check out, and just stunning, really,
smooth, skin, beautiful smile, really friendly, and of course the inevitable question came,
when she said, did you enjoy your stay, and I said, well, you know, yeah, except I won't come back,
if the internet isn't fixed, because it was so slow that I couldn't get any work done,
I couldn't, I just couldn't upload my files, it was, you know, it was worse than a modem speed,
she said, yeah, I know there's something wrong and it's been that way for a couple of days,
so well, it's someone working on it, she said, I don't know, you know, she does talk to the tech
guys, and they were maybe upgrading something, or you know, it wasn't quite clear, and of course,
I cracked the joke and I said, well, you know, it's going on, is that someone's downloading porn,
or they got some freaking porn server up and rolling, you know, that's what it looks like,
because the, the inbound bandwidth was okay, but the outbound bandwidth was almost completely gone,
so, and she laughed and she said, oh, you made my day, and I was so funny about the porn
comments, you said, you know what's interesting, she said, as she's completing my bill, she said,
I know the tech guys, and they don't really know this, but I know all the codes to the movie,
so I know exactly what movies you saw. My brain, of course, goes a thousand miles an hour,
I like, and she's, and she's snickering, I said, well, you see, I couldn't download any porn,
so I had to get it one way the other.
Were you a fan of Doctor Who? In that case, you need to listen to Doctor Who, Parachark.
All the latest news, reviews, and cast interviews, also thoughts on the longest-running sci-fi series
from a British. And American perspective, head over to the gallehraneembusy.org to your weekly
slice of your favorite Renegade Time War.
I should have queued up some more stuff, should I?
Hot chill. Content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
Hi, this is Kevin Crossman from the Frappac podcast. You know the Frappac, all those guys in this
comedy movies, it always appear in each other's movies, Ben Stiller, Vince Vaughn, Will Ferrell,
Owen, and Luke Wilson. Our podcast covers all those guys, plus other related movies like
40-year-old Virgin, stuff that Jack Black is doing, and more. We play music, we have interviews,
we have listener feedback, and reviews of these movies, and more. Come listen to our podcast at
www. Frappacpodcast.com. Grab that net and catch that beautiful butterfly, pal.
Call us now. I apologize, I'm all over the map today, it's I didn't cue anything up, it's
the dedication though. So just about that story that I was talking about before, those promos,
needless to say, I was probably pretty embarrassed. So anyway, she promised me the internet
would be fixed. So we'll see, I'm planning on going there Tuesday again, if not,
that will be held to pay. And right, so then I walked from Central Park South to Avenue of the
Americas where the serious building is, which is on 48th, I think, 49th Street is the entrance.
And a hustle and a bustle there, man, they're getting ready for Howard Stern to show up, and
they're building a studio, and it's all boarded up inside, so you can't see what the new studio
is going to look like, and there's a lot of excitement and a lot of buzz. And it seems like
series are doing really good, you know, they've got Martha Stewart, they got NASCAR,
and I really, we do so much on serious, and it's such a freaking bummer that I can't hear it,
I can't hear the whole, you know, I can't just can't hear the stuff that we're doing, and that's a
pretty essential part of, even the source code, that listen to the source code after I record it,
I don't change anything, but I let it go out, but I just want to hear what it sounded like.
It may be a different impression, and I can prepare myself for the onslaught of email coming in
or responses or whatever. So I had a really, really good couple of hours met with the press people,
and they've got something pretty, pretty cool planned for the end of the month, and some things
are changing, and some things are going to be changing with the pod show on serious, and I think we're
going to get serious. So, that's just a tease in the coming weeks, I'll be telling you more about that,
but I'm very excited about what's going on over there, and have you seen that new device, by the way?
I think I brought the whole on a second, come with me for a moment. I think I brought it with me,
I got the new serious materials, the product guide for holiday 2005, and that includes all the
radios. This new thing they've got, that's pretty cool. It's the serious S50. Introduces the latest
in satellite radio entertainment combining live reception within the home car office with a
wearable player, and it is pretty small. One of those, you know, like those, you know, a laptop
that you're hanging on your belt, the XM-thus stuff, has up to 50 hours of content storage capability.
The attachable wearable player is small enough to use while you're working out traveling or just
hanging out. Now, here it is. So there's, here is, make your listening experience your own,
whether you want serious S50 to do it for you. You want to save your favorite
serious songs and shows, or you want to create your own playlists. Listen to three personalized
channels called my serious channels that are automatically created and continuously refresh
based upon your listening patterns. Save your favorite serious songs or shows with a single
press of the button, transfer favorite MP3s, and we know the media audio playlist from your computer.
So, you know, it seems to me like they've got something pretty interesting that there's some
technology that we could really just mess around with. No one has an actual device. We have lots of pictures
of it, but of course, I've said, get me one of those, damn it. I want to be in the United States until
the end of the month. So I think that there's some cool stuff ahead as it comes to that.
And of course, I celebrated my 41st birthday over the weekend on Saturday and I really realized
how much more as I get older, come on sit on my knee and let me tell you about this. I really
realized that you appreciated so much more when someone, you know, from the past particularly gives
you a call and says, hey, I was thinking of you happy birthday. That's really a gift all
by itself. It's just have someone thinking of you. And that's kind of what I, that was the epiphany
from my 41st birthday celebrated here in the United Kingdom. But I did get lots of stuff through email.
And one that I missed, but it was so, it's so beautiful. I want to play it for you even though it's
it's belated. Hello, Adam. It's me, Manj Weinstein, your favorite lesbian on the instruments.
And I heard you have a birthday coming up and you're going to be 41. Well, I'm 56 and you know what
that means. In 15 years, you get to eat my Fred join out. Well, meanwhile me and my queer
partners, your cute partners, some of the homosexuals podcasting, decided to get together and wish
you a happy birthday. So here it goes. A one and a two and a three.
Oh, he's cute for an older man. I let him do me in the bus.
What a major multi-track extravagance. And I thought I heard it like a speaking spell in there as
well. So it was a twinkle boy, John Own, from the online podcast, Cheryl, Mercowski and Juan de Wisdom,
Patrick from the Patrick and Noah from the Patrick and Noah show, Marshall Click from Gabriel Hood
radio, podcast, Steak and of course, Madge. Everybody at qpotter.org. Thank you very much, boys and girls.
Much appreciated. Hey, I'm going to be in Chicago. Don't most of, well, Madge lives in Chicago,
Madge. I'm coming to Chicago. I'm going on a date with you, baby. Email from Bob Robinson.
Hey, Adam, talk about interesting. I just got a letter in the mail from arbitron. Those are the
folks who do the ratings in the US, the radio ratings. They want me to participate in their
radio and he has an quotes here, the radio station survey. I'm going to say yes, but I'm going
to log my podcast listening right alongside the traditional radio. Spiking it. Love it.
Fucking the man. And I already know, I listened to either podcast or streaming internet radio
much more often than over the air stations. I'll keep you posted. I bet they don't even have a podcast
section yet. I'll make sure that we get that that we get that changed. My period starts. My rating
period starts on 922 2005. Cool, Bob. Let us know if there's a little checkmark box there for podcast
or MP3s or anything like that. Remember, I did the sound advertising experiment where I asked
you listeners to pick a spot right now, wherever you're, excuse me. That's not since sale. That's
the palm in New York onion rings. Can you smell it? Pick a spot right now. It's a sign or it's a
house. It's somewhere where you drive by frequently. And then I put a word in your head like
sent sale. And then every single time you drive by it, you're going to think of sent sale.
So Kevin Crossman from Fremont, California wrote in says he had a normally I listened to the
dating source code in the karma way to work. So you had the right idea with your subliminal
experiment. Unfortunately, I listened to that particular show in bed before going to sleep.
So when you asked us to focus on an object, all I saw was darkness. The experiment was not a
complete failure, though. That night I had a dream. That night I had a dream. I was walking through
an airport. I sat down to wait for my flight and decided to strike up a conversation with the
traveler next to me. His name, Adam Curry. And Kevin is from the Frat Pack, by the way, play
that promo earlier for you here on the show. And on Monday, we rolled out the very first job
cast. Mark said it really liked it, but was surprised when the guys that would be Ron and Brian
and Michael Butler asked candidates to send in a paper CV. How about a CV cast with a candidate
at the CV as show notes? But then uses 10 to 15 minutes to tell the company about themselves.
That would be a great way to really shorten the recruitment cycle. The thing I got from the job
cast was that these guys sound like people I would like to work for. So I guess it might work in
reverse so that they hear someone they would want to have work for them. I'd say with them,
very good idea Mark, I like that. And I'm actually considering if someone does a CV cast,
if we should play it on the daily source code, although I'm a little worried because if it's
someone really good, then you know, he or she could get captured away from us. So maybe not.
And during the week, I played a like a six or seven minute piece from Ron's
group from the Zip 71101 podcast. He was interviewing evacuees. I want to read a little bit
of his email. He said he was listening to my show. And I was talking about the instant relief
that we expect in America about television and how we're being exposed to be all fixed up and
done in 26 minutes without commercials or if not Oprah will come and save the day. So then
you played a promo by Chris Rockwell in it. He said, quote, these people are not getting the
help they need to survive. I'm sorry, says Ron. That's not the case. What Chris is seeing on TV is
only a small amount of the people who are just now getting help. Why will because some have been
hiding in their homes not wanting to leave. They simply thought the water would go down quickly
or because they wanted to protect what little they have left. One person told me he had plenty of
food and water, but was afraid to leave because of the bad element. That was the shooting at the
record rescuers in evacuees. I know this, uh, Ron goes on to say because I've spoken with many of
the evacuees of the Red Cross shelter here in Shreveport, Louisiana. Yesterday he spent four hours
just talking to Red Cross volunteers. Um, and I hope he's going to put that on his podcast. The zip
1101 podcast. Now he also spoke again to the girl Tammy. That was the piece that I played on the
source code and she had no idea for dad and mom were safe because they stayed behind. So yesterday
as Ron was leaving he spotted her and she told him the Red Cross and founder father and he was
working with FEMA and they got him to a place to live in Lafayette, Louisiana for the family as
well and he was going to pick up her and her twin brother today. And the whole email that Ron posted
in here is definitely worth reading a hands-on eyewitness report. A real eyewitness report.
And it's excellent to see, um, you know, to see podcasting, uh, bringing out a different message
than we can then we can actually even technically get from television. I've said they can't zoom
out far enough to really show the scope of what's going on. Sometimes you need to use imagination and
theater of the mind and other reference points. Excuse me, Rob Kosslo, you know him is a big hit on the
podsafe music network at music.podshow.com. Um, of course, Rob Song I do, um, has gotten him a lot of
attention and he says that he just posts another song into the podsafe music network, a long one.
He says this one he wrote for his wife for their wedding. It's called Bliss and, uh, all the
info, of course, is on his page and I put a link to that in the show notes. And, uh, he's so he played
that, uh, almost that six years ago. So, uh, let's listen to a little bit of podsafe music here,
Rob Kosslo, which you can find at the podsafe music network. It's, uh, it is quite long,
but it's kind of soothing.
You know, it's, uh, it's a miracle they ever really got married.
If you played for that long with their wedding, I want to say though, um, I think that song would really
work well if you cranked it up really, really loud, uh, in the car and you don't like 110 miles
an hour just, you know, and then slowing down and then speeding up and then it gets that nice burst
at the end, uh, Rob Kosslo Bliss on your daily subscription.
I suppose you think you know where you're going. Yeah, I'm arrogant enough to say that.
Hey Adam, hope you're trip to New York when okay. Yeah, I'll be there soon as well.
Saturday, right? But I got a few things to do here. First, uh, such as a hit test, but I'm really looking
forward to going to the big Apple. So, um, I really can't wait. So, the hit test, three intervals,
and three answers. And this is number one.
Oh, it sounds like the first couple of notes of Bonnie Tyler, uh, told the clips of the
heart number two.
That's not enough. I know even when I listen back to this show, I'm not going to know it.
Number three.
All right, think we're going to make it Christopher Cross.
You who? Oh, man. I think I got two out of three today. And times up and these are the answers.
Ah, a slow start to hit test number 57. Bonnie Tyler, totally clips of the heart.
Every now and then, I get a little bit tired of listening to the sound of my teeth at a
wrong. Every now and then, I get a little bit nervous that the best of all the years have gone
by wrong. Every now and then, I get a little bit terrified of them. I see them looking
up.
Bonnie Tyler, totally clips of the heart, is answer number one.
And this is answer number two from 86.
Can't we Simon? It's currently Simon. This is coming around again.
Oh, man, it's got a new album out too.
I would not have guessed that one yet.
Oh, nothing stays the same. Bonnie, if you're willing to play the game, it's coming around again.
So don't mind if we're all apart. It's more than we've made a broken heart broken heart.
Coming around again is answer number two.
And third and final answer for today's hit test.
Also sung from 1983, it's rich stuff across and it's all right.
What a great song.
And so number three, it's very plus the few of Christopher Cross and it's all right. I think we're gonna make it.
Okay, and this concludes hit test number 57.
Don't know when the next one will be. It's very possible. It will be from the planes in New York.
It should be nice. Maybe I'll do some some sightseeing stuff in New York as well.
Don't really know yet, but we surprised if you see some weird things in the next hit test or hit test podcast.
Okay, you know what to do with feedback.
So send it to hittestidgmail.com
And of course the website yompolet.com.
J-A-N-P-O-L-T dot com.
Thank you for listening until number 58 so until then bye-bye.
Thank you very much, young.
Cast plastered 38,000 feet cool. Can't wait to hear it.
Yompolet's hit test and if you hurt any of those songs when all mail.
Oh, I love that track. I don't know where the iTunes music store. I believe Yon is now putting the links into
yompolet.com so you can go over there and of course if you click on the links then
Yon will get a little bit of renumeration for his tireless tireless work that he doesn't hit test.
What was that episode number 57 already? Well let me just check.
Was it 57? Wow, yeah, unbelievable. Okay, so tomorrow the girls leave tomorrow evening and
it's you know it's gonna be a month we really don't see each other all that motion.
Miss him. Damn. Such as life.
That's it for your baby source code for today. September 8, 2005.
I appreciate you listening. Feedback is welcome. Please do not send me attachments with the MP3 file
Sunderling to it. Make sure you've got your ID three tags all set and don't name it feedback or promo dot MP3, okay?
Now if you want to send promo's in for the
pod show on serious for the pod finder or for the daily source code send it to
Submit at podshow.com. You can also send your podcast there
anything you want that you think
We should pay some attention to
Don't forget the pod sake music network at music.potshow.com. It's really rocking
Got a lot of cool students coming in every single day. I think we're gonna do a
a new music show and
pretty soon also a top 10 the top 10 pod plays
I'm now 10 minutes after five in the afternoon. I've got a couple of pod show calls coming up in
I don't know how or so of course the west coast is waking up. So I will be back here tomorrow
and maybe I'll get the Patricia Christina on on the show. Christina of course is now back at school.
It's really enjoying it and it's always fun to talk to Patricia. You get some wacky going on
DailySourceCode.com for the podcast feed or go to iTunes. You can download it for Windows
for Mac. It just search for a curry or for daily source code and one click and you're subscribed.
I'll see you tomorrow. Stay subscribed. If not, subscribe, damn it. Bye bye.
Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.