Delta's here at Charley 2, 4, 6.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Monday, September 26th in the year of our Lord 2,5, good morning everybody.
Once again another beautiful day in Northern California, nice and sunny.
I just had my test, this is the big test that I've been waiting for,
it's the insurance test.
People who know me, know that I'm fine with everything except for one,
mine of detail, that would be needles.
I would make such a horrible junkie tell you.
So anyway, Patty from the insurance company came over this morning,
right in early.
I wasn't about to eat anything or only drink water.
In the whole nine yards, it was kind of like a flight medical,
where you get the full 12 lead EKG and take you blood pressure three times.
I'm a very healthy baby boy, 190 pounds, six foot, four and a half.
And I did not think.
In fact, I didn't even feel the pain.
Actually, Christina's really, really sweet.
She knows that I'm bad.
I am when it comes to needles.
I know I'm admitting it to being an incredible pussy right now.
She called me up and left me a beautiful voice mail saying,
don't worry dad, just pretend that I'm there because usually I take her along a whole night.
But Patty who came up and did this was great.
I didn't feel the freaking thing was fantastic.
Three, two is a blood.
Excellent.
So, lots of cool stuff to play for you.
I decided not to go through the email and read emails instead.
I figured out that I'd play a lot of these audio feedback bits that I've been receiving.
So, we got a couple of pieces of feedback about bio diesel and podcasting internationally.
We've got pod save music.
Also, young bullets hit test.
We'll show up.
Hit test number 60 is back in the studio.
And art from mashuptown.com sent me over a wonderful mashup.
Just before it's about to get the show going.
So, I was able to spot it in because I didn't have one.
This is Fidelsky.
And you can find more info about it at mashuptown.com.
Feels like making La D'D'A.
Mashed up on the source code.
You'll be this started already.
We like somebody.
We don't close.
We don't want somebody weird.
Just someone that's on the line.
And when we're on the ball,
we're on the line.
But all the young keep me young.
And when we're on the line.
Just before it's about to get the show going.
The show's about to get the show going.
Now that's a way to start our two weeks isn't it?
And let's make it great week out of this.
Look at all the opportunities that lay ahead of you.
that lay ahead of you.
Isn't this just a beautiful time to be alive?
Feel like La Dida, Dida, Dida.
A little bit of, what does that feel like making love?
Who's that again?
Is that bad company?
Who's not it?
This is the Daily Source Code.
I've been talking a lot about bio diesel.
I'm really serious about this stuff now.
The end of the year, I get rid of the Audi A8
and I'm looking at a number of different cars.
I've received so many emails about which car to buy,
which diesel to buy, where to get diesel.
How to create bio diesel, just phenomenal bits of information.
Lots of that started showing up on the wiki,
the show notes wiki, which I'm so in love with the concept
of using a wiki for show notes.
So wiki is basically collaborative writing environment.
And so I put one up for the Thursday show.
I'm sorry, the Thursday Saturday show was really the first one
that was utilized.
I didn't put it up.
There's two guys who have a company that create wiki
and they set up a daily source code.info.
Got my attention there, I'll tell you that.
And it was working, people were posting in different bits
about the show that I had done Saturday night,
the Saturday night special, a daily source code
in lieu of a Friday show.
And pictures were showing up.
And I could just see all the different edits
and it was fantastic.
And then all of a sudden, Sunday, this thing disappears.
It's gone.
And I've got like 404, so I got an email from the guys
and they said that they're working on it.
I guess, I don't know if it got hacked or if someone
something seems like something horrible went wrong,
which of course may be the entire downside of wiki show notes
is that it is an open and collaborative writing environment.
Anyone can come in and do anything.
But it was doing great.
So I'm hoping that the show notes for today
will also be able to appear in wiki form.
If these guys get the wiki back up and running,
I'm sure they will eventually.
I don't know if they'll have the data from Saturday night show
but man, it was really, really working.
And then there's all kinds of questions
that I have about Google and how it indexes wikis.
I would presume seeing the wiki PDF shows up
in lots of Google searches that I do that it will index properly.
And then wouldn't it be nice?
This is really cool.
I saw that you can pick up an RSS feed
for all the new entries on the wiki, which
is very cool.
The question is, can we also add an enclosure
to that RSS feed?
If we could do that, well, then we
might have a whole bunch of things in one,
they'll be very, very convenient.
Hey, yeah, Adam, this has been from the WAT weekly podcast.
You've been talking about biodiesel a lot lately
on the daily source code.
And it just so happens that my podcast talks exclusively
about energy and alternatives of energy
and thrown in there is some biodiesel stuff as well.
And actually in my last show, I was talking about
how the biodiesel market is just going to explode
in a couple of years because the U.S. is moving
to ultra-low self or diesel fuel.
I'm telling you this stuff really is going to explode.
These engines, originally, as far as I understand,
the diesel engine was made to run on vegetable oil
and any other crap you could throw at it.
And somehow, we migrated into a more petrochemical version
of diesel, and there's all kinds of pros
when it comes to petroleum-based diesel
mainly performance, I guess, because it has
higher octanes and it'll give you more power.
Who needs power?
I need power.
I just need to go from point A to point B.
And I just really want to do this on biodiesel.
I'm on this total kick, and I'm seeing more and more people.
You know, the electric cars, they're great.
The ethanol vehicles, they're great,
but the concept of dirty old castaway vegetable oil
that you pick up from the chip shop
or from the hamburger joint down the road,
that's very appealing to me.
This time next year, so in September 2006,
ultra-low self or diesel fuel is basically
the equivalent of taking the lead at a gasoline,
which happened a long time ago.
So it's a long time coming for diesel fuel,
but what it also means is that you're going to have
to add a lubricant to the ultra-low self
or diesel fuel, otherwise your engine will be happy.
And guess what one of the best lubricant is
for ultra-low self or diesel?
Biodiesel, by any chance?
But, but biodiesel, so around one to two percent biodiesel,
probably make it into a lot of the diesel fuel
that you buy in the US next year,
and there's a lot of diesel fuel being sold in the US,
which means that sales of biodiesel,
at least in the US will probably go from around 50 million gallons
a year, that's what's sold now,
to around 370 million gallons of biodiesel a year,
probably within the next two years.
So that's huge growth, that's 640 percent growth.
So I calculated that for my last podcast,
and that's where I put my money, biodiesel.
And that's where Willie Nelson has put some of his money, too.
He sells his own biodiesel brands called BioWilly.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
The guy who wrote crazy,
Willie Nelson couldn't come with anything better
than BioWilly, that was the most creative we could get.
And then, although there just goes to show,
Willie's into it, so there's got to be something good.
When Willie Nelson is doing something like smoking
joints in the White House, then you got to think
he's onto something good.
So BioWilly, I wonder, can you get that anyway?
I'm probably doing in Texas.
In some parts of Texas, and he's also got location
in Southern California and South Carolina.
So anyway, I just thought that everybody
know what's going on in the biodiesel world,
check out my podcast, The What's Weekly Podcast,
which you can download by going to my website,
TheWat.com, that's THEWATT.com,
or we're also in the iTunes directory search
for The What's THEWATT all one word.
Thank you very much, he's been Kennedy.
Subscribe, dude, totally subscribe.
I'm so into this.
I think it's the Mad Max vibe of it
that appeals the most, where there's no more,
you know, the premise behind Mad Max,
there's no more petrol, no more petroleum, everyone's
it's almost like a water world as well.
You know, where that everything's alternative energy,
except for the guys who have fuel and they're basically
the pirates and they rule everything.
And I like the idea of just having grungy barrels of oil.
You know, no matter what happens, I can always grow more.
You know what's going to happen, though?
Here's the thing that's going to go wrong,
because these things, the biodiesel gets a little too,
isn't liquid enough, really during the winter.
It starts to gel up and so you have to either pre-heat
or you have to start your car on regular diesel.
And I can just envision, we're going to have this great car.
I think it's either going to be a Mercedes or Volkswagen,
both have diesels that will take biodiesel,
but I don't like Mercedes-Benz.
I don't like the way they drive.
They feel so tankish and heavy.
And so it'll probably be a VW.
They have some nice cars these days, by the way.
Was the Faiton or whatever?
That's a massive car.
And they also have a diesel version of that.
So you know what's going to happen,
and it's going to be one cold morning,
and Patricia's going to need the car.
Fuck, it's not going to start.
She's going to hate me for it.
Hello, I'm Jürgen Schlund,
and in my podcast, from the podcast Cafe,
I'd like to talk about the best music
from the podcast music portal.
The interesting information
about the artists, news,
about the project music,
the interesting sites,
and of course, one or the other message.
And that's all about VW,
podcastkaffee.de.
We'll see you next time.
Hi Adam, my name is Erno.
I'm a French guy living in San Francisco,
Barry, and I'm working for Apple Computer.
Maybe I'll see you when you come over.
I'll be the very wearing dude walking around on the campus
with a baguette and an iPod.
Anyway, I've been thinking of going
to a little brainwashing, sounds, done thing,
find a deeply flawed.
What if you go sensitive?
And I happen to be in Paris,
one of my favorite cities in the world,
stepping on fresh, steaming, duck shit, what then Adam?
He would ruin the San sail brand for me.
Every time I see pieces done, I think,
since there goes your brand plan
for brainwashing us, podcasting, listening,
lemons.
You may control what I stick into my ear,
but you don't control my environment yet, Adam.
Got it?
You happen to have a sailboat,
but just don't let me do it.
Hey, hey, you catch a bloke,
just let me do that.
Demonstrate this to you, concretely, Adam.
You gotta give some direction to your listeners
if you want this thing to work.
All right, people.
That goes for you too, Adam.
Look around you and find something,
somewhat repulsive, a disgusting.
I don't know, grease stain on your desk,
a cockroach and a kitchen.
I got some mold between the thousand, the shower,
your roommate threw up in the kitchen.
Good, good, good, look at that vomit.
Oh, nice.
Look at it intensely, even though it repelses you.
Ready?
Okay.
All right.
Call Robe.
There.
Anyway, love you, show.
Mine is a heartily amateurish podcast
in French.
Done from my home in Mendel Park,
Silicon Valley, California.
The website is SiliconValleyFrogs.com.
It addresses the French language audience.
It's about living in Silicon Valley, gadgets,
pop culture, all that.
Ready, they're from 70, fellow tour,
SiliconValleyFrogs.com.
So iTunes, say, digro-nood, don't have any.
All right, Adam.
Thanks for letting me make that shameless plug back to you
and get that cooking oil, car cooking.
You know what I mean?
Thanks, Adam.
Put.
Merci beaucoup.
I don't know.
We are bad and international.
Actually, I'm going to be looking for you,
Bury, Wearing Guy with a Baggett and an iPod.
We're actually going to Apple today.
We have a meeting.
And yes, I have all your comments under my arm.
Although I'm pretty sure they know they're very aware of them.
So looking forward to that.
It's going to be kind of interesting week.
We have a whole bunch of candidates coming in candidates.
We're looking, obviously, to hire people.
You've probably heard the job cast a couple weeks ago here on the daily source code.
And we have, I think, two applicants each day.
And these are for, you know, high-end engineers, system architects, rock stars.
Let's call it that.
And boy, we got a couple of them coming in.
Some of them even had sent in their CV as a CV cast on an MP3.
So I'm very excited about that.
That's, of course, one of the main reasons that we hear in Silicon Valley is, you know,
we got, had all the media stuff down.
But never did we see the perfect meld and mesh of media and technology with user created
media, by the way.
So that's the smartest users there are when I'm talking about Hollywood.
And it's always been that tech companies have set up shop in Hollywood and have tried
to integrate that way.
I think that, well, usually I found, whenever you do something exactly the opposite
wave of the way the status quo is and the way people are doing it, usually it's the right
way.
It turned out to be really successful with that.
I got some music here from the Podsafe music network.
This one is in the top hot place.
I know it played, I think Sally went down by Matthew Ebo.
But this is another one I like a lot.
It's called Drive Away.
We're in that maybe little escape, what we need.
We love and you work like a dog every morning.
The city's paying like the latte's staying on your dress, hitting the band before you
raked down and don't cost the down to leave this town, we don't the road because we got
against this mess, so let's drive away, let's celebrate Jesus all day, I'm done
going to stay in a way, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive away.
Let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive
away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive
away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive away, let's drive
You're saying in a way, let's drive away.
Sorry, but I seem fast, but I gotta get going.
It's gotta be more than the coffee shops in the bar.
Lady, maybe it's due. Lady, maybe it's just me.
Maybe you take my hand again, but I don't know if it's time to drive away.
It's so nice, so so nice.
Maybe that's all I got to say.
We'll drive away.
It's the magic.
Drive it into that morning sun.
You can check the show notes when they're up on the weekend notes.
We've got a couple other great songs there.
There's a new song that came in and it's unbelievable.
This is good too.
There's a new show, I think it debuts today and it's the Podsafe music review.
It's pieces of all of the Podsafe music shows that are playing Podsafe music.
I think it debuts today, check out accident hash to find out more.
This is your daily source code, Monday the 26th of September, almost finishing out the month,
which means I'm going to go back to see my girls looking forward to that very much.
I think Christina wants to start doing some pod casts.
She's kind of hinting at it, so I think what I'll do is I'll engineer it for.
Pretty much I think Michael Butler engineers and Martina's Emogirl talk pod cast, so that should be fun.
And she misses me too.
So then I was just saying called the teen pod casters network and it's growing.
I've always wondered what the, I think the typical age range that I'm hearing people on pod casts,
responding to pod casts, skews a little bit older, definitely 18 plus.
But now the teen pod casters network and I used to check it out teen pod casters network.com.
It's growing and there's a lot going on there.
Yeah, he's a promo from shooting.
Hey, shoot man, it's me.
Shoot me.
It's my power here.
What the heck, man?
I'm not kidding.
If we must add to the beat.
I have an accent that's going to show you.
Shoot me.
Hey, you've reached the shooting show.
Which can be found at shibisho.com.
The shibisho is a podcast done by a 14-year-old me, shibis.
Let me talk about life stuff that's happening and my views on it.
And I also go over stuff that's interesting, grand effects.
I debunk over legends and stuff like that.
Sometimes I get my friends on like nebio.
Say hi nebio.
Hey, what's up?
All right.
Hey, stop me.
And I'm gonna shoot my little brother.
Hello.
So, go over and check out the shibisho at shibisho.com.
If you want to get inside a teen's head.
The shibisho is a pro.
Member of the teen podcast is network which can be found at
teenpodcasters.com.
Hey, out of my name's Michael Smith.
And Barry Mandinger.
We run a podcast called In the Cube.
In the film cast.
News reviews and interviews from around the world.
And a whole lot more.
It's all to do with independent film.
And we've had a couple of people give us a bit of a plug.
Uh, in the cube is in the know.
So, an online blog with news reviews and interviews.
www.inthecube.com.au.
So, Michael, who was that mystery man?
Mr Hugo Weaving.
Not the Hugo Weaving?
Yes, agent Smith from the Matrix.
Wow.
Remember, we're in the cube.
The indie film cast at www.inthecube.com.au.
Check us out.
Thanks, mates.
In the cube.
I went to Australia.
A number of years ago.
I did a documentary.
Went from Sydney to Melbourne from Melbourne all the way across to Perth.
The western side of Australia.
On the way, visited Cooper PD, which is where the Opalmines are.
That was a very wild west type saloon ghost town kind of vibe there.
That was pretty creepy.
There's holes everywhere.
Everywhere.
There's a hole where someone has dug a mine.
There's a claim office.
There's signs everywhere saying,
If you're a tourist, do not take pictures and walk backwards.
Because you have a good chance of falling in a fricking hole.
We went to William's Creek.
The smallest town in Australia.
A tour is attraction.
You really have to...
It's quite a trek out.
We went with the mail truck.
It's also a commercial ride.
You pay a couple hundred bucks to go on the mail truck tour.
You go straight through the Outback.
We slept in the Outback.
I went to...
How that was horrible.
Went to Rooshooting, kangaroo shooting.
There's so many kangaroos.
There's like a hundred million kangaroos versus 40 million people.
So they have to quote harvest the kangaroos.
These suckers are like six feet tall.
They had some of them taller than that.
The god at night.
It's really sad when we document all this.
They shine a huge search light onto a pack of kangaroos.
And invariably a couple will just go like don't like deer caught in the headlights.
Because they have really small heads compared to their bodies.
I don't know how much thought process there is in there.
And then the guy puts a bullet right through his eyes.
And they're very careful and they always hit on the first go.
And they always kill him immediately.
Like that's how he sawless.
And the reason why is not out of humanity.
But the bullets cost like a buck up piece.
They really told me that.
And then adds really just disgusting.
Then they hang the male kangaroos.
They don't shoot female kangaroos if they certainly not if they have youngins.
But really they go after the males.
And then they time up by his testicles and winch him up.
And they'll have like 30 or 40 of these suckers on their truck at the end of the day.
And they get money for each one they harvest.
Anyway, so that was one part of the trip.
The fun part was the bachelor and spinster's ball.
You should Google that.
If you ever go to Australia, you have to go to a spinster's and bachelor's ball, I think it is.
And the kids basically get in their youths.
That's their utility vehicles.
Kind of like flatbed pick up trucks with tremendously tuned engines in the front.
They buck the youths.
They bark them by revving them up.
And then they have a really high pitch sound.
And the party usually lasts over the weekend.
And there's a huge tent.
And when you come into the tent, you park a youth around it.
That's where you have your swag.
That's what you sleep in.
It's kind of like here.
This really big sleeping outdoor type sleeping bag slash sleeping mat combination.
And you get a cup tied to your neck.
And that's your cup for the whole weekend.
And they just pour the, you pay once and everything is just the booze just keeps on flow.
So basically all you do is drink all weekend and have sex in your swag.
And then mess around the mud.
It's awesome.
I'm telling you, Australia, they work hard.
And they also play hard.
Yeah.
You really are this stuff your fog on you.
Have you been?
You could not be more wrong about this whole thing with international implications of podcasting.
Okay.
I think what Curtis talking about here is where I said that the, that podcast and was growing
at such an astronomical rate in the United States because the radio here has really been packaged
down to something so unexciting.
And in other countries, it just isn't growing as fast.
And some it is.
And I think it's probably he's going to make mention that I said that in the UK, we sure we have over
100 podcasters.
But it's not growing that fast because we do have some great radio being made in the United Kingdom.
Other parts of the world have more interesting radio than the United States.
Give me a part.
Have you ever listened to Japanese radio?
No.
Chinese radio?
I do know that the Chinese marketplace is now becoming the, I think all the radio guys are moving in there.
Murdoch is moving in there.
They're all getting terrestrial licenses.
So it'll be interesting to see because China is also a very unwired country for data transmission.
So the lines really could blur for them between what is a radio transmission of radio audio or what
is a radio transmission coming through a cell phone or some other wired device, wired wireless device.
So yeah, that's an interesting point.
Well, you know about to the Chinese is the second largest radio market in the world right now.
It's also the fastest growing MP3 market.
Yeah.
Isn't China just the biggest market period for anything?
No matter what you say, if you said fastest growing market for toothbrushes, China.
I think they would wait every single time.
Lemon radio, lame, French radio, lame.
Okay, yeah, I mean, you've got some good radio.
There's some quality there, but in terms of quality, what you've got here is a three BBC stations.
I think it's five additional public stations.
Yeah, but hold on a second.
You have to understand it's not just about the number of stations.
It's about what's going on there.
And I have to say the BBC are very, very free in what people can do there on the radio.
It just hasn't been this package.
Look, look at the consolidation that's going on for the past couple of years in radio with companies like clear
channel buying up, you know, up to close up to what they must have at least 2,000 radio stations.
That's the final breath for foreign industry is consolidation.
So it was time here.
That hasn't happened in many other countries.
Nationwide, I believe about a dozen molecular regional stations.
Come on, let's not variety.
You can't possibly look at the variety of podcasts programming available.
And really think that people outside of the United States don't want it.
They're being the world traveler you are.
I wouldn't thought you were a little more savvy to international implications of this business.
Go back and look at the data points.
All right.
I'll show pitch dot blog spot.com.
I don't know what's at the big picture.
There we go.
Thank you.
I'll definitely check that out.
His comment went on for another three to half minutes.
I decided to break it off at the Andy kind of winds up saying,
Hey, let's work together because he knows a lot about the foreign markets.
Totally.
Of course, the foreign markets are going to happen.
This is also something.
It's not just a replacement of something, something completely news.
Obviously, obviously it's going to grow.
And it's going to look, of course, we're hearing from Germany and from Australia.
And I actually saw a couple of French podcasts pop up by coincidence on any
Potter dot org the other day.
So stuff is definitely happening.
But it's just rampant here in the States.
That was a great podcast.
I was listening to over the weekend Pacific Coast Hellway.
This guy is good.
He does a podcast on his way to work every single morning.
And I guess he records pieces of it.
And he must do some post editing.
If not, he's got a great mobile set up.
And he's funny, man.
He is, in fact, that a very Howard Stern asked moment or experience.
I mean, I was, when I lived in New York and I was commuting into this or a new jersey
and commuting to the city every day, always would listen to Stern.
You know, even the best of repeats we'd listen to.
And sometimes you get sick of it and wouldn't listen to it for a week or two.
And then you'd invariably always come back.
And I was such a big fan.
I remember whenever Howard Stern would talk about me on the air,
he would always say, I was a dick.
And it hurt because I was such a fan of the show.
And so I'm listening to this Pacific Coast Hellway.
Andrew Grummit, developer for iPod 11, turned me on to it.
And he played one show, which was pretty funny.
And so then I subscribed to the podcast and I've been listening.
And all of a sudden I hear this guy say, Adam Curry, that big-haired fact.
I was like, it was the same thing.
He was like, oh man, I'm such a fan of the show.
And well, to be honest, he's an equal opportunity offender.
He definitely slams everybody.
I'm not for the week at heart.
I guess that podcast.
But I love it, though, because it is.
It's the guys a great writer.
And he's got bits on there.
Check it out at Pacific Coast Hellway.com.
Hi there, Daley source code listeners.
This is Frank Senate, host of the alternative source podcast.
Available at alternative source radio.com.
And through iTunes, if you search alternative source or Frank Senate.
And I've been paying a lot of attention to the mainstream media lately, because they can't stop congratulating themselves for finally sprouting a spine and confronting government officials over the mess they made of hurricane Katrina recovery efforts.
Well, guess what?
The nation's alternative press holds officials accountable week after week on issue after issue.
There's no need for backslapping.
They know it's their job.
And as a bonus, alternative weeklys are often far ahead of the curve on cultural trends.
For instance, on our show, you might hear about butt bleaching.
The fashion east is at LA Psycho Girlfriend, reverse shop lifting,
underwear dance parties, and even pot head softball stars.
In under five minutes a week, the alternative source surveys these hot news stories and cultural trends.
So you can hear where the mainstream media will be in six months.
If ever, and if they ever stop patting themselves on the back.
So check out the alternative source at alternative source radio.com
or an iTunes under Frank Senate or alternative source.
That's the source for the source.
The motortools went forth and cast their pods in the direction of all who would listen.
And casting their pods in this manner, they were henceforth known as pod castors.
I've got your podcast right here.
She's a girl and we've got a bottle.
A guy, a girl and a bottle is a weekly internet radio show for people to
interested in listening to an innovative wine podcast from a pair of novice wine reviewers.
Join us as we visit and review both the wineries and their wines in and around Silicon Valley.
You can find us in the podcast area of iTunes or on the web at www.gngb.com.
It reminds me Saturday night we did.
I should do that more often.
The Saturday night special, just a source code.
We play a little bit of music.
Man, I so wish we could play back catalog older songs from the 80s.
I really would love to do an 80 show.
Oh man, there's so much good music.
I've been messing around with my iTunes.
I don't have any other source of sound or video in the condo other than the power book.
So I have no TV and I have no radio.
We go to the sending me over a serious receiver though.
How was I going to say?
Oh yeah, I was thinking, we've talked to all these different record executives.
There are a few of them who are in the position to really have a legacy.
Here's what it would be.
If you're in the record business, I make sure you pull your lawyer in so we can listen to
because he'll also be legendary.
If you make a statement and allow podcasts, there's under certain parameters.
Let's say you can't create an end to end play list of songs.
It has to be spoken word in it.
If you let us play back catalog, hey, I'll pay extra for it.
Just put a little thing there and iTunes Steve Jobs.
He has a great way for you to start working with the record industry.
They want more money per track sold on iTunes.
They want more than 99 cents.
I know why you don't.
That's a part of your product.
And now they're talking about wanting some of the revenues.
Screw that.
Here's how we do it.
You put in iTunes.
Songs that the record companies chose and that they'll allow you to play on a podcast.
Let's say they can't play.
Well, maybe they'll just put a star next to everything.
A little green star, which means you can play it on your podcast.
And when you buy it, it costs five bucks.
It doesn't matter.
You tell me what it has to be.
That's as good as a CD almost.
But I guarantee you people buy tracks based upon what they hear in podcasts.
We've proven it over and over again.
And people are not seeing they're trying to filter me out and get,
listen to the compression I've got on the show.
No one in the right mind would try to steal a song for this one.
It's just like the radio treated that way.
Do that.
Then we'll all sign up for our ask cap and BMI fees.
And then we'll be done with it and you watch.
You can be legendary.
I'm not kidding you on this.
That will be your legacy is that you really kick started the digital music
Revolution by allowing license music to be planned podcasts.
Okay.
We'll just note the day in the time that I said this.
By the way, it's 10 after 11 here.
Fantastic.
With Adam Curry.
I suppose you think you know where it is.
I should do.
What do you hear?
The hit test.
Young ballads.
Hey, Adam.
This is artist number 60.
And it's the first one without the notebook.
So I'm in the studio with the professional mic and the sound processing as you can hear.
Sounds great.
But as always, three in throws and three answers.
And this is in throw number one.
Legendary Duran Duran.
Good for good girls on film.
Are they all going to be that easy, young?
And this is number two.
Okay.
I guess they're not all bad either.
And the final one is number three.
I know that one.
That's good.
Jackson's playing it on the bookie by the A.
And times up and they were pretty easy.
This is answer number one.
And hit test number 60.
It's Duran Duran.
This is Girls on Film.
Still walking and in hand across the bridge and midnight.
I've done it for life, especially now it's all right.
Now I'm alone.
So we'll stay long.
Duran Duran is answer number one.
Girls on film.
And this is answer number two.
It's Gwen McCray.
Oh, man.
The lion's here.
Hit the five.
He's burning.
Hit the barrel in hot.
We're going to love this.
Yeah.
You gotta give it all you got.
Oh, man.
And a lot of times searching for love.
And never know where it's coming from.
And as soon as we get it,
Just look at some arms.
You still could think that I worked on.
So I'm burning.
Keep the fire burning.
Keep the barrel in hot.
Oh.
You gotta know I don't know.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
You gotta give it all you got.
And answer number two in this hit us.
Keep the fire burning.
Gwen McCray.
And this is the third and final answer in today's hit us.
The Jackson Five.
That's just blame it on the book.
Baby's always missing.
And when is the old dark thing?
But I don't get no loveings.
And that's no love.
We spend the night in the disco.
And every can of disco.
From that night, I can't stop them.
Bye.
You're living such a shit.
Don't play more than moonlight.
Don't play no sunshine.
Don't take more than moonlight.
I don't play no good times.
Play more than book.
The Jackson Five.
and sing some number three in today's hit-test.
Blame it on the boogie!
As always, I selected some good music for the hit-test at least I think so, and that is the most important of course.
Okay, well this concludes hit-test number 60.
As I said earlier, from the studio here back home with the equipment and the professional mic.
See, they're everybody.
And recording a hit-test like this feels different.
But of course the production values are much higher, so it's a good thing I guess.
Okay, well, as always, feedback is welcome at hit-test at gmail.com.
And you can find info on my blog about the hit-test and the hit-test podcast.
It's yompulet.com, J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T dot com.
And I guess there will be a hit-test podcast soon as well.
There have been some developments you can read about them on the blog.
And if there's time and opportunity I will create a hit-test podcast soon.
Well, thank you for listening.
Hit-test 61 is end-making, so on the way.
So until then, bye-bye.
All right, yom, thank you very much.
Most excellent.
I keep the fire burn and that was great, man.
That was absolutely classic.
Oh, man, forgot all about that one.
Okay, one more pod save song before I get out of here.
You could tell I'm practicing trying to get up to my 49 minutes cycle, so we can, uh,
Simal podcast these shows on series.
See, see, Chapman sent me this one.
We said, if you want to know about emo, check these guys out.
Brunswick letters never send from the pod save music network.
If it's not in the snow, catch up it when it's a go.
If it was me, you know, they'll love secrets.
But not if I saw you.
But now I've got my time.
You're meeting for this night to be a home fair.
And I can't find the best to go on.
We're living now, you said.
Go, you little guy can't be your partner.
Let it all out.
We're living now, you said.
Go, you little guy can't be your partner.
I'm all the same, you tried to get up all night.
It's so sour, my time is.
Has nickrpled to my knees.
My mouth's jam stops getting a long, re-trip.
I'll shine a light that goes by name.
Now, my friends, it was again.
I miss you all the evening.
So, they're high.
And I can't find the best to go on.
We're living now, you were there.
Better than you said.
Go! You little guy can't be your partner.
We're living now, you said.
Go, you little boy can't be your partner.
We're living now, you're there.
Check on my knees all the way home if there's deaths.
There's still no sort of way down.
No time, wait down
This song's not waged up
This night is waged up
This dream's not waged up
This day's not waged up
The song's not waged up
Well come to the yellow line
To help you not have a sun day
Let us ever send
But don't feel it, I can't feel it
I'm back, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back
That day's not waged up
It's not waged up
There's no new days
But don't feel it, I can't feel it
For nothing
From the album told in photographs, Brownswick
Graphs, Brunswick, letters never sent from the pod safe music network. I kind of rocked in the whole
recent CC sent me that track is because he heard me talking about the podcast that Michael
Butler's daughter Martina did with my daughter Christina on the Martina's podcast Emo Girl
talk and I heard a whole bunch of band names that had never heard it before and of course I've
heard some Emo stuff but this is cool and this is a real movement going on here.
Okay, I'm out of here. If you want to hear more new podcasts to listen to and other
worthless bansher about crapping in your tank to make your diesel engine run come again tomorrow
find the podcast feed at dailysourcecode.com. Bye-bye everybody.