Delta Sierra Charlie 214 and good morning everybody. This is the daily source code
It's out. I'm curry coming to you from San Francisco. It is late
The time is a quarter to one. Actually, it's that's not even that late considering how late I've been
How late I've been up and working this living on all sides of the clock here
It's my last evening in San Francisco tomorrow. I return home
Back to Gilford back to Curry Cottage. Can't wait to see the girls again. And you know
I I decided for two reasons actually that I would just do another
Talking podcast and we'd roll out any music or anything. The main reason being that my microphone is almost out of juice
I had one extra reserve battery for the transmitter and
Didn't have one for the receiver now. I have a flashing red light which means it could be good for 30 minutes
It could be good for 15 minutes. I'm not quite sure. So if all of a sudden we just
Fizzle out. Well, then you'll know what happened and then you'll be hearing from me again on Wednesday when I'm back home
So I have lots of great things
Going on here lots of good news. I still can't give you
The full-dam announcement because what we just want announced things properly
But I can tell you that I got an apartment here in San Francisco because it's gonna be just like the oil rig
I think I talked to you about that
Yesterday on the San Francisco sound seeing tour of union square
I'll be it'll kind of you had to be like an oil rig, you know two three weeks off one week on and
What I'm gonna do is I'm gonna get a duplicate set up of gear at the apartment here in San Francisco
I guess we should give it a name
Well, let me why don't we call it the curry condo. There you go
24th floor towering over the streets of San Francisco. I've got the
The movie view if you will the motion picture view. It's going to be awesome
So I'm gonna have a duplicate set up with you know with a real mic with a mic stand right now
I'm just kind of holding the love microphone in front of my face
Which doesn't work too well
Particularly because I'm using my left hand and I think it was Madge Weinstein
We left a very appropriate comment on on the show notes the other day
She said DSC doesn't stand for Delta's share at Charlie or daily source code. It stands for daily shoulder complaint
so
Actually the shoulder is not what's bothering me. It's it's still my hand my fingers my
My index finger and my thumb of my left left hand
They just go numb
Whenever there's too much
Yeah, whenever I've just done too much to my hand. I guess hey, it's the left hand, okay? All right
So I only use that for flying actually had dinner
The other night with some friends
One of the who's a neurologist a doctor and I had mentioned anything and then one of our tablemates said well, you know
Adam's had this issue with his with his hand and he immediately grabbed my my hand and
Exert some pressure on my wrist and he said it's carpal tunnel syndrome. I said it way to make it
You know, I've had all these people telling me that because of the nerve in the back of my
You know my shoulder blades that it's pinching off a nerve and he said yeah
Well, that's kind of what carpal tunnel syndrome is. I said oh, well
That's nice. Well, what kind of do about it? He said well you have to come to the office and we'll do five minutes of tests in the morning
I wanted you might have to have a splint on it or something like whoa, hold on a second
So I guess when I get back to to the cottage
I'll make an appointment with with the doctor and I'll go see if it's a carpal tunnel syndrome
It's it's not horrible, but whenever I do something
Whenever I yeah, it just depends on what position I'm holding my my hand in
But again, I've gotten so many emails from some from mainly pilots who who have this this particular issue
Also people who write motor cross
So I guess you know as you get older you just mess around with your body enough and shit starts to break and fall apart
And that's exactly what's starting to happen to me
But that cannot ruin my mood my friends because we have so much cool stuff going on
We're hiring people out here in San Francisco. That's all part of the damage
We'll be making because we've got an office that that we're going to be opening up here. I am
Really really really pumped because the East Coast guys are coming in town
We are bringing the new media the real public radio
We're bringing it to town. We're going to have a lot of fun. I can tell you that and of course
Being out in San Francisco means we have access to all kinds of great talent
Who can really start to help us on the technological front
Particularly with with bandwidth man. I've learned so much already about bandwidth my god
Let me tell you
bandwidth is not free okay
When once you get above a certain level and of course there are all kinds of different hosting solutions
Who claim to give you unlimited bandwidth and you can get unlimited bandwidth to an extent
But if you've got a podcast for instance if you're featured on the pod finder in iTunes
We actually offer hosting and feed management to anyone that we that we profile on the pod finder
If you haven't heard the pod finder by the way
The new one is being released today episode number three
You know, we have just
Thousands tens of thousands of people who want to go check out the show and subscribe to it and
Well, either you'll run out of your bandwidth a lotment or your pipe will just be completely flooded. So it does you know
There is some cost to all of this and
What we're gonna have to do is we're gonna have to figure out how to move people more towards subscribing to these podcasts instead of trying to get them
You know in real time otherwise, you know, we're gonna run into some real real issues here some real problems
This by the way is exactly what killed the streaming business now podcasting of course is very different in that
It's a mobile concept right you take it with you and you don't just let you don't have to listen to it
Locked into your computer but people are so enthralled by what's going on
They're loving these podcasts so much that you know in fact some people actually will fill in the date for the source code like today is
DSC-2005-07-26 and they'll just keep hitting refresh until the show comes online
But that was never really the concept and you know the concept was even if you have just a little bitty pipe and you know
Almost no no real
Speed of bandwidth at all
It doesn't matter because the podcast and you subscribe to it once it's available
It starts sucking it in slowly or fast whatever it is and then when it's in it, you know your iPodor or your pod catch or your iTunes will say
Oh, I've got a new show and that's when you play it
So we're gonna have to work on some of this stuff. Otherwise, you know, I can't mention any any
Shows anymore if I mentioned a podcast that doesn't have proper hosting
They're off the air, you know, and so that's that's a fucking bummer and everybody has to be able to participate. So
Excuse me
So working on all kinds of different strategies for that now I know that bit torrent would be a great solution
But you know
There is I don't think any way that that iTunes is going to integrate bit torrent for quite a while
And not that the engineers or the business people wouldn't want to do it and in fact
We discussed bit torrent very openly at Apple during this past trip
The big problem of course is Hollywood because the minute you say peer to peer Hollywood freaks out
You know, oh well peer to peer equals theft. That's basically what what Hollywood thinks so
We're gonna have to come up with some really smart ways to route around that issue and if it's up to us at Pod Show
We're going to
Definitely make sure that the small independent podcaster
Has that bandwidth and you know you shouldn't have to you know you shouldn't have to pay an arm in a legboard if at all
You know and it does come down to money. This is not free stuff, you know
Especially now that we've got the listeners on the march the hundred million listener march. It's happening
They're on their way. They're coming
Excuse me. It's oh, hold on let me just have a sip of water
Something stuck there
Once again a nice five dollar bottle of Fiji natural artisan water
Bottled at the source
Let me see where was I what else did I want to talk about
Pod finder there you go. I want to talk about what's featured on the pod finder on the upcoming episode
I think I actually have my outline here
Let me just open it up for a second hold on
Where is it?
Pod finder episode three. Let me tell you who's featured
I've been using Omni outliner recently. I don't know if you've checked that out
And I'm only using it because it does opml import an export if it had its own proprietary format
Which it does and it didn't export anything else and I for sure would not be using it because I'm a big believer in the open formats
Come on start up here we go
Okay, so we feature episode number two of the Spike Lee shadow cast which was made available today through iTunes
You might want to check that out. It's pretty cool
Dave's eye pack
Tim Riley's city desk
Planet Japan podcast. That's a very cool one. I'll have to play that promo when I get back
The squad cast another great one
Played a clip of digital flotsome
Also the thunder cast one of my favorite morning coffee notes by the way
Dave whiner has now officially released his opml
application or opml editing tool and it's it's fantastic
You know it takes you like three seconds to kind of reset your brain and try and figure it out
But I think that particularly because this will be released in this is released as a free application and it's open source
At least I think parts of it are open source. I don't know all of it is open source
But you can download it and and use it for free
Check it out at the scripting.com
It's going to be a great tool for a
Helping to manage the iPod the indie potter.org directory. I should say we got to change the graphics on that. Let's just go
Man, let's call this thing indie potter.org. I think that makes so much sense
So you can contribute to that by creating and maintaining nodes in a distributed fashion
You can also create your show notes with it
Which oh man that light is flashing you in fast now if I cut out then I'll just talk to you guys tomorrow
Okay, oh, maybe I'll do some on the plane, but it'll be Wednesday before you hear from you again
So you can basically you
You create your show notes entry in an outliner and I guess in fact you could actually import
I should try that see if I can import
An omni outliner outline anyway
You create your show notes in it you could actually
Add your podcast enclosure so you're file you could add that right into the outline
And then it publishes that into html which of course
Begets your show notes at the same time. It's an opml file
So I mean I couldn't quite even wrap my own head around it, but now we're basically creating show notes in html and opml
Simultaneously that is a big deal and you can cut and paste these things right into any other outline
Including your outline
For instance for a directory node so you know when I get back I'm gonna really gonna play with it
Right now it's windows only and of course I have the craplet running fine on that
It should be available for the Mac very soon so that's something you will all want to check out
See what else in the pod finer in this upcoming episode no idle frets portland jazz gems
Past and present that's the colonial Williamsburg podcast the wine cast we featured
And also my buddy's
Kenster J and
Cindy C. The squipper with the Ken and Squip show so it's about a half hour this week and I think you'll
Enjoy it and you can find that with it's an enhanced podcast so if you roll it out in in iTunes
You actually have the artwork that that changes along with each podcast and if you click on
The artwork then it'll take you to a subscription's page so it's it's very cool stuff
All right, well, it's gonna be a pretty short podcast because I'm really I'm excited
But I am very tired and I've got an early breakfast tomorrow
Let's see
Journalist from newsweek is coming. I have to sign the paperwork for the apartment. I mean, oh my goodness the trials and tribulations
It's so horrible and I have print flip print the plenty out of that
I have plenty of promos and pod safe music that I want to play for you which I'm gonna do
Starting Wednesday when I get back now. I'll be back for about I think about a week and a half and then we go on vacation and
We're gonna go first. We've changed our plans just a little bit
So it's me Patricia Kristina. We're gonna go to New York for a spend a couple days in New York
Hope to Jersey where we use to live and meet some of the old neighbors and say hi and hang out
Have a barbecue of the weather permits, which I'm sure it will considering the heat wave
Then we're gonna fly to San Francisco and of course Patricia is very excited about the apartment as well
So it'll be some
Some buying of furniture and stuff and so we're gonna get the apartment all set up
We'll stay in a hotel first and maybe if we get the all the stuff we want in and on time
Then we'll actually stay at the apartment and of course I will contribute to to the furnishings of the apartment by
Getting the new audio set up done
That'll be my contribution
So we're gonna stay out here for about a week. Then we're gonna do something very cool. We're gonna fly back to Vegas and
On our way home that is so will be a couple days in Vegas now
Since it is it's gonna you know vacation and what is a vacation right? There's always gonna be some kind of work going on
And when we're out in San friend
I'm sure that we'll be meeting with some people and we'll be hanging out and and I will have you know
It's not I don't consider any of this work really, but I'd want to spend
You know some real good quality time with the with the girl
So what I'm contemplating is asking the pod squad and
Several of the pod show family members if they'd like to take over the hosting duties of the pod show on serious
So maybe we'll have Madge Weinstein do a day and we'll have dawn on Drew do another day
And maybe the same for the pod finder. I don't know I got to think about that, but
That's basically what we we used to do on the radio you know if you want a vacation when your colleagues would have to fill in and
Do an extra shift so
And you're seeing is how there's so much cross pollination so many people doing promos for each other
Which at all rather third man he's doing promos all over the place for everyone including the four podcast four one one
So that's the general idea there. I do want to do the daily source code
And I think that I can probably get away with just you know we'll do a travel source code
You know we'll we'll talk about our travels where you view the day
We'll do some sound seeing in New York we'll do some sound seeing in San Francisco
We'll do of course some sound seeing from Vegas and
This coming Monday
August 1st Patricia and I have been invited to a party a playboy party in London and
I was specifically asked if I was interested in doing a sound seeing tour. Well, I thought about it
And I went you know, yeah, of course are you crazy?
So it'll be a sanctioned sound seeing tour of the playboy UK party
Dude, do I have a great job or what?
All right 15 minutes. That's it the microphone light is flashing like
You know, it's like now it's every half a second so it's about to die on me
I'm gonna go hit the hay. I'm gonna check in with you again
Wednesday
It'll be let me see I arrive lemon 30 so it'll it'll probably be a morning show for you because I have the times
Don't work in my favor
So talk to you on Wednesday as I said. I'll have plenty of promos and pod safe music and
We'll be back to some you know, I'll be back in front of my own set up feeling all good and getting to go and in the mean time
Have yourself a great day
It's all good
That's what CC would say stay subscribe to everybody. I'll talk to you on Wednesday. Bye. Bye