It's your daily source code for Tuesday, May 10, 2005.
Well, come to La Paz, oh, we're happy you're here.
We recommend that you stick to your ear.
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear since
radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
Your DJ, are you, John McLean?
Your DJ has only just begun.
$16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Oh, man, it's so automatic, I don't have to do anything.
Hey, everybody, welcome to the source code.
What was that?
No, no, it's not supposed to work that way.
It's your daily source code coming to you from Curry Cottage and lovely Gilford.
Bit dreary today, actually not as lovely as it could be.
I'm sleepy too, man.
What you get when the wife's not home, going to bed, way too late.
It's currently about 10 minutes to three.
Oh, I have my exact 40 minutes to get the show done.
Maybe a little bit shorter until Christina comes home.
Oh, man.
Yeah, telling you, Patricia's on a little business slash personal trip.
So it's just me and the princess here at the home, which means I'm doing everything.
I'm doing the washing, the cleaning, cooking.
Which of course means we had pizza last, right?
And the weather's not nice, I've been indoors all day.
But I got some cool stuff for you.
Once again, everything's lined up in the new software.
Apologies for not making the screenshot available yesterday.
Actually, let me do a new screenshot as we speak.
There we go.
Hey, and it kept on playing it perfectly.
So I'll post that with today's show notes on dailysourcecode.com.
Yeah, it hasn't been very nice at all.
As I said, it doesn't matter too much because Patricia's off on a trip.
So it gives me a chance to catch up on podcasts that I've been, you know, just keeping
to listen to.
Do a lot of, actually, did some work with the Cast Blaster developer.
I'm going to talk about that a little bit later on the show.
And, you know, got some promos.
Lots of great promos, actually.
And keep them coming if you hadn't seen it already on the show notes for submissions
for the daily source code.
And also for the pod show on serious, which would be kicking off this coming Friday, Friday
the 13th, send it off to submit at podshow.com.
If you got a podsafe tune, you want to promote your band or your music or whatever.
Send it off to podsafe podshow.com.
And of course, always looking for the mashups.
And I got a cool one right here.
It's the princes of universe remix.
Here we are.
We're on to the kids.
We're the rips, and we're the old, old, old, old, old.
We're the old, old, old, old.
Because we're the old, old, old, old.
Here we are.
With the princes of the universe
We'll deal with the love
Fight for survival
We've got to be the rulers of your life
I am the model
I have been tracking blood of king
And I am the rival
And I can't leave my home
Take me to the future of the world
All to be changed
Rinses of the universe
Fight in a tree
Got you running my hand
I'm here for your love and I make my stand
We'll deal with the love
To be princes of the universe
I'm here for your love and I make my stand
I'm here for your love
People talk about you
People say you're a judge
We'll men and we'll go far
Trying to move in reach for the star
With my sword and I get a pass today
For the time
Yeah
I know that people talk about me
I hear it every day
But I can run around because I'm right
For the time
Yeah
All right, let's go, let's go
Come on
Yeah
This is my one of this my final
We're here for your love and I make my stand
We'll go far
Here we are
All to be changed
Rinses of the universe
I'm here for your love and I make my stand
We won't deal with the love
To be princes of the universe
I'm here for your love and you make my stand
I'm here for your love and I make my stand
We won't deal with the love and I make my stand
We'll mode to be princes of the universe
I'm here for your love and I make my stand
Hey, this is where there was a gash or a rock and we had a brand new podcast so they will through our website
gash or rock.net.
If you're a puzzle by punk or curious about country, we're a bander, we're a little bit country, punk or punk country
and I just have to say right now, this probably will be the next big musical way to be the new grunge
to be the new metal, to be the new hippie camp band.
Yeah, this is it.
It's a coming thing.
So please give us a listen.
We're a podcast.
It's sponsored by free web town and we appreciate your attention.
Rock all right now.
Do you find yourself up all night looking at inappropriate things on the internet?
I won't get up.
You need to pour on love.
You need to pour.
Do you find yourself repeatedly showing up late for work?
French fries.
Do not make themselves unique to be here.
One time, every day.
Luckily for you, there is an answer.
It's the drag me out of bed.
Wake up call from one wisdom and lucky bit radio.
Yeah, who is it?
Get that hell out of bed, you dirty horn.
That's right.
Wake up calls aren't just for hotel stays anymore.
Now YouTube can get a personalized wake up call from America's top podcasting
drag queen.
You don't get your fan ass out of bed right now, Mary.
I'm going to come over there and smack you silly.
It's one wisdom's drag me out of bed.
Wake up call coming soon.
Head over to luckymetsradio.com for more details.
If you wouldn't have sat around on the internet all night looking at the horn,
I wouldn't have to call your sorry ass now.
You've never had a drag queen get you up quite like this.
Check it out over at luckymetsradio.com.
Yeah, that's a promo.
There's some gentlemen.
That is a dance of damn promo.
I love that.
I was talking to a reporter today from a Dutch newspaper.
The actually is a well respected newspaper,
NSA, Humbles Blot.
Right.
Like, go pick up a copy right now.
Rather young journalist who called me,
but actually she was referred to me by Father Roderick from the Catholic Insider
Catholicinsider.com.
So that's why I said, okay, I'll do this.
Actually, I'd swore that that would be my last interview with a Dutch publication
because, well, usually, well, usually whenever you give an interview
anyway, they never get it right.
We've been through that.
That's a two-way street.
It's how I communicate, how it's being received.
That's not necessarily anybody's fault.
And now that we have podcasts and web blogs,
it's a lot easier.
Yeah, I usually point journalists to my web blogs.
I'd look here, look here.
You want to about this.
Check this page out.
Just copy it.
Copy paste.
It's much easier.
And then I give them one quote.
But she said, you know, let's do the daily source code.
I listened to half of the daily source code.
Well, thank you.
That's a true representative sample of what I'm doing here.
I said, yeah, I heard all kinds of promos for other podcasts.
I said, yeah, that's exactly what my show was about.
It's, you know, it's,
I'm, what's they call it?
The audio directory.
There you go.
If I potted out org and then there's the audio version.
And I really like the promos that you guys are putting together.
You're collecting these in any other manner.
Then have I played one, have I played it before?
Now they've got mega segue set up.
And as I said, you heard me make the screenshot.
So hopefully the screenshot will actually appear on the show notes today.
This is just so much coming in now.
So many different podcasts.
But particularly promos.
And they're getting really creative.
Really, really fun.
That I just can't keep track of everything that I've played.
So mega segue is really I'm enjoying it very much.
Because it keeps track of everything you played.
You can set a separation.
So basically I say, you know, if I played this yesterday,
don't play it again.
And it will, I saw it actually happened today.
It removed two promos that were automatically scheduled.
Pulled it out, replaced them with different ones from the same promo category.
So really all the work goes in, you know, in ID3 tag.
So I just want to talk about that very briefly.
If you're sending a promo or if you're sending a podsafe music or podcast.
Any MP3 you send to me or if you send a link to it.
Please let's let's all can we all just work together and really do a better job with the ID3 tags.
Because mega segue also outputs a log file.
And it takes the ID3 tags obviously.
And it actually creates an HTML page.
I haven't created a template yet for it.
So I probably won't be until next week when I have that up and running,
which I will do for the for the serious pod show.
So you can see what was played.
You know, the better we do with ID3 tags.
The better it's going to be for basically promoting stuff through your promo.
Because it also saves a heck of a lot of work of going back to.
Okay, so this came in through an email, let me search for it.
Ah, yes, this is the website.
Put it right into the ID3 tags.
You put it into the into the comment field or, you know, whatever.
I mean, it's, yeah, that maybe put it as a part of the album field.
You know, something like that.
So it will actually show up in the in the log file and in the show notes.
Let's see.
Let's see what I have here.
A couple of things I wanted to talk about today.
Oh, yeah, well, I was basically working most of the day before that interview on the cast
cast blaster beta.
Man, this is going to be so cool.
Lots of people are using the cast blaster now.
And actually I received a shockwave file, which I will also put up today.
It's, it's pretty big.
It's like 27 megs or something like that.
One of our beta testers who did a screen recording of, you know,
right after he installed cast blaster that he turned on the recording,
the screen recorder, and he's narrating his way through the entire experience of
basically finding out what this thing does.
And because, you know, does it come with a manual?
No.
Well, that would be silly, right?
So, you know, it's, you see the mouse moving around and he's narrating.
And it's really cool to see, and I also learned a lot, you know,
to see how someone interacts with a new piece of software.
And learned a lot from it.
And I was working with Mike, lead development on the cast blaster.
And we're doing all kinds of stuff.
Now, the next version, of course, will automatically create your podcast.
And, you know, does all the, everything for you.
You don't have to do anything.
Just, you know, just like you see now.
And you'll probably see that shockwave movie.
Again, check, oh, sorry about that.
The show notes for today's podcast.
What was I saying?
Oh, yeah, you, you basically hit save.
It'll save a copy on your machine.
And it'll take care of all of the rest, all of it.
Okay.
Let me see.
Haven't talked to my mom.
After her, after her marijuana experience,
which we did talk about yesterday with Dr. Joel,
who's from the arthritis news and views.
But something else did come in today,
which showed up in the promo bin.
Another doctor doing a podcast.
Hi, Adam.
This is Dr. Alan Rubin.
I wanted to tell you about my new Dr. Rubin's health cast.
The purpose of this podcast is to help you and your listeners live a long quality life.
You can find my new podcast at DrRubin.com.
That's drrubiand.com.
I hope you enjoy listening to it,
and that it adds years to your life.
I hope you enjoy listening to it, and that it adds years to your life.
Stay tuned for the UCF Digital Media podcast.
Coming the week of May 23rd, 2005, summer semester.
Topics will include news and announcements, interviews in the industry,
plus a whole lot more, including some class lectures.
Check the website for updates, dm.ucf.edu slash till they podcast.
So last night, as I was listening through all the podcasts I'm in saving up,
I came across a beautiful podcast.
And I'm not sure if I can actually play something from it,
although there's probably in the public domain by now or close to it.
It's the old-time radio vault, and this is, it's at otr.libson.org.
Libson is l, I'm sorry.
Lima, India, Bravo, Shira, Yankee, November.org.
And what this podcast is, is it's old-time radio shows.
And the one that I listened to last night, actually as I was going to bed,
the crapplet, that's the tablet, laptop that I have, took it with me to the bedroom.
And just listen to this, it was the whistle I think is what it was.
It was a show from 1945.
And it was great writing, fantastic narration, good scary effects, you know,
like in your music that just kind of brings into the mood.
Ooh, this is suspense here.
Excuse me.
Yeah, yeah, had a sense out before I started the show.
And then there's a fantastic acting, and it's about 40 minutes in length.
And I subscribed to the feed immediately and I'm really looking forward to more of those.
So I think we can learn so much about what can be done with audio in this thing we call podcasting,
whether it's radio or whatever it is.
It's, it's, it's, it's fooling around having a good time with audio.
Do I hear, what is that sound?
Yeah, I see other, the other Mac, the fan is going off.
Nice surprise this morning when I woke up.
Easy net crapped out again.
God, I hate that.
It's not actually easy nets fault per se.
But that's the big mega pipe that I have coming into the cottage.
The four mega bit line.
So it runs through a BT British Telecom least line.
And these fuckers disconnected every single time.
You see, is it actually just reconnected again?
And it's like, you know, I don't know what's going on.
Maybe, I think what's happening is, you know, they're so not used to this type of
connection because it's called local loop unbundled, which means British telecom,
who is the phone company, essentially doesn't provide anything over that line.
It's just a copper wire going from A to B.
And they probably there's something like engineer going like, oh, what's the slow,
both?
And it just all pulled out of the socket.
It disconnects it again, you know, it's driving me fucking crazy.
And of course, I get pissed off at easy net and they can't help it.
And they're not really, you know, this is an expensive line.
This costs like, you know, I was like, was it four, four, five hundred dollars a month?
You know, it's a, it's a, it's a real line this company in here.
And it's a, and I said, look, I've got a mission critical business running over this line.
Gosh, darn it.
I got to be uploading the, the pod show to the serious FTP server.
And actually, we'll be, I think I mentioned this yesterday.
We'll actually be releasing at least one hour of kind of a test run of the pod show.
So you can get an idea of what it's going to be.
But I think you can probably already tell now that the initial, you know,
wave of comments as pass is that, you know, I'm not going to sit there for four hours a day in talk.
Shit.
That's not what I'm up to.
This is about promoting podcasting.
And I think that as you see, every single new car come off the assembly line in the United States,
which will have CD AM FM and SAT.
That's basically their satellite receiver.
There may be a lot of satellite radio listeners who may not have an MP3 player or may have one,
and may not be in the pod casting just yet.
I mean, still a heck of a lot of people who don't know what pod casting is.
You know, so the study says six million listeners.
Last time I counted this like, was it 350 million Americans?
Something like that.
Pod save music now on the daily source code.
This is instrumental to the, it'll be a change.
It's, uh, bicem particle.
It's titled Resolve.
It's like you sit back, close your eyes.
Imagine a white sandy beach.
You're on the chair.
Lay back, cocktail in your hand.
Some are breathe, floating by.
Like waving your hair.
You're on the chair.
podcast podcast podcast podcast
this is my call it mdc 2005 and I'm curry leaves in podcasting and so to
we join us at www.mdc2005.com, whack, podcast. Check out the people who build
the systems that make podcasting possible. At the mobile embedded developer's conference
2005 recorded live now through make 12th 2005 the Mandalay Bay Resort in Las Vegas
join us online at mdc2005.com slash podcast. Check out the Rumpus Room on safe
tracks, discussion of things social, political and cultural and the weekly Hornby Top 5
find the feed at austereb.com, OST, ERBY, or look for it on ipodder.org.
Right on, ipodder.org, submit your podcast. I was going to say something I was thinking
about submissions for, was it promos? I can't remember what it was. Interesting, though,
mobile and bedded device, mobile and bedded developers conference. There you go.
Man, it's good to see that there's podcasters there and you should check it out.
It's actually pretty interesting. They're recording sessions and interviews,
no kinds of stuff there and big shout out to the developers. If we can get some ipodder
like functionality in cell phones and MP3 players, that would be pretty cool. It's just a thought.
Hey, I'll promote it if you send me some specs on something you're doing. I'd love that.
All right, that's more or less it for today. As I said earlier, pretty busy week. We're
still working hard on getting the first pod shows ready, doing a test run about to call in.
It's funny. It's all these radio guys who work over at serious who are responsible for
a lot of the technology and there's big boom and voices everybody.
So I want to call was it Jeremy Savage. I think he used to work at a Philadelphia radio
station. So he's now responsible for receiving files through FTP and then making sure they get
up to the side lights. A lot of technology involved and we want to make this stuff sound
that's good as possible. If you take MP3s and you re-record them and compress them sometimes,
well, sometimes it's just like crap. So working on a lot of that and I'm looking forward to
the big launch on Friday, Friday the 13th pod show on serious. Tonight, though, something
even more spectacular, I wish I could do a sound seeing tour of this, but I know she'll never let
me. I will ask. I really will ask Christina, but I'm pretty confident she won't.
Since Patricia's out of town, I said, you know, why don't we go out to dinner tonight? You know,
you can go over, you want you to choose. Of course, you know, what's the choice? It's like,
TGI Friday is okay. But why don't you invite Benji? That would be her boyfriend who I haven't
met yet. And so she called me from school earlier and she said, well, can Ellie come with us?
Yeah, of course, Ellie can come with us. Tell her to meet us to meet us there and she said,
can Benji come to? And I said, oh, yeah. So I wish I could do a sound seeing tour of that dinner.
I'll just have to store it away in one of the fun memories. So I will report back on that tomorrow,
the first meeting with him, the other man in my daughter's life. God.
Hope you enjoyed the show for today, as always, send your comments to Adamacurie.com.
And if you want your pod safe music, your mashups, or your promo is played on a daily source code,
send it to submit at podshow.com, podsafe at podshow.com, or mashup at podshow.com.
And you can also send your podcasts or I'd rather you send a link to your favorite podcast that
you'd like to play it on the podshow. So you've got four hours to fill five days a week.
As always, daily source code.com is the place to pick up the podcast feed, subscribe
and your iPod or you can click on the link directly for each show. It's where you have the latest
show and the archives. And I'll be back tomorrow, same time, same dreary weather, unfortunately.
Looking forward to the weekend, doing some flying and with a wink of matter, weather permitting, of course.
Take care, everybody. I'll see you tomorrow on the source code. Bye, bye.