Adam Curry, web pioneer of Gumpshite, you decide.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky ingredients in it.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm guessing it's Adam Curry.
And it's the daily source code for July 8, 2005.
I'm living for a little bit.
I didn't expect to hang you so early in the program.
I'm just rebooted as well.
Everybody how you doing is the Friday edition of your daily source code.
Coming to you from Curry Cottage and Gilford, the United Kingdom.
Up 30-40 minutes of meaningless nonsense.
I do have a lot to talk about today.
In fact, I wrote down a list so I wouldn't get confused.
Also, I reached into the old firewire drive and pulled out an old pod save tune
that I hadn't played in a while, but just listening to the stuff.
Have a piece of audio from when I was 16 years old.
One of my first radio shows.
We talked about it so much on the show I figured.
And I'll actually tell you where you can subscribe to a feed of my old radio shows,
which is frightening at least.
So it is July 8, it is one day after the multiple terrorist attacks in London.
And I am so incredibly impressed by the Brits.
Man, the word I guess everyone using is vigilance.
Very vigilance.
Which means they are aware, they are paying attention,
but they are also getting about with their business.
Just getting on and we will not be knocked down.
And just very wonderful to see.
I'll talk a little bit more about that on today's show.
Also, this is a mashup.
It is a little wacky.
And you have to kind of get used to it at first,
but I think it is 40 intros mixed into one.
It is by Osmiso.
It is called intros inspection.
See if you can count all the intros and recognize every single one of them.
I love the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of
the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound
of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound on the sound of the sound of the sound an on the sound of the sound on the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound of the sound passing through the sound of the sound of the sound isows a sound of the sound of the
She must be great, you're great, you're great, you're great.
She must be great, you're great, you're great, you're great, you're great.
She must be great, you're great, you're great, you're great, you're great, you're great, you're great, you're great.
Come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man
come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come
man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, come on man, are you the boring one here Muronga is horror Governor about what happened in
There's no one's afraid, I was bad enough to love you
I'll feel you in every single day
The pain is not right in the face
This is the end.
I've told you it was kind of wacky, kind of weird.
I liked it though.
It was probably the only mashup I've ever played on the source code that actually fits into
some kind of fair use with the short little segments.
Very cool.
Very different.
That's for sure.
And the rhythm kind of changed along the way, but it was nice.
I actually reminded me of some of the work Patricia's done in the past.
I should play one of those, one of her medlies.
She's done a lot of cool ones.
Okay.
A little bit of complaining of first upfront.
I really messed up my shoulder.
And since I've been complaining to Patricia, I was complaining to you a little bit.
It's stupid, but somehow I've managed to aggravate a tendon in my shoulder.
And it's actually pinching off nerves that run down to my arm and into my fingers.
And so I'm actually in a sling and I'm kind of part of part of the part-way in the sling today
to be able to man the buttons to hear my other Mac go in the background there.
And it's on overdrive.
It's nice the day.
It's about 23, 24 degrees centigrade.
It's been good.
And of course what still dominates the news is the terrorist attacks yesterday in London.
And people were asked if you didn't have to drive into London, please don't.
If you could stay at home, please stay at home.
Now we had a trip planned for the city tomorrow Saturday.
And we wanted to go see the crown jewels at the tower and want to walk around, want to go on the London Eye.
And so what we're going to do is we're going to wait.
And if the word is, you know, please stay home.
Then we'll stay home.
If the word is open for business, we're definitely going.
And really, that's the general vibe here is, you know, this was a cowardly attack.
And we're not going to let it bring us down.
We're going to try it in the forties with the Blitz Creek.
They went through it in the 80s and the 90s with the IRA.
And, you know, it's tough, tough cookies here.
Let me tell you, New York, a former New York mayor, Rudy Giuliani was in London.
I guess by coincidence, maybe for the G8 that he was in the neighborhood.
And he said that the way the Londoner's responded was very admirable.
And I believe that completely, it's just amazing how,
how the press is taking this.
And also, something of nowhere to be.
I think the BBC does not, I'm sure they have really horrible footage.
But they just don't show it.
They do have doctors on talking about, you know, all the horrible things that happened to people,
victims of a bomb blast literally talking about dismemberment.
But they don't show it.
And that, I think, deafening.
And they also, they don't, they haven't been overhyping this the way.
The, um, that has probably been done in the States to haven't seen any of the footage,
but some people have told me that already the graphics are swirling.
And, you know, the war on terror took them to the drums come in.
And this was handled very professionally like, like any,
a humongous news event.
But with the, with a certain amount of dignity in class that is definitely to be commended.
A little disappointing, I have to say, is, um,
I think that lots of people have, um,
phone cams, because they were showing a lot of that footage on, uh, on TV on the BBC,
Sky News, ITV, they were showing, uh, video footage that were showing camera pictures.
But I just didn't see a heck of a lot show up on web logs.
It seems like there's some disconnect between these mobile phones.
And, uh, and, uh, however, you know, wherever the pictures go,
I know that people, uh, keep them on the phone a lot and trade them out through Bluetooth and,
and other means and picture messaging is pretty big here in the UK.
But it seems like they're still disconnect with getting them onto the web,
but it seems like there's a lot of links in some form structured like a web log where we can really find it.
So stuff to work on, uh, as we continue to take back the media into our own hands.
Oh, yes. And, oh, yeah, this was amazing.
Um, I couldn't believe it, although I did see a report, um, on the BBC News website,
which I'll put a link to it in the, in the show notes for today's podcast,
that apparently some hotels doubled the price of a room, uh, Thursday night last night.
Which is called price gouging. In the States, if you do that, if you're a price gouging,
man, you get, you get tired and feathered and driven out of town.
I mean, that is just, you know, unacceptable in, in US culture.
And I can't believe that, that hotels would do that.
Now, I'll, I'll say upfront that this was the BBC reporting apparently on, um,
last minute.com, uh, who had warned its members that hotel prices were doubling.
Um, but there's not a mention of a single hotel, uh, which, you know,
and then I always got to wonder, okay, how come, you know, you, you don't just tell us which hotels
were doing that so that we could, you know, take a consumer action.
Um, I can only assume because it's unconfirmed.
And, uh, the same goes for the al Qaeda group that has claimed responsibility.
I think it's secrets of the underground al Qaeda or something like that.
And, you know, apparently there's this website that had, um,
a statement on it claiming, uh, the terrorist bombings.
But they never linked to it from any of these stories.
I mean, what is that all about?
And then I go to Google and I type in the exact name of that group.
And, you know, there's no website that pops up, you know, that, that is connected to that.
So, like, uh, some of that stuff, uh, you just, you just got a wonder.
That's all.
So anyway, I'm sure that, uh, we'll get to the bottom of this.
And, uh, you know, the, uh, the United Kingdom and London in particular is so wired.
There's so many, what they call CCTV cameras.
So close caption, I guess.
Or, yeah, close caption.
How does it make sense?
Close circuit.
Sorry, close circuit televisions.
Stores have them.
Every street corner has them.
So I think they can probably follow, for instance, for the two,
it'll be a little more difficult, I'm afraid.
But for the, um, for the bus that was blowing up,
they can probably follow the entire route and see who got on and, uh,
and what they were carrying and, you know, it's, uh, and it's pretty high quality stuff.
And they use it all the time and they really do.
It is very, very effective.
So, let's get them.
Let's hope we can get them.
Okay.
Daily source code.
What are we at now?
We're at, uh, 16 minutes.
Okay, we're right on track.
Um, let me see.
I do have some promo's lined up for you.
Let's get to those.
Hot chill.
Content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
Skeptocality.com presents real skeptical thinkers.
Seals.
Skeptical thinkers.
Today we salute you the independent podcast creator.
When you believe everyone else is selling out, joining Pod Show, signing up for
ODO and submitting to iTunes, you are standing firm.
Quietly hoping for listeners and losing sleep.
It really makes no matter whether your show is just you and a cheap microphone,
chatting aimlessly about your day or you and your wife discussing each other's private parts
or just to show about new music.
I love the positive news.
Without you, the rest of us podcasters would lose our perspective and believe that pod casting
is losing ground to corporate greed.
Apple iTunes or the cult of the pod father.
So thank you, Mr. Independent Podcast creator.
Without you, Podcast Pickle, Idiot Vox, Podcast Ellie and all other podcasters
directories on the internet would just be, well, full of popular podcasters.
And for that, many of us can actually go on with our lives and know that you are out there
keeping the number of podcasters inflated for the media.
A message from Skepticality.
Visit us at www.Skepticality.com.
Truth in Podcasting.
I love those guys.
That's great.
Skepticality.com with a K.
Not the calm of the Skepticality.
Truth in Podcast.
Watch out.
You've been assimilated into the cult of the pod father.
By the way, there was a mention of Podcast Ellie in there.
Let me tell you something cool about Podcast Ellie.
I've been receiving a lot of email, a lot about iTunes and about the feeds that they use
about being listed in the directory.
First of all, the directory, they're doing that themselves.
They populated it with the iPod.org directory.
It's tough.
It's tough doing a directory.
And so I'm trying to see if we can get that a little bit more one-on-one because we have all
these volunteers that I potted.org who are essentially maintaining all these nodes.
Marcus, by the way, has now installed the new servers.
Hopefully we'll be able to get a more stable iPod.org for you.
It's just been so overloaded with requests.
Let's see where it was.
It's a lot easier to maintain it that way through a distributed way.
Because that's what you need when you want.
We need to do a big directory.
That makes a lot of sense.
And then let's put an OPML output of the iTunes directory somewhere on the back end.
So that can be used for yet more directories.
It makes a total sense.
So working on that.
But a lot of people are want to have an iTunes compatible feed.
And if you go to Podcast Ellie and you're registered there, you have your podcast registered
but just thought every single one of them is, then you automatically get an iTunes feed,
which you can submit into iTunes if you're not listed already.
And right now it's just a podcast Ellie slash and some kind of URL.
What we're working on is the ability for you to map a domain name to that feed.
So you could actually have it be whatever.yourpodcast.com or RSS.yourpodcast.com,
something like that.
And then you would be able to, if you wanted to, you could move away, which, you know,
basically mitigates, that's the right word mitigates lock in.
So it just takes, get it to get rid of it.
So we're working on that.
We're just working as fast as we can.
Basically.
So that is something that's really easy.
If you want to have an iTunes compatible feed podcast.
Sally provides them.
Just make sure you're listed in their database.
Something I wanted to say, I wanted to ask if there were any comedians who are out there
who are interested in doing stuff with audio and with podcasting if, you know,
if you're funny.
And I'm thinking maybe Ron and I on my next trip out west will go to a comedy club
and we'll approach some of the comedians that, you know, if they're any good, hopefully.
But if you, if you, or you know someone who's comedian,
send me an MP3 with some of your stuff, we've got some ideas that might be very cool
if you're interested in doing some stuff.
And I get a lot of comments from, well, podcast Paul has mentioned it to me before.
And he feels that the source code definitely doesn't pay enough attention to podcasts from the UK.
So I was scouting around today looking actually for, you know, any type of podcast from yesterday
if anything was was up and about and I hadn't found any.
But I did find something very interesting from James Gardner,
but the person who creates the, I think it's the wake up internet podcast.
And I wanted to share just a little bit of that podcast with you.
Nice little sound imaging.
There you go.
Adam Curry, web pioneer.
Oh, don't shout.
You decide.
Hold on.
Hey, baby.
What's that?
Oh, thank you.
William Curry, Sam.
Yeah.
Nice.
I think that I can't eat.
Oh, look at what.
I want to give my right arm to you.
Well, you can add my left ones.
Fucked up enough.
All right.
Thanks, baby.
Okay.
I should actually restart that.
Hold on a second because I was so funny.
Hey, listen to what he calls me.
Wake up internet.lux.com.
Adam Curry, web pioneer.
Oh, gobsite.
Okay, gobsite.
I looked it up.
A person regarded as mean or contemptible.
A gobsite.
You decide.
Like millions of other iTunes users who upgraded to version 4.9 for its integrated podcast features.
I rediscovered Adam Curry this week.
I see rediscovered because I'd become aware of him where back in the middle of last year
when the BBC first brought the concept of podcasting to my attention.
Having just listened to him for half an hour on the topics of ranging from podcasting
to him getting his pilot's license and his never minded ill informed opinions on the live it
concert.
I'm firmly of the opinion he is irrelevant and will remain so until he stops podcasting about podcasting
and how its very future depends on him and starts actually telling us something worth knowing.
The pioneer of podcasting he may come to be recognized as.
Even lorded over us as in the future.
He's simply not deserved in the light of the web nostalgia for what was hit last week.
He seems to have the whole of the west coast of America convinced is actually important, even viral.
So I hear by predict within the next year to a year and a half he'll be as relevant to podcasting
as Bill Gates is to open source software development.
This guy's great.
Okay, I have some comments about this but I wait until the end.
This is good.
The analogy being that while it was windows and Microsoft which dragged the price of the humble
scene down to realistic levels in the mid to late 1990s, it was this very increase in availability
which made the impons for an alternative to the windows operating system all the more pressing.
Similarly, Adam Curry inspires the DJ or in Osol to sit in a dark and room when a bright sunny day
talking to ourselves and pretending like a bunch of seven year olds playing the radio DJ game.
But someone is actually listening and if they are listening they actually care what we're talking about.
Okay, now this is the part where you're going off track.
So I'm going to let you finish up your statement here but you're wrong about a couple things.
Not because it's important or vital that podcasting succeeds and our involvement is key to it,
but because the net nerd in Osol feeds on failing like we understand new possibilities.
The possibilities thrown up by the latest trend in information delivery systems.
Just as everybody once led claim to having the most popular channel on down that,
who only days after founding it realized it's sucked to use the command prompt interface.
So all the majority of startup podcasters will drift back into obscurity.
Just as everyone who ever shared a file on Napster spend those nail biting weeks,
waiting for Lars Ulrich to come knocking on their door, demanding his royalty check.
So all will the podcasts about how cool it is to be young, white, middle-class student of computers,
in the bare area, realize the banality of their life and move on to the next big thing that further serves
to reinforce their faith in all its narrow and thoughtless.
Okay, all right James, so here's, you know, and I hear this a lot,
or people say, well, you know, it's just like web logs and it's all crap.
Well, first of all, it's not.
But there's a distinct difference here between what happened with web logs and what happened with podcasting.
What happened with web logs, it wasn't an inherent desire to publish.
People wanted to have a voice to have a way to get their message out.
And podcasting, it was the reverse.
People are dissatisfied with what they were hearing and they were demanding to hear something different.
It's not like with publishing of text and pictures and print and magazines where the supply is just endless.
There was a very limited scope of receptions to be made.
There's limited the number of channels, even though it seems like there's a lot,
but also the centralized infrastructure does not allow for all these channels to be of, you know,
to have original programming, first run programming,
which is why reality television has, has caught on so, so big because it's very efficient to make.
That's what television producers and television broadcasters love about it.
And people watch it.
They, I don't know, I didn't want to say they like it, but they do watch it.
So it's a listener demand driven medium podcasting is.
And it's, you know, not that we're all looking for the next top 40 radio station or show.
We're looking for something fresh, something new, and we're rediscovering all this.
The web tried to go from text and pictures to video.
And it kind of bypassed audio.
Yeah, we had a little touching go there because audio was music.
No, audio is so much more stuff that we, oh man, we have forgotten more than we have to learn.
I'm telling you.
So we're just going to slowly get back into it.
And it's going to be very, very cool.
Oh, let me plug something here.
If you're interested in making a podcast, go to castblaster.com.
That's what we have.
The beta version of our podcast creation software is there.
It's windows only at this point in time.
Lots of people asking for a Mac version.
It always takes longer because the focus is on the window stuff right now.
But, you know, we've talked about this before.
I'm a Mac guy, so I'd love to have it on a Mac.
So that, you know, that is definite directive.
I think you can create a 10 minute podcast with the beta version.
And you'll be able to do that forever with the beta.
Even when it goes 1.0.
And all you have to get from there on is hosting.
And that too hopefully will change in the very near future with more pod show offerings.
Let me just see what else I had.
I mean, it's such a shell shock isn't the right word.
But I'm in a very, you know, kind of a mellowish mood because it's just so weird over here right now.
You know, you can't really be happy.
You can't, you don't want to be too upbeat because it just doesn't feel appropriate right now.
This stuff has been shocking.
It really has.
Okay.
Let me see.
People, what do I want to say?
Oh, yeah, Michael Butler has a new.
That's the rock and roll geek.
Michael Butler has a new podcast.
You can find it is rock and roll geek show rock and roll geek show dot com.
But now he has the indie cast, which is all pod safe music.
It's a rock and roll geek dot org.
And I was listening to it.
And that was rocking.
It was really, it was really, really good.
So you want to give that a check.
And Michael's also been doing lots of interviews with.
So pretty big name.
Yeah.
Christina, I'm flat on from Divinals.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
I love this three part series with Kenny Laguna, who's president of black heart records and
Joan Jets manager.
And he played in Tommy James in the Shondales.
He had a lot of really cool rock and roll stories to talk about.
And it was great.
I had to cut up a three part to us all along.
And there's a guy in Australia named Tom Schooting, who, I guess he used to live in the Netherlands.
It sounds like a Dutch name.
So I'm just going to presume that.
But he lives in Australia.
And he was a, he's a big fan of a radio show I used to do in the early 80s.
I'm talking 81, 82, called Curry and Funinkle, which I did with a partner.
You're doing Funinkle.
And he had to tape the whole bunch of these shows.
And when podcast came along, he started putting up feeds of this show as a podcast.
And I did what I think, and in hindsight, I think it's a really, really good idea is
when we move from the castle, I was getting rid of all the all our stuff.
You know, just trying to get rid of masses amounts of stuff.
I had a huge cardboard box filled with cassette tapes, cassette tapes from my work at
Radio Veronica with Curry and Veninkle.
Apparently also some of my early stuff on the pirate radio station.
And I told you that I worked for radio decibel in Amsterdam.
And I was, I think, either 16 or 17, probably 16 years old at the time.
Yeah, I think I just was old enough to ride a motorbike.
And I called myself John Holden because it was a legal station.
So you couldn't use your real name.
You had to have like a DJ name.
Because, you know, they would eventually find you or find us and confiscate the transmitters.
And just, I was kind of the on-vogue at the time.
You use an alias.
And so I pretended I was 24.
That was my whole stick.
And if you listen to the voice, it's like, no way.
Didn't couldn't even pull off, you know, 19.
So just, just hear a little bit of it.
And I'll tell you what I thought I was going to listen to more of this tape.
Anyway, this came from the podcast.
And I'll put a link to that in the show notes, of course.
Bring it down.
Yeah.
Hey.
25 minutes passed noveenth o'clock and we will begin.
Giving away let's see four or five free albums.
And as my photography giving away one right now.
So collar number five on one eight four one six eight.
You will win the new dire streets double album, I believe.
Yeah, you hear that sweeper there?
I'm six, two, and stand there.
We spun down my boys to make it sound really low.
So, you know, like the song you're hearing now,
they're a whole, but I just listened to this whole hour-long podcast,
which of course, you know, wasn't just a podcast,
but it was actually, you know, a full couple hours of radio show.
And the music we were playing at the time,
that was really the whole reason that it existed,
is because we were into that type of music
and it wasn't being played on the radio.
So, I, you know, kind of doing automatic analogy
to our pod-safe music,
and I went back into the bin and pulled out Buffy girl.
That's just too.
Hope you like it.
You're so right, it doesn't make sense.
So put the fact that I never even asked in the past films.
It wouldn't be right to give my heart away.
But something is thinking,
and it couldn't be hope,
because hope could just flow away.
Whatever it is, I have to let it slide.
But I could say your paintings everywhere I go.
And I hear your music playing in the back of my mind,
all the time.
Ooh.
I already knew that you could never be for me,
what I could never be for you.
But so many times I follow any way.
And my heart is thinking,
because my heart's a little heavy for a man I can't explain.
You leave all your windows open in the rain.
And I can see your smile in every smile I see.
Every time I leave, I turn my head to see you all smile in back of me.
That I don't need you.
And I can see your paintings everywhere I go.
I hear your music playing in the back of my mind, all the time.
You're so right.
Buffy Girl, everywhere I go.
It's Pod Safe.
You heard it here on the Daily Source Code.
Link to Buffy Girl's website can be found on the show notes for today's Daily Source Code
for July 8th, 2005.
All right.
So yeah, I've kind of wrapped up most of the work I needed to do this week.
Got some phone calls and stuff coming up.
But it's five after four Friday afternoon.
I'm ready for the weekend.
I certainly hope you are.
Monday will start off with a fresh new week.
We'll be cranking it out.
If you want to subscribe to the Daily Source Code,
you can do that through iTunes.
Just go into the podcast tab and search for Adam Curry or Daily Source Code.
You can also go to data sourcecode.com.
Now, here's something cool if you're using iTunes.
If you're using Safari and iTunes, I have to say.
If you see a white on orange XML link for a podcast or just a link to a podcast,
you can actually drag that right into iTunes and your podcast to have.
What an hour!
It's automatic.
You subscribe to me.
Of course, you can use that for any iPod or pod catcher,
such as iPod or iPod or the lemon version.
Adam Curry.com is my email address.
You can send me audio feedback there if you wish.
I'm going to get pretty close to the limit again.
2 gigabytes worth of Gmail so far used.
Where's my infinity plus?
My infinity plus one, guys.
Time to upgrade to another gigabit there.
Make it three.
www.curry.com is the weblog.
I will see you Monday for sure.
Maybe over the weekend.
Have yourself a good one. Bye-bye.
www.curry.com
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.