Daily source code Thursday April 21st, 2005.
$60 million worth of airplane straps to my ass.
Transmeters?
The next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need not thinking crazy.
I like to think I'm sighing.
You can't hear anything.
I'm just taking it.
I'm curious.
Hey everybody, it's Thursday.
I'm at the cottage.
This is your daily source code.
The power of the Lord, the Lord, the Lord.
And we are back home.
How are you doing?
Oh my goodness.
I'm back on the mixing here.
On the mixer board here.
And I'm trying to get every all the levels all straight now.
And I'm working perfectly.
You like some bass?
Certainly got the bass in this one.
The power of the Lord is strong.
All right.
As promised, we just wind this down a little bit.
As promised, we have some sound seeing tour to take care of today.
I actually found out that the I River records things in the fashion that actually makes kind of an interesting to put together a sound seeing.
To remember now, I have this brand new microphone, the Griffin Stereo La Palo Mike.
Which I used yesterday during, well, basically the entire day.
Up in the morning, in the cab with Taxi Eric, a little bit of conversation there.
Then meeting the Marines as they repelled from a helicopter.
And wound up the day with flight training, which actually that's part of the reason I went over.
As you know, I flew from Pharaohs, the airfield, not far from here from the cottage.
And that was with Wind Commander William for most of those two days.
And I decided to rig up the recording for four touch and goes that we did at Tessel Airport, which is an island.
Just to the north of the Netherlands, to the north and a little bit to like northeast, which basically borders on the north sea.
But it has a beautiful long grass runway, so you can do all kinds of simulated engine failures and full flaps and no flaps landings.
And just about every single situation you might come across when you're flying.
Because the book of flying, man, I thought I knew all about it when I got my helicopter license.
Turns out there's a lot more to learn.
And we're also, you know, the Wind Commander is really teaching me in a fashion that sets me up to really understand how to get my instrument rating.
There's a lot to it, and I think you'd enjoy because the sound with the stereo microphone really came out well.
I'm very, very pleased with, at least with parts of it.
The part would be in the airplane.
When the helicopter came over, we'll talk about that as I go through each bit.
So anyway, I recorded everything on the Iriver with the Griffin lapel microphone.
And I'm still rolling here, yeah.
What's good about is each time you stop the recording, it makes a new sound file.
So you don't wind up with one huge file, you know, that you have to kind of shuttle through and cue and everything.
So I have all these different bits and I can just basically pull out each individual bit and play it.
And I could have edited this all together, but I thought it would be a little more fun to talk about each piece and kind of do it live and on the fly.
I also took lots of pictures, which I'll include in the show notes.
I didn't do a synchronized sound seeing tour picture thing because the pictures were not all taken at exactly the same moment.
But it does give you a good overview of what happened and maybe they'll help you a little bit with the theater of the mind.
So you can, you know, if you don't know what a cougar helicopter looks like for instance, then, you know, you'll have a visual representation.
Because that's the kind of helicopter that the Marines came to use to repel down from to hand back the transmitter that we used in Iraq.
So it started yesterday in my hotel room, testing out the Griffin.
I'm getting ready for my good buddy, taxi Eric. He's, he's not just a driver.
Taxi Eric, not just a driver. He's a buddy.
And he's been a part of my radio shows doing sports reports and he really takes care of, he's taking care of our family in more ways than one. He's a really good guy.
Kind of like a gypsy ring.
If you know what that is.
So the sound of the Griffin, no, I'm sorry, the bell.
Now, what is it, Griffin of the Griffin lapel mic is a little nasal. I'm not too happy about it.
There's using it just for a plain old sound seeing, but it did work very well for some of the other stuff that we did today.
So or did yesterday. So let's have a listen as my day start off early in the morning in my hotel room in Utrecht.
Well, good morning. It is the 20th of April, 2005, relatively short night after the last time that we spoke.
I'm up and about in my hotel in Utrecht here.
And today is the day that we meet the Marines as they come repelling down from the sky.
So I figured I'd try and capture some of that on, well, you can't really say on tape anymore, can you?
Catching it on the flash recorder on the I River, of course.
So hearing is actually a little balcony on in the room.
You can kind of hear the morning sounds of Utrecht, it's raining, of course.
And I can see people across the street already in their offices.
It's 10 minutes to nine.
And there's some construction going on in the background.
Skies are gray, cloudy, not very nice.
Okay. So we'll continue.
We're on our way in the next segment.
Yes. And then I went down for a quick breakfast.
And Eric had his car at the ready.
And we had to drive to the radio station, radio Veronica.
It's the station that we did a whole week's worth of live broadcast from Camp Smitty in Iraq from.
And just refresh your memory when we left, we left behind my personal FM transmitter.
It's a 100 watt transmitter at the base, all set up with a satellite dish.
So they could receive the Dutch radio signal for 24 hours a day.
And the radio station throughout the entire mission that the Marines and their other troops, other Dutch troops were there.
We were handing out weather reports, traffic reports for Camp Smitty and Asamaba, which is the province that Camp Smitty lies in.
So there really was a bridge that we built between, between the everyone back home and all the troops far over sea.
Well, not really overseas, I guess, far over the desert.
Something that is very uncommon in the Netherlands because there's no support for armed, there's no respect really.
Now, the way, and when I grew up in the States, you have respect for the police officer.
You have respect for the firemen.
You have respect for men and women in military service.
And you have respect for your teacher.
And then, of course, you get your religious leaders and all that.
But there is an in bread respect for these people, which does not exist.
And predominantly socialist countries.
And it turns out that respect really, people want to do it, but it's not fashionable.
It's not done.
You don't talk about that because that's bad and the war machine.
And my whole thinking is, hey, we might need these guys one day.
Maybe even at home, so perhaps we should have a little bit of respect for them.
And the Ministry of Defense caught onto that.
And, of course, they took the ball and ran with it.
They saw the good PR.
They could get out of it.
It was a great experience without a doubt radio history in the Netherlands.
Very proud of that.
And now that the Dutch troops are done with their mission.
They've been there for two years in Iraq.
Now they're back.
The Brits and the Japanese have taken over Camp Smidi.
I believe.
And so, it's like last, well, last guy out, turned off the lights.
And, oh yeah, we've got to take the FM transmitter back to Curry.
That was kind of what this was all about, just winding up the entire Iraqi mission.
And you can hear, by the way, the dynamics of that microphone.
We've got to figure out something.
And whenever a little bit of wind hits it and wait until you hear the downwash from the helicopter,
it just starts to fluctuate.
And you can almost feel the membranes rocking back and forth in your eardrums.
By the way, if you're not listening to this podcast on ear buds or headphones,
I suggest you do, because really with sound seeing tours,
that's what you want.
You want to be in the experience.
So just listen to it at your computer or, you know, on speakers, you won't get the full effect.
But let's continue now.
And with a little bit of conversation with taxi-eric on our way to the radio station.
And you'll notice a recurring theme throughout the today's show.
Which is the Pope.
This is a testing.
Oh boy.
It is so sensitive.
The minute I start to breathe into this microphone, it just goes nuts.
Okay, the good thing about this mic is that, in today, it's good because it's white.
And I'm wearing a white shirt.
So it's actually better than the normal black lapel mic that I have on.
But you can really tell when the wind hits it.
That's going to be tough with the helicopter.
Okay, I see Eric down there.
I think he just arrived.
Teach the E.
You can't hear it.
Eat it.
Yo, eat it.
Hey, dude.
Hey.
Yeah, I have a coffee coffee.
I'm eliminated.
Yeah.
Okay, so I guess you got that part right there.
That was basically me inviting him for some coffee.
And now we're done now.
We're getting into the car.
I don't know.
I can hear it.
Hello.
Yeah.
I think I've told you about that taxi system before.
Well, the cab drivers basically hand work off to each other through cell phones.
And since they're all on the same cell phone network,
they don't pay anything for calls amongst themselves.
So it's a very efficient and cost effective way of business.
So I'm not too happy with this weather.
It's just shit.
This is a typical Dutch.
And Eric is a typical Dutch day for weather as yet.
Very bad.
It's raining.
It's not too much wind.
It's a little bit foggy.
Yeah.
There's no way to fly that I think.
What do you mean for the helicopter?
That won't be a problem.
No.
Is there any problem getting out of the helicopter?
Because there is one that's pretty foggy.
I don't know.
Well, I mean, essentially no.
I mean, we can fly IFR.
Yeah.
You can fly in the complete blind if he wants to.
Never get you do that.
Yeah.
Just don't know how long.
No, not last very long.
Okay.
So right now we're driving from Utrecht to Niner.
And that's where we'll pick up the rest of the crew that went with us to Iraq.
And then from there we go over to whatever the rendezvous point is.
You don't know what that is, do you?
Yeah.
Somebody in the field because we're talking about the big helicopter.
Cougars.
Yeah.
I guess a Cougar is a reason.
It's not a Chinook.
That's really big.
But the Cougars are going to be reasonably big.
So.
I don't give you my camera, Iraq.
Yeah.
Do you take pictures?
Pictures of myself.
Can I be able to cook with me, man?
Right.
I take pictures, but you show me how to work.
Oh, please.
You were showing me how it worked yesterday.
What did you zoom in?
Yeah.
Believe me.
It's idiot proof.
It is.
Well, then get these cameras have gotten really good.
Do you think there's going to be any TV?
Yeah.
Show you.
Yeah, well, the Ministry of Defense sent out to press release.
Presently.
Yeah.
It was for the first time.
We're going to give something big.
No, come on us, not fair.
But yeah, the minute I said, yeah, I'll be there.
I confirmed.
Press release is started going out.
It's like they're really trying to make the army image.
Well, I mean, they really mean this.
I know that.
I know they really mean this.
But they are taking advantage of the situation.
You guys kind of the same way.
We took advantage of the situation.
I mean, going to Iraq was good for them and good for us.
Good for everybody.
Good for the station, too.
Don't deny it.
Don't deny it, sir.
I love the cigar.
So they were just driving along the highway.
And of course, he run into some typical Dutch traffic situations along the way.
Okay, so we're still in the car.
We're in a typical Dutch situation, which is a traffic jam.
Actually, it's not that bad today.
So, Eric, how's everything going in Holland?
Everything is going pretty good.
We are pretty happy with the German boat.
Like a boat, man.
You know, like the German boat?
I don't like the German.
No.
I'm not telling these.
You weren't even born in the second world war, man.
You're talking about it.
No, the boat was okay, but why don't they pick someone who's a little bit younger?
A younger boat?
How old is this guy?
Is what?
78.
78?
Well, I know why.
Why?
We have to choose another one.
Exactly.
How many Cardinals are there?
100?
More 140?
Yeah.
I think 200?
200?
Yeah.
So all those guys would potentially like to be the Pope.
Right?
I would like to go ahead to die already.
Well, you know, it's like, you know, let's not have to wait around for 30 years before we have another shot.
Maybe they still have a chance.
Maybe something like that, I don't know.
Is it due to my age?
No, I doubt it.
It's, I'm sure it's like any big corporation.
But I mean, how powerful is the Pope?
Can he decide to die himself?
Decide what?
Well, whatever.
Whatever.
Well, no.
Well, yeah, he, of course, he's powerful.
Yeah.
I mean, you're not dead anymore.
You know what I mean?
Well, I would hope that he has a direct connection to the man.
I mean, yeah.
Yeah.
You become Pope.
So right now it's 10 o'clock, which is good.
I like being fashion-related.
A real star.
Yeah.
A real star always comes late.
That's what you're driving me.
Yeah, exactly.
Okay.
So now the traffic is moving.
And actually, this doesn't sound too bad on the,
on the Griffin lapel microphone.
It sounds a little bit better.
Excuse me.
It sounds a little bit better than yesterday.
The acoustics also have changed, which I'm sure makes a difference.
From the hotel room to the car.
The window is cracked a little bit.
So that's the sound you're hearing.
Close the window?
That's okay.
Oh, wow.
Penal to the middle, Eric.
And instantly, the diesel force cylinder springs to life.
Yeah.
It's always fun to not taxi drivers cab, you know,
tell them that he has a shitty cab with a shitty engine.
So then we arrived at the radio station.
I was blown away.
They were walled wall, soldiers, marines, air force, ground troops.
They had jeeps, camouflaged vehicles.
And this was becoming a really big production.
And so we hung out in front of the building for, I don't know,
about 20 minutes, drinking coffee, just shooting a shit, you know,
with all these guys.
Some of them who we met in Iraq, others were new.
And they were just along for the ride,
or providing support for this show that we're putting it on for us.
And so, unfortunately, a lot of what I recorded is in Dutch,
which I'm not going to play all of just little bits.
I did hook up with a couple of the crew members.
I'm going to play a bit now from a short conversation I had with
Michiel Feinstra.
He was a member of the morning crew,
and he still does the morning show with another host now.
And also, has his own,
he actually, he wanted a marconi award,
a coveted marconi award for the work that he does on the radio
and the Netherlands.
And we had a quick conversation in Dutch just about our impressions of the day,
and what we were going to expect,
we call him Mike Veinstra.
We're here in front of the Veronica Radio Studios,
and offices.
The broadcast tower at tower light.
This is, I mean, he'll think so.
Mike, Mike Veinstra?
Yeah.
What the fuck is going on?
I didn't expect this.
You did?
No.
No, I mean, I expected, like, we'd all hook up,
and then we go over to the field,
there's, like, 20 marines.
Yeah.
Oh, they're so grateful.
And the police escort.
Yeah, I didn't know that either.
That's pretty cool.
Well, I know that the military are so grateful.
What is it, John?
Yeah, like it?
Yeah.
What is it for?
It's for Bart.
How is Bartcyc?
Of Focconi.
Oh, LED.
Yeah.
Fingers.
Yeah, yeah.
I want to think about it.
Yeah.
I mean, NAB.
We're not playing cards.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think.
What's your career?
Yeah.
I can put my studio microphone.
It's hot like that.
Okay.
Have you been playing?
Yeah.
Do you want to talk to me?
All right.
That was a small interruption
by one of Holland's most famous DJs,
and he's a special fan.
He's a fan.
Now, it's a big surprise for me as well to see so many of the military show up on.
But I guess that just on the lines, how grateful they are for us going there over a year ago, leaving the transmitter there, receiver.
It wasn't a big deal.
I mean, it was more fun for us, I thought.
It was great.
Yeah.
But the transmitter, I guess, that really did help them.
I mean, after we left the transmitter, so they could still tune into radio Veronica.
And over the year, E-mail message just came coming in from Cam Smith from the guys saying, thank you for the music.
The songs you're singing.
Thanks for all the joy or bringing it.
So, yeah, I guess they are.
So let me, yeah.
It's probably a much more big deal to them than me.
Then we realized.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
So the setup here is we've got a black hummer with our logo on it.
Of course, it's a radio station.
Yeah.
It's a really big logo.
It has listen now.
Cute in.
And just to bet with it, we've got to put the frequency on as well.
So what time is it now?
It's 1030.
So those guys already left for the field?
Yeah.
Already checked the spot earlier this morning.
So I should know how to get there.
Are you driving?
No.
Okay.
You're trying to persuade me.
I'm not driving.
No.
To me, he was only had his license for about a year and a half.
So, not a make that a year.
Where's your car?
Do you see that thing?
Yeah, that's it.
Oh, there it is.
Pimped out.
Yeah.
So one of the stars in a big guitar at the back.
Is that the Dutch version of Pimped my ride?
Got a hold of your car?
It's the Dutch sheep.
No, butchard version.
Oh, I'm going to ride.
The late late late late.
Late night version.
Yeah, my ride.
The cool thing is.
But then he just got some stickers and threw it on there.
He takes a fence and it and says, hey, it's a clear pimp.
But the cool thing is, instead of exhibit, we got this cool chick.
You're in.
Right.
Yeah, we know her.
So that's the one good thing about the big bird.
The big bird.
Mike.
There you go.
So that's a little bit of a setup there.
As we were just about to take off to go to the field where we are rendezvous point.
No, when we arrived there, it was just, you know, there was it was cord noff.
There was just troops everywhere.
Police escorts.
It was really, I was blown away.
In fact, I was humbled completely humbled by this.
Now, if you thought the wind was bad in that recording.
Wait until you hear the downwash of the rotor blades of a cougar helicopter.
I tried to narrate a little bit of it.
You hear photographers yelling at me because they want to get a picture of me looking at the helicopter,
which, of course, I totally ignored.
I'm like, God damn it.
Can't you guys just, you know, get your own shot, you know, do something, like do some work?
They're very lazy over there.
They'll, they'll, I think most celebrities in Holland will do anything to get their picture in the paper.
And this to me, although, of course, I knew it was going to be a press moment.
This was really about the guys who we have the utmost respect for.
So what you're about to hear now, and again, I apologize.
I've still got to figure out a way to put a wind screen on this thing.
And I'm going to ask Patricia again if she can help me with like a panty hose, wind screen or something over the, the lapel microphone.
You hear the cougar come over first.
You'll hear some background of me just talking with people.
Then you'll hear it land.
I, or actually the, the repelling down of four of these marines.
And I'll, I'll let it play for a little bit at a certain point.
It's just so much touching it that I don't think it'll make a lot of sense.
But enjoy this, because the sound, it isn't stereo,
and it did come across reasonably well.
Again, some downwash and the griffin eye mic.
It might, it may make your, your, your, your drums vibrate a little bit.
But now crank it up and enjoy.
As we say, if you can't cover it up.
Turn it up.
Oh man.
Okay, here comes the helicopter.
Full hunchmark.
Holy moly.
Thank you.
I've been to their coal.
Oh man.
Nice to come here.
Yeah.
My next one is it.
Thank you.
So it's turning and making a 360.
It's coming in for the cover, so you can see the doors are open, there's two guys on this side.
In the walkin of the top.
Tohisseld..
Open is always close to the left and right.
Oh, no!
My opening is good!
Get it cut!
I got the whole man!
Brother are coming down!
I'm just so full!
That's funny!
Put down!
Second and third are coming down!
I'll just run their hole!
Come back here on!
It's unbelievable!
1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 4, 5,
I can't sneak against that!
Back on the hook!
Drop the flyers!
I can sneak against that man's problem with me!
The car goes with the same load!
Okay!
Go!
Drop the flyers!
Stand up for fire down!
Aachon!
Hey there!
I'm dead in the NBA!
Nice trail to finish!
You're working on this.
Whether it's war or not.
This car will be San Francisco-
I'm so happy she said the dude was in for a test
he's gonna close it
I think they are meeting with things like this
Don't worry.
and then they won't touch anything
Don't say no to any time
Why are you laughing?
I've been so blogs lately
I'm not gonna see you
That was a little piece there of the commander who was actually going to hand the
transmitter to me once it was delivered by the Marines from the helicopter and he reiterated
exactly what we discovered there he said it was so great to get up in the morning in the
middle of the desert you know it's blazing hot you turn on the radio and of course they had
just regular transistor radios within they couldn't receive anything except one
transistor one transmission from a mosque which was pretty much mosque music and he said
it was great because you know you flip on the radio and then you hear the weather report you
also hear you know what the weather was going to be in camp smithy that day he said it was
you know it's almost like not being in the middle of the desert and that's of course
something that only the magic of radio can bring although it would have worked perfectly what
would pod casting as well I presume so you can hear that the cougar helicopter after he dropped
the former rains out he the helicopter landed and then from that I was just you know
basically shaken hands talking to everybody talking about our time there and yeah just kind
of getting re-acquated so when you hear all of this stuff there's you hear those choppers
coming over there's only one song you can play right a little bit of break and we'll be
back with more sound seeing from the sess no 182
although I might be the lapping loud and hot air deep inside and blue
so take a good look at my face you see my smile you saw a lot of place in the
close for the season to change the chance of my team
I need you to be me
since you let me up you see me with another girl
see me like I'm having fun
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh yeah
oh
yeah
Oh, it's fading, it's just the power that you put me down
My smile is my wake-up, I wear since my break-up with you
There's a text with blood, with your smile
Oh, so I know if you're my smile, I'm inside of you
Yeah, don't know, it's the same as you did
All the chats of my team, baby
Baby, baby, baby, baby, take the blood
All in love, yes, oh, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
You're welcome, let's go, let's go, let's go
Smoking Robinson and the miracles, the tracks of my tears
Of course, from the tour of Duties soundtrack
Just always hear that song whenever, whenever I hear chopper blades
Roofing through the air
So, once that was done, we went back from another quick cup of coffee
We hung out, talked a little bit more, and then, by that time
The Wing Commander had flown up from Antwerp
Where the Sessna is hangered, where he has his operations
And of course, we're going to do at least another four or five hours of flight training
Now, just to set this up properly
I have a helicopter license, I've flown over 700 hours on turbine helicopters
But it is a big difference between flying a helicopter and a fixed wing aircraft
And particularly the way the Wing Commander is teaching me
Because the first thing he did is he said, okay, no digital jockey shit
He took away the GPS, it's all being done on VORs
So that means that you're basically using World War II technology
And instruments, complete instrument navigation
And it's very important to learn how to fly
And the most important part of flying, if you've ever done a flight in a light weight aircraft
It's actually not too hard getting off the ground
I think just about everybody could probably get an airplane airborne
With an hour or two of less, and you can probably learn straight and level flight
Which is the first thing you learn, and then you're banking
Because you can definitely bank too far and you can turn yourself upside down
There is some stuff to be learned there
But the most important part is landing and landing is not just landing
You have all kinds of different airfield situations
It could be a short field, it could be a soft field
Meaning a grass field, it could be a really long field
You could have an engine failure
You could, well today we actually had quite a bit of wind
So we did some exercises, which you normally would not ever do in high winds
But there may be a reason for it
So essentially you're training for all, you know, it's expected that's basically what it is
And you're still never going to finish the whole book that is aviation
You learn with every single flight, I think you learn something new
So what I did for this particular bit, and we're going to do four touching goes
As I stuck the Griffin lapel mic into my headset
And it turned out really cool, first of all there's no wind noise
So none of that, you know, vibrating ear drum stuff
But you also were able to hear a good combination of the outside air noise, the engine
As well as what's going on on the cockpit
And I asked the wind commander who was very proficient at English
Of course most pilots have to speak English, but he's good at it
Oops, hold on a second
I'll have to call that person back, whoever it is
We did that instruction in English
I think he kept going English all the way through
Now this is not so, I mean you're thinking probably okay
And I'm going to listen to some flying stuff of a flying sound
Seeing tour, what I really liked about this, and I listened to it twice
First of all, as a student someone who's learning
It was very, very helpful to go back and I remember of course
Every single situation, I remember every climb, every descent, every landing
All the parts of it
It's great to be able to go back and listen to what my instructor was telling me
Every single time, because now I was forgetting some really crucial things
If you're a pilot, you'll know that the carb heat is a lifesaver
You can't forget pulling the carb heat
Which basically you want heat to go through your carburetors
Especially when you're landing
Whenever you're doing a slow flight maneuver
Because it can ice up, even if it can be easily 75 degrees outside
And you can still get icing in your carburetor
So that's something that I forgot once or twice
And that's just something you can't forget
That could cause a real bad day
So one other thing I want, so what's beautiful about this
Is the relationship between student and teacher
That's really what I like hearing in this particular sound
Seeing tour
And by the way, whenever William says it's an incident
I think he meant, well, what I know what he means
He's basically saying, oh, that's a coincidence
A coincidence is that you landed so nicely
A coincidence that you happen to be on course
So that's kind of his way of saying, okay, good job
So listen now to some touching goes, a Tesla airport
As we taxi out to the field first
The wing commander William and myself in our Cessna 182RG
Well, the brakes?
Yeah, no, go half to no
Good afternoon, wing commander William
Yes, sir, we are
You ready to rock and roll?
Okay, okay, ready to check out the Tesla airport
Tesla number 277, Delta share, ready to check?
That's a good idea, don't wait for it
Five as well, zero four, we're doing four touching goes
If what it pots you to a helicopter
And you know, okay, ready?
Roll, roll, sir, roll and we are
Okay, press and check
Mr. John makes a rich slaps up
Up to the car, please
Break us off, okay, it's okay
It's a power of a belly
Fuck again, it makes a kick of your sight
Makes a change on my side, my sped is wrong
Oh, baby, we take the right
We take the right
All
The point is, I guess, and I'm gonna go around that
Okay, lovely Tesla airport, whether it's very nice today
Nice bit of wind
It's about 20 knots crosswind on the landing
18 gusts and up 43
He goes about 75, 80 degrees
And he's out the car, I'm confused
He's heading until you reach the runway
That's just a problem, I don't wait for the right to check
He along the runway to fill the first runway markers
That's all complete, we go straight ahead
And just before the runway we turn to the right to the right
85 degrees, if you have any options
And then just before the markers
We pick up the center line for a couple of tips
And go to the center of the ocean
I don't click this at all, sir
That's great
Yes, there's a one as on this grass
Yeah
Okay, you don't need to do any cags to be close
We just, we just have to float here
We have to set this here, right now
Okay, that's one as sufficient
But wait for me at him, so we'll take a left here
Okay
I keep it going again, I have to go about 20 to three slabs
And there's no one coming in
Oh, I'm always all clean
There we go, sir
Okay
That's the stick into the wind, shall
There we go
Power is coming out
Thank you, power
Thank you, power is in power
It's sufficient, it's been getting to the slide
Okay, if you have a tight snowy, okay
You feel the air comes to the wind
Yeah, we have a positive, not the opposite
Rakes, we get up the brakes
We get all the crutes, we get the crutes, we get the crutes
Now, you're evenly sliced on your sleeves
Behind the BET
Okay, see, let's set them
You try to set them down, okay you're set them
You want to set them right
Can't be thestreight
Oh, okay, now we won't int datas
Why does it reflected inside?
Oh, really?
I'm...
Okay, okay, if you have 500 each, try to lift me tight, right
By my material on the left, I'm sure what you make, live it, it's free, live it and thank it.
The negating speed is 85, it's better, 80.
But the bank is making the place that it's okay.
The downlink speed today, and the digital consensus is rated temperature.
It's one of the most indigating, okay.
It's okay.
What does 80 knowing how to bend it one, two, five?
What does the speed coming up to?
85, one of the nuts, power bank, you make it putty, one, twenty-two, which is which you're right for right.
And now we have the left turning right, the downlink.
But if we turn left, turn right for the downlink.
Yes, we turn right and right.
I'm so right.
Okay.
You're gonna get me left.
Where you from?
Yes.
I won't roast you.
Okay.
I'll make a roll on our trail.
So put your nose about to sit.
Take it out to church and you want the front of the street and front of the front.
I want 100 knots of the downlink.
That's it.
And those left might get more density to the place.
And then you need to dodge the walk.
There's a red arrow there.
That is the water.
Just before you have to get it.
Okay.
You'll have to set your right for the future.
But they downlink, so okay.
Now it's just one.
Brakes on the church.
And there are three green and a couple more things for you.
Those two had to kick you and intent the left.
And the left are okay too.
Blest.
But I think nicely.
You can't.
Or these.
Okay.
And then we.
You're so powered and we can be sending them to the right.
And we're just powered.
There's a little bit.
A little bit of warmth left to make it about the 18 to the punch in the grease.
That's such.
That is final.
That can't pass.
That can't.
Such.
Right you.
Watch.
That can't be gross.
Because we don't want to offline that.
That we should know.
Should somebody don't want to offline the people.
Well.
I don't care about the people I am.
Okay.
Let's do it.
We're going to go in.
Okay.
I need.
Not to smoke it.
It's in a form.
Okay.
What you do.
What you do is you're out of your dog.
It's bleeding.
You're going now.
You need to be reducing.
It's the.
Okay.
I'm going to.
You have to.
Try.
We have a promise.
On the carriage.
We have.
You have.
Yeah.
And reducing the 80 knots.
Yes, sir.
What would you do if you win?
You quit right here.
Well.
And pull the nose up a little bit.
Blind him.
Should be on the quiet right here.
Tell him.
Let's rest.
Play for him to save you there.
So that's it.
We have a new pump.
Oh yeah.
Nice.
Somebody is so aware.
Okay.
I'm going to lose.
What do you want?
Yeah.
And.
Are you that?
You reduce a little bit.
Power to the power.
And.
And you're the right side of the center line.
The European.
Yes.
Well.
I agree.
But now I was wondering.
You did it.
It's not.
Okay.
Your city.
I got this.
Come on.
Yes.
It's very loud.
It's loud in us.
Yeah.
And.
Beautiful.
Ah.
Make all the needs of the joker.
Okay.
And.
That's.
And
And.
I don't see those things really, but it's a bad open dude.
I don't think so.
I'm gonna approach you.
What does it mean?
I don't think so.
I'm gonna approach you.
What does it mean?
I don't think so.
I'm gonna approach you.
What does it mean?
I don't think so.
It means the mount down with anything what shouldn't mean.
It's going to be right here, which should be about zero.
So you're zero.
That sounded amazing.
Wait.
Detrict.
button again.
When you control the controlangle
It won't keep doing it yet, it won't show it yet, it won't look a great green
100 knots
That's true, okay
That's true
Of course you
Okay, you can let them down if you're like
Okay, and just don't the guy that you turned in, I can't do base for the ditch, no, it was hit on the floor
Another but 277, got the share, turn in, right hand, base for touch and go with 0-4
Although
Okay, keep, keep to turn you
Okay, I want to reduce a little bit, I don't know what to do
We'll see you in the next few days, take care of yourself
Okay, what do you think is in the other shoe to know for sure to do a center line?
Fucking right under the middle of the center line now, okay, pick up, pick up the heading to zero
And then five, get a 4-5
And let's wait for you to do a center line, you see what I'm doing
Uh, I mean, you're a 4-5
Reducing speed
Yeah, I'm gonna
Okay, you're aiming for which speed
Okay, anything I can get
99, 90, 90s
And yeah, the other mountain goes so well, and then you're using slowly to achy
And then remember what I told you, you're doing lunch set
If you reduce the power, if you reduce the speed, you have to
Increase the angle of the pack, slowly
If it's some power, and it's, that will do, that will do, that will do
Okay, slowly bring it to the runway
Watch, think it down, let it go, let it go, let it go, let it go
Let it go, this is an height of control, letting you see
Okay, can I see a camera set, you have control, I show you
I show you the landing up, look, look, look, look, look, look, look
Yeah, I get it, that's you, did you sooner down, you should impossible to control, right
Yeah, sure I mean, yeah
Can you do this for demonstration?
Okay, this is possible at a earlier station, you know, it goes,position, cool, yeah
I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here, but I'm not sure if you're gonna get that wrong here,
Ahmm...
But it's just pretty exciting, 85' thought it's very easy to edit, oh great look it's pretty pretty, pretty fun, champ
Now we have just 3 oh 4 inch low on that line.
And then  that line then back there
I have to take off the checks and land power, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
at the right, come on, come on, come on, come here I saw this exception, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come have it, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on,
And right, let's go to the right, and space, just walk the people out here.
Yeah.
There are my 277 Delta share and 20 right hand.
And space touching out onto your phone.
And the right hand.
And then the share of mine share with that, you set it up into the line.
24 knots, 24 knots, so for a good job, share.
Okay.
And can't you speed, sir?
Yes.
Or you can back to 80.
Now, just don't back to 80.
Wait, you're making it happen.
Good.
Some flaps.
Okay.
That's enough.
Keep on turning.
Okay.
Now let it go.
Bro.
You're slightly above to fly across your hand.
This is all of an aircraft.
There's our answer.
Okay.
If I'm a big deal, it's final clear.
Me.
Very, yeah.
Same up to final.
Short final.
So you'll be there in a couple of seconds.
Okay.
That's one of my questions.
Thank you.
Do you want to local?
Okay.
Speed back 75.
Keep it going.
He's only five.
And the black and build up was the aircraft.
I wrote it.
Okay.
But what else?
Blow it with us.
And 75.
That is the minimum.
Because the wind is blasting.
Yeah.
And the transform.
Because it's a very tricky aircraft.
If you have full flaps on my girlfriend's situation.
If you stay in control until you're about half an incident there.
About the aggression.
Better down.
Lower your nose.
Okay.
Better down.
Final kicks.
You've got them no problem.
Better down.
Okay.
And fly just over to the main ground.
Left.
Okay.
Keep going.
All right.
There we go.
Flaps wall.
Okay.
Composition.
Keep going.
Okay.
We are positive.
Break.
Yeah.
Okay.
What is your speed?
They didn't.
They understeed the flaps.
No, sir.
That he right.
He was number three.
That was number three.
The wind is not on clear.
He didn't.
And the first.
And I.
I don't share here.
Hey.
Okay.
Yeah.
25.
Yes.
There we go.
I think I've been taking the distance better.
But I don't want to go to the city.
I want shall we go for the midship.
Subway to the engine.
Fill your nation.
Okay.
Stay up.
Stay down.
Be quick.
Subway neither.
Okay you didn't you.
Come sleeping.
Okay, now is up.
You that no is absiu and push.
Do we are okay?
You go back to the loop.
We've been under the ninety-seven summit.
Thank you.
Well, papas.
Same way you repent?
We are shortly going smooth.
Okay.
So I'm going to turn.
Is it okay to be able to shift?
No.
Okay.
Okay, we're really not so turning in now, if the ADNOT show, very, very important.
Wow, it's not so bad, you know.
Don't you have no background yet, you might, you don't need it now, you might need it this season, but...
And the gear is still off, you know.
Maybe you don't need any flaps at all.
The gear goes down, the gear goes off, the gear goes off.
The gear goes down, when you shell, if you can make it so that it's okay, lower the mouse, lower the gear.
Nopckets, enc Apollo!
Okay, we go forward. Now that's nowauto 5 seconds.
Oh, haha, Ngyz?
Let's go! Let's go, because we have no incoming opportunity.
This is still in!
I know, I know. I do not know, it's not an Autcope sir, that's turning in quite far.
Okay again, that sounds like this.
Okay, there we got it.
You see what I mean?
There we have it.
And keep this head in the wrong direction.
Okay.
We have 18.
Yeah, baby.
Okay.
Here we go.
We have a constant breaks.
Here up.
Okay.
Here we go.
Extend it.
Okay.
Distend it.
Extend it.
Yeah.
That's it.
Okay.
This was number one.
This was number four.
We can't get up here.
I don't even have that in prison at all.
Oh, gosh.
Okay.
I'm now in this section.
If we start talking, we don't know.
There's all two sons.
I'm going to share them.
You know what?
We know that we have that form.
We do just one form.
We play the next week.
Is that okay?
No problem.
You can make it.
Then if you like.
Okay.
We get back to the next week.
Now I appreciate these moments here.
Dear flips.
Okay.
Up and down.
We try to spawn.
You're blind.
Now hold these servos.
There's a lot of power.
But then you're all set.
You made it wrong.
We're about it.
No play.
It might block some trouble.
I'm not holding.
It's the key to not eating.
Think, think.
Okay.
There.
Up.
They're lucky.
I did you have such a good memory.
Yeah, really.
Okay.
Now flaps.
Brakes.
You know.
Carme needs.
Up and down.
The time.
You're done.
Crush.
If you do the key down.
You're just right.
I'm not going to end you off for the second thing.
And it's gone for you.
Or whatever you want to do.
Okay.
But I prefer this.
Let's use.
Brakes.
Up and down.
Make sure it's clear.
And flaps.
And it's clear.
Which is the first.
And.
From.
Three items.
Moving.
To.
Okay.
We turn the right.
Press.
Right.
Check.
Please.
Okay.
Keep on turning.
Yeah.
Hey.
And.
And look.
There's.
Okay.
Stay positive.
Go.
Hold on.
you keep this down zero and you keep it up and focus on the control yeah
beside anytime okay 19 take a couple of inches off and raise the nose
raise the nose the okay that's it okay I'm going to land up properly now
now you're okay now okay keep this speed which is speedy now's 28 times
okay another down this way this is great okay
if this speed you because you have the same clay five of the feet per minute
and the speed is 80 so that is fine
you understand the change over time yes has to survive okay go to that bike go to that bike
okay check your speed is fine and now you take a couple of inches off
and raise the nose and it all ends up down okay you see what you do now are to control
okay so there you go sounds seen tour from the cockpit of the Cessna 182
retractable gear after that we flew off to Hilversum and of course another a couple of
touch and goes there I'm going to leave it at what it is for now I actually I'm
so I'm pretty happy with the way the the Griffin lapel microphone turned out
on that particular sound seeing tour okay I hope you enjoyed again I'll be posting pictures
to go along with the show notes so that you can get a little idea of what the
Marines look like and have some more cockpit pictures to share with you and I will be
back tomorrow for the thank god it's Friday edition of the Daily Source Code which I'm
hoping will feature my partner Ron Bloom so we'll get a bit of a strategy cast
um if you have comments you may want to add them at curie dot com leave a comment on my
web log at www.curie dot com the podcast feed can be found at dailysourcecode dot com
stay subscribed everybody thanks for checking out talk to you soon bye bye
oh