Delta Shira Charley 2, 5, 7.
Beloved brothers and sisters, dear Adam, Patricia, Christina, welcome, I'm Father Rodrick.
We are gathered here for a last farewell to a trusty companion, a great and beloved partner
that helped and supported you in all your podcasting adventures and in many more things.
And to recently, always there, always reliable, always ready to give you what you needed.
Adam, may I invite you to light a candle for your deceased power book.
Thank you.
The last couple of days have been difficult.
Your laptop, one's a real power book, started to show signs of diminishing power.
I walked in and I could hear my hard drive going, and that's usually a bad sign.
The symptoms were small at first, little hiccups in the audio, sometimes a spinning
beach ball that didn't go away.
Oh, man, I now have the spinning beach ball of death.
After I asked it to advance to the next file.
And since your relationship until then, had always been perfect, you Adam didn't really
understand this behavior.
In your confusion, use sometimes, understandably, reacted with irritation, and sometimes even
anger.
I'm going to go throw this piece of shit out, but we know this map.
I'm so angry.
So bad, piece of shit.
But little did we know, these symptoms were the beginning of the end.
When you realize that your laptop was terminally ill, that no quick fixes or shaking the
box could help, you surrounded your ailing power book with all the love and carry you
had.
You spent countless hours in front of the freezer where your suffering power book was cooling
down, and you used every tool that you're disposal to save as much data as possible.
And then, much faster than we all expected, it was all over.
Please, it's crying.
It's hampering my work, man.
Sorry about that.
Try to take my composure there.
Of course, we are sad.
And at them, you told us that you can't think of another power book anytime soon.
It's too early, perhaps next year, who knows, take your time.
And as we seem together, the imparadism know that you can always count on my support in
these difficult times.
You know where you can find me.
My podcast is just a click away, and www.gatholicinsider.com.
And don't worry, my podcasts are a lot more cheerful than this sad goodbye.
Just how cool is that, huh?
Rest in peace, dear power book.
It is October 10th, in year of our Lord, 2005, hell, everybody, welcome from Curry Cottage,
11.25 in the AM, start of a brand new week, we've got a lot of stuff to do today, playing
that pieces of interviews, got some awesome mashups, and of course, you're probably
a power, you know, it's actually thinking about putting together a little piece about
my power book.
That's what I was thinking yesterday, and I was kind of hunting around for a couple of
pieces of music, and then father wrote rejects it, and with that incredible requiem for
my father-in-law power book, it's kind of confusing at the same time, you know, father
wrote from the Catholic Insider, Catholic Insider.com is a real priest from the Netherlands.
And there he is, kind of making fun of making fun of the whole religion, I don't know,
I like that.
Well, definitely put yet another new, you know, it's shown and yet another new light
on father-roadery.
For me, at least this guy is a funny man, I love the stuff he's doing.
I think he came out, did he?
They've seen with like the seventh Harry Potter episode of the Catholic Insider by now, it's
really quite unbelievable to stuff he's doing.
The English story is called jam back, as I said today.
It is a beautiful autumn day in the United Kingdom, the leaves are just starting to fall,
sunny, smells really nice outside.
Which means we can only add to the fragrances, right?
By adding some mashups to the mix, perhaps.
This is one that came from Pilchard, it was part of a full on mega mix that came in over
the weekend on the mashuptown.com RSS feed.
And actually it was like 25 minutes long and I said, dude, can you talk to Pilchard
see if I can get just this mashup, just this one piece I'd love to play it on the show
because it's one of, by one of my favorites.
I can't walk in these streets too long, singing in the same old song, I know if we
cracked in these 30 sidewalks of Broadway, but also the name of the game, and nice guys
get watched away like the snow and the rain, there's been a little cough from my
eyes, on the road to my eyes, but I'm gonna feel the tight, I'm shining on me, like a ranch
song cowboy, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a
horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need e horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need an horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse, I need a horse
I'm so proud of you
I'm a good man, I'm a strong people, I don't even know
And all those coming over the wall
I'm a good kid
Maybe it doesn't even qualify
As a master, maybe it's just a remix
I'm telling you, re-release that thing
And this version, you've got a guaranteed kid on your hands
You just can't take away from the right stone cowboy
It's a Glen Campbell remix on your daily source code coming to you from Curry Cottage
Only a few more days, end of the week, Sunday
I'll be back in California for a week
Then I come back, Christina has her full-term
Sorry, her half-term
She's pregnant, she's full-term
I think we're going to go to Portugal for a few days
Then we come back and then I'll head on back to California
So, and in this week, on Wednesday and Thursday
I'm going to the Netherlands, I've got some business stuff
That I still have to finalize there
Of course, I've coordinated that with some flying with the wing commander
Haven't quite said all the times yet
But he promised me to be available, so
Looking forward to that
Over the weekend
Well, as Father Roderick already kind of summed it up there
The power book died
May the power book, well actually the power book didn't die because the shell of the soul
Of the power book is still alive
He those birds in the background
They hear, they hear fall coming too
Here's what I did for those of you who have been tracking it and just want to know
I went out, bought a G5 iMac
And I installed a fresh copy of Tiger on that
Then
This is kind of cool, I have the desktop Mac
Which is on one of the cinema displays
It's actually my old-old power book
And the screen display, it's a type book
Actually the screen display broke on that
And I never got around descending it off
I just hooked it up to the external monitor
And that's kind of like the main desk machine that we have here
So I used Apple's migration tool
So essentially what I did was I got a fire wire drive
Had a 30 gig fire wire drive laying around that doesn't need an external power source
I cleaned it all up
And you know reformatted the whole thing
Named it Macintosh HD
Plugged it into the power book
Because of course, it's the drive that is completely hose
And I had done a lot of work over the weekend
Getting as much data off of this possible
Almost everything
I probably missed about 20 pictures that I hadn't uploaded yet to flicker
Of course everything else is uploaded to flicker
And my root 66 install and of course that's a great mapping program
Which I use a lot for aviation in Europe
And I can't find the install CD
So I'll have to figure that one out
And otherwise
You know it's kind of reboot a refresh of my life
Oh my MP3s that was a big concern
Because I built up quite a nice library
And of course you're always archiving stuff here
And then you hear now and putting some stuff to the side
But it really was like my complete MP3 collection
I was a little bit bummed out about that
I could not get that off and then
Yeah, I'm saying like wow man this is really sucks
How am I going to get off? I'm looking at my iPod
I'm going dude
I have my MP3 collection
It's on my iPod
Then of course I had to go through the whole rigmarole of
Figuring out how to you know how to sync that back into
A new iTunes which is Apple doesn't make very easy for you
But this plenty of programs out there that let you do it
It's reasonably easy to do kind of like a blowback
From your iPod back to a new install of iTunes
And then I did something interesting
After I had that 30 gig drive
Already to go
I used the migration tool from the desktop
So it pulled in an already familiar environment for me
It already had a lot of the applications installed
And it's running fine
It doesn't boot us now obviously
Because instead of sitting right there on the mother board
With some connection
It's connected through fire wire
So at least I have a portable machine
With all the data that I need
With me to take with me
Until the new power books come out
Which I'm still thinking is going to be this Wednesday
I think that that's the one more thing announcement
Everyone's talking about the video iPod
And I was just thinking again man
It's like
I'd basically
Prefer to listen to the audio
Of
Well, that's not entirely true
I mean actually I have a piece of
Video that managed sent me maybe I should play that later for you
See if the audio does it although
Looking at mad showing me
Fred and Ethel
I
Yeah, there's something to be said for that
That words and audio just can't
Describe if you've ever listened to yeast radio
Then you know what I'm talking about
And then I finally
Completed my
My the integration of the blackberry into my life
Of course all of my
Contacts and address books had been
Saved and synced in a million places including
Dot Mac and Apple does that so well
You know you just connect up your iCal
And your address book and it sucks in everything
It had reconciles all the double entries
And then you I bought the was it the the blackberry pocket Mac
Software
And installed it and it basically synchronized everything
Had to had to fix one or two
Phone numbers that didn't carry over the
We're already in the device that just didn't get merged and it's perfect
So yeah, you hear it the birds are singing it's beautiful weather
And we've got some promos
Why listen to the NRKX podcast?
Well, it's funny without being comical
If you're looking to classify this podcast
I wouldn't put in the comedy
Don't don't know how it's comedy man
Oh, why?
What do you mean I put it under?
Tragedy
To have a category for graduate
We can create one just for us
It's sexual without being sexy
You know one hand on her pants
You know the glasses are off so no shit now
I look fantastic. I look like Robert Rudd for now
You know and she's a fucking goddess without the glasses on
Stop looking my balls
She's back at it
It's sad without being pathetic by the way. I live in a tool shed
Did I tell you that?
It does
Absolutely true. It's not a lie
Matt House. I tell people I live in the guest house
But that's bullshit
If you're shed friendly
Yeah, I tell you what
I've gotten no complaints from the chicks that I've banged in the shed
That's the shit
They kick him over more
It's political
Without being politically correct
What gets me is that?
The other day on the news
I saw that this fucking shit eating grin on his face
What that what that grin is saying is
You know what?
Don't fuck around
We're fucking you over that
I'm gonna get away as the truth
Some of these people are cockroaches
And they operate in the shadows
And it's stupid without being idiotic
I'm a little lishy with a little more
I'm irrect
Oh my god
That's a man's man
There was one
That furry fucker
Yep
It's faggy without being homosexual
So come on down to nkx.us
Where we've got great deals on honor
Reason
And integrity
And our 1,000th listener
And we'll throw in some laughs for free
We've been when bamboo job man
They can close the window and drive well
That's right
And rkx.us
Where all our pets
Are have all
Now how do you misinterpret that?
Yeah, I'll tell you how you misinterpret it
You want it to mean something else
So you decide it means something else
This is gas blast or mic
And you're listening to my daily source ghost
I'm a surprise
I'm sorry
Adam
Is a parent you probably understand this
Help
They're taking over
I'm not sure we can take anymore
I'm sorry
Seriously
If you're looking for another podcast
To recommend for some family friendly entertainment
Please include the Love House radio podcast on your list
I a father of two boys
One who will be five in November
The other who turned three in June
Share my thoughts
From the ups and downs of raising the two boys
And things that are going on
And just give us a place for
Meet event
And for people to share some of their suggestions
Or event themselves
And we usually follow the second half of the show up
With some potsafe music
So that everybody can relax and enjoy that
So
Anyway, just wanted to add something to your list
Of the mommy cast and the daddy cast
And all that
So please give us a listen
Thank you
You can find us at lovehouseradio.com
And you can search for us on iTunes
Look for a lovehouse radio
I have some possum
Great
See
Listen to my daddy
I can't do my daddy because I don't
You will be assimilated
Awesome dude
Very, very cool
Today
I guess
It wasn't that much of a secret
Because
Yahoo would send out emails to a number of podcasters
This podcasters are not included by the way
That they were going to start pointing to podcasters
From different Yahoo media properties
And today it's official or I guess it went official
Yes, they podcast.yahoo.com
Yahoo has built a directory of podcasters
Which is
Fuh
Phenomenal
Once again
Another boost in distribution
I love this
I love it so much
So you know that today I'll be
I'll be checking out the server logs to see what the increase is
This is great
You know, the more companies that come online and offer access to podcasters
The better
I really, really, and dig in this
They've done something so to actually pretty smart
I like the way
I like their way
They're trying to stay away from a lot of the technology
And just driving people into listening to podcasters
Because I think that that's really
It's almost like, you know, how Tevo started
And Tevo had this huge budget
Marketing budget
They're like $300 million
And I think they spent most of the $300 million
Trying to explain to people what Tevo was
And you know, so they wound up
I don't know if that's the beginning of the end
But they took investments basically from all the major mainstream media
Companies, from the television companies
In all the fact kind of control what Tevo does
I think this is just the perception I have from
From now it'siders view
Where really, if you just given away
Thousands of Tevo's
People would have understood it once they, you know, because you know how Tevo works
You know, you install it and install it kind of like a BCR
And everyone can, I guess, kind of understand what the wiring is
And then you use it and then you just go, oh my god
You know, and oh, please, it's the trial period over
No, you can't take this away
I can't live without it
You know, once you've done live pause and you've figured out how to record stuff
And the interface is, I think, pretty damn easy
It's not advanced, but it's very easy and it works well with a remote control
So I think that's the way we should continue to consider promoting podcasting
It's just listen, go ahead, just listen to one
Forget about all the, you know, the synchronization part and RSS
And just listen to it first
And tell me if you're not completely blown away
By the freshness of these, these programs that you hear that you don't want more
And you don't want to, you know, eventually, of course
Figure out how to get it onto your MP3 player on onto your iPod
And you'll want to manage your subscriptions
Because you love this stuff
That's the way we should be approaching it
So tip of the hat to Yahoo for, for jumping in
And it looks like, yeah, it looks like they've really done a very good job
I haven't quite seen how they output their directory yet
And I presume they populated that from, from different sources
Including indiepotter.org
So I'm wondering if they have an OPML version of their directory on the back end
Which would make it even cooler that we could start integrating that into applications
And I'd love to have a feedback because, you know, we basically may not have everything we want in indiepotter
That's a possibility
That's something that Apple, Apple didn't do
Or has not yet done provide the directory structure on the back end
So I'm maybe just haven't seen it yet
And over the weekend, I actually was funny because I was thinking about calling Ron and saying, you know, dude
It's about time for another strategy cast
Now that we kind of have some of our strategy together
And we're actually building some pieces of our network
Well, we've been building for a half a year or more
Yeah, we've really got people in building some technological pieces of our network
And then I came across a podcast called On the Record
I think Eric Schwartzman is the host
And he was interviewing Ron and I was listening to it and like, you know what?
I'm just going to use some of the strategy cast space to let you listen to
A piece of this interview because it's, it's viewed as well it's right on
And also Ron sounds, you know, little feisty in angry
And I kind of like it when he's like that, check this out
As alienating as it may be to viewers
The mergers and consolidations that we've seen in the media world
Do play a role in what gets covered and what doesn't
I mean, I was recently watching
I think it was the early show with Harry Smith, which is CBS Network Morning Show
And they had a technology reporter on
He was demonstrating where's, you know, new technology things that you can buy
One was a portable DVD viewer
And you could load DVDs into it and take it with you on an airplane
That type of thing and he sort of said he sort of sluffed it off
But he said, oh, you mean you could put an entire season of Spongebob on this
That was Harry Smith's question to the tech reporter
And the tech reporter said sure and they moved on
Now you and I both know that CBS is owned by Viacom, Viacomones Nickelodeon
So that was very calculated that comment by Harry Smith
And as we've seen in the world of syndicated television
If you're an independent producer in our days
If you can't get distribution
Because the studios would rather
Make their station groups take a program that they're bringing out of the hopper
Rather than a program from someone else that could be less profitable for them
If it goes than something from their own studio if it goes
And in your strategy cast you guys when you guys were talking
I think it was Adam who said one of the ways that we build audiences for our podcast
Is by getting covered in magazines
So I guess my question is there a risk
And that you guys are sort of building this new media can glamour
But you don't have a sort of a traditional media partner
Well the chokehold look look look at what you're saying
You're saying that
That media which is about
They should even call it the media business
They should call it the frequency and infrastructure business
You know we've got a channel we own it
We have a chokehold on the content that goes through that channel
Our barrier to entry
Okay, our barrier to entry
Is that no one else has this frequency
That's that's the logic of radio
Television had that logic until cable
As soon as cable opened up the so-called unlimited channel universe
A few bright companies said wait a minute
Here's a here's a channel that came out of nowhere turner communications
Now it's said wait a minute
And 11 o'clock at night
There's three stations
And they all do the same thing at talk show
I'm going to offer an alternative
I'm going to buy a bunch of old movie
Don't care what they are as long as they're not talk
And I'm going to stick it up there
That's the birth of turner communications
Can you believe it? One little idea
How viewers might want something else
And it was very easy for them because the viewers were having
Only one thing jammed at their eyes
An audio is playlist and formats right in Jack
You know or or soft listening or whatever it is
Viewers are hit listeners are hit to that already
So so the idea of protecting
Your turf up till podcasting
Was on the on the frequency only infrastructure
You know on that and you and you
No matter what you find a lowest common denominator
And you strike costs down
And you put crap out there but people have no alternative
The delivery of crap against no alternative
Is what's driven the media industry for the last 20 years
Now
The argument of podcasting is
Can we have a source of independently created art or content that is competitive
Competitive with anything else that's out there
And the answer to that is a resounding yes, that's step one
That's before time shifting or RSS or any of that other crap
Can we make content this is good is what's out there in audio the answer is yes
Can we make music as good is what's licensed and limited the answer to that is yes
We got those two things going for us now
Our listeners in
Saciated with great listening alternatives the answer to that is no
What technology is out there that can able us to take this great shit that we can create and get it to those listeners who are interested in it
That's that's what happened
We did not invent a demand
We just enabled great content to be created and be delivered
It's much much simpler than trying to explain kind of what happened with the internet and social cocooning
2.0 and 1.0
It's without trying an entire media industry
Conspired against itself to create willing listeners wanting to do something else
It's a beautiful thing
Hot show content that will make you squeeze the dog and burp your mother
When you walk in the door and you change your shoes
Switch to a sweater and said how do you do neighbor
How do you do
I remember the look in your sparkling eyes that's clearly
I love you don't you love nice neighbor
You saw me looking at you
Open to picture
Up on the wall the ice tree
Standing on the merry-go-round
Spinning away, darling
Ooh, darling
Where do you go today?
Well, we've made the sand
And when we were walks in the park
You were a gentleman
We were home before the dark neighbor
Speed delivery
Let's feel it
Share a rocket show
It's out of backup
While lady and lady give him the eva
Our neighbor
You never had to that way
In the whole world
This and this only one me and in your world
I was happy to be your neighbor
Home in the world with lady I Berlin
Lady I Berlin
She was so pretty
I came home today
With a wave on my mind
Life isn't simple anymore
But I know where I can find you
He said there's only one me and in your world
I was happy to be your neighbor
Home in the world with lady I Berlin
In the whole world
This and this only one me and in your world
I was happy to be your neighbor
Home in the world with lady I Berlin
In the whole world
I was happy to be your neighbor
Home in the world
With lady I Berlin
She was so pretty
Thank you for
From the pod safe music network
LeCivius Bitties
And neighbor
Which is a song about the passing of Mr. Rogers
If you listen to the most recent Bittie cast
You get the whole explanation up front
That was live by the way
Cut those girls are good
I love them
I love those girls
They're music also available
On the iTunes music store
So check them out
Podsame Music Network
Music.podshow.com
Still a lot of cool stuff going on with the Podsame Music Network
Just what we saw we had over
One was over 1000 artists
Not registered
We were like 8,000 tracks
And I wish I had CC's mail here
I think it was
Over 3000 unique spins or something like that
It's unbelievable
Unbelievable what's going on
I think 3000 podcasters
Now registered
It's really really cool
And I also see I'll do that tomorrow
Reminder
That piece where the BBC used cruise box
To talk about podcasting
Actually I got the whole piece
It's from BBC 6 which is a digital channel
So I'm not quite sure if that probably is a DAB I guess
So they probably have pretty good audience
I'll play that tomorrow
They played a couple of pod safe songs
And you have to listen to it because
They're dorks
And really are mega dorks
And there's a guy here in the UK
Who have kind of avoided
For the ever since he appeared on the scene
His name is Roger Smalls
And he may be a little uncomfortable
Because he seems to be a bit of a stalker
Although he does have a lot of
I think actually inside knowledge of
A lot of companies are doing what people
Or what deals are being made in podcasting
But from time to time he'll send in
Either a voice message or he'll send me
Audio feedback
And it's just kind of creepy
But I want to introduce you guys to him
Because if you don't know him already, Roger Smalls
And in the show notes for today
DailySourceCode.com
You'll find a link there to the show notes
The wiki notes of course he'll be a link to his website
And he has like a photo fan side of me
It's kind of scary
But I want to introduce you to him
Because he's although frightening
Without a doubt he's interested
They're right here
So I haven't been recording this lately
They've been very busy working
But they're in chips this week
And they've been going to the gym
They've been quite a lot
It's been pretty good though
They're the gym
Because I started working together a little more
And getting at my confidence
I'm also losing a little bit of weight which is good
As I was seriously considering light perception
But well until I saw the price anyway
And now I've got a little tips for you all
It goes to gym
Just to meet girls
Now when you start up any exercise machine
There's actually typing in age
You wait and you're stamina
Which is kind of like what they do
And all those internet teaching websites
I'm always using
So trick is to get on the treadmill
Test an anti machine
Where there's lots of pretty girls sitting around
And then it's just a case of waiting for one of them to have fun
But typing all that particular
Listen to the machine
Friend wants to see
Now unless you really suspect
You don't want to think anyone about that
Just leave me all of you like
And a good one of the priorities
Like an old woman's equivalent of a date rate drug
And I use it to entice your men back to their chances of accommodation
Not that I'm first in 90
It just been nice to get something a bit younger and firmer
Now what's when the type in how much they weigh
Because you'll find there's a lot more accurate
Than trying to gauge how fat they are
And then big cognitive yet
Now the trick is to use information
To start the conversation with them
Because then you know how old they are
How fat they are
And how much they are
And how long they are left in the sack
For example
If a type in that they're quite heavy
Then you can start the conversation
By mentioning how soon they are
That way don't take it as a compliment
And you can use their age as a good conversation
Start too
I said to this woman last week
Hello name Roger
Let's just say you were born in the late 1960
What she played with decades before
Then
I don't think she knows talking about that when the mention
The Beatles and give me Hendrik
So she walks away
But never could take the start
At the gym to talk to girls
Is the steam room and the sauna
Now the ones that we're the keenest
Are usually very up to themselves
And aren't talked here
You know the dinbos
They're so often you find a nice thin one
Where in the swimming costume the friendliness
And this one girl at the way he came cold
Leaves that
And we got chatting about music and poetry
And murders mystery
I don't think so
But the only trouble
Is that you can't let you sit in the sauna
Two long talking to girls
To get really hot and you end up looking like
Dr. Zoe's bag
And it makes you skin
Or she'll fall down like a raisin
Now I'm going to keep going to the gym
Hopefully you soon
One of them will ask me out on the date
But well I'm now
I can't record any podcasts
So I'm trying to do some more
When everyone's back up all the day
And I don't keep having to do the shift work
All the time
But for now I'm just back to work
And so goodbye
Adam Curry
Should've said
Hey Adam this is Mary
And this is Carla
And we're the stars up
But Mary and Carla show
We are at Mary and Carla.com
And what's the show about
It's two twenty-something sexy girls
Who talk about whatever's on their mind
And that often includes
Boys, sex, rap music
And movies and TV
And whatever we did on any current day
We love your show
And we want you to know
We're not nerds
As a matter of fact Adam
We don't know it
RSS feed from our tight little asses
But damn we are inspired by the whole podcasting world
And it really gets us hot and bothered
To purr into the microphone
Adam
Listen to some exciting clips from our recent shows
I'm serious but all I want to do for you
I don't want to do
All I want to do for you
So we want on your daily source hoders to please check us out and give a girl a break, or at least
a few more dance subscribers on our feed burner length, I don't even know how to feed
burner ants.
They know me either, so when we know it's hot, check us out in iTunes, just search for
Marion Carla with a can, or go direct if visit MarionCarla.com, and whatever you do, don't
forget our initials.
Okay!
We love you Adam!
And whatever you do, whatever you do, don't miss us live in our video podcast right now
and iTunes.
Check us out, baby!
Hey, it's Jo Dion, I'm watching the movie Flight Plan, I'm seeing it because I heard that the
flight attendant unions were upset about how the flight attendants were portrayed in it.
And they're calling for a boycott, I know it's ironic, seems to be if you don't want
someone to see anything you should just not talk about it, or maybe go on TV and
tell everyone how it ends.
Anyway, I'm conducting a poll, if you saw the movie called 3-2-3-2-8-4-5-1-0-4, and leave a message
with your opinion.
Do you think flight attendants are portrayed badly in this movie?
Was this boycott warranted, or officially?
Did you see it despite the boycott, or are you not going to see it because of the boycott?
Do you think flight plans should be two words or one?
It's in German, I think up at the wrong movie, I think I want to see flip-flon.
Skype me at Joe Podcastor or call 3-2-3-2-8-4-5-1-0-4, I have to go now, they're throwing
a popcorn at me, wait, that's an M&M, I like M&M, right back.
Do you see it?
Go ahead
Do you see the power of a-
Hey, it's backwards and forwards.
No, I do.
Yeah, right.
You're listening to the Backtracks podcast
exclusively on the daily source code without I'm curious.
Hey Adam.
Yeah, I'm ready as always.
Get right into this week's quiz.
Okay.
Are you ready Adam?
Yeah, yeah, I'm ready.
Rock it, okay.
Here we go.
Number one.
I got it.
Chinatowner.
Nothing compares to you.
Here at a million times.
Time's up.
Number two.
Just another manic Monday.
I think.
Wrangles.
Time's up.
Number three.
Is that Sheila E?
Oh, she...
No, that's ready for the word.
Shh.
Time's up.
Okay, here the answer.
Let's hear it.
Number one.
I nailed this one.
Nothing compares to you.
My friends.
Where's the boys?
And here's number two.
Check us.
Yeah.
Manic Monday.
Number three.
The glamorous life.
That's what I did.
She like it.
Yeah.
It's a glamorous life.
So how did you do Adam?
Three, man.
I got three out of three.
Okay, Adam.
Here's a bonus challenge.
Oh.
What do all of these songs have in common?
Uh, all female lead singers.
Of course.
Time's up.
They were all written by friends.
Thanks for joining us on this backpack.
Time's up.
You can visit Backtracks podcast on the web at
Backtrackspodcast.com.
Catch you next time.
Backtracks podcast.
Spin it back.
Inivelling.
I know, I know, I know
I say, yes, I say, I know
I say, I know, I know
I know, I know, I know, I know
I know, I know, I know
I know, I know
I know, I know, I know, I know
I know what money they're thinking
I know, I know
I know, I know, I know, I know
I've been watching like a hole in the sun
In the sun, from my brain
When I found a ship with me to open it
And no, please, please
We don't look here, but we don't understand
When she found a ship with us, go
I've been holding back with a ship
I've found a ship to open it
And no, I've found a ship with us, go
They've found a ship with me to open it
And no, please, we don't know
When she found a ship with us, go
I've found a ship with us, go
bing her Gottmark, right in
Snow Bund, ciggy Neredened
Surprised so tight, tell me where that's all I'd crash
It's a beautiful, with some of these mashups, are really a whole new piece of art.
Whenever I hear that sacks from George Michael's family's whisper, I always think of
a particular girlfriend.
It's just at the end of the pirate radio days.
Ben Lebronth did that.
He mashed it up in 2004.
It's a Liya, somebody's whisper, of course a Liya mixed up with George Michael.
And his careless whisper.
It's funny because I hadn't spoken to Ben in quite a while, and I mentioned him on the podcast.
I played someone sent me a mix that he had done, and then he just sent me a quick email.
He said, with a link to this song on his on his site, which he'd put up and he, you know,
Ben, so he's so precise and so secure.
He said, let me know when you have it, and then I'll take it off.
But he said, I could play this one in the show, and I really appreciate it.
Ben, you are the OG, man.
Really, really are.
When it comes to mashups and mixes, kind of just doing it since, you know, 1980, probably.
I think we started on the radio show in 1982, and he was doing grand mixes and remixes
and mashing stuff together.
Awesome.
Okay, Doki.
So the start of a brand new week, as I said, have yourselves a really good one.
Why do you know what's going to happen Wednesday and Thursday?
My sister's coming.
She's coming Thursday.
So I'll get her on the show.
That'll be fun.
Tiffany, she's a hoot.
You'll like that.
And I'll be back tomorrow, right here.
Stay subscribed to everybody.
Thanks for listening.
Bye-bye.