Hi everybody, it's the Daily Source Code for what are we now at? Wednesday, at least this
will air, that is air in quotation marks on April the 13th, 2005. I'm in my hotel room
at the Waldorf Astoria in New York and it is now quarter past 10 in the evening. Another
stellar day here in the city, I've got to say the energy of this place is just so amazing.
It's good to be back in New York. I almost want to say a great place to visit, but you
wouldn't want to live here, but I wouldn't mind living here again. It's, it's, uh, man,
everybody. So energetic, the streets are just filled with people who want to get shit done
and are going somewhere and are doing things and everybody's gone an angle, which is
always nice. Um, oh, second. I'm, uh, on the I River set up right now with the wireless
microphone set. And I was thinking, what could I do for a podcast? I'm in the bathroom
right now. You can probably tell the difference in acoustics. Um, so for those of you who
are new to the source code and new to the sound seeing tour scene, uh, my set up is a wireless
microphone set. I've got the, uh, the lavalier microphone on. And I've got the, uh, the transmitter,
uh, pack on my belt. And I've got the receiver. Actually, it's in my left hand right
now. Uh, the receiver goes straight into the lining, put of the I River. And, uh, this
is what I've used many times. You can, it's almost like a phone call. When I'm on the
phone, I'm, I'm one of those people who likes to pace around and walk while I talk.
I wonder what, I'm sure there's someone out there, some psychologists who can explain why
some people like to do that. Anyway, um, one of, uh, our bokeh associates, uh, stayed over
an extra night here in New York, he's from D.C. Brian. Uh, and, um, his laptop broke. So I've
given him the, the tablet. So he can use that to do email and spreadsheets and God knows what
he wants to do with it. Download porn. It can just open up my hard drive. So, um, I don't have
all my, uh, all my jingles and sweepers and all that stuff all lined up and, uh, and all the promos.
So if you're going to do something a little different for tonight, um, also, we had such a long day.
It started with an 815 breakfast meeting. Man, I haven't done one of those in years. It was
royalty hotel. I don't know if you know it in New York, but it was great to start off, you know,
power breakfast and then meeting the meeting, the meeting, the cab to meeting and met a whole
bunch of great people, lots of people very enthusiastic about podcasting in, uh, in New York.
And of course, uh, as I've explained before, you know, we're, we're Madison Avenue, uh, the
generates. So we've been meeting lots of advertisers and people who are interested in what they
can do with podcasting. Um, so I thought that what we do is we do a sound scene to
the hotel and actually it wants to do an elevator cast. Um, elevators are interesting. You know,
usually people look at the numbers, right? Look at the floor of the run as it counts down or counts
up. And, uh, if there's more, you know, if people come in in a group, they'll talk amongst themselves,
but lots of times it's just silence and all kinds of different things. And if you really are
listening to what's happening, um, you can hear interesting stuff. So I figured what we do
for the next 30 minutes or so. Also, we just had a great dinner, um, at, uh, home and I brought a
card with me from the restaurant. Let me just grab that from my back pocket. Where do we have
dinner? Bellini, which is on 208 East 52nd Street was just phenomenal. And, uh, Ron, who keeps saying,
he's not snobbished about wine, but he is, uh, ordered a fantastic Italian red wine. And I'm not
a drinker at all. I think most people know, uh, who listen to this show that, uh, I like to smoke my
poisons. Uh, so I'm, uh, I'm a little slow in the speech. So I think what we do is we'd, uh,
run the hallways a little bit, um, ride the elevator for maybe a half hour and, uh, see what we bump
into. And if that's too boring, we'll go into lobby. And we'll just see if we can, uh, get some nice
sounds from the lovely Waldorf, a story in New York City. So let me get everything prepared here.
First of all, me do that. Okay. Now I'm going to remove the headset. There we go. So now I can't
hear myself. I'm just making sure that I river is in the lock position. So nothing goes wrong.
I'm going to do it. I'm going to put the receiver. Actually, I'll put the receiver
and I river into my, hold on. Let me not put it in my left pocket. That's where the cell phone is.
In case I need to talk and there are people around, I will just grab the cell phone real quick.
Okay. Carefully slipping the I river into my pocket as well. Okay.
There we go. Now I'm going to note the time. So 10, 21. So let's say it's 10, 22. So I started
10, 20. So we'll go until at least 10 minutes to 11. And I hope you enjoy the, the sound scene
tour and the elevator cast of the Waldorf story. Let's see what we come up against. Let's see if
we can get any conversations. See if we actually all grab the phone as I walk out the door here.
So I, this is our, this is what we do when we actually heard magic do it the other day when
she did a cast of a target. You do feel a little bit self-conscious when you're doing this.
So I'm on the 15th floor and walked out of my room and just heard the door close.
I'm going to left here past the ice machine and we're going to go on the elevator and let's just see.
There's usually a lot of people going up to their room at this point. The American paper
and forest association is holding a conference in the hotel. So maybe we'll hear some interesting
conversation about paper. So hang right towards the elevators and the minute there are people in
the elevator. I'll stop talking and while I'm alone again with you guys we'll talk again.
So here we are. Getting into the elevator down to the lobby. Hopefully we'll pop up against somebody
12, 11, 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3. I'll have to get off when we hit the lobby.
Otherwise people think a very strange just riding the elevator up and down.
Okay. So a very fast elevator.
I'm walking to the lobby for a second here.
We're now in the lobby of the Waldorf. That's why I'm behind these guys.
This will be fun. Let's see if we can follow their conversation. Bear with me now.
We leave them by. We lost Chuckie too. Okay, so unfortunately for those guys weren't going
up in the elevator. So we'll just wait here. Some people are going to ride up.
There's a guy in the phone. Let's follow him.
I don't have a car for you. I've got a couple of essentials.
Cell phone. What else? Toothbrush. What else do you need, right? You with the paper guys?
Is that me? Good night.
Okay. When we started with the conversation, actually this elevator is a little bit too fast.
Okay, I take it up to 15 and then we'll have no one's there. We'll go down again.
No, he didn't. He didn't. No, he doesn't hit. Okay, El. There you go.
14, we're stopping. Let's see if someone jumps on.
It caused briefly and just kept on going down. Man, learning a lot about the elevator here at the
Waldorf. Okay, it looks like we're going all the way down to the lobby. So, good try.
And we're back down in the lobby.
Okay, we're going to follow these people back on the elevator. See where they're from.
Yeah,
I, dude, but I was there a little bit a little bit.
Good night, floor.
Good night.
Okay, they weren't very talkative.
Guess what? We're going back out to 15.
I'm getting dizzy already from this riding the elevator stuff.
Hi, sir. Going down?
It's busy tonight, huh?
Yeah.
Every day, the board office is always busy.
It's crazy.
There's a lot of people from outside the country, just out of town.
Yeah, over, yeah, there were competitions, yeah, beer,
on the time of your competitions.
The American Forests and Paper People?
Yeah, Paper People. They're living tomorrow.
Are they nice? The Paper People?
No, I'm nice.
I'm not.
It's lovely, sir.
Thank you very much. Good night.
So I'm here in the lobby.
I'm just going to stand here for a couple of minutes and see if we bump into
another group that we can follow in.
I just kind of wind no shop.
I see three light expensor shops here in the Waldorf.
You want some bling, man? This is the place to come for your bling.
Some of the conversations are just absolutely hilarious when we listen to them.
So just to throw everybody off track,
we're going to walk across the lobby for a second.
And then we'll walk back and see if we can find another group of people to
ride up with. Again, see if we can strike up conversation.
I'm noticing that the elevators here are extremely fast,
which makes it a little difficult to talk for too long.
But there's also a couple other elevator banks.
Maybe I'll try some of the other ones.
I could also hang out in the bar, but I really want to try and
keep it going with the elevators.
By the way, in the hallway here at the Waldorf, this is beautiful.
It reminds me of home actually, it's a Louis Cutters table with beautiful flower
arrangement that they cut fresh today.
Look at this, there's a whole movie crew here.
I wonder what the film is.
See if we can figure that out.
Looks like a 16-millimeter set up.
So now I'm at the Park Avenue entrance.
It's a ladies who are dressed beautifully, like Game Outfits.
They're a security guard or a cop in the lobby talking a couple of people.
Nice piano in the background.
And it seems like everybody's on their cell phone here.
Which, of course, could mean, hey, what's this?
WB extras holding.
Maybe we're doing some kind of audition for the WB or for Warner Bros.
But it's just walking here and see what we can do to find out.
This is some kind of audition statement, but it's...
Oh, this is that one.
It's definitely a cattle call.
Oh, they're doing some kind of play.
And then it would be at the...
Mm-hmm.
Yes, they are on the end of the...
There we go.
Are these auditions?
No, they're picking photos now, but people are really on this.
No, no.
And the hotel just curious, nosy.
No, this is photographing here and we're doing a background for a movie or a TV pilot.
Really?
Do you know what the name of the pilot is called?
Do you win it?
Yes.
Okay.
And then it would be exciting.
Well, I don't know, it's late.
Great.
It should be exciting.
Look, look.
Look, look, look.
Look, look, look, look, look.
Are you a principal?
No.
I'm Adam.
I'm dear, friends.
I'm dear.
Yes.
Do you have friends?
So where are you?
Yeah.
I'm a business here in the city from London.
Can you tell me my accent?
No.
Yeah.
Interesting.
The friends say, but it's for the W'd be?
Yes.
All right.
Tell me the B.
What do you apply?
I'm playing a party girl.
Really?
Okay.
You have lines?
No.
Oh, that sucks.
I know.
You got a card?
Are you a bag?
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'm normally pretty full and bust.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
I was not working.
I just got back to Las Vegas.
I decided to go.
Working in Vegas or a party.
Yeah, actually.
I actually did a little bit of both.
There isn't that working.
Was it the celebrity program in Bravo?
Sure.
And, um, oh, yeah.
How are you?
I'm my friend, Richard Bells.
You're a small child.
I'm fine.
Right.
He plays for a picture?
Yeah, of course.
Anyone plays for a picture?
Right.
Yeah.
Cool.
Who is for Julio?
That's good.
No.
And.
Did well.
You've met with a lot of other people in the business.
He was really good.
So the business was not.
That's not.
Yeah.
Sorry.
You can combine it.
It was always nice.
Exactly.
What have we discussed?
It's a miracle of my technology.
Hi.
Good.
Fine.
Thank you for welcoming me.
Hold it.
I know.
It's your card.
Me to get up.
It's not good.
I know.
Birthday girl having to get out.
I feel good.
I feel like.
You know.
Yeah.
To which cake.
No, not enough stuff.
Substance.
And if it's put it on.
I'll be back.
Mm hmm.
So I'm just.
You can go.
I'll bring up your dinner.
I'm going to be.
You can go.
So I'll bring up your dinner.
I'll give up.
Yeah.
I'll be back.
Thank you.
Okay.
That's it.
So.
All right.
So I'm back up.
I'm so.
But that was interesting.
So I clearly.
Clearly, it's an audition for extras and there must be only three, three, four, five, six.
There must be twenty people here standing in line to get the picture taken to be
extras in the pilot for the prince.
Okay.
Say, what, I'm just going to walk out of here and see if we can go find some more people to talk to.
We could, of course, always talk to some of the extras, but they're boring me.
Welcome back into the lobby.
A little time check here, oh man, times flying, we've already been at it for about 15 minutes.
Let me just double check the eye river, make sure we're still recording.
Indeed, actually 19 minutes, so far, go to a lot faster than anything.
Really, the cell phone is just the best cover you could imagine.
So it was nice meeting, dear Dr, from back into the main lobby here.
So, people taking pictures of themselves and the lobby being from habitat on that's a big
deal.
You can take a lot of pictures myself.
Okay, so, back in front of the salini window shops, okay, people are going up in the
middle of the pool boiling.
Good night!
No.
Not recommended, but no.
I don't think you have a card tray for competition, could you give it to me?
Okay.
Okay, so much for that ride.
I guess what I really should do is wait for, how you doing?
Hello.
I should really wait for like a group of people who are already talking to go up to make
a little bit more exciting so we can get some actual conversation
from the maids who just said hi to me.
So let's take another ride down and see if we can catch a group going up.
Here we go.
Waiting for the Vader. These things are so fast.
Okay.
Back down to the lobby.
I wonder how long it's going to take for some of the hotel staff to catch on and think
that I'm a freaking idiot. A Vader fetish.
That's what I've got.
Just love riding the animators.
So if you could beat you and kind of along the floors and other we have now arrived at the lobby again.
So here we go.
Okay. Back down to the lobby.
Walking the other way towards the lex...
I think it's lexing to have on the side of the lobby.
Let me see this.
Let me just check for you.
Yeah.
Lexing to have new entrance.
Okay.
Okay. Let's follow these people up.
They seem to be talking.
Listen to your cool.
Just a hand by.
Okay.
Follow the barrel.
Go down.
You're going to do it.
Yeah.
So have a nice trip there.
See you next time.
You're going to go ahead and then tomorrow afternoon.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
What are you from?
Pointi, t-tea.
Can I..
Damn.
Damn, it really sucks.
The elevators just too fast.
I can't get a conversation going.
So, actually that guy got off on the same floor as I did on 15.
So, we'll ride it back down again.
Maybe we'll go back to the WB casting call
and see if we can strike up a conversation there.
Oh, man, static electricity in New York is nuts.
Okay.
Back down to the lobby.
It's a big little old.
I wonder if there's a camera in this elevator
and they're registering me riding up and down
as a couple of guys in a security booth somewhere,
worrying about what the frick I'm doing.
Lobby, here we are.
Okay, back in the lobby.
And see, probably going to keep it going for another 10 minutes.
What I'll do is I'll wait by the lobby and then when, uh,
the next group of talkers comes through.
I'll just follow him up.
So, right now, walking behind the door.
A couple of the women's beautiful gala dresses.
We're back out through past the flowers,
with the Louis-cut on top of the Louis-cut tour desks.
Back in the central lobby.
Okay, standing here, uh, once again in front of the, uh,
the WB-extra's holding area.
All kinds of interesting people here at this time and night.
Okay, what should we do?
Should we walk into the holding area?
Or should we do another trip on the elevator?
What a horrible time to be doing on additions to being extra at, like,
quarter or another night.
That's pretty intense.
Everybody's on theirself, but let's just outrageous.
Okay.
Okay, well, we're going to walk back through the lobby.
See if we can catch a, um, a group of people who are at least talking,
follow them, ride back up again.
I think I can only do this, we want it two more times,
and then we pretty much done the complete sounds seeing tour at the elevator cast.
Okay.
Well, that was bogus.
I followed four women to the elevator, thought they were all together.
Three of them got off on the 11th floor, one stayed on until 14th.
I pressed 26, I have no idea where the heck I'm going.
So what I'll do is I'll get off here and then ride back down.
Okay, since there's no one here, I'll just hit the lobby in.
We'll go back down. This is a different elevator bank.
The bank that I mean doesn't go above 19, I think.
Hey, that's interesting.
I thought there was no 19th floor on this cab or this car.
What is it? Elevator cab? Elevator car? Elevator car, I guess.
Okay, back down to the lobby. We'll walk across the lobby again,
and we'll wait for the final ride up.
Got the cell phone to the ear once again.
They may just also be a little bit too late.
Everyone's kind of retiring for the evening, either that or the just going out.
Nope, nothing going on.
Nobody and nothing. It's a baby crying in the background.
I think he's at way too late.
Pause here by the dresser.
I'll follow these people.
You folks here with a convention?
Yeah, we were.
Baker?
Broadcasting business.
Yeah, that wasn't me though.
You too, good night.
Oh, they were nice.
Well, I think that's just about it.
Didn't get too much trouble, didn't get to, you have to too many people.
Please, we got our money's worth out of the elevator.
So I'm back on the 15th floor.
Back to my room.
Yeah.
Okay, that was almost a pretty lame mistake that I may just there.
Talking to you guys and around the corner and someone can the other way.
That didn't mean like I was from freaking Mars.
Okay, so we're almost back at the room here.
Get my key.
So it's almost been exactly half an hour.
Okay.
Here we go.
All right.
Well, I hope I didn't bore you too much.
We didn't accomplish as much as I hope we would have.
We had a couple of conversations with him folks.
Tomorrow is a work day in the city.
We've got a conference room and a white board and some stuff.
So it won't be quite as intense as the past couple of days.
So I'll be able to do a quote unquote regular source code with promos.
And actually, note I've mentioned that I'm staying here in the Waldorf people are
sending CDs up to the room and all kinds of interesting things that I can play on the show.
So that'll be for tomorrow.
Thanks everybody for tuning in.
Hope you stayed all the way through this.
And please stay subscribed.
If you have any comments, add a Maccurry dot com.
The podcast feed is at dailysourcecode.com.
Of course, you can always leave a comment on the weblog at www.curry.com.
I'm going to bed.
Take care everybody.
Bye-bye.