Delta Shara Charly 2100.
It's July 18, 2005.
How you doing, everybody?
Coming to you from Curry Cottage on Monday,
18 July, it's a five minutes past two in the afternoon.
It's the daily source code to show that we try to bring you every weekday.
And you think it about three out of five.
But enjoy an every time I do.
It looks like Europe is getting a cool down.
The heat wave seems to be dying down just a little bit.
We're looking at 23 degrees Celsius today or centigrade.
Everyone wants to say it.
It's nice.
A little bit of sunshine, a little bit of cool wind.
The continent is even a little bit cooler.
So a nice refreshing break from what we've had.
Although the weekend was absolutely stunning.
Man, we have a great weekend or what.
At least here we did in the UK.
So Saturday, I sat inside and worked on pie pod finder episode number two,
which would be released tomorrow on iTunes.
It's unbelievable.
What's really cool is we have no network time that we have to have to adhere to.
This thing just keeps getting longer on like,
oh man, we're almost an hour.
But I think you like it.
So that'll be released tomorrow.
And yesterday we had some guests over.
So we hung out a little bit when in the town.
It was nice and quiet because the big deal fest was taking place.
Gilfest is a big music festival in Gilford.
I think takes place every year and status quo were one of the headlines.
It was very cool.
And nice dinner last night and rested up.
Well, went to bed a little bit too late.
But we're ready to crank it out for you.
I've got all kinds of promos, pod safe music.
News about the pod safe music network.
And actually have a backtrack podcast.
So stay tuned for that as we roll out the mash up for it today.
Bangers and mash.
Calling it bad.
So scum.
And he can't stop but stop.
Holding up to forever your group.
We don't think it all have been right here right now.
I'm going to welcome you all to have fun.
Now he is.
And it's good to talk.
I make it to my new meeting.
So take your time.
Grab a train.
But we got food to see it.
Now we're down to get your news.
Please give my head.
People see my name.
There's more.
They make it.
And they mean it.
From the future.
From the new division.
You know what?
Even you can read it back.
And your little life.
Or she has broken it more.
Hey man.
A blessing on her head.
Say again.
And I've been.
On that topic.
We got it in agreement.
I never went in front of my challenge.
Never been.
She been.
We got it in agreement.
We got to get it in agreement.
We got it.
We got it in agreement.
We got that.
We got it.
Oh man, I had that cranked up on the speakers here.
I'm sure Patricia heard that downstairs.
Hey everybody, let me see.
I was gonna talk about a couple of things.
First of all, about the new geek toy I got,
the MDA3, which is this PDA phone Wi-Fi Bluetooth Mega Box.
Spend lots of times since I picked it up,
which was, what was it last Wednesday,
if there's, I think, configuring it.
And I, wow, there's a lot of software available
for, for pocket PC, that's unbelievable.
I had no idea.
And there's all kinds of GPS programs.
There's lots of aviation software,
which of course I'm totally big.
And I don't have a GPS unit yet.
I got it, I haven't really hunted around yet.
First thing I did was look for better carrying cases
because it's too big.
It's really too big for a phone to be a phone.
Unless you can slip it into your pocket.
But, I don't know, I kind of like the idea
of, I'd rather carry something around.
If I'm, if I'm carrying everything
and this thing does everything, since it has Wi-Fi,
it's got Skype, I configured the email client
to work with Gmail, which is kind of a mindbender
because you can set up Gmail in different ways.
Excuse me.
One is, and actually this is the way I have it set up.
Once you've accessed your email through the Pop3 client,
then it automatically archives that email
and throws it into, well, keeps it in your inbox, obviously.
Oh, by the way, guys, thank you very much.
Infinity plus one seems to be happening my,
the size of my email box is growing right along side
with the size of the files that are coming in.
I wonder if that's automatic or if that's just
coincidence or if they heard me bitching about it over Google.
So I'm now 96% I'm doing okay.
Thank you.
So now on the Pocket PC, which, of course,
you can use with GPRS as well as Wi-Fi,
you don't want to just pull down everything,
because that means you could be sitting there for quite a while
as it pulls down MP3 attachments or anything like that.
So you can receive headers only on your email.
This is not gonna last too long as GIG talk,
I promise, but I just want to get this out.
So the trick kind of is, if, okay, so you read it
and then you have to, you have to mark it for download.
If it's already downloaded, it'll show you that.
And then if you wanna do something with it,
you gotta reply then.
Because the next time you connect,
because you've read it, it then automatically disappears
from both your Gmail inbox,
as well as on the inbox on the Pocket PC.
So it's a little bit of a mind vendor
or once you figure out how to work with it,
it's really nice.
It's a great way to synchronize your mail,
but it did take me a few minutes
to kind of figure out what was going on there.
And I've used the Skype capability quite a bit.
I like that.
It's just an amazing amount of software
that you can get for this thing.
It's, I have to say, it's pretty darn cool.
And quite a bit better than the last time
I tried out a Pocket PC, which I think was
six or seven years ago, was like an HP,
one of those plastic things.
And, you know, of course there was no,
no network card had used dial up.
And that was just, it was horrible.
I just synchronized with your PC at home
or something like that.
So, they've come a long way, baby.
Have you ever looked at the world
and wondered how things got to be the way they are?
I'm mad to tell a little of Matt's today in history.
And it's my mission to answer that question.
I tried to bring a little light to the events
of the past with a short informative podcast
that will hopefully enlighten you and form you.
And maybe even send you on your own journey of discovery.
You can find Matt's today in history
at opaquelycity.com.
That's OPA, QUE, LUC, IDITY.com.
If you use iTunes, do a search for Matt.
Bring it a little, we'll get straight to your world
with Matt's today in history.
Hi, Joe.
Content that will make you walk the dog
and kiss your mother.
Once upon a time, they'll use the jackroom and a deer.
They transformed me.
Jack, scared.
On the best phone cards, around.
Joyce, I don't even know you don't.
She, you, she just don't call.
Slash soybean, essay, U-E-R-B-E-A-N.
Slash in next door, H-D-A-M-L.
It's absolutely splendid.
Thank you for listening and good night.
Ha ha ha.
That's jack.
I've been emailing back and forth of the jack.
He's 14 or 15.
And his dad won't give us credit card
so that he can register with iTunes
so that he can then actually register his podcast
in iTunes, which is a bummer.
Is that true?
Do you have to have an account with iTunes in order to submit?
I thought you could just submit it without being a paying member
of iTunes or the iTunes music store, not to be short about it.
But I didn't think, obviously, I can't tell anymore
because all my computers already are logged in
and already synced up to the Apple stuff.
So today's Monday, Wednesday, I'm off to San Francisco.
We've got some really exciting news to announce.
Of course, today, no damn announcements.
The NDA is in effect.
But somewhere probably a Thursday or maybe Friday
will be announcing some very exciting news for Pod Show
and everyone involved with Pod Show.
So excited about that and looking forward to a nice trip
over.
I'll be saying, I'm going to take my,
a lot of work on the plane.
I'm going to do the Virgin upper class thing again.
I really did like that.
I was pretty good.
It doesn't, it doesn't compare at all to their cell phones.
Which has, you know, sucks.
And I've moved over to T-Mobile.
By the way, that phone that was blacklisted,
it's still blacklisted, you know?
How many times, well, I called four times,
went to the store once and I forget about it.
It's not going to happen.
They just don't care about me.
So I hope it won't be too long a trip.
I think probably a week or so.
Maybe on the way back, I think actually I have on the way
back, I'll have to hit New York because it's just so much
to be done.
And so many people to hook up with who we've been talking
with over the past couple of weeks or pump out past couple
of months actually.
On the way in the source code today,
we've got the backtracks podcast in lieu of a young
bullet hit test, spoke to Jan over the past week.
And he's kind of got other like nine weeks
that he's in this rehabilitation place.
But he sounded great and hey, you know,
he's got his Wi-Fi, he's got his laptop,
he's got his headphone and microphone,
he's got his gas blaster.
So I'm looking forward to probably have another hit test
from Jan this week.
See what else?
Oh, and of course, I news about the pod safe music network.
That's all coming up.
Hey Adam, this is Brendan over at the radio brand
domain podcast at brandomand.com.
I just want to say what's up.
And I love your pod cast when listen to it.
Since I was a back in China in October,
I just recently found out because some guy
was asking me because he's in China now.
He's podcasting and he thought he was the first guy.
The pod cast from China.
And I guess I was.
And I didn't even know that.
So I guess that's sort of cool.
You know what I'm saying?
That's actually interesting.
I just heard that China is starting to really big radio deals.
And they're starting to divvy up their spectrum in there.
So commercial broadcasts are now moving into that space.
It's going to be really interesting to watch because clearly
pod casting was there before, as far as I know,
before a commercial broadcasters.
So this being a, I think, I don't know about China if it's
like Japan, if they're completely digitized.
I don't know about that.
But it'll be interesting to see what goes further faster
pod casting or broadcast.
I'm back in Cali.
So I guess I can't say I'm pod casting from China anymore.
But I was for several episodes.
I recently became the co-owner of a independent record label
found at www.potloxmusic.com.
We support Christian artists who are Christians.
We don't want to have that CCM label.
If you read our mission statement, we're big on.
I don't exactly know what the CCM label is.
But it sounds like maybe there's a little bit of politics
going on in the Christian music scene.
We want to encourage Christians to create their own art,
not try to copy someone else, not try to just,
I mean, I'm sure you know a lot about the CCM industry
and what kind of cliche and crap it can be.
There you go.
No, I don't know a lot about the CCM industry.
I'd love to hear more.
And we want to kind of just encourage artists who are Christians
to make their own art and that's kind of our mission.
And we really want to stay independent.
And we really want to raise pod casting.
I want to create a pod cast for the label.
I'm interviewing some of our artists.
That have recorded with us and spotlighting some of the music.
And I also want to get it out there.
Get out, make a page, maybe, of some pod safe music
for people who put in their pod cast.
And I was wondering if any other tips you had,
I submitted some stuff to pod show,
but I didn't hear back on that.
I don't know.
I'm sure you get a ton of stuff.
So just want to hear any other tips you have
for the label owners who want to get their stuff out there
and embrace pod casting and digital distribution.
And anything else, any other tips you have
because you've been involved in this way long ago
and I have anyway, keep up the good work.
And I'm using a cast blaster right now.
So just out.
Oh, dude, that's awesome.
That goes a long way that point out.
I got the boring right there at my fingertips.
I've also tried out a pod producer.
So I was wondering if you've tried that out
because it's kind of similar to this.
And it's going to stay free.
And this doesn't look like it's going to stay free with.
That's cool.
I like this kind of has a little bit more features.
I mean, it's got the show notes and everything
that you can put in here and other stuff.
But I do like cast blaster.
And I think you're doing some great stuff out there.
Don't let the bass is grinding you down as Bono would say.
Anyway, take care, man.
And I'm glad to hear you were OK after the bombings and everything.
But my hearts go out to all those affected, including you and your family.
So take care, man.
Let me see how to sit.
Stop on this thing.
There you go.
OK.
Good day.
All right.
Thank you very much, Brendan.
Castblaster.com is where we can find the castblaster program.
And of course, anything that you heard in the show today,
you can find links to it in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com or www.curry.com.
Both sites soon to move to their new servers.
The weblogs being set up, Drew Domkis from Don Drew is doing the design for the Curry.com
site, which I'm really excited about.
And the wait until you see the daily source code also sent in just by a listener to the
source code.
So you're going to love that, but just to get all the servers rejiggered.
Now that we have now that the traffic issues have calmed down a bit and we've got our
optimization stuff all working.
We've got some other plans for distribution, which I'm hoping will benefit everybody.
So working on all of that.
And in reference to what Brendan was talking about, of course, we now have the Podsafe
Music Network, Podsafe Music Network.com.
You can also get it to it by typing in music.podshow.com.
It's going great.
And I think that I don't see why we wouldn't accept labels.
So what you should do is probably email ccchapman over accident hash accident hash.com or
info at Podsafe Music Network.com.
I think is also also works and probably I'm pretty sure a cc goes to cc, of course.
We should be able to do that.
We should be able to facilitate labels and we can work with you.
That shouldn't be a problem.
I was looking at the stats that cc sent me over the weekend, and this is up until Monday morning
169 artists have already signed up with the Podsafe Music Network and 309 podcasters.
This is fantastic.
And I've just been breezing through it and totally, totally loving all the new music
is in there.
Just one click.
You know, you get it immediately.
Sample the stuff.
The links between what's being played, where it was played, what shows are playing, what
the top, the listens, the top pod play.
Fantastic.
I'm really enjoying it.
So I pick one, of course, today, which was one of the top rated ones.
So we'll get to that in a second right after this.
So my just got done listening to Daily Search, could number 208 with the feature of the
David course, the interview, and it reminded me of the sort of unique situation.
Hold on a second.
Yeah.
I should have set this up.
The David Coursey interview.
That's what I did on Friday I think.
It was Rob Greenley interviewing David Coursey, the longtime pendant in the technology
press, trade press.
And I got a lot of response to that.
Let's listen to the comment.
We should have it work.
I work for a small media conglomerate in the United States, and I work at a particular TV
station in this media conglomerate that also has a radio station attached to it.
What's interesting is the TV news director represents sort of the David Coursey point
of view, which is I'm a long time media person and trust me blogging and podcasting
is where it's at, blogging is where it's at, Citizen Journalism is an important part.
And it's going to be an important part of our future media sort of set up.
I thought it was interesting, and I just thought I would let you know that I think this
in my opinion, at least the David Coursey point of view is the typical struggle against
a changing market.
These old school news guys can't recognize that the landscape of their future is changing
and they see the change and rather than try and adapt with the change they decide to attack
with the change, call it names, say that it's not called real news, close quote, say
that it's not legitimate, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera, while those like
our radio news director can adapt and change with the changing market.
And they see the need for this new component to the news marketplace.
There's a place for his and journalism for this grass roots kind of journalism in
the form of podcasting and in the form of blogging that goes just hand in hand with
our, our, quote, traditional close quote media outlets.
And I think that those media outlets that don't recognize this are going to have to face the face
the music at some point and either adapt or die.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
His voice, by the way, was changed to protect his identity.
So the person who sent that in was a nonny mouse.
Well, it's going to get interesting.
Rob Greenley ping me after I talked about that interview that he did with David Corsi.
And he of course wants interview me now.
So we'll do that.
We said a date for next Thursday.
So that'll be an IT conversation with the next couple of weeks.
And I'm not looking to pick any fights or anything.
I was just amazed.
It's okay.
Everyone can have their own opinion, but I really thought David Corsi would see that there's
much more to it.
Same goes for Mark Cuban, who also wrote a piece on his web log that said, you know,
podcasts are going to go nowhere.
This is, this is something different.
You know, this is, this is not like web logs.
This is not the same thing.
This was created by listener demand,
not by publishing desire by listening demand.
Of course publishing desire is a part of it because, you know, now that you can do it,
why not?
We might as well.
Listener demand and just really shitty radio for the past 15 or 20 years is really what
created this.
Hey, Adam, it's Chris from financiallypodcast.com.
If you're looking for the latest in student loans, scholarships, financial aid, or anything,
education, finance related, you'll find it on financialaidmodcast.com.
We're in almost daily show.
Sometimes our daily, I know we look at everything in the news.
Some mail calls stuff against our readers questions on the air.
And have a great time, so tune in.
Got lots of positive music too.
You can find us in the iTunes Music Store just so you can find an angel aid.
Gentlemen, let's broaden our mind.
Or just find us on the web and find an angel aid podcast.com.
This is, this is very funny.
Johnny, let us know.
If you like, we're here to give us a shout at 6173815656529.
Very warm here.
Or shoot us an email at financialaidpodcast.com.
Thanks a lot, Adam.
Most of our high spots were coming to us now by TV.
Sirius Central.
But not this one.
Sirius 148.
Adam Curry's pod show.
Experience the unexpected.
Tell the world.
Tell this to everybody wherever they are.
Sirius Central 148.
Hi, this is Bruce Williams from audio to u.com.
We're not another podcast directorie.
At audio to u.com, we control the quality of our content by only working with the best people.
As I said.
Why sing lyrical with Dom Romeo?
You're one of the few musicians who actually has a rhythm of beats named Arthur.
The bow did lead beats.
Yeah, because I was the one who had been invented.
Fuzzy logic.
With Alex a horror off-road.
Well, if they're all heavy and empty or all done in this case.
That's Bible where, but this is email recipient to be where.
And that was any Latin for that.
No, that's right.
Email us.
Beware us.
Fun notes.
Hi, Bruce.
This is punk rock.
Patty Smith was recognized this week with an award.
She was awarded the command of the order of the arts and letters.
Francis highest cultural honour.
Building the pod.
So in terms of building your podcast.
The sorts of things you'll be able to do in audition will be record your voice.
Stand and deliver.
I imagine in stand-up you get to fluff a lot of facts for the sake of the gag.
But when I read your books, you have a very real respect for knowledge.
Where does this come from?
I do, but then a lot of it is also made up.
I mean, I like to.
I don't like novels.
So when you've had enough of the light fluff.
And then you get the good stuff.
Audio to your top.
Hello, this is Franklin McMahon from mediartissecrets.com.
The podcast for the creator professional.
You are listening to Adam Curry's pod show ticket.
Alright, everybody.
Time to crank it up.
We've got some pod save music for you right now.
This is when I checked this morning.
It was in the top 10 of the most pod play pod save music network.com.
Grab them both.
Summer time.
I was young.
I'm talking about the good times.
Just doing it.
Was all we ever cared about.
We had it all.
I'm talking about the good times.
Drinking all day.
Drinking all night.
Dance by the fire light.
Come on.
Because you are the hot air sound.
You know that you are the hot air sound.
Summer time.
I'm talking about the simple times.
Hey, answer the call.
No right, no wrong.
Read me the lies from the all they were told.
Make our way up to Prosper's mind.
I'm talking about the good times.
No reason to fight.
Cause friendly is tied.
And everything is alright.
Make our way up to Prosper's mind.
You know that you are the hot air sound.
Summer time.
I've been thinking about you now.
Sit, sit, call, I've been down.
I used to call, sit, shoot, and jump.
You're my summer time.
You know that you are the hot air sound.
I'm talking about the good times.
You don't go how much
so much
I'll talk to another 5th minute member
ah it's perfect for a day like today
Love it
I'm...is, im gonna be 41 in...
and less than 2 months
oh yeah, 6 weeks, September 3rd
And so that really puts me squarely in the middle of people who are 80's guys, I really love that kind of production
You know get a little stop gap there in the beginning and the reverse stuff. I dig it these guys have got it together
Really do like it. This is your daily source code in lieu of the hit test today. It's time once again for a hit test of a different nature
Backtracks podcast
So you think you know your hits backwards towards
Yeah, right
You're listening to the backtracks podcast exclusively on the daily source code with Adam Curry. You know hey Adam
Hey, how you know what if you change this?
Oh, I don't like changes. So let's get right into this week's quiz. Okay. Are you ready Adam?
Sure. I'm cranking out.
You guys ready? Okay. Here we go.
Number one
Yeah
Right
It's a song Martha Quinn played for a month when she broke up with a boyfriend. That's missing you
Time's up. Number two
Sorry, no clue
Time's up. Number three
Oh, yeah, I know this
This is the same beat forwards and backwards past the Dutch team musical youth
Time's up
Time's up. Okay. Here are the answers. Number one
That's right. It's missing you
And here's number two
Now what the hell was this?
Oh, sorry. We closed our eyes
Go with
No, I didn't get that
Number three
Yeah, sure
So how did you do Adam?
I'm back to out of three
Oh, you enjoyed this week's Backtrack Spotcast quiz
You can visit Backtrack Spotcast on the web at
Backtrack Spotcast.com
Catch you next time
Backtrack Spotcast
Spin it back
Thank you so much. I love it
I love it. Hey, that's it for the source code for today
July 18, 2005
So I told you the pod find your podcast episode two will be out tomorrow
And iTunes if you're subscribed, go come to you automatically
We actually left about two weeks in between
But now I'll be every single week and anywhere between 45 minutes in an hour
Of all the coolest new pod
Not just new ones, by the way
Anything I can get my hands off is
So besides that tomorrow
The official release of the first episode of the Spike Lee Shadowcast podcast
The human human goes on location
To the pre-production of Spike Lee's new movie, which is titled Inside Man
It stars Denzel Washington, Jody Foster, Christopher Plummer
And it's really interesting to listen to Spike
I think you're going to enjoy it
So that'll probably be featured all over iTunes by tomorrow
As well, so be on the lookout for it
The Spike Lee Shadowcast podcast
All right, do you want to send anything in
promo as a podcast that submit at podshow.com
Podsafe Music is podsafeofpodgeshow.com
And of course, mashups mashup and podshow.com
The dating source code.com is where you can find the archives for the show
The latest podcast of course the podcast feed
And then this is my weblog www.curry.com
Or I post a little bit more than just the shows
Put all the crap up there as well
Pictures from my MDA3 now that I know how to get them into flicker
Or getting somewhere with all that stuff
Adam at Curry.com is email address
Your audio feedback is welcome, specifically now the Gmail has started to give me my infinity plus one
Thank you very much guys
Stay subscribed
Another podshow podcast
Stick it in your ear