Geltis Yara Charley 2-7-2
There are no secrets.
Only information you don't yet have.
Now I'm Korean.
16 dollars worth of silk box are shorts wedged in my ass.
And so much sense say it's coming out my ears.
We don't need lost digging prison.
I like to think I'm flying into the toilet.
I'm just taking this battle curry.
November 2, 2005.
Welcome to the daily source code coming to you from Curry Cottage.
And Gilford Suri, I'm in a bad mood.
And it's the bitch cast.
Good morning.
I lost lost the first one by all the tips.
Good job.
We can speak to Trump to fight some bitch out.
We can all day.
Some say they put on tin.
Look up the pen and put it in the neck and stuff with the right now.
I see feminine mowers.
I see him continue to win.
She's on top of my field of pain.
But what's funny?
They're waiting.
And y'all never bless us again.
Jumping.
There's him.
Go back.
Jumping.
Go.
Go back.
Aether.
One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one
, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one,
one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, another, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, one, two, one, one, one, one, one, one, the only one, one, two, one, one, one, one, one,, one, one, one, one, one, two, three, one, it won't come under the heart, the whole, it won't come under, so, and one, this, good, have the word, be well.
I'm gonna spin for it's up
Hopefully it won't be at the championship
I can't stop it
It can't help so well
And I know I'm not far away
It can't have all the games I know
This is the biggest thing
The problem is you've been there
Hold on, you won't mess
Bring us a night dance
The problem is you've been there
Hold on, you won't mess
Oh, it leaves my load
The breeze can draw a population
The river might have been there
And I don't mean no big hits now
But for you to go
I'll go so far
Dream of Galliford and Kesha
Yeah
We're gonna spin it with some full time
You let them over
No, we saw some full
Better spin it
I'll make our money
When time's the press
I knew something was wrong with that
Witness the foreign occasion
Witness the problems with technology
It's just looking at the time
I'm like, huh?
They started a whole new verse there
And I knew it only had three seconds left
Okay
I've got to medicate myself
It's not been a good day
I just was reading an email
This is amazing
Everything's been going wrong technically today
It's pissing rain outside
I've got nothing but angry podcasters
Some of which I'll actually play for you on this show
I've got a ground loop hum
Somewhere that I can't get rid of
And then I look at my emails
I'm during that mashup
And I'm getting ready to pull up my source code emails
And I see my tax lawyer saying
You know, something about taxes
And 11,000 euros
And like, oh my, which, you know, it's like
130,000 dollars
And like, what?
Oh yeah, great
Then I get a fucking excuse me
There will be plenty of bad language in today's show
Not that I can really help
But it just kind of comes out
Okay, so it turns out that I'm actually getting that
That's a tax refund
But still, I'm pissing about
It's, you know, screw money
I'm pissing about all kinds of stuff today
Let me see, let me just tell you what
It's about this house that we have, the cottage
It's, it's picturesque
It's beautiful
The location is almost fantastic
We love the town
Everything is great
It's not quite big enough for us
But that's okay, I mean, it's great
But it's an old house
And the shit's falling apart
I can, I understand
Patricia's frustration
She keeps telling me you want me
This guy's coming on
And we got that guy
We're pairing this, we're pairing that
And, you know, the landlord was so nice
Not to raise our rent this year
Because of all the troubles we've had
I'm sorry, it's just not cut and I want to
Frick and
Reduction next time
So today we had the painter
Painter, painting up the
The spots that the boiler
Created in the ceiling
Because that was leaking
And, and these are all nice guys
By the way, and then the electrician
And then the heating doesn't
Just, it's just one thing after another
And this is not a chief house
It's not cheap
Oh, yeah, it's Wednesday
It is the daily source code
And we got plenty to complain, you know, there's another thing
So Patricia loves to call her mom
And her dad and her sister
And they're all live in the Netherlands
And calling Holland
It's one of the most expensive countries in the world
And you know, there's some kind of monopoly
Going on there and it's messed up
And the prices are not at all in line with the European Union
And they like the gab, you know
They like to talk a lot
Now her parents don't have a computer
And don't have broadband
So, you know, all the obvious things
That you would email me about a got it
Now that's, unfortunately
We don't have that kind of set up with them
But I got a wonderful Skype out
Account for her for Patricia
And I got one of those cordless USB phones
So for her, it's just like a phone, you know
It's great, you can walk around, use it like a phone
And she's very, very patient
Because this thing breaks so often, you know
And then of course it's on
It has to be on the Windows computer
Is there a cordless phone for a Mac please
Please tell me there's a cordless phone for Skype
For Mac
If not, someone
There's a market here, it's, you know
Because the Windows ship, man
Then you plug in, Christina plugs in her webcam
And then that captures all the devices
And then the phone won't work
And then at the end of the day
After I've trouble shot everything
Creating new accounts on the Windows machine
To log in then
It turns out the Skype out balance is toast
You know, and I don't like that
There's a great set of warning lights that goes off
Or a way to auto renew or anything
Smart like that
And believe me, now that Skype has been purchased by eBay
And I got an email from a guy who works very close with the development team
And I can tell you who it is
And I want to embarrass him
But there's no more development going on
Maybe it'll pick up again
But right now that company is completely influx
And then so check this
Doesn't eBay own PayPal
Because that's how I pay for the Skype out account
Every single time you go from Skype
From their upgrade your Skype out account
To the PayPal page
You get the reset your password
And have to reset my password
Every single time
And I reset it to the same thing
And there's no warning about that
Same warning that you've already used this password
Yeah
It's stupid
Oh, hide that shit from
And Windows in general
What is wrong with this
God, I hate it
I just, I really am not sorry
I'm emotional about this stuff
I hate Windows
Live update
And critical update
And rebooting your computer
Stop it
Oh
It looks like this
Windows live stuff might be interesting
So you get all the benefits of
Microsoft Office through web browser
I could deal with that
That would be good
I don't know about that
I mean I'm going to be pretty loyal
To Gmail
But some of that other stuff
Pretty good
It looked like they had an interesting homepage
And the search and stuff
A lot of blogging going on about it
I'm not quite sure what it is
It seems like it might be a suite of stuff
That you can access over the web
Well, that's good
I'm all for that
Then it won't matter what kind of computer you have
That's yeah
That'll definitely do it
Okay
So weather today is
Crapola
It's been raining
Really not nice at all
Patricia's downstairs
Finally I think everyone's gone
It's two o'clock
It's much later than usual to record today's show
And I have, as I said, morning
I've got some more bitchiness coming up
Not for myself
But in the form of one of my fellow pod squatters
We'll get to that in a second
And plenty of email
Let's see
What should we get to first
Luke Renault
Says
Would you be so kind to stop using the ping sound
At the end of the daily source code
I use Gmail Notifier
Whenever I hear that sound
My brain tells me that I have an email
So I rush off to mail and check it
In spite of the fact that
No growl alert box has appeared
Well, you know that's interesting
That is I kind of like that at the end
Because that's
The Chimoo timer is what that is
Find Mac OS X
OS X
Sorry
Got so many emails about
I'm not allowed to say OS X
I have to say OS X
I'm letting it all hang out today
My friends
And it back times
Because I like to set a timer now
And kind of back time to see where the hell I am
And it seems like kind of 50-50 on yesterday's show
People
Everyone liked it with a lot of the pod
Say music
A lot of we're afraid to say
You're not going to move to this format full-time
Are you?
No, no, no, no, not at all
Just didn't have a lot to say yesterday
So why give you a whole bunch of diary of the mouth
When there was a lot of cool tunes
The share
And maybe you didn't like all the tunes
About mashups
Here's another thing I received tons of email about
Okay, bottom line
No, it's not legal
It is completely illegal to play
Any form of licensed music in a podcast
I mean now that there's jurisprudence over this
But common sense tells you that
Why do I do it?
Because it's art
It's beautiful art
It's not a commercial art form
It's people taking
Other is derivative artworks
It's a beautiful thing
We can never get it licensed
And I'll play it until someone tells me
I really can't
And no matter what defense you put up
You can't win against a big lawyer
Stuff
I'm reading this book
Or actually I should say I'm not reading it
Let me get it
To my iPod
I heard a
Let's see
Was it a podcast?
Yeah, I think I'm not quite sure
It was maybe it was on the media
That I heard about this guy
I already heard about the book
Let me see if I can just go back here
And go to my audiobooks
I want to get the title exactly right
Yeah, the future of music
Unabridged
By Dave Cusack and
Gird something
The iPod's not scrolling
Let me see
The future of music
Manif
It says
Dave Cusack
And Gird wool dot dot dot
Okay, so I can't tell what that is
That's unfortunate
Anyway
Very interesting
Let me see
Is it playing now?
Is it stopped?
No, stop, please.
There we go
He made this guy makes a lot of really valid points
About the music business
And he specifically said in this interview
And I'm pretty sure it was on the media
He said
If he's
Predicting the full collapse of the music business
The commercial music business within
12 to 18 months
I kind of sign up to that
That there's already been a real collapse
And he says, look at what's happening
The music business is letting themselves become irrelevant
Because the numbers of people listening to podcasts
And interested in
In music that can be shuffled around and shared
freely and used in other forms of media
Are making their one and a half million songs
Which is all the music services have to offer
Which is all that apparently is valuable
And in music in the world
One and a half million songs
That's it
They're becoming irrelevant
And it's absolutely true
And it's only because they can't figure out
How to license this stuff
I mean how many times we said we'd be willing to pay
To play it on a podcast
He greedy
That's what you are
That's why it's not going to work
And that's why we had the pod save
Music network
Which I'm sure we're talking about a lot today
All right, let me shut up for a second
Hey out there in podcast land
My name's Chris and I do a show called Allcast
Out of Vancouver British Columbia in Canada
Basically in my show is about
Anything and everything that's going on in my life
And then the world around me
It's basically a mishmash of me talking about
News, TV, movies, music, comic books, books
And well, tell anything
I play a lot of pod save easing on the show
And I do a special spotlight every show
On local Vancouver artists
That are trying to break into the industry
So if you like hearing someone
You have to book things in the world
And you like good music
Check out Allcast
At allcast.logspot.com
Or just subscribe and high tunes
So here's an email
Which was titled Living Like The Flintstones
Thanks to Wilma from
Jeffery says Jeff, this is Adam, this is Jeff the podcast listener
Who is the guest on podcast four and one's 100th show
Found a cut up on Delta Sierra Charlie
Using Wi-Fi at a local Panera Bread
They got their power back
I live in broad
Broad County, Florida
Where we were hit dead on by wicked Wilma
That was on Monday, October 24th
Listen, please
Because I'm pissy about a lot of things
Today and we got some pissiness on the way
But it pails in comparison to what is happening
And I'm amazed that I have to hear about this through email
And it's not on television
Because you'd expect it to be there
So Florida was hit dead on by wicked Wilma
That was October, Monday, October 24th
We still do not have power phones
Or running water where I live
And no power or phones at my office
Schools were closed all last week
And this week
Your analysis of life without power
And your apology to Pida
Barely scratches the surface
Suffice to say it blows
Her cane pun intended
And he goes on to say about
What kind of
What kind of damage
And this is really, this is really horrible
Personally, I experienced extensive damage
So my property lost in beautiful old trees
A deck, ironing fence, storage shed
My son's half-pipe skateboard rampy built
That sucks, that bites ass
As well as some leaks and roof damage
From trees falling on our house
Also lost an old sailboat that was washed up
On the rocks and destroyed where
It was kept in coconut grove
First few days we literally bathed in a lake survivor style
And cooked hot meals and cans on a sterno
This is really, really, really messed up
What can we do, Jeff?
Besides, you know, send money to hurricane relief
Shit man, we should go, I mean, that's horrible
That is horrible
So it's been over a week now
Right, 24 plus seven
So it's been eight days
And I wonder if they have power back or phones
And all we see is that fricking fat jerk Al-Roker
Falling on his face, which of course gave me some pleasure
I said, I mentioned this the other day
I met him a couple times, professionally
Working together on stuff
He's a dick
Oh, self-serving
You know, I sound a bit like mad
Hmm, should I be concerned
Hello Adam Madge here
What's again, you've managed to piss me off
To the point where I have to comment on your goddamn show
First of all, you're keeping bitching about how
you can say you won't pay you to advertise
Why the fuck should they pay you to
Sponsor to be a sponsor
When you're doing it for fucking free
Every goddamn day with your goddamn
Sincere bullshit
You know, if they're not sponsoring your show
Then don't fucking mention them every five seconds
Because why the fuck would I pay you
To advertise when you're doing it for fucking free
Every goddamn day
Enough about it
And the coffee's not even good anyway
It's goddamn nasty
But you know, I drink it because it's fast
That's the only reason to drink the shit
Because it's a notch up from instant coffee
And all those people that call him and say
Hmm, Sincere, they're just full of shit
Give me a goddamn break
Anyway, the second thing is
Give me a fucking eye dog too
Huh?
What lesbians don't get toys?
Bye Adam
And from the bloated Jewish lesbians
We go to the bearded lady of Gilbert
Hey baby
And the biggest lesbian
Excuse me
You got to talk into that mic
It sounds like shit
Really?
Yeah, I don't know what it is
So sit in this
It sounds like
Sounds like it is a waterfall behind it
People have been asking about you on the show, huh?
Oh?
Yeah, they want to hear you on the show
They love you
Of course they miss you
Well, that's nice
Yeah
That's nice to hear
They want us to do another one of those music shows
Oh really?
Yeah, where you critique the music
Oh boy
How they like that?
Come on
It was alright, it was good
Yeah, I'm nice
Hmm
You know, I know how it is
I know how it feels
What?
Well, if somebody, you know, says something about your music
I know that
Yeah, I have to like, I can't see you
I can see you
Behind this big grey thing
It's not just a big grey thing
It's the podcast complex
I know
I've been there
Oh, this sounds like shit
I got to fix that
So I was just, today is the
Bitch cast
I'm complaining about the house
I'm about Skype
And about
Yeah
I just bitched about it
To my mom
And she said, no, it's a lovely house
It's a lovely house
Yeah, but it's falling apart
Yeah
And it's not, well, and that's one thing
But you know, we're paying real money to this
Yeah
Yeah, a lot of money
Sox
Yeah, I know
Well, that's why we said we're never gonna
We never gonna buy
Or rent an old house again
No, not after this
We've been in a lot of, you know,
All the whole
Historical
Yeah
With historical charm
Shit falling off
Yeah
Who?
The one in Belgium was 1880
And the one
That house was well put together actually
Yeah, but that
Yeah, but that had been completely
Remodeled
So that was actually good
I got it
Everything was new
But when, when should happen there
I was really expensive
Yeah
Whenever something like that
Open up walls
Do you remember
When
When all the
All the toilet plumbing blew up
Underneath the house
Oh man
Because
Because you
Would empty out the cat box
Into the toilet
Well, not you wouldn't empty out the cat box
Did you do that in that house too?
Yeah, because what you do is
If the cat would do a dumb thing
You'd get your little, little shovel
And pick up your scoop
And throw it into the toilet
And then you flush it
You know, little stone
A kitty lay there
Stone
Right
Pick to that to the pool
Yeah, right
And those would all sit in the bottom of the pipe
And I thought you know
It will nice and clean out the pipes
Yeah, well, I did the opposite
Did not
But do you remember
What I did in America
The pickles
Because you
Thinking it's the same
It's the same size
I'm same shape
The only is not made of mush
It's not made of poop
That would be the difference
And it was totally blocked and blocked
But I liked the thinking
That it's the same shape
Yeah, that's what I said
To the plumber
The plumber said
Why did you put pickles
I said, I want to
You know, I was a jar of old pickles
And I thought I'd throw it away
Don't want to see it anymore
And
You know
Why not that?
Oh man
Yeah
Okay, I'm going to place some
Magis pissed off
It's Steve Jobs
Oh yeah
Yeah, I was listening to
Magis Weinstein yesterday
And
Magis really really really pissed off
Oh
Because you know how on iTunes on the
Like the homepage of iTunes
There's the list all the podcasts that are
Hot and happen and whatever
And he says there's never
Ever ever ever ever been
Yeah, never been a gay
Or lesbian podcast
Featured on the on the homepage
On purpose, you think?
I don't know
Well, yeah, you want to listen
You want to hear this?
Yeah
I don't have another pair of heads
Oh, shit
I'm not prepared
No, it's okay, it's okay
Everything you can't hear
No, it's a whole thing
I'll hear it later
But I believe you
Oh, let's play it
Hey, hun, thanks for coming on the show
You're welcome
I live here, you know
Oh, that's right
Yes
Sorry
This is from the spec
It's a section being featured on the iTunes homepage
Right
And iTunes
We're constantly on the lookout for podcasts that are
Breaking new ground at this medium
Oh, oh
Have new and unusual contents
Or just capture our interest
When do we find them?
We like to feature them on the podcast homepage
Well, there are no sure if I
A ways to get your podcast featured
And no, we do not accept payments for promotion
Yeah, right
There are some minimum requirements
To be featured by iTunes podcasts
Must have colon
M
One in image for image specs
See the iTunes RSS tags section below
Two
I robust an accurate description
Three a proper language category
An explicit tagging
And I would add
General audience
I would add four
A profound and disgustingly
Overt heterosexual message
Because if you're gay
We won't feature you on this shit
And that is bullshit
Have you ever
Ever
Seeing a cue product
A queer kiss
And there are close to 200
Now we're close to 200 I think
Yeah
200 podcasts
Or maybe it's 150
I don't fucking know
But it's definitely over 100
And
Have you ever seen one of them?
One of them
Featured on iTunes
Even though our pod shows are some of the most entertaining
The most creative
And the most popular shows
We've got
You know, of course
Fox and the city
We've got the wander wisdom
We've got the Patrick
Noah show
We've got John on
All these
There's too many to mention
The archer radio
And everything like this
And there's so much
Out there
There's something for everything
We've got lesbians
Now with the lesbian soup
The crash and belly
So much entertaining stuff
Political stuff
Engaging
Intertaining stuff
And none of us have ever been featured on the iTunes homepage
And I think it's because we're gay
And I'm sick of it
And when iTunes first came out
And we bitched because there's no gay and lesbian category
Listen
We don't have any rights in this country
The least you can do is give us a fucking category
And god damn iTunes
Fucking Steve Jobs
You need to learn how to god damn dress
Yeah
Maybe you'll listen to some gay podcast
You learn how to not wear a god damn butt
Turtle neck
And jeans
All the way up to your vagina
Every god damn time you do a gay note
Leave your shirt on
Talk to asshole
Why does every fucking heterosexual
And we're a god damn cell phone on his belt
I've got damn sick of it
I am god damn sick of it
Oh man
Oh man the whole show is like this by the way
I've all the luggage on the waist
I am so fucking sick of it
Take your shirt, add your pants
Stop tucking in your goddamn shirt
And put it all that shit on your belt
It's god damn annoying and stupid
And I'm taking my shirt out right now
And all it does is say I'm a heterosexual jerk
Who's only purpose in life is to get buzzed around by my wife
And repro fucking doce
So stop it already
I'm so fucking pissed at you fucking
Steve Jobs
Fuck you
Yeah right
I can say that
You know why because I spend all this god damn money on you shit
All these q-pots do
At least a third of your customers are god damn thugs and dikes
The least you can do is give us a fucking category
And feature one of our shows once in a goddamn while
Hello
Oh and by the way
Don't think you're off the hook if I'm not talking about you yet
Because you're on the list
Speaking of podcast for one one
Why don't you ever
Talk about gay podcast and held
How about you podcast Ali
What about you
Huh
You got people like Reagan Fox who every fucking month is begging people
The go to that goddamn site he was promoting the shit out of that goddamn site go to vote for me vote for me
Vote for me never once have we had a gay and or less be in podcast featured on podcast Ali either
So what's going on why this why this sort of subtle yet unspoken home of fuck god today over modular home of phobia on
And the iTunes
Oh man, I was laughing. I had a laugh again when I hear that you know I guess it's true you know Madge Weinstein certainly a podcast pioneer there from the early days good times everybody and
And I like it when when magic is really angry because that's when she really focuses in on our targets, man
You know this show and also East radio our broadcast every weekday on serious satellite radio stars 103 channel 103
channel 103 which is right next to the Howard Stern channels. He is two channels. I think and
You know, so people tuning in who who love lesbians which is a lot of Howard's appeal
Yeah, switch over to our channel once in a while. We've got lesbians of the bloated Jewish and very angry variety
Aloha in the house it. This is pico for the Hawaiian concert guide at Hawaiian concert guide calm
We featured the most excellent artists of the Hawaiian islands as they perform off island around the mainland
If you've ever been curious about the uniquely Hawaiian art form then this is the place to be we feature an index of the artists their schedule
Performances with links to their albums take a good look and a good listen. You'll be glad you did
Mahalo and Ahui Ho this is pico for the Hawaiian concert guide
Yeah, Mahalo my Hawaiian concert guide dot com. I got to go to Hawaii again
Boy, I love going up there when they're with MTV one time to cover like a skateboard competition or something. We were baked with it
right now
Oh, remind me
Right after this next positive tune that I'm going to roll out front row, which is the name of the software that the new iMacs
Come bundled with it gives that so called ten foot enter interface with the remote control
So yesterday did a kind of like a shout out saying does anyone gotten that running on any other computer other than a G5 iMac
And oh, I got such an onslaught of email with even with some attachments, which was really really cool
So I've got it running on every single computer in my house now and I can even use it with a different kind of remote control
Which I'll be happy to tell you about
After this one from the pod save music network founded on the homepage today, the miss fits
Here's imperfect harmony
Who are these people?
I hear a lot of good people from me
I hear my living address, my personality
They come out when I'm least in space
People think I'm out of there
I see my face when you first I can't breathe out from the wall
My friends
And me
We're left together and in the weeks of our name
And I am in the wind stream
We're left together and in the week of our name
We left together in the next five
We left together in the next six
We left together we left together in the next five
We lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together and we lived together
All right you're probably sitting there yelling at your MP3 player
going it's not the miss fits not that it can't be you right miss prints with the Z at the end prints the miss prints
In perfect harmony from the podcast music network music dot pod show dot com couple more comments coming up about
the positive music network, but first about front to row which is this apple OS X application
So there's now a hacked version out on the net that's flown around because I guess if you start some hardware
That doesn't isn't compatible or I guess it just says it's I'm not a I'm not a G5 I Mac then
It won't fire up so someone's hacked the application and you can basically run front row and here's what's really cool
Because of course if you don't have the remote control it kind of loses some of the appeal
But you can hook it up to the
salient is salient. It's the salient clicker, which is a Bluetooth application that will allow you to fire apple script
So I
Yeah, so it fires off apple scripts and then you can basically use yourself on cool is that I love it
Very very cool hack. Thank you all so much for and you could just google it. You'll find it
There's a whole bunch of places
We can pick that up and and just the fact and I think that I'm actually gonna set up the clicker stuff
Back at the at the condo so I can operate it with my cell phone as well
I don't always have that remote control around but I certainly do
Have my my blackberry. Oh, it might not work with a blackberry. It has like limited lame-o
Bluetooth support. Oh, yesterday by the way. We went
We went and looked at a diesel. Oh, yeah, so what we're looking at is the
Jaguar S type
I can hear Run Bloom laughing very loudly right now
His wife Marta has an S type and I've berated that car over and over again because
It has a dashboard panel that looks like it's a Ford and of course that is a Ford dash
You know, it's basically the the climate control thing. It's a ugly ugly green LCD screen
To show you how high your fan is or whatever
So they have a new version which has like one big console and it's a touch screen and it has a
As they call a sat nav here or a navigator or GPS navigator
But it all it's also your interface to all the car control so it doesn't look as 40 on the inside and you can get it in some pretty cool
Versions now, you know, I like the wood on the inside that gives that real Jaguar feel and
And it comes in a six liter 2.7 turbo diesel double turbo diesel
Rails thing ruby on rails whatever the hell it is and and producers I think like 250 horsepower
Something like that well, maybe 240 but it's but the that's the brake horsepower
But the torque is it has more torque than the 4.2 liter
Engine the regular petrol engine so I guess the question is
Does anyone have any experience or have any suggestions or ideas about filling that puppy up with biodiesel?
I asked the the sales guy and he went
No, no, we don't really do
Biodiesel engines and he didn't know what the fuck was talking about basically
So I just skipped that I wasn't interested
I just wanted to hear about what price I could get on the car. They're not cheap, but the car, man
It they are kind of nice. It's so it's not too big. It's much smaller
Less powerful than Studio A8 but we you know if you when you said how many miles you think it'd be driving with this car?
You know like a thousand a year
Really not more than that
So a couple people have seen a sense say oh add
On television here's what's cool and this match is probably one of the reasons why I
Keep talking about it besides the fact that I do like the coffee
Now when people see a sense say oh add on television. They think oh daily source code hey now that's a free bit of publicity
Huh like that
And then Christopher Penn writes in and says part of the soundvertizing fell flat for me
Certainly with a logic tech MM 50
He feels it's a really lame product name. It says nothing and when you enunciate it on the show
It sounds about as compelling as reading entries from the phone more
Compare how you enunciate the sense say oh name in the original soundvertize soundvertizing experiment with the MM 50 promotion
That's true MM 50 is a little harder to anchor into your mind
Goes on say MM 50 means nothing could be a part of a jet engine to speak or system a deld a door dildo no one knows
Why do you want to make a suggestion to your partners a logic tech to come up with a stylish name that sounds good
Why do tech is an unfamiliar with stylish naming thing that denobo keyboard system had a very slick name
They they could play up for that audio novo or pod novo or something like that. No, that's pretty good idea
And while I was thinking about that
Here's one for you so we have the eye dog which is one of the sponsors of the pod squad or of this show and a couple other shows
And we've talked extensively about the eye dog. You haven't seen it you can just click on the link to the eye dog
And the show notes the banners are all over the place podcast alley has him and then we have two other things
So it's the MM 50 from logic tech and then something else cool. What's I haven't tried yet
So I can't really tell you how how they are but when I get back to San Fran
I'll start talking about him the
Logitech Bluetooth headset which is a Steve Gilmore actually using he liked him once he got him out of the
I heard him talking about him on one of his shows on attention tech
So I haven't actually opened the box yet
She's Steve great endorsement but he's come around and he does like I saw him using him the other day
During our we call our food bar Friday, which is our kind of end of the week drink at pod show HQ
So how about this?
I'll give away my personal MM 50
We should of course I'll have re-planished but
Or yeah, I'll give you a new one
how about making up a very cool
funny
different
reinventive ad
That would fit within this podcast for the MM 50 or the eye dog or what either one is for
You know, let's try and change what advertising is can we still make it entertaining for the listeners of this particular show
and still sell some product at the same time. I'd love to hear about it so
Maybe I'll do
Well, depends on what I get you know if we get some cool ones in I'll play a couple of them
But we'll choose a winner somehow or maybe only the winner gets played and
I actually is probably it would probably be good if if we have all the crappy ones too
Send this get creative help me out here. Let's figure out how we can make advertising more interesting, please
We have
Man, I don't have time to do everything. I wanted to okay. I want to do some promo because I was kind of light on the promo yesterday
I'm second
Hey, this is Darrell Falon the law student at lawschoolpodcast.com
I'm a first year law student at University of Missouri came to the city talking about my experiences in law school every week with my great cohost and friend Chris off
Hey everybody, I'm the good looking one listen to this every week talk about law school and preparing for law school
I tell all legal miles at score. What are you doing in the tub?
I'm becoming a nice dog man. It's been a long week and Chris keeps us in a team by doing things like talking to us while in the bathroom
I wrote it up there. Hey, Darrell my hands just went into water
So please can listen to the law school podcast at www.lawschoolpodcast.com
Our search for law school podcast at the iTunes music store. Hey, that's not the soap
Easy gun this promo right if I bring look at that easy dump hot 2.com
You're in need of a serious attitude adjustment young man
Smart wrestling sound.com
This is lightning my quiet
Young man
The smart wrestling fan wrestling review show from smart wrestling fan.com
The weekly review show that brings you wrestling news coaches stupiding in some saints at elite plus law reviews
Smackdown TNA impact
All wrestling paper views local and indie reviews like Jakara and Ring of Honor
We also feature wrestling video game updates with collaborations from firepercle.com
And with the Japanese wrestling updates from Zach Arnold with PPH, as well as field correspondence and guests.
Let's take a listen.
What's the coach calls out Stone Cold Steve Austin?
Oh, that's all coach music.
Where's the new coach music?
Oh, there's two coach music.
And now the coach's silly and stupid saying another night.
Well, here comes the pay.
All right.
He's in the cyst.
So coach says Stone Cold, I'm going to give you three minutes.
No, we had to roll this back.
Wiggly even rolled this back just to make sure he didn't say three seconds.
He didn't. He said, I'm going to give you three minutes to get out here.
One, two, two.
Yeah.
That's what he can't manage.
That's how he can manage.
And you did genius.
You know, you know, all the WWE could you have two angles in which
Randy Warden kills the other takers, hit someone fire.
And then immediately goes, WWE.com for a chat.
Then you have Mickey games as a soccer who, the week after,
immediately a trained pro wrestler who is in the ring with her.
That's a smart wrestling fan, wrestling review show with Joe and Wiggly.
We hope you like this. Bye, bye.
That's got to be a big audience for that.
Wrestling is huge, dude.
I was interviewed by the London Times yesterday about some football podcasts
that are being created here in the UK.
That's a soccer to you and I.
And I was thinking about it.
It makes so much sense because in all the reporting you see on football,
or perhaps any sporting event.
But particularly football, which is like baseball or American football.
You know, where is the voice of the fan in mass media?
You know, it's always some idiot with blue and white paint on his face,
holding up a sign or standing next to his mates with a, with a big letter on his belly, you know?
Or it's the epitentiary here, shouted from the stands at the,
at the, at the ref or the, or other, or opposing team players.
But where is the voice of the fan?
You don't really hear it.
You really don't.
So it makes a hell of a lot of sense at that's happening.
Cool to see it because there's no outlet whatsoever for him.
Oh, let's see.
A couple of things that are worth mentioning, just this final thing, apparently,
and it was on slash dot.
Sony music has, if you see one of their CDs or a couple of their CDs,
install shit on your computer, what's called a root kit.
And it basically opens your computer to some hacks.
But I think that whole thing sounds pretty legal to me.
And I think that someone, so there's got to be some consumer group that should take him to court over it.
That's horseshit, man.
And don't install stuff like that.
If you think that's the way to go, I mean, you're going to be so, come so insignificant.
Because we have the pot safe music network.
Which means we got songs we can play.
And people do love to hear.
And we'll go out for the album.
And look, we've even got some R&B, like Arianna.
I've got to have to admit that I'm a sailor.
It's been written in it's own.
It's all on the real moment tonight.
I'm always wrong with the feeling so strong.
I really want to keep no more.
I really have to watch it up the front floor.
I can't take him to the wall.
It's time I let the man in my life go.
And baby, I want to be as can be.
And I want to let the man in my life go.
I'm a sailor.
And I want to be as can be.
You're a sailor.
Because I'm a sailor.
I want to let you pass your time.
And we'll even live on it's very good.
And we'll live on the love.
And we'll face baby.
And I hope that you can understand.
I'll be coming.
I won't let you pass my love.
I'll never pass it up.
I love you.
I really want to keep no more.
I really have to watch it up the front floor.
It's no matter how slow it's going down.
And baby, baby, baby.
I want to let the man in my life go.
And I want to let the man in my life go.
And we'll even live on it's very good.
And we'll face baby.
Another one that came in on the podcast,
a music network was uploaded last night.
Ariana Daddy's baby girl from the R&B category,
which I haven't found a lot that I like yet,
but this one I definitely do.
So you can check that out at music.podshow.com.
And there was one last audio comment I wanted to share with you
because it pertains kind of to the biodiesel.
It's Lee Ann from the Beast.
I'm listening to you talking about getting yourself a greener vehicle.
And although I wholeheartedly support it,
I've a really hard time imagining you pumping your own grease out of the back of it.
McDonald's.
But I will tell you this.
The bitties are not above that.
In fact, I can see that becoming one of our favorite activities.
So if in your travels you discover a van that runs on vegetable oil,
please put pod shows name on it.
Our name on it and hand it on over.
Because we're about ready.
This last tour, the car rental place,
didn't have any vans and stocks,
so they gave us an SUV.
And all of this stereo was pimpin on our gigantic forward enterprise.
It was a little bit humiliating driving that thing around the road.
So help us out.
We really, really, really do want the grease van.
Alright baby, I will definitely look for a grease van for you.
But sure.
That's it.
Add them on credit.com for your feedback.
If you can, if you're going to send an MP3,
don't attach it, just put it up on a server somewhere.
Add your ID three tags and send me the link.
And daily source code.com.
And of course, you can screw a subscribe to the show through iTunes.
Hey, thank you very much for letting me bitch a little bit with you.
It was very cathartic.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.