Delta Sierra Charley, scrunch grunch, 2-8-0.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Transmitters?
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need nuss.
Thinking turns me in.
I like to think I'm flying into the shunt.
Fantastic.
It's Adam Curry.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Welcome.
Man, my mixer is all scrunchy.
Hold on, there we go.
Okay, no more cracks.
Crackling.
Hey, welcome to Seattle, Washington.
I'm here at the Western Hotel.
It is...
It's Tuesday, the 15th of November, 2005.
And it is high noon.
I had a very short night and a very busy morning.
And I have about an hour before I have to go to the airport to fly back to San Francisco.
Whether a willing, of course, if there's one thing I hate about Seattle, it's the ground fog.
And not just Seattle, but also San Francisco.
Yeah, I think the on-time chances of a flight is like 20% or something.
So hopefully I'll get out of my 3-20 flight, 3-21.
So let me bring you up to speed.
Apologies about lack of a source code yesterday, but since I've done two over the week,
I've figured you'd have enough to listen to and a lot of people like to catch up
and sometimes it's hard if you're doing seven days a week.
Witness Dawn and Drew, I've heard their listeners talk about that, but actually they do listen every single one.
So, let me see what I'm going to say.
Alright, so I didn't do a show yesterday because I wanted to have some time in the office to hang out with everybody
and it's been a couple of weeks since I was gone and check up on stuff and look over everybody's shoulder
and be obnoxious as usual.
Rushed off to the airport with the Pod Pamp, Aaron Bersel, to Seattle, got in last night.
This is a brand new hotel, by the way.
This, this Western, I think I'm on the, was the 14th floor.
I think about floor 20, they're probably still completing it.
They're still putting inside walk out front and it's funny because the room has almost everything,
but the coffee machine, I don't even know if the room has been used yet, the coffee machine, the coffee maker,
not a stencil, was, it still had the original wire ties, the cable ties on the electric lead,
so it wasn't plugged in, so it seems like it hasn't been used at all.
And the reason for being here, as I think I told you in a previous show, is to meet with,
or actually to present in front of 300 brand managers and media buyers of the Johnson & Johnson company,
which is just unbelievably huge.
Let me see, I think I actually have a list of the stuff that these guys make.
I had no idea some of this stuff, I got, this is going to be a Gmail show, by the way.
Oops, tab, I need my caps locked there.
Since I really didn't have any time to prep, we'll just go through some Gmail and play some stuff
that I have collected throughout the day.
Let me see, I'm looking for the products.
I just did something really cool, by the way.
I needed to get Patricia's passport, a copy of her passport, to send off to a lawyer in the Netherlands.
And, you know, I don't think she's ever done any scanning, here's the J&J products.
I don't think she's ever done any scanning on the computer at home at the cottage.
So what I did is I have a VNC, watch that, so I have my airports set up at home,
so I could basically SSH into the iMac at the cottage.
Then I set up, because you have to kind of direct the ports on the router,
so that it knows which machine to talk to for certain protocols or basically for all protocols.
And then I fired up VNC, then on this end, here in Seattle, I used chicken of VNC, opened up,
so I could see the machine there, I could control it, opened up another terminal window on that machine,
on the local network, and SSH into the desktop machine that Patricia's on,
as her, of course, and then fired up VNC again.
So I was actually able to create the entire scan and email the result to me,
while sitting here, controlling her computer.
The only thing she had to do was actually put the passport on the top of the scanner,
or the absolute amazing.
Okay, here we go.
Johnson, Johnson products.
Of course, Johnson, baby care products, Nutrigina, OB, stay free, care free, bandaid,
adhesive managers, KY, monitor stat, Tylenol, motrin, pepsid,
ammonium, malanta, splenda, benacol, lactate, all kinds of shit for your gastronomic
issues.
And then they have a huge pharmaceuticals division.
I don't recognize any of these luckily, but they have something for a hyperactivity disorder,
migraines, hormonal contraceptive, rheumatoid arthritis, and Crohn's disease, anti-anemic
with indications for oncology, HIV, just like cancer and AIDS drugs.
And then they have active U-life scan, cordus, ethan,
active U, by the way, is already working on a plan.
They've got a podcast coming out, which is completely underwritten by active U, two girls.
You know what?
That'll be kind of cool.
I'll play that for you here.
Heather and John L.
The show isn't available yet, but they've done their, they're what I call imaging,
they're all kind of their sound effects and stuff.
They've got all that done.
And these are two girls that were recruited specifically for the show, which is kind
of interesting.
And they cut a promo for me to play at this Johnson and Johnson hold down.
So imagine me, on stage, I'm like a little Steve Jobs.
As Madge would say, I had my pants pulled up to my vagina.
And then I played.
Eating Johnson and Johnson, how y'all doing there in Seattle,
bet you drink lots of really strong coffee right now.
This is Heather and Janelle and New York.
So how's it going at your big global media summit?
Just how global, isn't anyway.
Yeah, is Antartica there?
Is Bali there?
I hear Adam Curry, the pod father is there.
Well, he's sort of global and pretty hot, well for an older guy.
Okay.
Not to get too much time away from your important PowerPoint presentations and fancy sandwich lunches.
We just wanted to give a shout out to our awesome sponsor, Acvew.
Acvew brand contact lunches.
Yeah, Acvew, you rock.
Thanks so much for sponsoring our new podcast.
Download with Heather and Janelle.
Check us out at download.acvew.
That's acuvew.com.
That's called a call to action.
We'll be talking about lots of important stuff.
Boys, clothes, music.
Yeah.
And all guys.
Boys.
Talk about some old guy.
Do you really care if they listen?
They are not.
Our target market.
True.
Then tell your kids.
Yeah.
Tell your kids to tune in.
Download.acvew.com.
That's called viral marketing.
Okay.
No back to your regularly scheduled conference.
Yeah.
See ya.
So you can imagine I got, I got some laughs with that and some other stuff.
It was great.
It was, it was unfortunate because Judy McGrath, who is the president CEO of MTV Networks,
also presented this conference.
She did it yesterday.
She did the keynote.
And I had the keynote this morning.
She wasn't there.
But I did hook up with Mark Rosenthall who, of course, ran MTV Networks for a number of years.
And he's now the chairman and CEO of Interpublic.
So I got to tell ya.
Whole bunch of people who were really, really interested and excited about, particularly
about the creativity of what can be done here.
So I was very, very bullish on that.
It was great.
So I was done.
And last question, you know, like 50 minute, 500, 50 minutes into the, into this.
So once I said, what about subliminal advertising?
Oh man.
I ripped into them.
That was so cool.
I did the wholesale thing with the burping.
It was, it was, it was, it was really, it was a lot of fun.
So even though I usually hate doing things like this, this one worked out okay.
Hey, yes, my favorite song of the day.
Candy Butchers.
What to do with Michael?
They met in Paris in 94.
Oh, was it 95?
She was bestying abroad.
He was on tour.
Playing in another time.
They potted hard and they potted wings.
A little north of the sand.
He dreamed about her in so many ways.
She dreamed about her in France.
Well, she knows what to do with Michael.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's his mother son.
Not like anyone.
It just needs time to heal.
They met in New York a few months later.
He was still living alone.
Hugging the ball and masturbating.
Never answers.
Fun.
Never's date.
Was a movie together.
Outside of Brian Park.
Well, the spirit I've seen the week just went off forever.
Until they drank one.
Till they saw stars.
Well, she knows what to do with Michael.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's his mother son.
Not like anyone.
It just needs time to heal.
They finally hooked up for the first time.
The night before the fourth of July.
He felt so awkward saying goodbye to the girl.
Just changed his life.
Now my friend, they are in separate ball.
She even gets that boy to go to the gym.
Now if you don't think that's love, you must be cynical.
Oh, make a man.
You're just dreaming in friends.
Yeah, because he knows what to do with Michael.
She knows how to make him feel.
Yeah, that is the one.
He's his mother son.
Not like anyone.
It just needs time to heal.
Well, she knows what to do with Michael.
She knows how to make him feel.
That is the one.
He's mother son.
Not like anyone.
It just needs time to heal.
Yeah, he's the one.
He's his mother son.
Not like anyone.
It just needs time to heal.
Well, that's right.
He just needs time to heal.
Okay, I love this song.
Candy Butcher is what to do with Michael from Hang on Mike.
Pot say, although not yet, on the Pot say, the music network.
I do have permission to play it.
I got a really nice email from from some folks who work with the
band.
And working on getting that on the Pot say music network.
And cheese Louise.
There is Michael Butler is now, you know, rock and old geek.
The rock and old geek show is now responsible for a lot of what's coming into the Pot say music network.
This guy.
He just signed up an epita record.
I think which includes Merrill, Merrill,
Haggard and dude is just he's going to send me a whole list.
Actually, he did send me a list, but I haven't.
Processed yet.
I want to tell you about some of the great artists that are coming into the Pot say music network.
Some established names.
And it's great, you know, because as long as they own their masters,
they can decide if they want to, you know,
give up the one time or wave any fees for the right for podcasters to play their tombs.
You know, it's great.
So you can get that Candy Butcher song off of iTunes.
The whole album is really great.
Really is.
Speaking of that Matthew evil, you know,
I've played his top down driving around song.
There's a drive away, I think it is.
And a couple of times on the show.
And he sent me his new CD.
And he said, you know, or he sent me a CD.
So I'm really looking for some thoughts on what the next single should be.
You know, what, what should I start promoting?
So I said, no, I'd have it.
I have a listen and then he emailed me like half an hour later.
And he said, I can't believe I'm taking CD track advice from a guy who
he's in a bottle at 5,000 feet.
And you guys really like that.
That's pretty interesting.
I didn't expect you would hold on to have a note here about the Candy Butcher.
Let me see what this is one second.
Hey Adam, real quick note on the Candy Butcher.
I did the same thing.
I heard a one accident hash, loved him.
Turn around went to iTunes, bought the album.
And then when preparing for my next show,
one of the pot safe music network and looked for them.
Couldn't find them.
So he emailed CC and caught him right before he left for the expo.
And he said that they were not on the PMN yet.
And he encouraged me to email them.
Let them know that I had heard them on accident hash.
Try to convince in this podcasting thing.
Really is working that it really will give them exposure.
So just wanted to share that.
So maybe you can pass on the word to your listeners.
That we need to do that for all these artists.
Let them know that we're hearing them on podcasting.
Let them know that it does work.
It will increase our record sales.
And this is the way to go.
So I just wanted to share that with you real quick.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Yo.
That's PD love from Love House radio.
Cool, dude.
Thank you very much.
We got to keep moving him because he is a working.
Oh, this is another thing I received through through Gmail.
I love this one.
This is so great.
Check this out.
Hey Adam.
This is Eric Skip from the Glitchcast,
where I feature great independent artists
and encourage them to bring their music to the pot safe music network.
I was listening to commercial radio
to get a feel for what our competition is doing.
And I heard something that I think you just have to hear yourself.
I think you might recognize the voice.
Tonight we've got a very special.
Long distance dedication.
Going out from the radio industry to one Mr. Adam Curry.
It reads.
Dear Adam, we know it's been a long time since we talked.
But there's just a few things we wanted to get off our chest.
We've heard what you're doing.
And frankly, we just don't get it.
Who the heck are these artists you're playing?
We hear they're not even paying you to play their songs.
Second, we really wish you'd cut out all the cussing
and blathering on about your life.
It gives our DJ's ideas and they've got songs to play.
Listen Adam, we'll cut you a deal.
If you come back to us and bring your listeners,
we'll loosen up the rules a little bit.
Love.
Commercial radio.
Well, I tell you what commercial radio.
I don't think Adam's coming back.
But here's that long distance dedication anyway.
This is Bruce Cox,
with what the fuck's a podcast.
We're on it.
We'll get it.
You're with us now.
Ready?
What's the podcast?
Do this?
That's great.
Adam, we'll just come.
Let's go.
You feel you.
That's all it's done.
Adam, we're in the zone.
Come here.
Some of the best independent music on the pop-sake music network.
The glitchcast.
GlitchNYC.com slash glitchcast.
I love it when everyone starts working together.
I think I got the complete music track from cruise box to do that.
So I'm just going to run through some Gmail stuff.
All this is so good.
You guys have been sending amazing stuff from TQ White.
The second two minutes about DRM,
the language of the RIA and the characteristics of a good file format.
Okay.
I'll bite.
Let's see what he's got going on.
Two minutes.
That's worth the investment.
My name is TQ White.
I run a weblog called just kidding.com.
And I'm a big fan of your stuff.
Thank you.
This morning I was listening to your discussion of the audible DRM announcement.
And you said something that for the first time I can remember,
jolted my conceptual consistency with your viewpoint.
I know that as an unreconstructed hippie a few years older than you,
we share a lot of concepts and shall we say practices.
It came when you were considering the goods and bads of digital rights management.
You said that something to the extent that DRM was disliked
because it prevented people from stealing music.
Though I totally understand that you weren't making any point about that,
I want to caution you here.
I don't believe it's stealing.
Lots of people don't think it's stealing.
I'm opposed to digital rights management because it prevents information from flowing freely.
I love the MP3 because it can be universally accepted and used.
I can receive, send, share, use.
The information contained in them without restriction.
I won't bore you with a long rant about my political theory against intellectual property,
but there are lots of people out there that don't believe it's stealing to share music.
That said, I like you, lot of musicians, programmers, writers, and all the other information producers
to be rewarded.
I just don't want to be coerced with either technical or legal means.
I pirate everything and pay for the stuff that I like and use.
So what's this mean to you?
Don't join the RIA in using the language of crime to refer to the issues involved in DRM.
Don't accuse me of theft.
Though I personally don't believe that it can be made to work with anything less freely usable than an MP3,
I could get behind a data format that supported additional features, tracking and so on,
including the built-in ability for me to easily choose to send money to the author.
Formats like audibles.AA that include digital right restriction features will never be played on my computer ever,
and I don't believe that they'll succeed in the big picture.
Anyway, keep up the good work.
I think you're doing a great job.
Best regards.
TQ White.
Hey, TQ, that's great.
You hear my fan kicking out on the, oh, that was your fan on your power book.
Wow, that was a mind-fuck.
Okay, so that's very interesting.
And I really appreciate the fact that you pointed out that you would be open to talking about a file format
that allows some reporting.
Okay, that's good.
I had a mini epiphany last night, well here in the hotel.
And I was thinking, now, because we can still kind of mess around with the pod safe music network before it gets, you know,
too big and too many people are in there and you can't really reverse engineer anything.
What if we gave the option?
So the pod safe music network, if you register as a pod cast, you can actually download the full MP3 tracks and then play the money pod cast.
As a listener, you can listen to any song in the pod safe music network right from your computer by clicking on the on little play button.
So what if we enabled the pod safe music network so that the artists could enable a track to be purchased?
Which, and the simplicity of this really really hit me right between the years last night.
First of all, it's real easy to create, you know, a transaction e-commerce engine like that is easy.
So you pay money.
I'm thinking 50 cents, right?
Let's undercut iTunes just to make the experiment interesting.
And then any artist who's willing to participate in the experiment could just check a box next to a track that they would like to make purchaseable.
So what that means is as a listener, you would download essentially the same track that the pod cast or downloads and gets for free.
But of course, it's trade off because the pod cast or plays it on his or her pod cast.
And then you pay your 50 cents and that goes to the artist.
And it's a clear, clean MP3 file.
I think that this would be a really interesting experiment because if it's really true that we pay for the stuff we like and we're not thieves.
And of course, I'm not a thief.
So I think I'm much closer to you, TQ in your philosophy than you might imagine.
Then we should probably be able to make some good money for these artists.
As long as you make it really simple because I think that's the beauty of iTunes is it's dadadly simple.
And they even keep your credit card information so you can purchase at will, which is great.
And there's a 50 cents, you know, it's a pain in the ass to pull it out your credit cards.
Maybe just register once and then you couldn't buy any track you want.
And our success will prove if it's worth it or not because we'll know how many times something is played.
We can see sales results, the artists will have all this information and they can then base their future purchasing habits based upon that wouldn't be interesting.
Wouldn't it be really, really interesting if it turned out that sales were astronomical within our little world, of course.
We don't have JLo's yet, but that's soon to come because these podcasts are proliferating.
There's a lot of propagation of cool tunes out there.
Wouldn't that be really interesting? Wouldn't that just break a whole bunch of business models?
It could break DRM.
So maybe we say the only DRM we believe in is don't rob musicians.
That's probably a good one. I want to try that out.
I think it will work. I, you know what? My belief in humanity tells me it's going to work.
Hey Adam says Chris Copeland.
At first I bulked at the enormity of the download for DSC279.
At first it was the pure size 101 megabytes.
Yeah, then the bit rate, 192K that had me thinking you would flubbed it and send it out at higher than need be.
Well, I'll be honest with you Chris. Yeah, I did flub it.
It was my mistake, but I noticed it because I was like, wow, this upload is taking a long time.
And that's 100 megs. What's that? That makes no sense.
But I was already well committed in halfway through it, so I figured out whatever.
In fact, I actually thought listening to the, to the file that maybe no one want to listen to it.
But I felt it would probably be a good idea or it wasn't bad that it was uploaded at such a high bit rate
because you'd get better audio than at a lower bit rate, of course.
The audio was already quite, you know, crappy with basically the intercom system in the plane.
So Chris Copeland said, I was wrong.
With the audio pipe through my cars, JBLs, I felt like I was right there with you in the plane.
The rumble of the engine caused my interior to vibrate and me with it.
Wow, that's hot.
The theater drew me away from the daily traffic to a plane over California as it made its way.
The higher bit rate was worth it to have a full range of audio and be able to hear the conversation,
the radio chatter and almost feel the turbulence right along with you guys.
Thank you for taking me for the ride, Chris Copeland.
Very cool, dude.
That's excellent.
Thank you.
Some more feedback on that.
Damn you, Adam, says Tom Martinek.
There I was sitting in traffic thinking,
bad, I had to pee.
And you start talking about needed to go like a racer horse.
Then you get a bottle and start letting loose,
listening to you,
get some much needed relief was maddening as I sat there on my car with my legs crossed.
Have you ever tried to drive with your legs crossed?
It's not easy.
Damn you.
Damn you to hell.
And have a nice day.
Says Tom.
Fantastic.
Let me see.
Enjoyed the plane.
I'm telling you this, it was really quite amazing to see how many people really enjoyed it.
He felt like I was up there flying with you.
He's no more peeing on DSC, says Cade.
When you describe your peeing experience,
I suddenly had to go real bad.
I couldn't imagine you having to cut the flow in the middle of either.
Now that was messed up.
Let me tell you.
That was no fun.
Audio feedback.
Okay.
Let's, if it's too long or for the,
this is actually the way that I,
that I go through promos and feedback is by,
basically listening to him and if they bore me,
then they go on the,
Yeah.
And this is Angie B.
I love spirals.
We're on the Podsafe Music Network.
I've ever wanted to give you some feedback regarding the whole BMI
ASCAP issue,
which you just brought up again recently this weekend.
We're an indie band that was signed to a small label for the past 15 years.
We sold a little over 50,000 CDs.
So while we're not totally unknown,
we're by no means a major label artist.
In fact, we recently began our own label
and we just put out a first self release CD this month.
Now I've been hearing about the Creative Commons copyright quite a bit over the past few years.
And I wondered if we should go that route with our new music.
But the thing is that the BMI actually does collect and send us money.
Of course, radio play for smaller bands.
It doesn't really bring in any significant money.
But if you're lucky enough to land placement in a popular TV show or commercial,
then BMI or ASCAP can bring in hundreds of dollars per check,
which is really great for smaller bands.
I noticed recently that pump audio, one of the companies we worked with,
has been advertising on Garage Band.
And Garage Band is hooking up independent bands with Creative Commons.
So I'm assuming that a lot of independent artists working with Creative Commons
are now starting to license their music on TV.
So my question to you is,
how can bands that are in a position to make a little bit of money like this?
Really afford to give up working with BMI or ASCAP.
I mean Creative Commons doesn't collect money, period.
I mean, I honestly feel stuck between a rock and a hard place right now.
On the one hand, being a smaller band, we really need the support of podcasters.
We're more than any major label band does.
But on the other hand, we need to try to collect any money that comes our way.
Even if it is through BMI, because as you said, creative people,
such as bands and podcasters really kind of need to quit their day jobs,
so we can continue to be more creative.
Just to try to help out in this dilemma,
I decided last week to update our website to include an official statement about podcasting,
along with the free downloads that we provide.
So there's a public record of our permission.
Maybe other bands listen to your show should consider doing something like that too.
And by the way, our website is lovesparals.com.
We've got the free MP3s I mentioned, as well as our podcast.
Chillin' with love spirals.
So come check us out if you haven't already.
Okay.
First of all, you got a hell of a sexy voice.
Let me check you out on the website.
Love spirals.com.
Let me see loading pictures.
Oh, he's so cute.
I got to twist my head all the way to the right to see you.
He he.
All right.
So of course, you confuse me with a lawyer, which is unfortunate.
I have actually looked into this.
And it's a lot simpler than you'd think.
So ask cap and BMI.
They are collection agencies.
And they collect money from more than just the broadcast industry by the way.
They collected from bars, from elevators, hotels, and even from businesses.
If you have a business and let's say you have a mechanic shop, a garage.
And you have the radio on.
You will eventually get a visit from Ask Cap and or BMI.
I'm not quite sure who drops by.
Maybe they both drop by.
And they'll start asking you about who you listen to.
How often, how many people listen to it.
And you have to pay money for that.
So the groovy thing is you own all of your stuff.
I presume.
So it's all yours.
So you can license this.
Anyway, you want to anybody in any manner.
So signing up with Ask Cap BMI is not a license.
That is a, it's basically, you copyright your work with the US copyright office.
All that information is on the BMI and Ask Cap websites, by the way.
I think costs 35 bucks and doesn't matter.
You can send like 10 tracks at once and it only costs 35 dollars.
And you copyright it.
So that is your work.
And then you sign up with Ask Cap BMI.
I don't think, one of them doesn't have a fee, I think.
But so anyway, you sign up.
And then you're in their database.
And whenever your name pops up for an air play either on radio or TV or, you know,
and then of course they have these huge complicated structures.
Well, we're figuring that if you were played three times on a radio station,
you might have hit an elevator once or something.
I don't know how they do it.
It's all mumbo, jumbo.
They try to explain it.
They will then send you a check.
So when you register with the pod safe music network at music.podshow.com,
you're basically handing out a different license to a different set of people.
The podcasters, essentially by clicking OK, sign that agreement and agree to,
to the terms as set out in, in the terms at the PMN.
So that doesn't mean, and in fact,
it states there that it's yours and that no performance license or royalty or anything
will have to be paid.
And that's a license only to those people who are a member of the pod safe music network.
It's really simple.
So you could license it anyway you want with any terms you want to anybody.
Now, as it, I'm not, again, I'm not a lawyer,
and you should really talk to Larry Lessick about the creative common stuff.
But I'm pretty sure that if you put it up under creative commons,
that you can still license it to ask happened BMI.
It shouldn't be a problem.
In fact, I encourage that because if your music is used in that manner,
in a broadcast or public performance, then of course you should get compensated.
Now, when it comes to TV shows, that's a little different because that's a synchronization fee or a sync right.
And I think you can basically call the shots on that.
Because they will have to contact you.
They would use it for a commercial.
And again, I'm not a lawyer, so I could have this wrong.
But I think that, you know, look, the basis of everything is that it's your stuff.
And if you want to license it to me for free and to ABC for $10,000,
that's up to you.
That is up to you.
And I encourage it.
And I'm really, really happy you sent me that email.
I really appreciate it.
You guys would like to try out the experiment with the free and clear MP3 for purchase.
Wouldn't that be interesting?
Gosh, I really want to check that out.
Okay, I think I'm about ready for some more songs.
Let me just go through some more Gmail here.
See what I can find.
Hi, good people of Pod Show.
Man, I'm just looking for some, for some action here.
I tag everything with the, not yet another comment about what is about the expo
and Pod Safe Music from James B.
Okay, James B, I'll bite.
Let's see what you got cooking here.
I have to look it up, transferring data.
Just playing quick time.
I ask this is James from JamesB.com producer of Navalcast.
Oh, of course.
I'm just getting home from the portable media expo and wanted to send you a comment.
The expo was great.
My wife and I enjoyed it very much.
My wife who is an elementary school teacher commented that she had never been to a conference,
where there was a line to the men's restroom, but not to the women's.
Hopefully next year there's enough women podcasters that they have to stand in line as well.
It's unfortunate that I didn't get to meet you, but I met a lot of friendly fellow podcasters.
Regarding the recent talk about Pod Safe Music, one of the messages I took away from the conference,
is an understanding that there's no good way to play R.I.W.A. licensed music.
With that in mind, I too am changing my show format to be entirely pod safe.
My past episodes have featured clips of licensed music to punctuate the stories I tell.
I'll be editing them to make my past episodes pod safe.
I commend you and PW for your move to pod safe music and encourage other podcasters to do the same.
In addition, like PW indicated in his most recent digital flotsom,
I am going to do my part to support pod safe artists by only buying music from those that support pod safe music.
Why spend our time and money on an industry that is held bent on suing their customers?
When we have talented artists that are willing to work with us, thanks talk to you later.
Dude, thank you very much.
While you were talking, I was going into my playlist here at the pod safe music network,
where I was, for instance, I was listening to pod show music rewind episode number eight from the pool side at the expo.
It was funny.
Guys, they're a riot man.
Brother love dropping by, big mayhem.
It just sounded so good.
You know, I've learned and we did a lot of stuff at the expo.
We had mad running around, Dawn and Drew did at least one show,
a magic, a million shows, I did a show, a Michael Butler did a show,
almost every one of the pod safe music network did something,
if not together, then they did it individually.
And I've learned that even though the content sometimes,
certainly the mad stuff was a bit over the top to say the least,
but just looking at it, you kind of did get the feeling,
oh man, I wish I could be there, and I heard a lot of that from people,
so that to me usually means that we did a good job at making some of the expo come alive
of those pretty cool.
Okay, so here's the song that I heard on the pod safe music network,
where the hell would it go?
Oh, don't you hate it when that happens?
I'm here like, I'm staring at my desktop and can't find it.
Okay, let's go window, no tools, downloads.
No, it should, I could just click open, there we go.
This is, okay, this is from Epita Records, I guess,
so this is one of the one of those cool bands that have been added to the PMN.
This is Danger Doom and Mint's Meat.
The villain ain't crumbin' off credit alone.
Then I'm getting some cognac, I might kinda head for,
smoke the mirrors, call her in the mince,
couldn't read the shorthand, the mortars and bricks.
If any negative thought lingers, he netted that,
wrote this one with his middle finger and wet the cement.
Did it on the side, before he's gone by by spit it on the fly,
brush your teeth, rinse and garble,
a true nerd that's put in words since garble,
and you flang and scrabble,
brine with the northern jaw, twang and babble,
glossy penjar, didn't break the world record,
through a forest in bargain and take the girl naked.
More spots than a leopard,
Jenny had to stop the block with hot pepper,
shepherd, leading sheep's out to slaughter,
kept it sold and wrapped it, every time he saw ya,
trying to doubt some pinch of weed in a frat street house.
I only links me out of that beat, mouse.
Welcome to the show, remember whatever you do,
do not pull the flow, school the dumb on the number one,
what a fool.
It's too never met a cooler bum,
keep the drummer's from,
enjoy keeping the shot,
just to get his shoes high,
surely only as it's fine.
A stranger who speaks to you,
vocal, danger made the beat get up for it to do the vocal.
No bull, everything we wanted they grabbed him took,
whole lab look like an ill left jabbing hook,
even had a secretary to take the balls,
shake it and make it fall,
I told her, don't break my balls,
whatever mouse gold trouble follows,
the bouncing on his throw was kills,
and double dollars,
fills pill bottle flows,
that before the scholars,
thick bluff a little girl,
the bubble hollers,
he's rock lathering gold,
a fat blouse,
and neither brother was sold to let her back out,
even if the rat couldn't compete with crowds.
I make me scream out of that beat, mouse.
Tap your toe,
crime and strap,
a dope rat for show,
to let the whipper snappers know,
sucks to read him,
now pass that loop,
up under the ducts,
you or a hazmat suit,
sound to light Friday,
so the radius of potions,
be up in the party with the fiveiest emotions,
on the list of lobbies,
for save the oceans,
gave his donation
to the lady with the lotions,
swole hand kitchen,
the old man bitch,
and switching with the fan,
with the gold band,
switching,
spitting like a bionic sneeze,
that frees vodka,
just to clear the air,
like the ionic breeze,
quadro,
slick enough out,
try a box for it,
chicken pot pie,
thinking outside the box.
Love to taste her gritty,
but got no time to be wasted,
and chasing putty,
how for daffy duck,
bucks,
porky pig,
bunny,
boomper,
or for that type of wrapped country,
or deep house,
?
hmmm,
anyway,
you don't get a lot of wrap hip-hop,
rmb from the pod safe music network
that I really like about this.
Yeah,
and I keep the hand,
it sounds good,
sound in it really,
but I like it.
Homers.podshow.com
is where you can upload your promo to me,
feedback,
you can still probably send through Gmail.
You can also put it up there. It's really cool because I've set it up as a as a
You know the RSS feed is a pod cast
So I can just basically open up. I'm using iTunes for that open that up, but you know
Oh geez, I must have at least
Oh, it looks like I have 30 or 40 different promos in there. So we listen to a couple of them just to see
Yeah, and and of course this the same rules apply if I get bored or if it sucks
Then I'll just go move on to the next one
Hello Delta Sierra Charlie fans. I'm Lauren I'm an I'd like to tell you about a new podcast geek counterpoint
If you're like a lot of people you may find mass media coverage of scientific and technical issues to be
Confusing and consistent even annoying and if that's how you feel I've just got one thing to say to you
It's not your fault
The fact of the matter is coverage of science and technology is being dramatically reduced
Many reporters that have been dedicated to covering science and technology have been laid off and the
Resulting coverage is often mangled dumb downs sensationalized and stripped of any context
So if you've fed up with soundbite science go to geek counterpoint.net
You can subscribe to the podcast either through links on the website or straight through iTunes
That's a counterpoint. It's a podcast. It's a blog. It's a complete mental health program
I like it. I like it. I would definitely check that one out. Okay
Onto the next one here
Oh, that's interesting. Oh, of course. It's a podcast. I mean, why would it play the next episode automatically?
Oh, sorry. That's the same one. Here we go. Yeah, I'd cast that brings you the latest news
Interviews and reviews of all things diabetic. I'm Pristel Marchant and each week
Diabetic feed has the latest information about a disease that affects over 21 million people in the
U.S. alone. If you're diabetic or know someone who is we have something for you
For more information go to www.diabeticfeed.com or subscribe to the podcast at feeds dot feed burner dot com slash diabetic feed
Okay, one more then this is kind of fun. I like this. Hey, Adam. This is Chris from the financial aid podcast with exciting news for your Delta Sierra
The listeners. We are giving away an iPod nano plus the cool line your headphones more a student loan payment for one month up to $300 on the financial aid podcast
Subscribe to our podcast at www.finageleadpodcast.com and we will do the drawing on December 1st
2005. That's Thursday, but you must be subscribed to win subscribe today www.finageleadpodcast.com. Okay now another one from the pod safe music network
Which I got from pod show rewind. Graining. I think this was uh, track the CC Chapman shows.
Love this song. Sex in the box on your dating source good.
I'll take to the back. I want to push you on a need. Try to walk to the craft. It's one of my favorite beats tell you that I'm sorry for this
Down and getting by without dude when I did couldn't take it and along with the weeping me down
Such a beautiful surrounded now. Oh, there's love in rediscovered. It's got me feeling alright
If I try everything and the boat to make you forget. If I send over steaks that I may
We're in the past. If I could take it back. I would do this all again if I could.
I
rely
You
Thuccard relax keep track on the facks is agrees in the amnesia get out they delays
It'll count a drug that keeps me from ripping away
Where I needed anything, I suggest
Going beg for 1 day all the things that I would swim
If I tried everything, and the hope to make you forget
If I said, all the mistakes that I made were in the past
If I could take it back, I would do this on a game
If I could, I would, real life
If I said, all the mistakes that I made were in the past
If I could, I would do this on a game
If I could, I would, real life
I would, I would. I would, real life
I wonder it, there's probably a lot of the Johnson Johnson people probably listen to this show because now they're like, oh, I don't want a second
Let me go check out what that guy's talking about and since I'm here in Seattle
I mean you can't be in Seattle even if it's just for 18 hours and not play a promo about a Seattle podcast
No, that would be a travesty no, no, no, no
Are you looking for great music from a thriving jazz community?
tune in to Seattle jazz scene on red raspus radio bringing you the best jazz and all its shapes, sizes and styles
with a greater Seattle area from mainstream to Latin jazz big bands from jazz beginnings
to its progressive evolution
Seattle jazz scene is a weekly program devoted to one of the Northwest's musical treasures
For more information, please visit redraspis.libsim.com for feed links and doubts
Seattle jazz scene on redraspis radio
Cool, I'm going to subscribe to that. I'll be great for the plane ride home. I love the jazz
So in closing today email from Heather Bowler from initiative.com
A funny thing happened on the way to the forum. I went to a presentation this morning by someone who looked remarkably like a kind gentleman
Who got some hotel staff jumping to let me back in my room last night
Many thanks had no idea who you are, but now I do presentation was great
I publish a quarterly magazine for advertiser clients and we're writing a feature on podcasting in the next issue
If I send you our details could be interview you regards Heather Bowler will of course
Heather now that may have sounded a little bit weird
But this was when I we were checking in last night around quarter to ten
And she'd locked herself out of a room and had a credit card, but it wasn't her credit card
Didn't have her name on it, so it was but anyway, so I
I told the when the the check in the desk clerk said anything else I can do
Yes, please please let this young lady back in her room
And so it happened okay
I'm still using the Heil microphone by the way. I love this mic. This is great
It sounds wonderful
Ron heard the switch the mics switch as well on the Saturday podcast and he's a real audio file
And he said it sounded pretty damn good too. Yeah, this is good and someone sent me an email about the Heil stuff
Let me see I saw that coming today
Some super star celebrity works with it. Here we go Nate doer doer doer
Just catching up on Delta Sierra Charlie to seven eight heard you mention it
You got a free Heil sound mic Bob Heil makes very nice stuff
Ah Joe Wall Schwartz with Bob regularly doing promotion of his mics and gear
Okay, yeah, there you go. Well, if it's good for Joe damn it's good for us wouldn't you say
So again, it's promo dot pod show dot com please
Feel free you got a register, but that's not just a email address and you make up a password and then you can
Post something about your promo and if you want you can attach
Or just a post a link in there which points to an MP3 file and then it would you will be guaranteed that I'm going to hear it
Because it plops into a nice little playlist in my iTunes, which is extremely nice now it would be great if we could
Sign off with our signature sound which of course
I don't have
Shoot I don't have my pod show sign off thingy
Ah, that sucks. Okay, we'll do it this way. Hey everybody
Please save me from people who've been told what to like and then like it
In my opinion if you're over six years of age and you're still getting your music from the radio
Something is desperately wrong with you
I can only hope that somehow MP3 players and file sharing will destroy FM radio the way they're destroying record companies
Then even though the air will probably never be safe to breathe again, maybe it will be safer to listen to