Delta Sierra Charlie 2-3-9.
And now, coming to you from higher top podshow headquarters in beautiful Newark, Ohio,
home of the world's largest basket.
Yes, as all of you, hey!
They are part of your secrets.
Only information you don't be a liar.
And I'm Korean.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio concert in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
And good morning, good afternoon, good evening,
Daddy's source code September 12, 2005.
And it's a Monday.
I'm very excited today.
We're going to try a couple new things.
We're going to mix it up a little bit, so to speak.
And the first thing we're going to do is we're not going to kick it off with a mash-out.
It seems like the mash-out well has run a little bit dry.
I think everyone's having the same problems.
And I also think that's completely socialist.
I mean, it's like when shit's happening and when hurricanes are blowing through town
and people's lives are uprooted and the news media is all about it.
I saw a drop in a slight drop in non-subscribed listeners.
I see less mash-ups coming through.
I see a raised activity of blogging.
It's very interesting.
So anyway, no mash-out today, but that means, of course,
we'll have some mash-up songs in the form of a hit-test pod-safe music
and actually aviation.
Aviation stuff.
What I say.
And I'm practicing something new.
You're going to like this one.
For the first time in the history of my podcast,
have a timer running.
So I've done a lot of thinking and a lot of talking to other people
and it seems like the ideal link for a podcast comes in blocks
and each block of time should be about 20 minutes.
So that's pretty much what people have timely
of the discretionary listening time in the morning.
For the discretionary listening time at the end of the day.
And of course, you can split it up.
So what I'm trying today, just to ease into it nicely,
is to try and create a 40-minute show.
And I'm going to do it exactly.
I'm going to time it.
I hope exactly to the 40 minutes.
I don't quite have the tools that I'm normally used to do this.
And the theory here is that if I commit to at least 20 minutes,
then either it's going to be a very compact rock and show,
or if I have little time, I could talk for 20 minutes,
and I guess still make it worth your while, I think.
Or just go to the full 40 minutes.
I'm going to do today's full 40 minutes without a mashup,
which is interesting because that usually does take a good 3-5 minutes of the time.
The first thing I want to talk about though is about iTunes 5.0.
I didn't see Steve Jobs' keynote live until this week.
I didn't see the keynote or not keynote.
The presentation of the iPod Nano and the rocker phone,
and the other announcements that he made.
Of course, the iTunes 5.0 application, which is now out.
And I hadn't had a chance to see that,
but this weekend, of course, the girls were going.
So I had a major, major geek out weekend,
which, of course, means after I do the show,
I've got to go through the house like a whirlwind,
because the girls would be on the way pretty soon.
They're just getting on the plane,
so they will arrive probably on 435.
So probably 530, they'll be home, I hope.
So I have to have everything to speak in Spanish by then.
Until then, we'll just keep it nice and messy.
We won't tell anybody.
So I had time to look at a whole bunch of stuff,
which I'll be talking about, including the keynote.
Man, I gotta say,
I'm such a fan of the way Steve Jobs does those presentations.
And especially the way he had the iPod Nano,
which was the big surprise,
and he had it in his little pants pocket, the whole while.
If you haven't seen it, you know, guys,
you have that little pocket on the right hand side of your trousers.
And you always wonder what that one's for.
Well, so Jobs was going through this whole thing,
showing, you know, presenting everything,
different guys on stage.
And then he says, have you ever wondered what this little pocket was for?
And that's where he pulled the Nano out of.
And that was, you know, just great showmanship.
Fucking fabulous.
And also I noticed that the way he was talking about podcast,
very much resembled the way we were,
and myself, I recognized, you know, my own,
maybe excitement in the way he was talking about podcast,
but, you know, like six months ago,
maybe even longer than that.
So, and I just kind of made me realize
that listening to all kinds of text shows
over the weekend, of course, you know,
nice and loud throughout the whole house.
Everything's streaming, one computer to the other.
I really took advantage of the situation.
You know, perhaps we still do really live in this
vacuum of tech and of geek.
And, you know, we think people catch on so easily.
And, you know, of course there's a million better features
and a thousand better ways to do it.
But I think the masses are just now starting to tune
into this whole concept of podcasting.
And quite frankly, I want to play right into it.
I want to make the best listening experience ever,
because it seems like what we've been dreaming about
these 100 million listeners, they're actually going to come.
Look at the sales of the iPod.
What they sell, they sold six million iPods
in the last quarter alone.
I mean, this is just outrageous.
It really is.
Something else I noticed that was interesting though.
I just don't quite understand all the math.
Is that, what was it?
They have 68% market share in the US of all MP3 players.
It seems to me like there's, you know, that you're not taking some
devices into account there.
But it doesn't matter.
I mean, I like my iPod and I have to be honest,
I think I'm going to pick up an iPod Nano.
That really, I think that really fits my lifestyle
because you already have this humongous MDA thing hanging off my belt
with, you know, limited playback capabilities.
Of course I can load software for it.
And of course I can get, you know, like a one gigabyte card
and all that.
But at the end of the day, there's so much good functionality
in the iPod platform that I really do like it.
Now, what I'd also heard is that a lot of people had trouble
when upgrading to 5.0.
And I heard some noise about subscriptions being lost
and libraries not working.
So I kind of resisted, you know, like I'm, I'll wait for 5.01
or something like that.
But of course, I was doing so much stuff over the weekend
that a couple of reboots were involved.
And eventually you start up iTunes and it doesn't let you choose
anymore.
It's like, you will upgrade now, dammit.
Wait, can I do this?
Hold on.
Let me see.
If I can do this, this may have may not work.
You will upgrade now, dammit.
That was pretty good.
Good.
Now I know that works too.
So upgraded and low and behold, when it fired up,
it said something wrong with your database.
All my podcast subscriptions were gone.
And I said, you know what?
This is the right weekend for this to happen.
So I, and I'd also decided I would do as many iTunes subscriptions
as possible just to see how that worked.
And I really hate the process.
You have to go back, you subscribe,
but switch as windows, you have to go back,
click directory, search.
It's not a very handy way to do it.
It seemed like the directory, and I've read lots of reports
that the iTunes directory is a little bit
fruity, I guess we would say.
Not screwy, but fruity.
Not everything is coming back,
or result that used to come back as a result.
So clearly they're working on something, doing some stuff.
And so I resubscribed to most of the podcasts I had,
and some new ones as well.
And I started to manage a little bit differently.
I wanted to throw out old episodes that I've already heard,
because I really have to cut down on my disk usage,
my space is getting full everywhere,
not just Gmail, but everywhere.
It's time for a new computer.
The asteroids are full on this one.
And this morning,
and I'd actually taken the laptop with me to bed,
because I was listening to a couple of podcasts,
and you just had the screen go blank,
and it was just listening.
And I, you know, just when I was done, I closed the lid,
opened up this morning, fired up iTunes,
and your database is corrupted, and low and behold,
it has all my songs,
but the only thing it blows out is all the podcasts subscriptions,
which of course completely blows.
So I hunted around on the web, looking for stuff,
and the easiest fix that I found is what I tried,
and what actually worked is,
in iTunes just to go to file import,
and then import the XML file,
which is your iTunes Music Library XML file.
And then it brought everything back in,
and then under the podcast tab,
there were all my podcasts,
not just my new ones that I'd subscribed to,
but the old ones as well.
So I was actually pretty happy.
I did have to physically click on the subscribe button
for each one, for it to go out,
and I guess read download the podcasts that probably already had,
but that worked with I need problems.
So I'm hoping that it just,
it hangs together,
and I think that there's something,
there's something buggy going on.
I don't know if it's,
if you use subscriptions that aren't iTunes subscriptions,
or if you shut down while iTunes is running,
right now I'm definitely shutting down iTunes nicely,
before I let the computer go to sleep,
or anything even closely related to that.
So that was a big part of,
and that was a big part of my cake weekend
that I wanted to share with you.
I did some other things as well,
and also hunted around for a couple of promos,
and they're always sitting there in the Gmail box somewhere.
It was actually one of my favorites.
When you want to get away from home and leave reality behind,
you need a place like no other.
They're going to give daddy the reinvance,
we take that, we're going to Vegas my cake.
Place where you can gorge yourself,
and in all you can eat buffet for $5.95.
Place where you socially acceptable to go.
A place where you socially acceptable to order a couple beers before breakfast.
A place where little men will hand you free porn just for walking by.
I hope that you're having an enjoyable stay here on Las Vegas,
and also hope that you've been fortunate.
But where does such a place exist?
Vegas, baby, Vegas!
If you want a complete escape from reality,
there's only one place to go, Las Vegas.
If you want a podcast dedicated to all things Las Vegas,
there's only one show for you.
$500 by midnight, the original Las Vegas podcast.
Join me, Tim Dresson, each week,
as I bring you everything from the latest Las Vegas news,
and tips for finding the best bloody Mary on the strip,
to getting free stuff from your favorite casinos,
making the most out of your Vegas vacations.
I'll even throw in some Vegas sounds seem tourist for good measure.
Listen to $500 by midnight,
the original Las Vegas podcast by visiting
www.500bymidnight.com
Vegas, baby, Vegas!
It's like hitting a jackpot on your MP3 player.
Hot Joe, content that will make you walk the dog
and kiss your mother.
Hi, Anna.
It's Laura from the Pod Squad that's POD, SQOD,
who are a podcast all about audio.
We take a podcast and review different types of equipment,
and we try to help people sound a little bit better.
Not as good as you, of course,
because you are the godfather of podcasting.
But we are here to help all of those other people.
So, tune us in, check us out,
that's Pod Squad, POD, SQOD.
And we just want to say how much we enjoy
the daily source code.
I listen to it every day.
And I do remember you as a VGNM2D,
you were the hottest VG of Vermont.
And if you could just say hi, Laura,
in your VGN kind of voice,
but who really make me happy.
So we add them, don't forget Pod Squad.com,
check us out.
So that was without a doubt,
one of the highlights of the weekend.
Hey, Laura.
So you want me to say,
hey, Laura, in my DJ voice,
this is a favorite wallet,
because it would make her really happy.
Okay.
Hey, Laura.
How are you doing?
I want to know what you're doing with that.
Hey, Laura, how are you doing?
That's what I want to know.
So that made me feel pretty good,
as you can imagine.
That definitely struck the ego.
And then I,
you know, I told you, I was messing around with my subscriptions,
and I came to a podcast that I'm subscribed to.
The,
Jabberjaw podcast with a hard G,
bitches.
And,
that was definitely one of the low points of my weekend.
But anyway, okay,
today,
I just want to say this week,
two day,
September 8th.
But this week,
there were some birthdays.
And I would like you to tell me,
what year do you think this week was Adam Curry's birthday?
How old do you think he is?
Now,
I want you to think for a second.
You probably know,
because we've talked about it.
But this was the first year that I heard anything like this.
Adam Curry?
Mm-hmm.
I think Adam Curry is 43 years old.
Ah!
He says he was born in 1964,
which is 41,
which is a year old,
a year and some change older than us.
Okay.
Right.
So you're both 40 and we're 39.
Do you think that when we saw him on MTV,
he was the same age as us?
Now, why would I not,
I mean,
I don't really remember.
I'm going to say he's fudging a bit.
Oh!
I think he's in it.
As a matter of fact,
I think I saw Profile on him saying he was like in his low 40s.
But not out.
Profile?
Like one of my IM chat profiles.
But not 41.
Yeah.
Because I would have made that connection.
I don't think so.
I think he's girlifying his age.
I think so too.
Like he's going to be a model or something,
and he's trying to get him out.
Yeah.
I started,
I started early.
I said my first TV gig was when I was 19.
And I think I was 22 when I started MTV.
So yeah, what's your age?
I was only a year older.
But that really hurts.
Now, this is the question is,
do I look like I'm 43?
Do we look like I'm 41?
I needed some more ego stroking,
but it didn't really come along over the weekend,
unfortunately.
I did see something very cool on Fox.
I had the Fox News channel here on my Sky TV,
which is great only.
When they go to commercials,
then they show this weather of the world.
And it's very repetitive.
And they play a hokey music under it.
So that's kind of boring.
But they were live.
And I don't know if it was,
it was somewhat, some flooded area.
I don't know if it was New Orleans or not.
And it was, you know,
now we've gotten to the point where it's the same.
So they're just coming up with shit.
And particularly these Fox News hosts,
they just talk really talk out of their ass.
They're very suggestive putting words in people's mouths
to steer a conversation.
That's fine, you know?
I don't care.
I can tell the difference between news and infotainment.
And then the interview this one guy.
And at first,
it was about,
they were talking about either the credit cards
that they were made at Houston,
that they were handing out to people or checks
or basically getting resources to them.
I think we're talking $2,000
to start off with per family,
I believe.
And so the guy clearly wasn't happy
and had some, you know,
did see reporter on the ground
with a baseball cap on in her,
her, her, all weather,
you know,
all weather with standing down to ground zero vibe.
And the host in the studio was even,
he was probably even worse.
And so they're bantering back and forth.
What absolutely nothing,
this guy said something in the background
and then the host in the studio says,
you know,
bring him back on.
What was the question about,
you know,
was that about the money?
And this guy just goes off.
And he's like,
who, you know,
it was like,
at a certain point,
you know,
he was saying,
they're treating us like slaves,
you know,
the notes get on the bus
and not on the slave ship.
And that's okay.
That was just his opinion.
But then he said,
they should just give us what we fucking deserve.
I was like,
whoa.
And then the,
and the way the host,
I wish actually I should have,
you know,
that probably was automatically recorded.
I found and taped that for you.
It was amazing.
This guy tried to recover.
And he's like,
well, you know,
10% of our flying high and,
and people are very tired.
And I was like,
you know,
finally we can get this in real news.
There's a guy who really wanted to say something.
And they cut him off.
And it wasn't because I don't think they were interested,
but they're pre-programmed and pre-packaged,
you know,
not to let any of that
particularly because he said,
the big F word.
And then I'm going to ask you,
which I was spoken about before,
but what it really is the problem with the F word.
I mean,
so it's an explotive,
but what is the danger in it,
if you say it?
Does that mean that people will go out
and say,
oh,
fuck.
Maybe I should go and fuck.
I mean,
is that the danger?
What, what is the danger?
Where,
and you know,
where is that?
I'm just trying to understand,
you know,
what is the root?
When did that become a bad word?
And why?
I'm sure someone out there will be able to tell me,
or if there,
if probably this going to be
5,000 different urban legend reasons why,
or whatever,
but when did that become a bad word?
When did that become outlawed?
Who said,
and why?
I just like to know that.
I'm happy following along with the program,
because people do seem very offended by my use of the word.
So we're up to the 21 minute mark here,
so normally,
on a short day show,
short show day,
I would be winding up right about now.
And now,
I am,
well,
not even halfway through,
so this is going to be interesting.
I'm going to shut up now,
and play some feedback that I got from,
from my body over at exit 50.
I,
I think you'll enjoy this.
Adam Curry.
Yo, man.
This is Andrew Coffee.
You know me from exit 50.
How are you doing?
By the way,
he's from,
Adam Curry.
Oops.
Oh, that's a rewind,
didn't know that.
He's a Jersey guy.
So that's kind of,
this is how Jersey guys talk to each other.
This is Andrew Coffee.
You know me from exit 50.
How are you doing?
I'm doing.
I was going to email you this,
but I figured,
you know,
I don't feel like typing.
I figured it's in your MP3 file.
Right now.
Hey,
that news you've put out on skip the calendar today,
Derek.
Man, it just tripped me out.
I was driving home.
It was Friday.
And,
kind of,
this is kind of weird story,
because you're from Jersey and I'm from Jersey.
Yeah.
And I go down to Stone Harbor,
and have a line every year.
And I actually know Derek's dad,
but that's,
it was only after I did the interview on podcast 401 that I,
he called me,
he email me,
he says,
Hey,
you're from Stone Harbor.
It's like we grew up together,
but we didn't know each other.
So just briefly,
what he's referring to here is Derek
from the skepticality podcast,
who was now in a drug-induced coma
after a form of brain aneurysm that has,
you know,
lots of people know each other in the podcast and community.
So,
everyone's concerned and,
and everyone's,
you know,
start old,
if not,
shocked about this.
Ah fuck.
I'm so sorry.
How did that?
I don't understand how that happened.
We'll see if I can,
oh,
man.
See if I can pick it up where we left off.
See if that'll work.
Oh,
this really sucks.
Hold on.
Ah,
this is eating into my time, too.
It's now is,
is Megasex stuck?
What's going on?
Don't tell me it's going to
start over at the beginning.
Adam Curry.
Yeah.
I'll follow you on podcast 401 that I,
he called me,
he email me,
he says,
hey,
you're from Stone Harbor.
It's like we grew up together,
but we didn't know each other.
And,
when I went into the bar this,
like last week,
over the Labor Day,
I talked to his mom.
His mom knew who I wasn't going to know.
I was like,
oh yeah,
my son was telling me about you,
because my cousin works at that bar.
And the last day of summer,
I was hanging out with Derek's dad.
And we were sitting at the bar
during,
well,
he was drinking too,
but he was turning me on to this towaka.
And I said to him,
I said,
do you know what's going on?
So because I didn't realize that was his son.
I said,
oh,
that's your son.
I said,
okay,
this all makes sense now.
So when you told me that today,
and you said,
skip the counting,
you said,
Derek, I was like,
oh fuck.
I'm just like,
man,
the dad's so cool.
He hooks me up with the local price,
because he knows my cousin works there,
you know,
everybody else has to pay more.
So when you said that today,
I was like,
fuck anyway.
What,
fuck there goes my,
my cheap drinks.
I'm hoping you would think it's something else.
Enough of that.
I hope he gets better.
I know I'm going to see him.
I never met the guy.
I go,
Even though I said,
dude,
you coming up down the shore.
And,
anyway,
I was going to start listening to a
shoggycemic.
You know,
I know I'm on other things.
We've got these parallel lies, man.
I'm standing it in my upright desk like you.
I've had mine longer than yours though.
I use it for work when I'm a broker.
But working with the street IQ.com,
they're flying me up to New York City next week,
and I don't know if you've been checking out the site,
been checking out the site or what I'm
been doing, but we've got a pretty
ask kick and revenue model for a podcast
adventure here. It was already publicly
traded company. Sorry, I was downloading
porn instead. I've said this to you
million times in emails and like you said
today on the show, you don't fucking
return your emails. Hey, that's cool.
We're going to we'll meet sometime. I know
where we'll probably meet the first time
and that's going to be at the podcast
media expo because street IQ got that
award. Oh, that's right. There's no
word ceremony. I got to go to that. I really
want to go. I was in November, I think. To
give out. You are part of it. So I'm sure we're
going to hook up there, but I'd hopefully
look, we did, you know, I'm thinking about, you
know, going. Maybe you should take a whole bunch of
the pod squad and go have a good time.
And I don't know. I want to do something cool, though,
if if we do go to the podcast expo, you know, we
should do something cool. I'm not quite sure yet,
but we'll come up with some. You know,
mess some ideas between now and then. And I don't know
how we can integrate, you know, music to financial
content, but I got a pretty good take-home
what's a lot of money out there, you know, in the
financial arena. So anyway, contact me, get in touch with
me, Skype, whatever. I don't know what to fuck. Stay in touch.
Let me know. I'm going to New York next week. I just
missed you. Maybe I catch up with the in San
Francisco, whatever. Stay into the show. You look like
that pretty much put everything online. And
you have a good time over there and wherever you are,
England. Ciao, man. Oh, by the way, go to my site
to do the sound scene tour while with New Jersey.
I got some funny fuckers from South, South Philly on the
tape. Since you've grown up down there, you kind of know what's going on.
Yeah, we got along great. Anyway, yeah, you bummed me out there.
You fucker. Anyway, later. So he did make me smile with all that.
All right, let's get into some pod safe music here. This
one came in through email. It's actually already listed on the
pod safe music network. You can find that at
pod safe music network.com or music.podshow.com. It's the
stepford wives on the daily source code.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh hey, hey, hey hey, hey hey, hey, hey, hey, they're the real hellers of them.
You're not practical, you're not practical
Your Character 3 likes it if the image
Is it drawn between the eyes, or the appropriately
Are more digital and you but that looks.
You're not practical, you're not practical
You're notarlesehen, you're not practical
you're not practical
You're not practical, you're not practical
You're all practical, you're not
You're not Python, do you know where you're
Python, do you know where you're
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah you, I, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flex
I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, I'm flexing, amening, amening, amening, amening, amening, amening, amening, amen explaining what exactly does that mean?
For some reason, I had a real mashup quality to it, but it's PodSafe, my backpack and my Boss 2 tides, step for wives on the Daily Source Code.
you can find that in the show notes, of course, a daily source code.com or at
curry.com and they'll take you over to the podcast, music.network, music.podshow.com.
So I just, and that we have 10 minutes and 25 seconds left. I'm trying to time it into my
exact 40, 40 minutes. I had to make an executive decision, had to pull something out,
and I'm not going to tell you what it is, because I'll just put it back in tomorrow.
Hello, this is Chef Mark Tafoya from the remarkable Palette podcast. I'm a personal chef
in New York City, and my program is all about enjoying the pleasures of food, experiencing
the gastronomic delights of the world, and doing it in a relaxed and fun way. Join me as I explore
world cuisine, present some fun and interesting recipes, and experiment with new ingredients.
I also interview producers, perveires, and other food professionals, and talk about being a
personal chef. It's all part of my quest to develop a more remarkable palette.
You can find me on iTunes or read the blog at remarkablepalette.logspot.com, and there you'll find links to the
show. It's a tough world out there for a geek. It's hard to enjoy the various entertainment
mediums. Where's a geek to go when television is being over-branded by reality shows?
Where's a geek to go when they're on a limited budget, and it's hard to sort through the
crap that makes it to theaters? Where's a geek to go when he wants the latest and video game
information? Where's a geek to go when she wants the latest news, rumors, and facts at
for the entertainment world? If you suffer from public anxiety, mild depression, superior
complexes. You feel the need to sit in front of a computer or television screen for hours on
hand. Does your family and friends criticize you for your habits and hobbies? If so, chances are
you're a geek, playing in simple. Hi, I'm Randy McKinney, and I'm Wayne Porter. We are the hosts
of Geek Entertainment, and we are here for you. Fizz us on the web at www.geekshow.us for all your entertainment
needs. I got a place where geeks definitely want to go. You know, this show Rockstar,
which I think it is on CBS, I think. You're going to like this. There's a big controversy
brewing now, because one of the, let me see if I have that page open, one of the performers on
the show, who eventually the winner, of course, will become the new lead singer in excess. Let me
see what's this guy's name. I'm sure it's on this page. Of course, there's a link to this page.
From my show notes, shoot doesn't even say. Anyway, one of the candidates, and you'll see this
on this page, was wearing a shirt that looked like he had like congee, letters, 3 rows, 3 vertical
rows, and if you turn your head 90 degrees to the right or the picture 90 degrees to the left,
you'll see that the shirt actually says, go fuck yourself. It's a great, a great hack,
and they got away with it, because I guess that episode aired, I just thought it was fantastic. So
make sure you check that out. And also Rockstar, I mean, screw it. eBay, that's what I want to say.
eBay bought Skype. I just saw it press release about that. That's pretty interesting.
I can't wait to, you know, they say that it's a very natural fit for them. It doesn't matter.
Shoot, I like the service. I'll continue to use it as long as they continue to maintain it,
make it better, but I thought that was in shape. It's like $2.6 billion.
Okay, eBay is your new phone company, never bought it. And then some aviation stuff. And I have to
say it was great having iTunes kind of blow up on me over the weekend, because I really went searching
for all of my favorite podcasts. And I found a couple new ones. And there's even a stewardess now
who was doing a podcast, or a air hostess, or flight attendant, I guess I should say,
Betty in the sky with suit with the suitcase. I think it's called. And she is definitely affiliated
with the fly with me podcast, because, well, there's some overlap there. I don't know if they're
married or whatever. But Joe Dion does fly with me is a pilot or copilot for a major US carrier.
It is a great show. I want to talk about that in a second. But first reflecting back to
what we're talking about, the Cessna versus the Sirus. I know now we're talking about airplanes
all of a sudden. And I said that I really like the Cessna, which is the one I have, the 182
RG. And, you know, I like the Cirrus. It's pretty. But, you know, Todd really summed it up.
And email he says, Sirus may be a sexy modern plane, but the biggest problem I'm hearing from
other pilots that are looking to buy one is Sirus's longevity. The Sirus, you see, is a composite
airplane. It's value drops over time, whereas the Cessna is does not. I used to fly a 1957
Cessna 182, it mines a little bit younger than that. And almost none of the major components have
been replaced. That won't be true with the composite plane. I have flown the Katana and the
Sirus and the great planes. They just won't stand the test of time as well. A Sirus is
fun to fly for its modernness and sexiness. It's just not an investment. Now, that's all great.
But the important part of this comes at the end of the email. And that would really smidge
sway me if I were still in the market for a new aircraft. He says, I bagged my last girlfriend
in a Sirus. Picture up from work in it for a sunset flight. Regardless, Todd. Well, okay. He
is, he truly is a real pilot. Okay. And then the fly with me podcast. Oh, man, I'm not going
to be able to make this semi. Oh my goodness. The fly with me podcast is Joe Dion, who records
his colleagues, his flights, all kinds of stuff. And the most recent episode episode number eight
and you can find it from the show notes or from iTunes is all about danger and crashes. And
it's some really interesting stuff. And it may have been Betty. I can remember it was someone
who was talking about the about a hijacking to Cuba and how Fidel Castro came on board after the
hijacking and how they how they got everyone out of the plane. It's fascinating stuff to listen to
absolutely fascinating. And you really get a whole new respect for flight attendants because they
really are there for your safety. You know, they're there to make sure basically to save your
ass in the event of an emergency. And so they wind up talking about they wind up talking about
the air France plane that skidded off the runway and basically burst into flames that
everybody got out and how amazing that was and how they all sat and watched the TV coverage in
horror because, you know, they know exactly what's going on. And quite frankly, they were amazed
that everyone got out alive. And it really makes you realize when you listen to this podcast
that makes you realize just how important a job these flight attendants have. And, you know,
next time you're thinking that your drink isn't right or your meal was the wrong temperature or
whatever, you know, think about what they're really there for and they don't really get a
respect for their jobs anymore. I think it's, you know, people just don't realize what it is,
what their primary objective is. And it's really to keep you safe. And so there's a little bit
that I'm going to play now from the fly with me podcast, which is, it's kind of a mash up all on
its own, but it's just a little bit about about that plane evacuated. We evacuate airplanes every year.
Smoke filled cabins and fire blocked exits. By the way, I think in this case, they're talking about
their actual training. That's why they do it every single year, not that they have an accident
every year where they have to evacuate an airplane. So, I'm curious if like, you know, you're
looking at that as you see those pictures on TV, you're rehearsing it in your mind like what would
I be doing? Right. And you rehearse, rehearse, rehearse your exits. Thank you. And every circumstance
that could happen because it's always something different. Every time every crash, no crash is a lie.
Everyone's different. You just, you hope it's never going to happen to you, but.
Grab ankles, heads down, stay low, bend over, grab ankles, heads down, stay low, bend over,
grab ankles, get out, get out, get out, keep everything really steep out, get up, get out,
keep everything we keep out. Good exits, come this way, leave everything, arms straight ahead, jump
inside, leave everything, arms straight ahead, jump inside, good exit, come this way.
Ross and Nightmarish managed to listen to that it really is fantastic though and they do do a
fantastic job. Okay, so another executive decision, I guess we're not going to do the hit tasks.
I swear to myself, we make it 40 minutes a day and I have not done a good job of drop two
entire segments, which means my planning kind of sucks. And this immediately shows the disadvantage
of podcasting because I could go for the extra, what is the hit test is five minutes and 21 seconds
today. But I'm going to keep it, I'm going to use that tomorrow. I'll have less time tomorrow,
so I can still do a 40 minute show. The reason why I'm doing this is I'm ramping up, I'm practicing
because I want the pod show on serious, I want that to start replicating
some of what we're doing in the podcast space. So what that means is we're going to create the first
simulcast on satellite and podcast through the daily source code. And so that's why I'm trying
to get it down to either 20 minutes or 40 minutes. And it's going to be an interesting experiment,
but this is probably the final frontier for me, the final bit that I've been able to
to kind of finagle and shift and shape and form so that it works with podcasting is the concept
of, well, I actually do have to stop after 40 minutes. You know what? We'll leave it at that for today.
I still get to do the signature sign off, though. Stay subscribed.