Delta Sierra Charley 2-6-6
They're on your secrets.
Only information you don't get out of.
And I'm Korean.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
It is Tuesday, October 25th, 2005.
$25 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
And hello, everybody.
Second, let me just adjust all the levels here.
Welcome, it is, once again, right now I know it's going on.
There we go. Oh, yeah.
It's all that Apple stuff confused my mix here.
Hold on one second.
Oh, yeah, that's much, much better.
Yes, welcome to the Curry Condo.
On a Tuesday morning, it is bright and early.
It's about five minutes to nine,
funny to hear that transmitters.
We don't need those thinking transmitters.
As I look out the window, the condo is straight at the hills.
I see this huge antenna standing there.
My God.
I don't wonder, I just think I'm happy that I'm.
I don't have to be more for that thing.
Come in to you through iPods, MP3 players,
and computers everywhere.
Your daily source code for the next 15 minutes.
On safe tunes, promos.
A little bit woozy this morning.
We had a nice dinner last night to folks were up in San Francisco.
Actually, one was up from Los Angeles, Julia.
I'm pretty sure I've told you about Julia.
And Andrew Grumman from the iPod 11 team.
He was over from Massachusetts.
I'm from Boston.
And so we had a nice little sushi.
My goodness, the fish is still swimming around.
So if I were to say,
how could I get your day just popping off right?
This might be just what the doctor ordered.
Something that a dog from mash up town sent me a week or a week and a half ago.
It's a mix that kind of starts out and like, well, you'll hear it.
It's a mash up and starts up in kind of this like 60's vibe.
But when you get into it and you hear the songs that are mashed up together,
I think you'll think it.
It is title just what the doctor ordered.
The daily store's code for Tuesday, October 25th, 2005.
I don't need one to stand.
What a girl boy.
Whatever they say.
Have a sense in the face of the time.
I don't need one to stand.
What a girl boy.
There's one at the time.
I would mind how it's so good to you.
Right away, it's the height of the wrong view.
A cravings you never did.
And then I knew myself alone.
Baby, let's don't let it go.
We get the clowns like you should.
That's how you know.
It's for keeps on.
It's for sure.
And you're ready to win and give me more than what a girl boy.
What a girl boy.
Whatever they say.
Have a sense in the face of the time.
I don't need one to stand.
What a girl boy.
What a girl girl boy.
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh I just can't get enough of these Mash ups I
no I know I know not everyone feels that way yo some people say I hate those
Mash ups I shuttle right passed and well that's good
because you know at the beginning of every source code you can just shuttle past
the first four minutes then if you wish all though I'm going to surprise you
and I'm going to surprise you're going to change that around once in a while
So yesterday, we had a little porn fest here on the on the podcast.
Hold on, let me just turn this thing on here.
Something I wanted to tell you about later in just-
Okay, I'll get to that in a second.
Wait, actually, I should put a little bit closer so you can hear it if it acts up.
There we go.
So I opened up the the power book box and we sniffed all the Apple porn together.
And when I got to the office, I do these shows in the morning when I'm on the on the west coast.
Because of, well, obviously, of the the time difference.
God, I feel so behind the world out here.
I don't, I, how can, how can a part of the country that is so technologically advanced and has silicone valley feel so behind?
It's just crazy.
So I got to the office around 11 after uploading and doing all the stuff that I got to do.
And I got an email from Patricia and now Patricia rarely rarely sends me an email.
Maybe to forward something from somebody because we talk every single day.
You know, so anything that, that, you know, that needs to be said.
We talk about it when we're on the phone call or on the eye chatter, Skype or whatever.
But the subject was like, you know, nerd BS or some Dutch equivalent of that.
Because she sent it to me in Dutch.
She said, oh my God, I can't believe you're getting turned on by a power book.
You're sick.
But what that means is Patricia is now listening to the show.
Something she has not done for a year and a half.
I mean, sure, I'd play bits for her and, you know, we talk about stuff.
And she's been on the show many times.
But rarely will she just sit down and listen to a show.
And I'd set up her computer at home to be automatically subscribed to the source code.
And I guess she really does miss me because she's actually sitting there and listen to the source code.
And hopefully, dig in most of it's a high on me.
Hi, baby. How you doing?
I'll be enjoying the show.
Hey Adam, I'm Mary.
And I'm Carla.
From the Mary and Carla show.
That's Mary and Carla.com.
And we have to say, we saw your latest video cast.
And we hope that we are your first video promo.
That would be really cool.
I would be awesome.
And we love your rock and pad.
You have such a pimping pad.
If you need two hoties there to be laying out on your couch,
we'll be the one there.
We'll be wearing these pastoons.
That's all that we don't got a sexy one.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Maybe it looks witches.
We are two witches.
Well, we just wanted to say happy Halloween.
Happy Halloween and hope to see you at the X-Bow.
Cheers.
Now, what you did not see is Mary and Carla dressed up as witches.
Full on, full on witches costumes.
Of course, I'm going to put that in the podcast feed for today.
So you can enjoy that on your iPod or just download and take a look at it.
They really did a great job.
And let me just tell you, I love witches because my wife is one.
She is a white witch.
That's right.
Because you've got the black witches with the black magic.
And you've got the white witches with the somewhat less black magic.
And my wife definitely belongs to the latter.
And you know, it's, people always thought,
oh, it's pretty cool.
Adam's got a helly pad in his backyard.
That wasn't for the helicopter, my friends.
I was a place where Patricia could land her broomstick.
So yeah, okay, girls, we're great.
We'll see you at the podcast X-Bow.
Very cool.
It's not the first video promo I've received as such,
because I have received other forms.
So this is really the first one that you even called it a video promo.
And both of you were on camera.
So very cool, appreciate it.
And hopefully you got the Windows XP.
My buddy from Microsoft was going to send you guys.
Seeing as you needed that to hook up the Samsung or something like that.
So last night after I got back, it wasn't all that late.
It was like 1030.
And I flipped on the TV.
And this, this car rove and Libby and bush stuff.
It's really complicated.
At this point, I do no longer understand what is going on.
Now I'm only just picking up the sound bites,
which of course is horrible, and the sound by pretty much these days is,
well, so a perjury isn't illegal if they aren't indicted,
but perjury is breaking the law, but it isn't really.
And it's just confusing me.
What is going on?
And so what happens?
What happens if the president's advisors
are indicted, and lots of people will be resigning.
And I guess Harriet Myers will probably decline the nomination
to the Supreme Court.
Well, then what?
Who's next in line?
Who's going to, we need some guys somewhere,
or some woman to stand up and take charge.
And I'd love to hear your feedback on that.
We haven't done any real political stuff on the source code recently.
And that's basically because it's all been about the same topics on television.
And now I'm at the point where I don't even know if
the reporter who was thrown in jail, I forget her name.
Susan, I think.
I don't even know if she's on the up and up anymore.
It's so confusing.
What is the true story?
Who can just give me the facts on one paragraph?
And please don't write it, send it in as a,
let's get some audio feedback on this.
Let's get going and understand what's happening,
so we can open up a dialogue.
Because to me, it seems like everyone is just kind of,
you know, slapped back by this whole happening.
And it's just kind of like, okay, I guess it's kind of going,
it's course.
Except for John Stewart, of course.
I finally caught a new episode of the Daily Show last night.
Man, I guys, good.
He really is.
And it's the same John Stewart that was doing the John Stewart show.
God, like, 10 years ago, it's the same stuff.
It's exactly the same stuff.
Only now he has the outlet and it's being recognized,
and that's extremely cool.
So let's, let's get our own dialogue going here,
because we really haven't talked about,
you have listened to Madge.
Madge does a lot of, you know,
does a lot of political stuff.
But sometimes she winds up reading,
like, you know, complete articles,
and that's just boars me to, you hear that, Madge,
you bore me to tears with that.
I want the angry Madge back who has her own opinion,
it isn't reading other people's stuff.
And it just realized that I haven't even put in a
a pod-sake music track for today's show,
so I'm going to pull out a while,
I'll play the next two promos.
I'm going to pull out some good stuff,
some stuff that we've played previously,
pod-sake music, because that's one thing that I have noticed.
I wind up choosing pretty much a new pod-sake music track
every single day, but that really doesn't help the artist
just to play in once.
We've got to play him a couple of times.
So I'll look for that and you'll listen to this.
Everybody, how you doing?
Yeah, that's a fun day.
I'm afraid that something I cannot allow to happen.
This is not radio.
It's podcasting.
Hello, everybody.
This is Dan the Geek from the new Geekaster podcast.
I want all you guys to check out my podcast
at geekaster.tripod.com or just search for us in iTunes
under Eekaster.
Each week we talk about the hottest tech news
and play a bunch of awesome podcasts and music.
Please check us out at the Geekaster podcast
either at eekaster.tripod.com or subscribe to us in iTunes
under Eekaster.
Even if you just somewhat interested in technology, we want you.
What's the podcast that delivers all these things?
Um, um, what is going deep with the parallelizer
Fucking crap!
You just want to please the description too.
Go and deep with the parallelizer, Mr. Clean.
Oh, and the parallelizer.com.
I like to vote donuts.
Okay, I guess you'll have to wait for the show notes to figure out what that was about.
This is the Daily Source Code playing
absolutely the best and pod save music
there is to be found.
This is the singing waiter from New York, my buddy,
Brother Love.
And when we get our unlabeled going,
we're just gonna be the first guy I saw.
Someone else doesn't get to it before me, God damn it.
There she goes. Brother Love on the source code.
Hit it by brother.
It's alright when it's okay.
Yeah, you never saw that anybody else says,
such a stuff that want to think I'm in love with you.
Come on.
Your size is sweet and little on it.
Your smile is the least in the love me.
Just that guy.
We're going to start.
I don't want we can do it.
Yeah, I go.
And yeah, I've been told I can't win.
So there it is.
First you sing you can't.
Well, let me say you can't.
You don't want to take it's hands.
Well, my name is hilarious.
I'm a laborer.
I must be the biggest sucker.
The status of the bill.
Believe in me.
This guy was, this guy was,
this guy was, this guy was,
when she goes, no one knows.
Oh, oh, man she's bad.
And I should know that she'll be back again.
This guy was, this guy was,
when she goes again.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So there it is.
This guy was, so it is.
So there it is, so there it is, she died.
She died to tell the story.
Oh
Oh my God, she doesn't want to cut him up,
I really love you, baby, I love you, baby, I love you, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby,
để when I fall in love with you, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby baby, baby, baby baby, baby, baby, baby, baby baby, baby,
But as he comes, I can't
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, it's not I'm about to laugh
I know you need a lot of faith
I'm at myże choose a place when you think of your mind
We go red I was going, go pandas with each edge
I'm like a candle, not a candle, not a candle, not a candle
But I told you that you got my 으
No you've got my name on Bertiousuck
restore your brightness, i don't drink
Get it ya know, let's eat run
Let's eat run, let's eat run
Let's eat run, let's eat
Let's eat cuters
Let's eat, let's eat run
Let's eat run
There she goes from the pod save music network music.potshow.com and I got lots of emails
still every single day people asking about music on podcast and what the rights are.
So here's the basic lowdown.
If you're new to podcasting and want to play some music, the best place to go to the
pod save music network because once you sign up there as a podcaster anything you find
there you can play on your show royalty free.
Doesn't mean there is no license involved in fact there is a license that's what you sign up for.
And the deal is are just put their songs up there you can use it on your podcast
as long as you report it back into the system everything's hunky dory.
And you pretty much want to stay away from everything else.
Although there are some other sites on the internet where you can also get pod save music.
I'm not too sure about the license is there though.
What you don't want to do is play something you purchase off the iTunes music store.
And let me just tell you about the hit test and the backtracks podcast because people ask me,
how do you get away with that?
That's pretty much under the fair use version of Doctrine if you didn't call it that.
In fact, ask happened to be am I don't even pay artists if their songs have been played for less than 90 seconds.
And so we kind of keep it under 60 seconds on the hit test.
And in fact, all it does is it inspires people to go and buy those tracks off of for instance.
iTunes music store and that really does work.
You know, and you just head over to yonpolet.com and you can find links to every single track that was used in a hit test.
If available in the iTunes music store, of course.
So that's how we get away with that.
And now that I've set up my new computers, now I still have my old iPod,
which has filled with my 6,000 tracks.
But even back to the Napster days when we could freely share MP3 files.
So I've got, you know, all the oldies I've ever wanted are on there.
But all my new machines, I've made kind of a vow to myself.
I'm only putting pod safe music on it.
And really just for the experience to see, you know, how, how will it work for me?
Is that going to be enough for the satisfy my, my musical desires?
And guess what?
It's doing fantastic.
It really is work.
Particularly the G5 iMac.
I got to say, they've done it once again.
This whole concept of the 10-foot interface, which, you know, if you, if you saw the,
Steve Jobs presentation of the new iPod and what I think was more exciting was the new,
the new iMac and that presentation.
You get a little remote control with it, which,
amazingly enough, it actually attaches to the side.
There you go.
Of the iMac with little magnet.
I don't know how they did that without screwing up hard drives.
And it gives you, literally, it's like the size of a shuffle.
In fact, it's probably a shuffle case.
Julia pointed that out yesterday.
It's probably a shuffle in casing.
As a menu button on it, and that brings up this,
what, you know, what they're calling the 10-foot interface,
which kind of turns your iMac into a huge iPod.
It has a very similar type of scrolling,
and, and clicking interface.
And you get your, your volume and your forward, your back,
and your, and your pause buttons.
But so I just swing the iMac around.
It's done the couch and, you know,
and stuff just comes in.
That's what's so cool about it.
It's, it feeds itself.
So new podcasts come in.
I'm subscribed to a couple of XML feeds on the pod save music network,
which means new tracks by certain artists or tracks that are played on a certain podcast.
We'll come in automatically into into the system.
Video podcasts, which we're very well.
Oh, man.
Father Roderick did another Catholic minute.
He's really on the forefront of experimenting with, you know,
what you can do.
He took a train ride to France and documented the whole thing.
It's only like two or three minutes,
very, very good.
Go to CatholicInsider.com to find out how to subscribe to the Catholic minute.
And, and what's happening is my machine is turning into just this really
fun device that always has something new for me, you know,
and you just sit on the couch and use the remote control and click it.
And of course, I've got to hooked up to the,
MM50 Logitech speakers.
So it fills the, the condo nicely.
And I'm really enjoying this.
And, and as I've been hinting at,
we're going to be coming out with,
what the unlabel, because just as everything else has turned upside down on,
it's head broadcasting has been completely turned around.
So we'll, the music industry,
we're already proving that with the pod safe music network,
creating our own superstars,
right in our own, in our own world and it's,
and it's like an oil spill.
You know, it's spreading out all over the world.
People everywhere talking about the pod safe music vibe.
And so, of course, the next logical step is the unlabel.
And what is that?
Well, we've got some ideas.
And I think that within the next month or so,
we'll be announcing ways that anyone can participate
in the unlabel concept.
Oh, we were talking about it earlier.
Okay.
Madge has something to say, hold on.
Hello, Adam.
It's Madge here once again.
Hey, Madge.
Listen, I have another boner to pick with you.
Uh-huh.
This time it's about this video blogging business.
Yeah.
Now, you said, and you show yesterday,
that there doesn't seem to be very much good content out there.
Well, did it ever occur to you, Adam's carry?
That may be video blogging existed before you found out about it.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Calm down, Madge.
Calm down.
Uh, I've been video blogging myself for quite a while.
This is the first time, though,
that we have a portable device that it sinks to,
but okay, I'll let you have your minute here.
Did you ever think of that for a change?
Christ's sake.
Anyway, I want to tell you that there are some wonderful sights,
and wonderful feeds that I've been watching for several months now.
These, I'm going to tell you what my favorite ones are.
They are amazing.
You know, I like video blogs that are stimulating.
What is it?
Is it video blog or is it video podcast?
I'm going to stay with the video podcast.
You know, because I think the podcast is,
can be anything.
It can be anything you can ship along with an RSS feed
to take into the technical realm,
but video podcast, audio podcast, PDF podcast,
all that is possible.
Okay.
You know, it doesn't have to be all pussy and down
with the home boys and all that business.
I like intelligent work.
Adam's carry.
And you can, you know, find your sense.
I'm put it on a webcam or whatever.
But here's what I like.
And these are really stimulating wonderful web blogs.
There are so much good stuff out there.
So don't start with that bullshit about this.
Nothing good out there because there's no titty porn.
And well, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, match.
Perhaps I should have let the audience enjoy your girdle
gazon.
No, that wasn't porn at all, my dear.
And fisting porn in all the shit.
Besides, it probably is.
Anyway, bottomunion.com is wonderful.
It's a Dutch guy who is, well, he's American,
but he lives in Holland.
He is a very tall, good looking man.
It's phenomenally amazing videos that you may actually
want to grab a pencil and jot some of this down.
You know, this seems like a really long comment match.
I'm going to let you go for a little bit.
But I don't know if I can listen to another five minutes of your,
or your, you get to write.
Just write that on your way.
So it's bottomunion.com.
Human dog dot com.
That's human dash dog dot com.
Somebody I have had here on my show often.
That's Chris Weagle moment showing.
Is J. Deadman.
J. Deadman has been spearheading the vlogging revolution.
For the past year or so, he founded the video blogging conference.
And he works on fire ants and a whole bunch of other stuff.
Maybe he didn't find found it alone.
I'm sure Dave Wine did it too.
Yeah.
I'm sure Dave Wine owned bed today.
Everything.
Free vlog.
I think it's free vlog.com.
Michael Verde and Ryan Hubson are doing this.
And this is an amazing site where it shows you how to do video blogging for free.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Madge, why don't you just make a blog post somewhere so we can read all those links.
Oh my goodness.
Well, put this crap on your own show.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
So, well, Madge just rambles on the background there.
I wanted to share a little new toy with you.
Hold on a second.
Let me turn it on.
Okay.
So when we were in New York,
this must have been about six weeks ago.
And we were presenting to Madison have new advertising agencies.
Advertisers themselves.
You know, Ron and I were doing these little road shows.
Talking about podcasting, showing the possibilities.
Is Madge still doing this thing?
Is that called the vlog of the day?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
And so one of the agencies,
OMD actually was very excited about a new product that they
definitely wanted to promote via podcasting.
And it made a lot of sense to them because it's basically part of a
an item that is a part of the iPod economy, which means, you know,
it's like the MM50 from Logitech is part of the iPod economy.
And when I heard about it, wait a minute, what's Madge saying?
God damn shit.
As soon as that hurricanes of it,
this lady I love laughing.
Okay, so Madge will just continue there.
And when they talked about it, you know, the first thing,
you know, we kind of all looked at each other when like,
my God, who's going to want that thing?
I mean, that's like that sounds just lame.
And then when I got home,
when I was back home at the cottage,
unsolicited Christina,
who I definitely feel is on the cutting edge of hip.
She, I mean, she knows what's cool.
Okay, all kids know what's cool.
And she's not a kid, she's a young adult.
And she said, you know, dad will be very cool
as that is the eye dog.
And I went like, huh?
What do you mean that thing that I saw that we may be promoting soon
on the pod show podcast network?
And she said, yeah, it's this thing.
You hook it up to your iPod or who you hook it up to your speakers
of your computer.
And it does stuff and it dances along.
And you know what?
Well, here we are.
We're a couple weeks further.
This is the Hasbro eye dog.
You can hear it's a shut up match.
Let me see.
It's kind of a cross between, well,
obviously a cross between iPod speakers.
But, you know, the Sony eye bow, the robot dog.
And I had both the first and the second version of the,
of the eye bow, the Sony robot dog.
Which was in, in a way, it was very cool
because it was kind of like a nano pet
for grownups.
Only, it was $5,000.
Which made it all that less cool by the time you actually
were kind of done playing with it.
It was a very freakish type of toy.
Now this, of course, doesn't cost, this is like 30 bucks.
Someone who was in 30 and 40 bucks.
And it actually is.
It's, it's kind of cute.
It's a dog that has, it's in the same color
and kind of a nearing finish as an iPod white.
It's, it's small, it's about the size of a, of a mouse.
And what it does, it has a, it has all kinds of sensors in it.
So, if you rub it on it head, then all kinds of lights go off
and it's, and it's, in its head.
Which it also does in synchronous air.
You should have seen this thing,
Bob and to brother love.
It was pretty cool.
And then you can, I think you can,
it could, does have some of those nano pet capabilities.
And so if you, if you hit his tail,
that means that he's been bad.
And of course he'll do nothing after that.
But when you play in music,
and either you can, you can stick it,
they, they supply a cable.
You can stick it in, you know,
into your speaker jack.
And then it'll actually function as an external speaker.
You can put it, you know, you can attach your iPod to it.
So you can use it as a speaker,
but at the same time, the dog is just vibing.
And you don't, you don't just put it near a speaker
to work because it has a built-in microphone.
And I must say, it's,
it is kind of cute.
And probably the perfect Christmas gift.
If you want to give someone who's into,
look at his shaking, it's head and moving to Sears.
Oh, that's what I'll do.
I'll do a video podcast on the dog.
There you go.
Well, synchronize the dog's movements with, with some audio,
which, of course, it kind of does automatically.
But it's, it's probably, it's a really good Christmas gift.
If you want to know more about it,
check out the show notes at dating source code.com
or curry.com.
And just click on the picture of the, of the eye dog
to find out more.
Let's see, 31 minutes.
I'd say a little more pod safe music right now.
I've played this one before too, but I'm just so crazy
about what this girl is doing.
Her name is Robin Stein.
This is Sweet Blossom.
My dear, I'm crazy for you.
I don't know what I should do.
Stay here, or follow you on home.
I make him for a kiss.
I'll be a sweet tender lips.
I'll either have your start to warm.
Because I can't be around you.
And be with you.
If you refuse to come with me,
I'll go at a long time.
I'm waiting for a day.
When I can't find her, we'll see.
My dear, sweet Blossom, there for me.
I'll go at a long time.
Because I can't be around you.
And be with you.
If you refuse to come with me,
I'll go at a long time.
I'm waiting for a day.
When I can't find her, we'll see.
My dear, sweet Blossom, there for me.
Straight from the current condo,
from the 24th floor, San Francisco, Northern California.
Robin Stein, sweet Blossom from the Podsake Music Network,
I got to hook up this eye dog to an input on the mixer
because he actually starts barking in rhythm with the music.
It's so stupid, it's cool.
I don't know what it is.
If it didn't look as cool, it might not be so nice,
but I'm digging it, I'm digging it definitely.
So Robin Stein, of course,
can be found at the Podsake Music Network,
music.podshow.com or Podsake Music Network.com.
And a little bit more about those music rights.
I've been doing some more research on exactly how licensed music is sold.
And man, I gotta tell you that it's almost like you're setting yourself up
for failure with this stuff.
Look at these music services.
I found out how kind of the money flows.
So we know that on the iTunes music store,
it's 99 cents and the record companies are really trying to raise that price.
And of course, Apple will be fighting that because that's kind of the whole point of their offering.
You have this wonderful, beautiful looking device in many, many different forms.
And you can fill that up.
And it's a 99, it will basically buck a song to fill it up.
And now the record companies want to raise that price.
Notice that they never ever want to reduce the price on anything.
And I think that Apple is probably making, this is not,
this is more guesstimate, but I do have some insight information.
They're probably making about three cents a song.
Each time you purchase a track through the iTunes music store.
And I thought that the services like Napster and what else you have,
Rhapsody and Yahoo's music store.
I thought that that was basically a performance right.
You know, because all you do there is you don't get to keep the songs.
Download and put them on your MP3 player, keep them on your computer.
And then when you stop paying the monthly subscription, which is somewhere like 20 bucks,
then the songs basically go away.
Now, I thought that that was more or less done like satellite radio,
where you, they pay, ask at BMI for each song that is essentially transferred.
But it turns out there's a whole complicated mix of pieces that go to the performance rights companies,
like ask at BMI, pieces that go to the record companies.
Once again, the guys there wind up making very, very little money unless they have huge scale.
So, I'm just, as I said, it's pod say fall the way for me.
And, oh, keep those Christmas tracks coming to the pod sake music network.
I'm still looking for the, you know, a couple of quintessential tracks that we can really promote
as the Christmas songs.
We need some new ones, you know, I'm so tired of grandma got run over by a reindeer
and root off the red nose reindeer and here comes Santa Claus.
I'm sure we, you know, someone out there has some new tracks.
I know the Lee Harris 3 has uploaded like 50, 50 Christmas tunes.
I haven't listened to them all, but I'm certainly going to be playing one of those.
And if you've got any Christmas tracks that you deem pod safe,
just sign up to the pod sake music network and give her a whirl.
There, Adam, this is VT from the Gaming's Edge weekly roundup podcast.
I was just sending you some audio feedback to let you know that I'm totally jealous of all
your hot new Apple porn, such a fucking tease.
I dare you to play that.
But you know, I can't afford new shit.
Apple porn.
Anyway, speaking of Apple, I was curious to get your thoughts and maybe you can share them
with the, the, the listenership here as to the current state and future development
of the podcast section in the iTunes music store.
You know, that's pretty much become one of the major places where people go
to find podcasts and subscribe to them and such.
But it occurs to me that there are a few key things that are really missing from that,
that section of the music store in its current state.
So here are my big three.
Okay. Number one, I think it would be really cool if they had user reviews for podcasts,
the same way they now do for albums.
Number two, I think it would be really cool if they had, you know,
just the star rating system type thing like they have for eye mixes that
users can submit for podcasts.
And number three, I think it would be exceptionally cool if they had sort of
back end for actual podcasters to be able to go in and see how many times
people are clicking on their their show.
How many times they're listening to previews via the music store or what have you.
And also if they're, if they're unsubscribing, if that data is being collected
somewhere, I as a podcaster would definitely like to be able to see it.
Now, I know you meet periodically with the folks at Apple and talk about podcasting
and other related matters.
So I figured I'd drop you a line and try to get your thoughts on that.
On a totally unrelated subject, well, it's related because it's podcasting.
I just wanted to mention that gaming's edge now has two podcasts,
the weekly roundup, the one we've had for a while now,
and a new video podcast called Gaming's Edge Video in Pressions,
where we pick a different video game each week and spend about 15 to 20 minutes
going through it with video footage that is, of course,
a viewable on things like your sexy new iPod.
So give it a look.
Let us know what you think.
And by all means share your thoughts on the ITMS stuff that I just mentioned.
Thanks.
All right, buddy.
VT.
Yeah.
Well, you know what's cool about Apple is that they say,
this is Steve's words, Steve Jobs words.
They say no a lot to a lot of stuff.
They really Apple is a relatively small company in comparison,
certainly on the development side.
And that's kind of the big secret is that all these big companies do have relatively small
development groups.
And I think that what you're seeing is, of course, Apple could do all of that.
But that's not their core business.
They want to sell iPods.
And so what they do, and I think they're very smart about this,
is they facilitate a lot.
And they leave a lot of stuff open.
I mean, without the, the iTunes API, the application programmers interface,
now I never would have been able to create the first iPod or to get stuff,
you know, that was downloaded onto onto your iPod.
So they do leave a lot of that stuff open.
And I think that all the features you described is pretty much,
what anyone who's doing a directory in podcasting or a place,
you know, creating a discovery place is going to have all of that.
But you're really talking more about some of the social networking aspects of podcasting.
And we've got our eye on that.
And our finger on the pulse, if you will, it goes from everything from,
you know, one to one podcast, nothing wrong with that, by the way.
You know, making a podcast for one person or, you know,
how about, you know, a happy birthday podcast.
Or look at Mary and Carla, duking it out with the tipsy chicks.
You know, that's, that's two to two, basically.
That's their tag team and we're allowed to watch in a voyeuristic mode.
The user reviews, the big thing, of course, is statistics.
That is the number one thing that has gone wrong with just about every podcasting initiative
or just a podcast distribution initiative that has cropped up.
And I think that that's something where a lot can be done.
Because if you're doing a podcast, the first thing you want to know is,
you know, and if you can't get the numbers, then it sucks, you know,
and certainly the distribution partner that Apple is using isn't very good at,
because they don't do that themselves.
They're not very good at providing statistics.
In fact, very poor at providing statistics.
So that's a lot of the stuff that we intend on making better.
So I totally appreciate the feedback and believe me, the team is listening.
Hey, you had a Mark Jensen from Potsquad.com.
Not, not your pod squad, but this is, I guess, the Florida pod squad.
And I hope you don't mind, but I had no idea that you guys had a pod squad before I got the name.
And so anyway, it's PODSQOD and I came up with it, did some Google searches.
And of course, after I got the whole site set up in WordPress and everything,
you know, I found out that you had your own pod squad.
So I apologize and I hope you don't mind.
No big buddy.
I've kind of kept it, but of course it is spelled differently.
So anyway, the reason I am sending you the voice note here is,
Ray Lane, I was listening to the DSC.
And I heard you mention his name, and it's like, wow, I know that guy.
And I worked for Oracle Corporation.
And Ray Lane was probably one of the best things that had ever happened to that company.
And of course, he's no longer there.
I think he went on to bigger and better, but I just wanted to tell you you're obviously with a class act
and to tell Ray Lane that former employee of his says, hi,
from sunny Orlando, Florida at one of the super centers here right by the airport.
So anyway, I thought that was pretty cool that you've partnered up with him.
And he is a great guy that really cares about what he's doing,
and cares about the people that are working not for him, but with him.
And you know, he's just got that kind of philosophy.
And whenever you get the opportunity to work with somebody like that, it's really a privilege.
Anyway, just a quick hello from not so sunny Florida anymore.
We're waiting on the hurricane, probably just going to get kind of a windstorm,
maybe some rain here in Central Florida, but we'll see in the next couple days.
But meanwhile, people are kind of freaking out.
And I really don't expect anything more than a beautiful windstorm.
We went to the super market and water sold out people are kind of freaking out about that.
So anyway, I think things will be fine and hopefully not a repeat of what happened
to be poor people to the little bit to the west of us.
So anyway, Adam, hope to see you at the Expo.
Can't wait for the four and a half hour plane ride and talk to you then.
All right. Obviously, this is some feedback I've been holding for a couple of days.
I just haven't gotten around to it.
And you know, this one more piece of feedback I want to play just a wind up today show because otherwise,
these things just really run out of sync when they were sent somewhere they're being played on the show.
This is, well, this is from Dennis.
Hi, Adam. This is Dennis Gray from 101 uses for baby wipes.
The aka the daddy cast.
Yeah, that label kind of stuck.
Just wanted to send you some audio feedback.
First off, let me say thanks for all your help in promoting all of us starving podcasters out here in the puddle sphere.
And I really appreciate it.
I'm having way too much fun doing this.
Frankly, I forgot how much fun Mr. Mike phone really is.
Now, my feedback is about three issues.
Number one, I'm really hoping that one of your upcoming dam announcements is going to be the official launch of podshow.
So as budding podcasters have a place to host our files.
You know, it's a double-edged sword. You get popular. You get a bunch of subscribers.
And then you can't afford the bandwidth.
My server right now is in a quivering puddle of goo over in a corner of a server and somewhere in Minneapolis, I think.
The second item.
But I'm really looking forward to more details on your promo additions.
You've really kind of teased this in the recent source codes.
And I'm celebrating all over my pod filter here.
Could you tease us a little more?
But my last point is aimed at the podcast community in general.
You know, I'm finding out as I do this.
We have a pretty large audience.
And we have the ability to affect change in things that we believe in.
And I have approached several nonprofits for permission to play their PSA.
Since a lot of them are done by big name artists and I don't want to get sued.
Just want to cover all the bases and make sure it was legal to play these things.
And to my surprise, all the organizations that I approached didn't just say,
Yeah, but hell yeah, play them.
They're enthusiastic about getting their message out.
And I have approached charities that I support.
And I play their PSA's way of helping out their causes.
And I'd like to encourage other podcasts producers to do the same and support their favorite charities.
Anyway, that's it, Adam.
I'm a faithful listener, pod father.
Now I now bow and kiss your feet and kiss your ring.
Thank you very much.
I'm an evangelist for the podcast cause, really.
I believe in it.
And so let's get those 100 million listeners marching and get the advertisers to come with it
cause I really like to quit my day job.
Thanks again, Adam.
See ya.
All right, buddy.
Well, indeed news coming soon about the PDN and about those auditions.
Oh yeah.
And that's it for today's show.
Story.com.
Send me your feedback.
Podsafe music network is where you can find any of the songs played on today's show.
Except for the mashup that can be found at mashuptown.com.
And I'm sure we'll have lots more to talk about tomorrow.
Once again, coming to you from actually today it is sunny northern California.
So take care of y'all.
I'm gonna.
That's it.
Only one bark for everybody.
I don't have to do the lighter click.
Another Pod Show Podcast.
Stick it in your ear.