Delta Shara Charly 2-3-3
Yo DJ, are you the next player?
Your DJ has only just begun.
With $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
I just think it's a battle curry.
Bunny Bunny, it is the first of September 2005 at your source code.
Wow, those of you who have been listening to the source code for a while will know that at the beginning of each month you're supposed to say
Bunny Bunny or Rabbit Rabbit or something like that, and good fortune will come to you.
It's exactly what my fortune could be said the other day.
It is Thursday.
This is September 1st.
Your deadly source code from Curry Cottage in Gilford.
Time now is sort of 7 minutes before 2.
It is much smaller today.
Yesterday was a mega scorcher.
31 degrees centigrade in the shadow.
Dude, it was very hot here in the studio complex.
I was all psyched up today because I got some exciting news to talk about.
All right, it's supposed to news.
Yeah, it's news.
It's something that we've changed.
I think it would be interesting.
And my bar stool was supposed to be coming today.
That will happen tomorrow, but I've got one coming to complete the podcast complex.
That of course, the pod save music ready to roll for you.
It's morning.
Again, I got a really late start.
First of all, Patricia had a major coughing attack around 6 a.m.
Of course, I woke up.
My brain starts to spin.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Curry.com is down.
Any podder.org is down.
I'd take Patricia to the hospital.
Not for the coughing.
She got kind of sailing for that yesterday.
But to have an x-ray taken over neck, which is bothering.
I've been bothering her for the past couple weeks.
Everything's okay, though.
We're rolling now.
And curry.com is back up.
And indie pod.org will be back up very shortly.
So I'll tell you what the genesis is of all of that.
And some important news about the pod safe music network.
All of that today on Thursday's edition of the Daily Source Code.
To kick it off, though, we've got an awesome mashup.
The dog smells like roses.
99X served up to you by mashuptown.com.
On the daily source code.
We're rolling now.
So close.
We're going.
We're rolling now.
We're doing.
We're rolling.
We're rolling now.
Well, I smell smoke, he smells like a dog, the old junkie, to the ROS ESC team.
The dog smells like roses, 99X mashed it up for you here on the daily source code.
What ever happened to apps, Axel Rose?
I know he was back doing some stuff, but man, those days of guns and roses, they
will never return.
I'm afraid.
But where were they superstars at the time?
Man, that was good times.
So we have established now that the daily source code, when playing, and not just the source
code, but mashups and other features such as the hit test and the backtracks podcast.
They sell tracks on Apple's iTunes.
It's a proven.
We have a good sample of people who have spent anywhere from a couple bucks to over $3,000
Canadian, just a purchase, music that they've heard, all from the back catalog, wouldn't
be surprised if someone ran off and purchased a couple of guns and roses tunes today
after hearing that mashup.
So I've been experimenting, put a couple of Amazon links into the full outline of the show
notes, which you can find now at www.curry.com, back up online, and daily source code.com.
So I'd also applied for an iTunes affiliate status.
And I received an email this morning.
Dear Adam Curry, we regret to inform you that iTunes has chosen not to accept your application
for the iTunes affiliate program at this time.
This may be because the content is unrelated to iTunes, doesn't sound right?
Your site is temporarily down or under construction, well, that of course could have happened
yesterday, but this application went in much, much earlier than that.
Please make sure to apply again after two weeks.
So I got to wait two weeks, at least for that.
The wrong or mispelled URL, no, I did that, did the right one.
Your site is aesthetically unpleasing.
Yeah, it could be that.
Your site promotes tobacco alcoholic beverages or excessive drinking or drug use.
My site doesn't.
Your site contains extreme religious content.
Your site is international.
With a majority of visitors based outside the US or written in a foreign language, it is based
outside the US, but the majority of visitors, I think, are US.
So if any of the above problem on a criteria can be resolved, we look forward to your
re-application.
Okay, I'll do it after two weeks.
Or of course, if anyone in Apple's listening, you could just kind of shuttle me through
when make it happen.
You can prove more points and make more money and sell more iPods, but that would be just
up to you guys, not up to me.
Okay, what should we talk about first?
I think curry.com is a good one because it was down for cash.
Must have been down for about 14 hours, as well as indiepotter.org, formerly known as iPotter.org.
Problem.
He's going to love this.
Now, we're in the process of migrating this stuff over to a much stronger server.
You know, this is a server, I'll actually a couple of servers that I've had for a long
time.
I'm, you know, in in server years, like three years is a really long time.
And I built up a whole infrastructure at an ISP, actually, a co-location facility in
the Netherlands, who I work with for a long time, and they've always done great justice
by me.
So I've been up quite in infrastructure, you know, servers talk to each other and handing
data off from one to the other and load balancing.
And, you know, the typical stuff you get set up over the years without doing a formal architecture,
you know, kind of just doing it.
And so, you know, there's all kinds of strings and wire and a gaffer tape, but it all works
kind of.
And we've been doing a lot better.
And now that we've, you know, reduced the traffic, which was really killing the server
of comments spam.
I'm talking like one a second, you know, boom, boom, boom, boom, just sending comments spam
and comments, of course, you take up server resources, because there's a post involved
in a database access.
So we've been resolving that mark as we've been doing a great job.
And, but still, the application that's running does fail once in a while.
And, and sometimes, you know, also just for this whole move, we've got to be in the box.
And the hosting facility that I've been working with, apparently, the beginning of this
week went into chapter 11, which means that now the cash flow positive, it's one of their
debtors has debtors, creditors, I'm sorry, has put them into the Dutch equivalent
of chapter 11.
So they still continue to operate because they are cash flow positive.
But there's a court-appointed entity called the curator, which is just another lawyer,
who came up with the luminous idea to block port 22, which is the SSH port, as you know.
So that no one could change anything from the outside.
Well, of course, there are customers there.
I believe even you too, as a customer, I'm not sure.
I think some of their multimedia stuff is at the same hosting collocation.
So you can't change anything, or you can't log into your box via SSH, which is the only
way to get in, really, on a secured box.
And so, you know, we couldn't get a work around.
We basically had to wait for a court order to gain access from dedicated IPs.
And what we basically, we finally figured out the guys and gals over there worked very
hard to help us out.
And so that's back up and rolling.
And in the meantime, we done some DNS tricks to at least resolve something.
So we could give you a message about what's going on.
That's why IndiePotter.org probably, by the time you hear this, it may start resolving
back to the normal server, but that can take up to 24 hours, even longer than that.
So a little glitch in the system.
Sock to just a bit, but there you go.
We're back.
That really sucks, though.
It's a freaking horrible.
When your server is down, you can't do anything other than literally jump on an airplane
and fly over and go sit in front of the console yourself, which was not really an option
at this point.
So I said that my bar stool was going to come today.
Tom Hickey emailed me a while ago and he says, look, I've got a bar stool store online.
It'd be happy to sponsor the Daily Source Code with one.
He didn't even want anything in return.
He said, this is actually just for all the fun shows you've given me, which is great.
But of course, I'll plug this shit out of him.
He was going to show up today.
That's actually why I kind of planned the source code to be around this time.
But I guess he's going to show up tomorrow.
So I'll try and coordinate the show when he actually comes in.
So we can test it live on the air.
So to speak.
One quick little email here, this is a fun for an experiment, something we can do.
Well, I'm moving around my stuff here.
I want to talk about the Podsate music network in a couple minutes.
Email from DGA Stapons.
He's from Belgium from Bossles.
He says, this is really interesting.
And I like what he said here.
I listen a lot to podcasts when I walk to the office and when I work out, running, writing
my mountain bike, race bike, bouldering, whenever he's bouldering.
I've noticed that locations can trigger my memory about a particular podcast.
It happened again today.
I rode my mountain bike along a route I take frequently, west of Brussels.
And in a certain road crossing, I remember a discussion about a new tablet PC on the tablet
PC show.
I'd listen to it in the previous time.
I rode past that location.
Kind of a reverse sound seeing.
Things I see trigger sounds I hear.
Have you experienced this or have people mentioned this to you?
OK.
Now, this is very interesting.
Because what I want to do in experiment with you right now, you listening to this show.
Look up, look at your environment, look at a road sign, or something by the road.
Just something that the first thing you see, the first thing that comes to mind.
And now, remember, senseo.
So the next time you drive by, see if the senseo, this is a great advertising trick.
See if senseo pops into your head.
If it does, then we'll have learned something very critical to podcasting,
and the way they're consumed, and open up a whole new avenue for advertising.
So whatever that road sign was or that house, or some stationary object that you saw whenever
you see that next time, you're not going to be able to help yourself, but think senseo.
I was not paid by senseo for this experiment, but I'm happy to do so.
Hello, it's me, which you taught, Rutherford.
Hey, you know what? Nothing's funny today.
That's close to that hurricane that head down there.
Oh, he is bad, and I know you're saying it on the news and stuff.
And there's a bunch of people down there that lies this Torah.
Thank God, now I have to live in, nothing to eat, nothing to drink,
hang out, no, nothing, no clothes, they don't need some help.
They really are now.
If you be so kind, it's a go-like to the salvation army and give some clothes,
some old clothes or your shoes and stuff.
Now, if you go red cross dot org, and it's given some money or some time and years,
that'd be so good if you could do that, he just be precious.
Cause they need some help, and I think we all ought to just lean into it and give them some help.
I'd really appreciate it, and I know they would, do you know what, as you would do?
Now, this is Richard Talbrath, a fern, and we're seeing.
Pot, Joe, content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
Yeah, this VT, here with you, Con, we're here to tell you about the gaming's edge, weekly round-up.
It's not your typical gaming podcast.
It's better than episode two of the Star Wars movies.
That's really not saying much, is it?
Unless anyone in the world thinks that the United States has the market cornered on reckless,
irresponsible behavior.
This flash jack, there's porn available for download.
This podcast by www.gamingzedge.com.
Okay, that promo was sent in by Michael.
Who actually responded to my question about what DS was, and GBA,
he says the DS is the Nintendo DS, the latest handheld gaming device.
Letters DS refer to the system's dual screens.
And the GBA is the Game Boy Advance, which was Nintendo's previous handheld system,
still in the wild use by gamers and backwards compatible with original Game Boy games.
And he said, okay, now please play the damn promo.
So did that. Before that, of course, which you tall rather third, with another plea to help out
for the victims of Hurricane Katrina. I've got a great email about that as well.
From Daria Muirhead, I believe.
He says, my new podcast, boutique cafe is almost ready to launch.
We're doing a show late this week about Hurricane Katrina.
How people can help and get involved.
Our boutique selling community is vast and a big heart of the group.
Many of our fellow designers that we have known have lost their homes and all of their possessions.
Fellow designers have joined together to give from our hearts.
Please go to eBay and search boutique angels.
These talented designers are donating 100% of the proceeds
through the Verifiable eBay Charity Association of Mission Fish to Mercy Corps.
Hurricane Katrina Fund. These sellers are giving of their talents,
time and materials to make some beautiful boutique items.
So please ask your listeners to check the oxides out,
bid on some gorgeous one of a kind items to support Mercy Corps.
And those that need so much help right now.
And that's boutiquefade.com.
Links, of course, in the show notes as a man, as it continues to really suck in New Orleans.
At part of Louisiana, Mississippi, Red Cross.org is where you can continue to go and donate money.
And if you have time and you can donate that to help, I think that's going to be very, very welcome.
It does seem like we have a lot of government resources coming into view now.
Big naval ship coming alongside. We've got some reserves.
Who aren't in Iraq coming in, but see, I think that this is a pretty big disaster.
And it's hard to get resources down there.
The news media are just now kind of really setting up big camps.
I'm not quite sure they knew what to think of it, but once again,
we only need to come together and help each other out.
I think the Red Cross is the best way to go.
Quick note from Bill Lefler on the biodiesel.
He says he loves the biodiesel idea about being able to crap in your tank.
I think we need to talk to Rota Router about some joint development of this technology.
I mean, if they're pumping this stuff out of my septic tank already, why can't they pump it back into my gas tank?
Of course, if the cooking oil biodiesel smells like french fries, dot, dot, dot.
It would be cool if that was actually possible. I would love it.
Okay, let's talk about the pod safe music network.
The last week was the last week.
It's more than more than a week and a half ago on boingboingboing.net.
Cory Doctro posted a piece about the terms of use and the agreement terms for podcasters
at the pod safe music network at podsafemusic.network.com.
The piece that he wrote was poorly researched and poorly written.
I have to say they're all kinds of factual mistakes in there.
But he did have an interesting point that the terms basically limited free speech for podcasters
by saying that you're not allowed to talk about hacking or other illegal activity in your podcast.
And let me just tell you why and how and how we work at pod show.
First of all, the pod safe music network has been in data for a couple of weeks.
We actually had a closed data before that.
When we brought in six or seven music podcasters, we brought in,
well actually they brought in a number of artists and we beta tested the whole site.
And a big part of that beta test was actually also the terms and conditions.
And we did adjust some terms and conditions during that beta period.
So we've been in beta for about four weeks now.
And we're just about actually we put out a press release.
And over a thousand podcasters have signed up already.
Over a thousand artists, there's thousands of registered listeners.
It's really going quite well.
No one had complained about any of the terms or services.
And I believe we put out a press release saying,
you know, we're open for business, come on check it out.
And that's where Cory Doctro decided to go pick up the terms and conditions.
And so we made a posting about that on boingboing.net.
And obviously this, the start to get around and it came to our attention.
And we've been looking at it evaluating it, looking at the comments, talking to different folks.
And yesterday we were pretty much convinced that we had to make a change.
And so we did, which was very simple to do.
And we've actually removed the entire paragraph about what you can or cannot say on your podcast.
And we've replaced it.
Actually, I should let me just have the, uh, can I do this here?
Now, of course, the issue is if I open up my web browser.
Is it going to immediately break my recording? I guess not.
I'm going to read the actual term to you.
So while that's loading and it's now is just turned into one sentence,
which I think everyone should be happy with.
If not, we'd obviously love to hear from you.
And that's the only thing that bothers me just a little bit.
You know, terms and conditions are, um, I mean, if you ever read the package of an end user
licensing agreement on a piece of software, um, then you probably be very scared to
Cory Doctro to spend some time on that.
Or even if you go over to, um, current TV, current dot TV, El Gore's project,
take a look at his terms and conditions.
You know what, take a look at garage bands, conditions.
They even own your RSS feed over a garage band.
But, you know, I, I understand that, uh, uh, lots of people want to scrutinize what we're doing.
So, uh, I'm happy to do that, but it would have been, it was a little disappointing that no one.
And I mean, absolutely no one emailed me, at least directly and said, hey, you know,
these terms and conditions, uh, maybe you should look at that, or can we, what do you mean by that?
Or why did you do this?
Uh, and I would have expected it from a site like Boeing Boeing, but, uh, no email from Cory.
And of course, I hope that he will pick this up, that we've changed it.
Here it is, uh, number eight.
So instead of, um, the stuff you can't say, we now have, in point eight, under the terms of conditions,
Podshow is not responsible for the content of the podcast on the network.
You acknowledge that you are fully responsible for your content and you acknowledge
that it is your responsibility to obtain any and all necessary licenses, rights, or grants,
for your podcast and any other material that is in it, you also agree in a knowledge that Podshow
will not act as an arbiter of any disputes and all claims are your sole responsibility.
So, there you go.
It was a very simple change to make and I like it.
Uh, we talked it over CC Chapman, he likes it, uh, and now would like to hear from you.
And actually, maybe we should put together some kind of independent committee for, um, uh,
for some of these things, um, you know, whatever it is, I think we can do a little bit better
than just rampantly posting all over the place.
You know, there was absolutely no, no discussion.
So, uh, but just, you know, we're kind of, the way it started to go is, you know,
these guys are evil and, you know, they're trying to dictate what you can say in your podcast.
We're not, we're just guys, you know, um, and we listen, it's that simple.
So you gave us the feedback, we listened, uh, we made a decision and I think, uh, I think we're
perfect now. And if not, just let us know, you know, this is, uh, this is the open web.
This is where we're supposed to be able to, to talk to each other and have opinions.
But, uh, got, got a little bit of ugly here and there. And I was a little disappointed by,
the way some people, uh, reacted in public and did nothing, absolutely nothing, um, you know,
no independent private, uh, communication. Anyway, so now you can say whatever you want.
And by the way, I was in violation of the terms of service all the time. So another reason they
definitely had to be changed. A quick email from James Martin, uh, because I was talking about
the video music awards the other day, says actually I found out that, uh, Diddy or Sean Combs
didn't give his watch to the guy in the audience at the MTV video music award. Well, he did,
but after that during the commercial break, a security guard came down asked him to take the watch
and then they gave the guy a watch, but it was a cheap knockoff of the actual one. I love that.
That's probably, uh, Diddy probably has, you know, knockoff watches of the watch that he wears,
that he's going to start selling. Oh, man. I was listening to the latest Bitty cast.
This is from them in Cambridge. And, um, I liked it a lot because they actually,
uh, they discovered that they were turning off the recording device at the most critical moments.
There was even a critical moment right there where they were fighting about who's going to carry the
eye river. I mean, is it that big? Is it that complicated? I guess no one wants to walk around with the
mic and look like a dork, uh, but it was beautiful to hear because finally there was a little bit of,
you know, a little bit of negative energy there in the in the Bitty camp. Not negative, but, you know,
just a little bit of caddy, caddy vibe. And I kind of, yeah, that did it for me. And then I was
listening, um, one of my favorite songs by the list of these Bitty's, um, they have a live recorded version.
It's an indirect recording. So it's basically just a mic hangin out there in thin air. So you can't
really hear it the way you'd like to hear live performance. But, um, I just want you to hear how great
these girls are live. Um, you know, Lee Ann just sings her ass off. Um, and, uh, you know, the
improvisations that she does, um, playing off the audience is great. And, and it's the whole thing is good.
So I want to play that. It's a famous, it's the Lassavius Bitties Live in Cambridge.
You can't tell me that you love a better way to play music or go to a music group.
Because I haven't yet experienced it. So thank you so much for welcoming us onto your stage.
Um, hopefully I will help in the road to making us famous. That's not so delicate,
safe way. The next song.
There is also on a t-shirt. Oh yeah, she must have a t-shirt.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Tell us my hand
Hand me from that bridge to sign
I'm gonna say some rebate
Talk to my assistant
I want to be famous
Tell my assistant what I need
She's up
I want to be famous
Go and do what we do is on the streets
Then you and I'm old
I have a bone
Then be sure that I'm living it all
When I have to look yes we'll fall
To the knees
And then I'll slip across
What I'm gonna be used to
I want to go and do what I choose
When I'm very much able
Same to the same
Same to the other
I want to be famous
It's no use at all, and I ain't as bad as I do, in dawn.
And every morning I'll get high on,
Motherville's martini's dry,
A little wee and just a touch of glow.
I want to be famous, famous,
Fair enough all my friends so much better than I would.
But it was a big slowly and a long time ago.
I ended up bitterly and old.
Not just my body, but also my soul.
But a legend is my goal, and a legend I'll be.
When I'm bright, I'll be out here.
The Sylvia's Bitties Live in Cambridge.
Bittiesforever.com is where you can find them.
Of course, Podsafe music.
The ones that started off for me.
And if you want to know more about Podsafe music,
you can now head over to Podsafe Music Network.
Podsafe.com or Podsafe Music Network.com.
Podcasters, welcome.
Say whatever the heck you want.
Just keeping with a couple of the topics we've been keeping up with this past week.
Email, hi, I'm a 17 year old teen from Australia.
Just wanted to pipe in the not all parents are horrible.
Since I'm a fourth child, that's between parentheses and Catholics.
My parents are pretty much accepted.
I'm going to grow up, and that I just want my privacy.
That respect helps make a good relationship between my parents.
I just thought I would tell you that not all parents and teens hate each other.
Oh, I don't think that they hate each other, of course not.
And Patricia and I are talking about this a lot these days about Christina,
who now says, I'm 15, so I'm going to do this this and that tomorrow.
I'm going to go here and stay overnight there.
You know, as scary as it is, we've got to, you know, let her go.
And find her own way.
We just hope we've given her enough ammunition.
So that, you know, when she gets into situations that she might know what to be
and that she either knows how to walk away from him, get out of him or,
and that's really the relationship I hope we have.
And it has proved to be that way, a couple times in the past.
This, that she knows to call us and say, hey, I'm not comfortable picking me up.
I have a rule, you know, it's like you can call me 24, 7, and you say,
picking me up and no questions asked, promise, no questions asked.
And that's the, that's the thing that my parents did with me,
and I really did appreciate it and use it only once or twice,
but it was well worth it.
Okay.
Holy moly, already, I've been talking my ass off today,
30 minutes and not a lot of promos.
You know, what, let's do another piece of potsafe music here.
This is grittal, that's the band that Patricia likes so much.
This is another one of their tunes.
So, preoccupied.
Because I don't want to treat you that way,
and if I'm not quick with a compliment,
I hope they can tend to have lost all to love.
I love you, find you, at least I'm sincerely,
love with what I love.
And if you question my intentions,
affection and man, I'm so time to know,
they do what they're so, I told you to submit me.
Question what they love,
I wish I could be in one of my side,
and I always see you in me, I feel I'm trying to raise you.
I'm trying to above my mind, find you better than me,
dull or dull or dull or dull or dull,
dull or dull, dull or dull,
dull or dull or dull,
dull
I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling
I'm telling you," I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you so I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm wondering I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you, I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I I'm telling you I'm telling you I I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you I I Ki 't I'm telling you I'm telling you I Ki NK subway
There's one thing I forgot to mention about those terms and conditions, you know, the ones
that limited the podcast or I remember how it came up in beta testing, we got a couple
of questions from artists who said, well, what do I do if a hate podcast starts to use
my music?
How do I, you know, how do I prevent that from happening?
But that I think is where those terms and conditions came from, actually, meant well
to protect the artist, but of course, had an adverse effect for the podcasters.
That question does still remain open though.
Now, of course, the way it's written, you know, the license that is granted to you as a
podcaster by signing up can be revoked, I guess, and I'm not a lawyer, and this is all
just, you know, hypothetical shit, but we should talk about that.
I guess that, you know, it is, you can just go sue anyone for anything.
So I guess you could fix it in the end, but it's just a, it's a pain in the ass.
And you, you gotta have some terms and conditions.
I'm glad we got it all sorted out though, because it makes me feel much better, you know,
just knowing that we're all back on the same page.
And I, and I love this about the internet.
It reminded me of all the feedback we got when I did the hotel, which hotel was that in New
York.
It was, um, that old fancy schmancy, uh, it's now a Hilton, uh, I can't recall.
Uh, so I was writing up and down the elevators, doing a sound scene tour, and then
people said, well, you know, you're really recording without permission.
And, uh, so I, you know, I'm sorry, fixed it, and won't do it anymore.
So in the same, same case here, sorry.
We, uh, we overlooked it, didn't think about it enough, and we're all good to go.
SCC would say, it's all good.
Oh, I'm counting casting with Adam Curry, I suppose you think you got it in his room.
Is he puking again?
Yeah.
He pissed.
YUMBOLET!
Hey Adam, I'm feeling much better.
Oh, thank you.
So don't worry about, uh, the smell of my breath.
It's Thursday morning, it's been 45, and I've got a new hit test for you.
So here we go, this is intro number one.
YUMBOLET!
I'm gonna take a whole sound of the DX7, of Cindy Lauper's Time after Time.
Can't miss it.
Number two.
I'm sure I'll recognize it when you play it, but no idea.
And number three.
Is that new shoes?
I can't wait.
Yeah, I can't wait.
And times up, this is answer number one.
From 84, this is Cindy Lauper.
And also number one and hit test 55.
Time after Time.
All of them circles can feel, which is nothing.
It's no love, you can love, you can love, you will find it.
Time after Time.
If you fall, I will catch you.
I will be waiting.
Are you singing along again?
No, no, no, no.
We are so bad.
Time after Time is answer number one.
Cindy Lauper.
And this is answer number two.
You're at mix together with Richard Franklin.
Sister is doing it for himself.
Good one.
Mom has set.
Yeah.
I'm running over to iTunes right now, but I'm going to buy that.
Let unlocking Franklin working together on this song.
Sister is doing it for them.
And number three.
Three news from 1985, uh-huh. This is no shoe got it. I can't wait
The most sampled and remix song ever
Hey
Well, and so number three concludes today's hit test number fifty five
I do have a bit of a problem because I'm out of clips
I have to create some time to
Create new files
Also for my
We can new york. I'm a lot of clips. So, um, yeah, I hope I'll be able to do it to create some if not this is the last hit test this week
Hope you enjoyed it
And again, there's always two addresses hit test at gmail.com for feedback
And of course, yompolite.com. J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T.com
For info about the hit test and the hit test podcast. Well, thank you for listening see you next time for number 56
So until then, bye-bye. Thank you very much, yompolite. Sorry. I had the mic open for sure walked in. She said are you okay?
He making all kinds of weird noises
That was my singing dear so sorry
Okay, so I can't do links to iTunes because I've been declined isn't affiliate member
But uh, if you are so inclined and I'm gonna go over and get sisters are doing it for themselves
I'm gonna get that on the iTunes music store because that's a great jam. I love that song
So go ahead on over and purchase any of those tracks and if anyone at Apple happens to have a way to
Help me through the fast track and get me approved it would be yeah
Well greatly appreciate that's it for the show
40 minutes as usual
Actually 43 minutes it's been I've been gone way over my a lot of time lately
I've gotten some response about that most of it positive people seem to like a lot of the email feedback and the stuff we're talking about on the air
So oh coming tomorrow by the way something new called the job cast on the daily source code
Yep, you want to tune in for that for the thank god is Friday edition of the show
I've a lot of things to do now since once again behind on schedule first order business take a shower
God damn stank
And then I'm gonna look through the 15 million Skype messages I've got
Which people are now basically using its email? I wish Skype wouldn't send the message after you reconnect
Because people are starting to now use that as as email. I'm not liking it
Oh well
It's interesting. It was a fire at the office so across in the office
That's interesting Sam Francisco Chris McIntyre's some pictures he probably posted in somewhere on podcast alley
Yeah
Just a lot of biz to go through
Okay
Excellent
So by tomorrow indie potter.org should be back up in role and hopefully we can keep all the other servers
Mozing along as we finish up the transition stuff
Adam and Curry dot com is the place for your feedback please don't attach the MP3's
I'm running really close to 100% on Gmail
Oh
Any source code dot com for the podcast feed for the show just check it out subscribe through iTunes
Thank you for subscribing if you already are thanks for listening
Tonki tomorrow when the bar stool comes bye bye
Another pod show podcast stick it in your ear
You