Daily source code for February 22, 2005.
Transmeters?
We don't need no stinkin' Transmeters?
Get ready for the Federation of Rocker!
Podcasting! It's Adam Curry!
Oh, hello from San Francisco!
Everybody, hi!
Welcome to the Daily Source code.
It is Tuesday, February 22, 2005.
Coming to you from the lovely Adagio Hotel in San Francisco, California.
Your Daily Source code, it's about 9.30 in the morning.
It's cold out, let me correct that immediately.
It's about 8.30 in the morning.
I'm so messed up.
I didn't have any jet lag in New York really to speak of, although,
I was feeling a bit tired around 8 o'clock in the evening,
only a week of fish in my microphone.
Make sure we can hear each other well.
But you're out here on the coast.
Ooh, yeah.
It's a little bit wacky.
I went to bed last night shooting.
I think I went up to my room around 8 o'clock.
A big black Angus burger steak for the room service and crashed.
And totally crashed.
In fact, the black Angus burger is still sitting almost like a look.
I wonder what that looks like.
I've never really looked at my room service the day after.
All right.
Oh, it's that.
Ooh, yeah.
That does not look very, you know what it is.
Just kind of the fries or the fries are left there.
So I woke up before my alarm clock this morning.
I had a set for eight o'clock because I wanted to talk to the girls back home.
Since we now have a eight hour time delay.
You know, when you're hooking up with people you're meeting and, you know,
it's always inconvenient time to just talk for a little bit.
And the wonderful thing, of course, is that, you know,
these days you can talk for hours and hours and hours with anybody you want in the entire world
because of Skype.
And I use Skype out since, you know,
Patricia likes just the regular handset and I still haven't completely,
I still haven't ordered that Skype handset for downstairs.
But even so, you know, what do I pay like,
it's like two cents a minute to call anywhere in the world.
Skype just absolutely rules.
So, unfortunately though, this hotel, even though they have
an amazingly fast connection, it's really nice.
It's a wired connection.
So you have to, you have to plug in.
It's not wireless.
So otherwise I can walk around the room and do all kinds of stuff.
And I have the world's largest cell phone, basically.
And the reason why I can't do that now is because it's one thing that
Mac is done that is really not smart on the power book is you have two
stereo speakers.
So you got, you know, speaker on the well, you have stereo speakers.
So one stereo on the right hand side of the power book,
one on the left hand side.
The microphone, the internal microphone,
is actually built into the left hand side of the power book,
which is right next to the speaker.
So if you're on a Skype call, you're not wearing headphones on your
power book, then whatever the other party says,
they will hear that come back to them and kind of like a delay
depending on the latency of the connection,
but that could be almost be, you know, just like an echo.
So, not very handy.
So I was wondering how they fixed that with,
because I've used I chat, I chat AV,
which I like quite a bit if you're doing video chats.
And I've used that a lot and I've used it hands free without headphones.
Like, what are they doing?
What is different?
You know, is it the software?
Is it filtering it out?
Until then I figured it's actually pretty simple.
What they did with I chat AV is the audio from the other party
that you're talking to comes through the right speaker only
and they disabled the left speaker.
Okay, that would remove the, that would remove the horrible echo effect
for sure, but it's kind of like a, you know, like a, you know,
well, it's not a very interesting fix because, you know,
Skype doesn't know how to do that, I guess.
Maybe Skype can figure out how to chop one channel off.
Anyway, that would be nice if we could get that working.
Because I do like the idea of talking hands free
and I've been investigating some equipment
while I've been here in the States.
Looking for, see, I went into New York.
Well, first, when I'm looking for, I'm looking for a pair of wireless headphones.
They aren't too bulky to take with you, you know,
and actually even better, perhaps.
And that's why I went into New York.
I went to Sam Ash, which is a famous store for musicians
where you can buy instruments and all kinds of gear.
Managed music stores right next door across the road.
And I'm looking for two things.
One is for a, kind of like the Madonna headset,
which has a monitor there as well.
So it's basically a telephone headset,
but it would be wireless.
So it have one little box that I hook up to my laptop.
And then I, and I could walk anywhere I want
and receive the call that I'm getting.
And of course, use the wireless mic.
And I could do the same when I'm recording the source code
because, you know, I'm pretty constrained.
I have to sit right near the computer
because of the length of the headphone cord
where it's, I love roaming around as much as possible.
I was also looking for a small,
yes, a little teeny battery powered mixer.
You know, something that I could just use on the road
because I stupidly forgot my eye river.
And I have the yep here, but the quality of what that records
is nowhere near what I could do with eye river.
I can't believe I forgot to bring.
And I thought I had everything with me.
So I haven't really been able to do any of the outside stuff
that I was, you know, potentially planning on, on, on doing.
And I couldn't find it.
I could not find the little mixer.
There were lots of, you know,
a little bit bigger mixers, which would actually work quite
in a nice state home.
But I want something I can take on the road.
And I was talking to Madge Weinstein, who was in Florida
talked to her for a couple of minutes the other day.
I said, Madge, you know, what are you using?
And Madge is using a mixer from radio shack.
And I went, yeah, I got to hit the radio shack.
The radio shack always has exactly that plug
that you never thought existed
conversion cable that no one would ever dare make.
And if not, they've got all the, all the plugs in the wires
and the solder and the soldering iron
for you to put it together yourself.
Hmm.
So I'm taking a sip of tea here.
In the room, they have a,
it's a nice hotel, by the way.
They have a little beverage center.
So of course, you got a mini bar.
But then they have a coffee and tea.
And you can set that yourself, which I always like.
I really, really enjoy just being able to make my own coffee
and not have to order up or tea.
Because I like drinking tea a lot.
And what happens inevitably, usually in US hotels.
I don't know about San Francisco.
But in most hotels in the States, if you order up a tea,
you have at least a 70% chance that the tea water
has been put into a container that held coffee
and it just tastes like shit.
So it's nice that you can, you know, kind of control that yourself.
So daily source code.
Today, we want to talk about commercialization,
because that's been what a lot of my trip has been about.
I want to talk about radio, because I've gotten so much feedback
from so many smart people, particularly in New York,
about the future of radio, where they think it's headed,
you know, just, well, the future of radio, where they think it's headed.
They're not enough.
And today, this afternoon, or I think, yeah,
that's probably a cocktail thing or whatever,
but this afternoon, this evening,
are the, the wired rave awards.
So I was planning on
gussying up a little bit and going to check that out.
And just a chat a little bit for the next half hour.
So with you guys, talking about some stuff,
and of course, we've got a hit test, you know,
a young poet.
He would never let you down.
He's gotten number 13 lined up for today.
And I have, let's see, got a mashup.
This is, I can't remember who sent me this,
but I don't know if it was, if it was said or not.
But it's cute tip versus huge Lewis in the news.
It's called The Power, Don't Stop, Mr. Shaky Hands Man.
Yeah, if you got it.
You got it?
Since you are working for me.
Oh.
You got it?
You want it?
Y!!!
You got it?
detective
All right, cute tip versus Hughie Lewis and the news the power don't stop Mr.
Only call it was Mr. shaky hands mix what is it the yeah Mr. shaky shaky hands man
All right, it's all your daily source code for today, which I remind you if you're just getting started with your day
Every ball that it doesn't really matter what day it is because you know you're getting this maybe a day later or two days later
Hey, something funky I noticed
I have a Sony Erks and what is it?
K 700i telephone which I use in the UK. I have Virgin Mobile as my provider and
I didn't really notice it at all until Patricia
Until I called Patricia yesterday and she said oh, you know did you hear the message? I left it not in getting you message
It just said did you call me so yeah, you know called you on your phone and I'm I look at
Low and behold no network. I've done the rescan
I've done everything I can it's it's not receiving a network. It works fine in New York work to find well
I know it works in when it works in New York fuck it
But why isn't it working here and I have another cell phone which is
That I carry with me usually if I go to Holland because it's my Dutch cell phone and that does get a network here
So I'm kind of pissed that the Virgin for some reason. I don't know they just don't have a
If they don't have a Rome I mean why don't pick up a network? It would that doesn't make sense that
Well, they just don't have a network that they roam with they be that is indeed the the
The problem what's that?
Yeah
I thought I heard some interference. I just put fresh batteries into the wireless set
So that shouldn't work fine for a while, but you know, I think if you've got a city where your airplane airplane's fly from
And Virgin Atlantic flies from San Francisco twice a day
Then perhaps it would be kind of smart to have
Your mobile telephones work in the city, but maybe it's just this particular area of the city. I don't know
So I want to talk to you bit
about
The future of radio and what I've learned what the feeling is from people
Particularly who are either in radio or a different forms of radio or
Or an advertising and advertised for radio and I think I can sum it up from our
Conversations in New York with and again advertising folks that I know
Radio people marketing people who sell sponsorships and advertising for radio
They're pretty much scared shitless
I can't say it any other way. Well, maybe not scared
Well, yeah, I think scared is probably the right word because they know they know and everyone who's in radio knows
That there is a whole generation coming up that does not give a shit about radio doesn't care doesn't listen and
You know, and we think about it. Well, yeah, that's my daughter. My daughter is part of that generation and anyone who has kids
And if they're let's say anywhere between like 11 and 14 or you know
If you got pre teenagers or teenagers and listen to radio the way you use to they've got a whole bunch of other things
They're doing they have MSN that they're on all day
They have their iPod that they're filling up and and maybe they're not even listening to podcasts
But they have an iPod that's how they're enjoying their entertainment. They've got an Xbox
You know, there's all this stuff that is basically detracting from and in this case
I'm just going to talk about radio, but because of course television has pretty much
You know the same issues and the people that do listen to radio
I think that they're pretty disenfranchised that's at least what we've you know what we've kind of in our
In our little informal studies have seen is that you know, wow
People are bored. They're running away
There's there's not a lot that they'd like to listen to everyone knows it's there and everyone has the radio on at some point
And it may be just a backdrop for for you know, like a soundtrack to your life
But you know that's what people are basically choosing to program themselves
You know setting up their own playlist and I have to say by the way
I don't think that many people use playlist features on MP3 players and to prove that
I guess or the proof would be in the pudding is why Apple came out with the shuffle
Because that is pretty much a thing what everyone was doing
And at the beginning you set up your playlist and of course you've got a playlist that is just right to get everyone in the mood for
Something sensual or something fun or if you want to pick me up or you know a rainy day
Played list, but after a while you get kind of tired of it because guess what it's like fucking work
You know
I
Actually once made a playlist generator. I should dig that code up. It was pretty cool
Cuz you know radio stations have have a format and the format is well first of all
There's probably a genre most radio stations have to have a genre
So we play the best of the 60 70's n80's everybody. Oh, we play today
Racking it or we play the light only the light or all talk all the time
But let's just take music for a second even within those formats. So let's take a
60 70's 80's mixed station or 70's 80's 90's or what is it 80's 90's and today?
So basically that could be my my iTunes or my my iPod could be 60 70's 80's 90's and today
But you know what it does a format do well a format is a clock
And if you would take a clock and split it up into sections let's say
Five minutes sections that would pretty much equal what just about every single radio station and on the planet has is their format
And oftentimes the format is of course a secret formula for success and no one really talks about their format
But a station may start off the top of the hour with a big hit golden old
And these are all tagged by the way in
Programs that radio stations use the most prevalent one is called selector and
They have all kinds of tags, you know, it's like if it's the tag would be female artists tag would be sunny song happy song up tempo
You know
Probably well obviously the the date range so there's a whole bunch of ways that that songs are tagged and I wish we could merge
some of the professional stuff that is out there
Into more like a prosumer version because all the all the study that on the stuff has been done, you know
It's it's all been developed. It's just in very expensive packages that we really can't access as podcasters
But so that format will say all right
We'll start off with a song from the 60s that we want to hit a
Recurrent which means something from the past five years then we want to go with an 80 song
And we'll do another 80s but a
A slow song and then from that slow song will go into an up tempo. So that would be the format and what I created
many years ago
Was I had all these tags. I'd basically tag my music
But I did it just simply first by a tempo and by a date range and
Had a format which would say exactly that I want to start off with this type of song that song will be next
And please make sure that you don't repeat a song right so there's no repetition within the hour
Don't repeat the artist and it would just delve into my iTunes and and pull out songs and create a
Format for me and it would start playing and when it was almost at the end of that playlist
It would create a new one so I basically had this automatic and this loop running throughout the house now on your iPod that's a little more complicated
But really, you know, who's gonna go through all that trouble of tagging their music and doing all that?
You know, it's it's not what you do is you put it on random and if it hit it the random hits the song
That you don't like you just you know hit the the the the the skip button and you go to the next one
So there's a big
Big opportunity I think
How do we how do you even start on talking about this about the randomizing okay?
Well, so anyway, yeah people are randomized and creating their own stuff and and they're really
They're probably manipulating more than actually creating there's always die-hards
But I think the majority of people don't bother creating playlists
The point being that
Radio sees that it's in trouble now of course
Several years ago and I didn't even realize that this was like goes back to you know
Almost more than 10 years ago is when the satellite guy started to figure out this exact problem and
That you know, we they would have to figure something out to you know to be able to either offer more programming or different programming
Or and this is all pre iPods when they set up these satellite radio stations which is supposed to be the big alternative to
terrestrial radio broadcast
There were no iPods so they thought that they would be the shit. They would be the bomb digity and that how all these
You know these pre-programmed channels which would give you a format, you know very much like what we see
in our playlists
And of course those markets crossed each other and then they went oh shit, you know, we've got to come up with something else at the same time
I think the satellite guys also realized that you know users were defecting listeners didn't want to
Stick around anymore. They're bored of what they're hearing and
And
One of the biggest misnomers by the way if we it's of course obviously this comes into a Howard Stern conversation because radio can be all kinds of things
It's not just music. It's not just all talk. You know, it's it's radio is a technology. Okay. It's you can't put
Podcasts in a box and say this is a podcast, you know, there's this is a podcast and cover villas a podcast and a skinny on
Sports as a podcast and rock roll kick shows a podcast and match wine is a podcast and wine seems a podcast and Don and Drew is a podcast
Everything's a podcast. It's just a technology that's being used
And it can be a for profit podcast and not for profit podcast and none in
podcast, you know fucking understand
you know it's just a technology so
The big miss understanding I think about Howard Stern and of course I want to talk a little bit about his move to serious radio
is that
serious which has no
FCC regulations or not regulated by the FCC they are regulated interestingly enough by the digital millennium copyright act
Which gives them some other hurdles they have to address
Anything goes so you can say whatever you want essentially very much like a podcast because it's not regulated by the FCC
People who think that because Howard Stern now can say shit piss fuck tits count motherfucker cock sucker
Whatever the seven dirty words are that all of a sudden, you know, this is gonna be like some big
Revelation, you know other people are saying oh, you know, maybe he'll be like Lenny Bruce and once he gets all this freedom
People won't be as interesting anymore and I say nay to both, you know, this is not what Howard Stern is about Howard Stern is not about
Saying dirty words or or being indecent Howard Stern is about honesty and
This is something that I learned a long long long long time ago when I started first moved to New York
It started listening to him is that he would just he wouldn't put on the fake voice. He wouldn't you know
Pretend to be someone else although that is obviously always a bit questionable
for everybody me included
But he was just telling stories and telling talking about his life and and talking about stuff that interested him and and guess what?
You know in all honesty in all honesty many guys like to talk about
sex
Is it a surprise to you
So if that's what people want to talk about and they can talk about it honestly and openly and use the words that I mean
Look life is indecent life is indecent
I've said this before the way we talk the way we communicate with each other are actions
What we write it just everything it's indecent by today's FCC standards
I don't think it's indecent I don't care what you say to me how you say it
But it is deemed indecent by the broadcast regulations
But it's nothing so it's not about the language it's about being honest and being able to say
Whatever's on your mind and starting a debate and if it's about lesbians that's fine
You know Howard Stern is not always about lesbians either
So I completely believe he will bring
An enormous following he has about eight million listeners now. He claims a bit more, but eight million
I'd say he's a pretty fair number across the US and he has to bring one million subscribers to
To serious and then they basically make make money. You know, he's making hundred million a year
If he brings in a million subscribers then they have then they're probably gonna do
Just on the Howard Stern deal. They're going to make a minimum of 20 to 30 million dollars a year
Pre-tax because Howard brings in enough to cover it up. You know a subscription to serious radio costs was at 12 or 14 bucks
12 bucks a month so you wind up paying 140 bucks so do that times a million want you
You see that you're at a hundred and forty million dollars and if Howard Stern cost a hundred so there's you know
30-40 million left over so that makes total sense
The question is
Since Howard Stern can't make the move until 2006
Will people start defecting to other avenues before then can they wait that long or are they finding that podcast or delivering a lot of
Because that's what I keep hearing people say over and over they say
I don't know why I listen to it
You know this person doesn't have a great voice or you know he says um and uh and the quality sucks and you know
What what is it it's about the honesty and please make no mistake. It's not about the amateurism of
The podcast that can be a part of the entire vibe and people don't really give a shit
I think that's what we're finding out you know it's like college radio
You know I don't give a shit if you if you crack the mic the wrong time
I just want to hear what you have to say and it's kind of funny you know and I think that
The amateurism and the unprofessionalism that you might hear once in a while or all the time
Doesn't matter whatever podcast you're listening to it. It's just it's exciting to hear something you haven't heard you know
so after a while after
we're all
You know we're used to listening to crappy
Non-professional podcast then the occasional one that is produced a little more slicker
Well, that'll be exciting. So that's just what we're used to
But it's about the honesty. It's about hearing people talking and and you can almost
Sense that they don't have to hold back. There's nothing in the back of their mind that they can't talk about
There's no you know corporate
I was like what we talked about the CBS
When I was interviewed by CBS for CBS evening news by the way
They're holding back on releasing that report. This is great because they they want to do the report about podcasting in conjunction with launching
CBS news is own podcast
I feel a bit used but it is kind of exciting so that'll be cool to see that happen
So
You can tell and that's what's getting everyone hooked on these things because
You know you can tell and of course after a while if it's not interesting or it's not entertaining and a tune out no matter what which is why you know
I keep my time in check. I don't want to do more than 40 minutes
I have my balls aren't big enough to say I think I can entertain you any longer than a 3040
30 or 40 minutes that I do every day
So in the conversations in New York we talked a lot about
ways to move
Advertising money revenue
From radio where it wants to leave because the numbers are dwindling into new areas
Now with serious it's an an XM I should mention them as well the two
Satellite radio networks in the U.S
They're doing a combination mainly subscription
But they will also be doing advertising and how it's turn will carry advertising as well
So you're going to pay a monthly fee and you'll be subject to advertising by the way
I don't have a problem with advertising. I like listening to it if you know I like
Being marketed to I like hearing about new products if I don't then I'm gone. You know, so you can lose me really easy
But it's not you know, I've nothing against advertising. It's a fact of life. You know
So there are people looking to to move into the new market now. We don't really have
The eight million listeners that Howard Stern has you know, we don't you know, I have
What we up to like you know, well we're well over the 50,000 mark that I had several months ago
But you know, it's still if if you look at it, you know, they use something called a cost per thousand CPM cost per meal
To determine you know how much is paid per
Per advertisement and that's just not going to work. That's like you're trying to shoehorn the wrong thing and to you know
It's kind of like what happened with banner ads, you know, and now
You know, all everyone cares about the banner banners of the same size and it's just it's it's
It's not very innovative. It's not the best use. I think of you know now we have all this freedom
We can do it every one what a revolutionary concept
Maybe we could make commercials interesting and not having be just 10 20 or 30 seconds maybe we can integrate them into
Into programming and I've really and I've really thought about how and and that was part of my point of being out here in San Francisco
I want to talk to a lot of the top podcasters and get their feeling for you know, what are they looking for and and what's been interesting is
I've been talking to a lot of people out here on the west coast
Every single person wants to make money on what they're doing
I think everyone's very realistic and understand that it's no one's going to be making a
billion dollars in any type of
You know any type of new media venture just because
You know the numbers it doesn't add up, you know
It's unlike the old
centralized model where you'll have a few people who have all the viewers and all the listeners now
We have a much larger scope where you're going to have your 15 listeners or your 150 or maybe your
5000 you know it all depends on what you're doing and obviously the more
People that are in there the more interesting will be for advertising but it's not just about advertising because we you know
I've been testing a couple models
I have to say that I am just tickled pink about this whole San Seo deal
So, you know, here's a way you to make money with a podcast
You like something and you talk about it and then all you have to do is make sure you give people an opportunity to check out that product and go buy it
I like lots of stuff
And actually what I've noticed with the Amazon associates
You know, I'm gonna associate with Amazon and I've been talking about the San Seo coffee maker because I like it
I use it. It's a great product. I wish I had it here with me on the road and by the way
I thank you everyone so much for all the emails and the pointers on how to create your own coffee pods and
Fill them up with other things besides coffee
Next time I'm an Amsterdam. I'll be sure to create a really big pod that I'm gonna try it out
You know, and people are interested, you know, look at coffee futures
You know coffee is a big ass market lots and lots and lots of people drink coffee. So
I'm talking about something as a product. I don't even make, you know, if I made the product it would probably be better and if my podcast was only about coffee
I would probably sell more of them but just through the fact that I'm talking about this great coffee machine that I like that I use
And I want you to be able to have the same wonderful San Seo coffee pod experience
You can go to curie.com
Click on the on the picture of the coffee machine and you'll be able to buy it now because you buy something
I get a percentage and right now I'm beginning like five percent or something, you know, that's Amazon's deal
So I'm not really feeling extremely happy but what if it were my product? What if it were my CD?
Like the lascivious bitties. They're gonna be doing their bitty cast. It's already started. So
They're gonna be talking about themselves and on the road and you'll get hooked or you won't get hooked and
And you'll want to buy the CD. It's just the way it works, you know, it's on television. They have a word for it
It's called an infomercial now of course that conjures up all kinds of images of really bad actors and
Overdubbed voices of you know with beautiful bodies who have these wonderful machines that could make you as tone and fit as well
But it is a bit that's very successful, you know for companies that make or or
Market those products so very much I guess I have to admit like what Dave Weiner has said many times on how to make money on weblobs
Only now it kind of you know we've opened up this whole new area of of creativity and opportunity for people who just aren't writers
I'm not a I'm not a writer. I'm not a good writer. I'm a shitty writer. I don't you know, just don't I'm not good at it
I always fire stuff off and just post it up to the blog
I don't really think about it and go back later and think oh, I could have committed that better
This is my my arena. I love doing this. I love doing audio. I love talking. I love experimenting with it
a lot of construction going on today by the way. You probably hear that in the background
So there's
There's ways that will be able to do that and we need some infrastructure obviously to make that happen
So that if you have an idea and you want a podcast first we should make the podcasting part pretty easy you know
How about just click record click done
Or pick up the phone and call a number and hit pound and it's done and you've got your feet and you've got your your archive and and show notes
This is going to be important show notes is going to be important. I'm really happy that I started out by
Doing it in OPML even though it's really had it's made no sense up until now
But a lot of people are doing it and I really appreciate you following along
Because
The next thing that's going to happen is we're going to have to be able to find stuff based upon the content inside the podcast
So you know these directories like we have at ipod.org and other ones that kind of take the ID3 tag information
It's not going to be enough
We have to add extra metadata to the podcast in order to make them indexable searchable
Got a couple of ideas about that
And then on the sponsoring sponsoring advertising. I think are two different things
And I've been listening around to a couple of podcasts my my favorite example is WGBH in Boston
WGBH a WGBH is morning stories are sponsored by ipswitch and ipswitch is a
Provider of downloading tools connectivity
It sounds like a provider. I'm not quite sure but I remember the name right and
So in a perfect NPR model which to me just sounds like it's commercial
I don't see any difference between this program brought to you by ipswitch for morning stories or you know this program brought to you by
MS mobiles for Don and Drew. I don't see any difference there, but apparently there, you know, it's I guess there is
Maybe because the show maybe that's a throwback to the to the good old days where if a show is interrupted by
Commercials then it's a commercial show but if it's sponsored by the beginning in the end and you're not
And you're not interrupting the flow of the program then it's not commercial
So anyway, I'd call that sponsoring or underwriting and we're seeing lots of that happen already and I and I and I encourage that and what you're gonna get is you're gonna get people who are specifically
Underwriting a podcast for the content of the podcast or the audience that will be listening to that to that podcast and it's like you don't really need numbers to prove it
Because the sponsor intuitively knows
The people that I'm gonna reach there are the ones that I want to reach because it's just clear
It's not based upon the shotgun approach of I've got 8 million listeners, so you know
You just want to buy a spot with me because you're just blasting it out and you're always gonna get someone you want
There is a way to do that by the way, and I'm not against it. I think it's a very
Interesting idea, but we have to bond together and this is the long tail that people talk about you know
So we'll have if we have a couple hundred podcasters just like the you
Weblogs, so there's a couple weblogs that everyone knows about and get get shit loads of traffic
But then there's this millions of weblogs that all get little 80 bit of bits of part of of traffic
And if you can find it if we can find a way collectively to
Use each of those smaller audiences to aggregate them into a big audience
That will create something that the advertisers who understand the shotgun approach and that's what they like to do
It was just you know fucking load on baby
We'll get someone
We can do that. We can totally do that. So I think a combination
By him I have to say most excited about
Being able to talk about a product or maybe just you know going to a store how about that
You know if you just if you just go into an online store and say I really like that product and I want to sell that
I want to advertise that we could turn this whole fucking thing around think about that so instead of
You determining you know saying okay, you can come and advertise with your cell phone, right?
So the virgin mobile
Says I want advertising your show. Why don't I
Have an opportunity to go to some place
Where I can go through a whole bunch of products and services or I can search for one that I perhaps like already and know that I want to talk about
Because I'm passionate about it if I like something or a particular cigar that I smoked and go and get
The the automatic right to market that product that would turn it all upside down and then the
The longer I'm on this plan at the more I'm seeing in recent years that if you turn the model upside down
It's usually exactly what people are looking for
I don't know why but it seems that way it's like you know instead of streaming
We're gonna do
We're gonna do caching basically and put stuff on your on your machine that you don't know about and tell you about it later
I mean everything if you turn the paradigm upside down it usually starts to make sense in our new world
And so I'm pretty excited about that idea of just being able to go into it into an online store
Choose a product that I like or search for the product that I like and as I talk about it on my podcast
Send people back to my website my weblog whatever wherever I post my podcast and say, hey, you know click on
Click on that link and get some more information about it or buy it, you know, then all I'm doing is I'm just I
Become the market or the advertiser and I determine what I'm going to sell and I can hone my skills with my advertising message
To my audience like Michael Butler
He had did a sponsorship or a commercial someone
I think I think they were basically going to give him free beer
Which is fine? That's that's what Michael wants right now. You want some free beer
Heinrich and you idiots you idiots
You know talk about that later
And he on the spot he made up a song and sang it for him and that was it, you know because he knows how to talk to his audience
To anyway hey let's play some pod save music and I still want to do the hit you know what or
I'm going to save the pod save music because we're 38 minutes already. It is time once again everybody for the hit
The answer that is test 10 bucks. I got your answers
Time for Adam Curry to take the hit test
With y'all polette
Hi Adam. Hey on it's time for hit test number 13. I'm ready my brother again. There are some changes
Okay, in the format the clips are very short. You'll you'll hear each clip two times
And right after you'll have five seconds to think about it. Oh, here we go. There's clip number one
And once again number one
And how are you gonna five seconds to think about it
Okay, I don't like this new format young. I'm not good at it. Time for number two
Once again number two
Sounds like a Mr. Mr. Okay, five seconds for you
And sound like Mr. Mr. But again, and this is number three
It's very short one more time
Okay hold on hold on all right young
This sucks at least I suck. I can't finish five seconds for you to think about it
My goodness, you know when I hear these songs I'm going to say oh, yeah, I knew what it was right it's too early
Maybe for me and I would start for the answer section number one
It's gross, but that's a 90s soft. I don't know so much about the 90s, you know, I need some old fit
Okay, I would never guess that even if you played it for an hour
And the second answer in today's hit justice
This curiosity killed the cats. Oh, man
This is down to earth. Okay, I could have known that that's like 83
Song
Me
And the third and final answer
It's a richy family
With me a break and cowbell to boot
I got the nation
Did anyone get those the anyone get those?
The richy family is answering number three in today's hit test
Well, and please let me know what you think of the changes I've made
A lot of feedback is welcome at hittest at gmail.com
Hittest at gmail.com
And the site has already changed again
You've been find all information on www.yumpolets.nl
So let's g a and p-o-l-e-t.nl
You can find information about the hittest the RSS feed and the new independent hittest podcast
There have been already two
Check them out at www.yumpolets.nl
See you next time
Like we've started a little cottage industry here
Yumpolets got his hit test podcast going check them out
Yumpolet.nl thank you very much yum. No, I think it's great the four minus great
Could I have ten seconds or so two things one I'd like ten seconds to think about it
And the clue well first of all, I wouldn't have gotten these I a curiosity killed the cap
Nost and my brain is too fried for that richy family
It wasn't one I mean because you know what I know so many songs because I've played so many songs
Over and over and over again on the radio and that's just one that you know, I've never played curiosity killed a cat
I could have known and
What was the I even forgot the first
So now I just suck this time, but give me yeah give me like ten seconds in between that's great
I love the I love hearing you know the snipers the the snip's
twice in a row
What's always hard though is to is the clues of the hardest things because you want people to be able to guess
You want to have you know give me a little bit of a chance
I we did this on the radio back in the 80s mood play like just like just like a
Not even a second worth of audio and people would still get it so I think the length of the clips are good
I just yeah, and I just suck what can I say I'm looking forward to tomorrow's though
That'll be a very exciting. Hey, I'm going to wind it up 43 minutes 40 seconds. That's it for today's source code
Thank y'all for checking it out
Better on the hit test than I did tomorrow. I will be back. We'll know how the wider the words went
And another day in San Francisco then it's off to
Seattle and then back home. I can't wait. I must say I'm
This is my girls a bit these days
comments at him at curry.com
I have not had time to empty out the MP3 feedback at gmail.com account
I guess the only way to really do it is to
Pop all that mail out of there or delete it and then basically let it fill up again, you know
Google I love Google. I'm willing to pay for more storage
I will pay Google just let me know
Famous source code dot promise where you can find the archive the latest show in the podcast the and of course my weblog
WWW dot free god prom. I'll talk to you tomorrow everybody take care have a great day. Bye bye
you