This is the Daily Source Code for March 21st, 2005.
But it's still the 21st summer at the Universe, right?
It's the Daily Source Code for Monday, everybody.
Man, I gotta tell you, I'm completely wrecked from today's activities, which, too.
Actually, the first daughter of the day was kind of nice.
It was outside for most of the day, but after about three o'clock,
I've been on Skype nonstop.
I'm telling you, you can build an entire business with Skype.
That's actually pretty outrageous.
So, family is asleep right now, and I'm up here.
Excuse me.
In the office, slash studio, because, well, I gotta do a show every day.
That's kind of my commitment.
So, I apologize upfront.
If the energy is just a little bit low, but I just can't punch out what I normally do.
Not only because I want to sleep, but I'm just totally, completely wrecked.
But I got a great show.
Can you tell I've been smoking some cigars?
Man, it's been an interesting weekend, too.
To start off with, Sunday night was the big good Charlotte show.
As you know, that's Christina's favorite, favorite band.
They were playing at Brickston Academy.
Yeah, that's to the south of...
It's actually...
I guess it's south of the West London.
It's not a very nice neighborhood. I'll tell you that.
Oh, boy.
But I haven't actually talked about this during the week,
but Christina, of course, had been looking forward to this for quite a while.
But, well, you know, you know how when kids are basically,
they've got a big mouth and they're, you know,
mouthing off at mom and even a dad and doing things that shouldn't do
and forgetting things they should do and you get into that mode where you say,
like, hey, look, you know, if you don't straighten up, it'll be no good Charlotte.
Well, at a certain point, you've got to make good on the threat.
And it's the most horrible, hurtful things I've ever had to do.
And, of course, it hurt me more than it hurt her, but it came down to where we said,
I'm sorry, you can't go.
So, that totally sucks.
I really was bad, especially because she had her friend coming over
to stay with her and that when it go to the concert together,
I was going to take him.
And, of course, her friend had already made the plans and so she, you know,
basically, she showed up, couldn't do anything about that.
And it was not really fair to punish her, so I wound up taking her friend to the concert.
Yeah, it was just a major league, painful parenting moment, let me tell you.
But I think it really worked out for the good, you know, to really,
sometimes you've got to go all the way through, you know, the threat is just not enough.
You've got to actually do it.
And it certainly is made a difference in a real big attitude adjustment,
but that sucks to have to do that.
I really did not enjoy that at all.
Particularly because my buddy James had set up passes for the after show party.
It was just sucks.
Okay, so that was kind of, you know, what we witnessed from Thursday Friday Saturday.
And so that's why there was no PPP podcast, yes, they either.
And I see today, I got up, well, of course, a ticker student at the school.
She's just, she's a wonderful child now.
It totally worked.
Yeah, no matter how much it hurt.
And after that, you know, I did my email stuff and did my aggregator scans.
Let's do a couple podcasts.
And then I went off to purchase a aviation map of the UK,
because I'm starting to get really starting to do some training.
Wind commander William and I will be flying on a Wednesday.
And he'll be training me in the assessment of 182 RG,
which stands for retractable gear.
And we're really going to hit it hard.
And if, if it all possible, whether permitting and, well, et cetera, et cetera,
we'll actually fly home or fly here in, in the assessment.
And then he'll fly it back.
So I'm really looking forward to that all a part of the training.
But I talked about for, um, for my fixed wing, uh, PPL,
private pilot's license.
Excuse me.
Ah, I wasn't going to behind the desk.
I don't know what it is.
You know, if I'm sitting, uh, in back of the big green easy chair,
then I don't get all this gas.
I don't burp whenever I'm leaning forward into the microphone.
You by the way, I've been on the computer so long today.
You can actually hear the fan pumping away.
Listen, I'll see here a little bit of that.
I have no patience right now to figure out where the hum is coming from.
But, uh, everything's been, uh, been rolling nonstop.
As soon as we've been, uh, oh, man, talking a whole bunch of people, uh,
really, uh, getting pretty exciting.
No damn announcements today.
I'm too tired to do anything.
But, uh, we're getting pretty close to be able to talk about some, uh,
some of the cool stuff that's going on with, uh, with pod show and with, uh,
with Boku and podcasting in general.
Now, if, um, I got a lot of great comments on the, uh,
sound scene tour from Friday, um, the trip to the BBC.
Thank you all very much.
I'm glad you liked it.
I thought it was, it was so long.
I had to, uh, head it down four and almost four and a half hours
down to, but I tried to get it, you know, to less than an hour,
but wasn't able to do less than like an hour and 20.
Um, and there was one, uh, particular piece from, uh,
uh, from that show that I only played a very little bit of that,
it's a, it's a mashup, um, that came from, uh,
digitalinterference.org.
And I really wanted to play it because there was so much work
that went into it and it really didn't, uh, get its props, uh,
being played through the speaker, being picked up on my,
on my wireless microphone, uh, while I was, uh,
uh, why played it for the, uh, for the BBC piece.
It's, um, it's all about the TSA and, uh,
my issues with airport security, which I'll be, um,
witnessing again pretty soon as we're going on vacation, uh,
to Florida in just, uh, well, uh, what is it, uh,
less than a week now, uh, east of vacation, of course,
and looking forward to some nice fun in the sun,
but I did want to play this one.
It's the drop system versus Adam Curry.
He went in two, three, two, three, four, five.
This is the individual interference.
Take that one.
Give us all the answers.
Homeland security.
It's not protecting us.
It's not making your flight any safe for you.
It's really slowing everybody down.
It's not protecting us.
It's not making your flight any safe for you.
It's really slowing everybody down.
The citizens of the United States,
the Americans who are putting up with Homeland security.
Homeland security.
The robotic voice is talking,
it'll all be really convinced that we're safe,
and you can sniff,
and then nothing can explode,
or dangerous, or pointy, or whatever,
and look inside of you,
to be in danger, brain.
And we're soaked into the wounded process,
we pay for the flying attach...
NASA's...
One checkpoint.
Another checkpoint.
We're gonna do this for safety and against terrorism.
Terrorism.
That there my friends is the drop system versus Adam Curry in airport security.
You can find more drop system tracks at www.thedropsystem.com.
I don't have much more to say today other than that.
I like that mix a lot better than the other mix that was featured on the daily source
code.
I like this one very, very much.
Thank you very much.
Digitalinterfearance.org and actually I've got a whole bunch of promos and stuff lined up
for today.
And a lot of promos have also since my Gmail account started to fill up on MP3 feedback.
So whatever is ordered to do now is just send me a link to the MP3 file and a lot of people
am doing that and I really appreciate it.
So I've got some promos lined up and by the way and all the conversations and stuff
that we've been doing and working on some investments in podcasting talent.
That's not just for people who make podcasts by the way.
Also for there's lots of opportunity for developers and for producers.
There's just a minute so much.
I think we finally got into the point where it's about the content.
I remember it's about 10 years ago to the day almost.
We were saying content is king and this is where it's going to go.
And finally I think we've gotten there where it's not just about the podcast showing up
on your iPod or MP3 player.
It's actually about the show.
People are totally day in these shows and I think that's what's really got me jazzed
about all the stuff that's going on.
Also I wanted to mention that the tests that I've been doing with basically selling stuff
talking about stuff in the podcast or stuff that we've already talked about and then putting
an Amazon link on in the show notes or on my weblog at curie.com.
Once I started doing that, which I think was, let me see, how long have I had the
Sensei O'Coffee machine up?
A couple of weeks, six weeks, maybe something like that.
I checked today and I have sold over $4,000 worth of goods.
Of course that's not, I mean, I just get a percentage of that but my goodness, over $4,000
worth.
This is amazing.
And I was supposed to cue, let me try that again, $4,000 worth.
That's just amazing.
Hi, I'm Georgia and the group you're hearing in the background is 3K now.
One of the great Caribbean artists, as you can experience, if you tune into a podcast,
Caribbean Free Radio.
You'll also hear me, and they're the more interesting voices and vibes from the Caribbean region,
plus lots of birds, frogs, and any other creature that happens to form part of the backdrop
in this fascinating crossroads where we live, work and play.
Caribbean Free Radio, the podcast.
Check us out at www.caribbeanfreeradio.com.
That's actually, definitely one of my favorite podcasts, the Caribbean.
I was always Caribbean, but I guess it's Caribbean Free Radio, so you're far.
It's short, it's like 15, 20 minutes, it's always got some great music in there, and
if you ever been to the Caribbean, I'm a big Jamaica fan of, oh man, I think I've been
to Jamaica 15 times.
I love it there.
It's actually, we should go back again, oh man, it's just such a pain and
ass pain in the ass to actually get there, it's no direct flight.
I think actually, but I just think corrected, there was the used to be no direct flight.
There is from London, I guess, maybe, hey, that's something we could look into.
Need to go back to Jamaica, desperately.
Funny, I was a Patricia's been talking about getting a tattoo, and not just any
old tattoo or for any reason, as a part of her heart medicine, instead of taking pills,
she has kind of like a sticker that she puts on her arm every day, and it dispenses
like this three milligrams or whatever of this blood thinner and heart healthy stuff into
her bloodstream.
It kind of does that gradually throughout the day, and what she wants to do is, it's
kind of like a little oval sticker, and she hates the whole fact that she has to have
it, and she's bummed out about it, so she wants to do some kind of really cool tattoo
that incorporates the sticker, so to be around the sticker, I have no idea what she's
going to come up with, but I guess she's working on something.
So there's been a lot of discussion about tattoos in the Curry Cottage.
Of course, Christina, I immediately jumped into, oh yeah, I want to tattoo as well, I don't
think, oh man, I've never had any drive for anything like that, but now that I think
about it, maybe a nice little marijuana leaf on the shoulder there, maybe it's just
experienced.
Download the new edition of the digital experience podcast, Available Now, only at
the lab.teethville.com.
That was like quick to the point.
So tomorrow, I will be doing a podcast, not quite sure what time that one will be up.
In fact, I'm even going to try and do a podcast with Ken Clark doing MTV Chronicles.
That may be what we'll be doing tomorrow.
I'm traveling to, I got to go visit some lawyers basically tomorrow, so real fun day, that's
why I'm staying overnight, strap on some practice with the wing commander right after that.
So look forward to hopefully MTV Chronicles.
Ken has been actually, he pulled out some of the old memos.
He's such a hamster man, he's got the infamous Michael Jackson King of Pop memo.
I think I've told that story before, I won't spoil it if you haven't, because it's
absolutely excellent.
And there's a couple more in there, I think, that'll, that'll ticker your fancy.
Again, today's pretty much a promo podcast, and it's got to kind of keep it down and
can't be yelling throughout the cottage, because, you know, it's not quite the castle anymore.
You know, I don't have that bar area that I can just yell all night, no one hears me.
So let's check out what we got here.
Hi Adam and daily source code listeners, I'm Anna, and I'm Jason from the Delta Park Project.
We don't know anything about sports, but we went to a Myrlic hockey game here in Portland.
I made a sound seeing tour of it.
Adam, you would have liked it.
The soundtrack to the game was pretty much a CDC in Scorpions.
Here's a clip.
Here comes our first fight.
Oh, yeah.
That breath I'm breaking them up.
Oh, is that blood?
Yeah, there's blood.
That's really loud in here, and there's this old lady over to our right, and she's got
like these industrial strength, sound protection, and then she's reading a book.
Oh, they're making a ranting run!
Yeah!
Woo!
Half of the door, half of the door!
Oh, the credit goes, wow!
If you want to check out the full show, head over to Adam's sound scene director.
Just go to our site, DeltaParkProject.com, where you can also find our most recent show where
we visit Portland's only nude beach and go looking for Kirk Cameron's career.
Oh, Kirk Cameron's a nice guy.
Don't be so mean.
I just did some sound seeing at the good Charlotte concert last night.
And I actually recorded it on my phone.
I was just wondering, maybe I couldn't have Bluetooth this over right now.
Let me see if this is, okay, yeah, that's the one, hold on a second.
Let me see if I could, oh, this would be kind of cool.
Let me see if I can send it now.
Here we go, send it via Bluetooth.
So I just recorded on the phone's internal recording device that you can also
record phone calls with.
So now what I've done, I'm actually trying to send this file,
straight from the phone over to my laptop, which is what I'm using for playback.
There it goes, it's connected, oh, this is so cool.
Oh, man, okay, so it's, how much longer does it have to go?
It's, uh, what is this, uh, 275 kilobytes.
Oops, I got to kind of keep the phone near the computer.
Because these damn G4 laptops are so much titanium and metal or whatever the hell it is.
Oh, it's like that, uh, it doesn't really receive, uh, Bluetooth very well.
Okay, cool, now this is going to rock.
So it's received it.
Now I can just click it, click on the little, uh, search thing there.
It should bring up the file in a finder window.
Yep, did that and I can open it and it should open it up in a quick time and I should be able to
Okay, um, uh, right outside the, uh, uh, kind of, right outside of the auditorium,
and it sounds like the name is about to come on names.
It's like some kind of new opening of the cast, uh, and selling it like this out.
I get it like three seconds before, then I'm starting to raise up and start to bring up.
Oh, there you go.
Stand, aye.
I'll have to go in in a few minutes and go check it out.
That's right, my for brick and the cattle is good sharp.
Obviously.
So clearly not edited down. Let me see if on the kick out.
Just fast for a little quick.
There you go.
Okay, so let's establish that that sound really sucks.
Oh, by the way, um, people are asking me about the sound that I, um, that I actually was able to create with the, um,
with the I river for the sound seeing tour of, I mean, a lot of the, of the beauty of that sound is because,
I'm using this wireless microphone set. Now I know that, you know, we've discussed this before and people
keep asking me what kind of microphone you're using. I'm using a electro LECTRO or Lima echo Charlie
Tango Romeo Oscar. Uh, it's a wireless transmitter and receiver. And I think what, that it's all
really in the, in the, in the, in the preamp that's in those, uh, in those two boxes. I'm not sure if
it's on the receiving sender, a side or the on the, on the transmitting side. But that's really where
all that great sound comes from, you know, it's just, you know, kind of goes to show that,
you know, it's, you still need some kind of equipment. If you really want to get the sound out of the,
I mean, you can't compare it to the internal mic, it probably can't compare it to a microphone.
You just plug into the I river. Um, it's, uh, I mean, that's just really, really good sound. And I,
I'm curious to know, uh, I think, um, actually Madge Weinstein uses some kind of microphone on the
I river, which is also a love microphone. Maybe, uh, she can post, uh, the, the details of what she's
using because that's, I mean, it's really, uh, that sounds pretty good too. And what I like about the
I river, which we've talked about is that you can actually choose between a line in or a microphone in.
So it does have some form of preamp in there. Um, and, you know, so it's, it's kind of working on
the, on the right combination. So if anyone else has any experience, let me know because I definitely
want to try and, uh, and codify some of these setups, what, uh, what works best for people.
Um, you might have seen or heard about the, uh, announcement about Nomdex 5.0. I'll be, uh, doing, uh,
I don't know if it's the keynote or one of the keynote's really excited about that. I remember when,
uh, we were in Guilford and Patricia and I were, I think was that, was that Nomdex was that web
2.0. I think it was Nomdex, wasn't it? Um, pretty sure it was. I think that's when we were in the hotel
and, uh, we were listening, uh, via the Wi-Fi. Um, Chris Perilla puts that show on. I'm, uh, pretty excited
about going out there. I mean, it's way out on, uh, it's in Seattle, basically, but, uh, and it's, uh,
I think it's sort of the July 25th or something like that. Let me just check for a second here for
your hold on. Might as well do that while we're at it. Okay. Uh, it's Nomdex.com. GNOMEDEX. It is, uh, June,
not July of course. June 23rd through the 25th, 2005, which is great because, um, on my way back,
I'll go through Portland and that's where I'll actually do my, uh, test for, uh, for my ticket for my,
for my fixed way. Trying to combine things, you're on a daily source code, boss. Hey,
Adam, it's the E-Man from Podheads Radio. Just dropping into let you know what's going on
with the Podheads. This week, we completed show number six of our weekly series. And with this show,
each of the Podheads has had an opportunity to host their own little corner of our world.
What do we do on Podheads Radio? Well, we talk about radio. If you were going to pick a
commercial radio station anywhere, that was podcast worthy. I think it would be these guys because
I hear people doing podcasts. I hear what they're talking about and, and that is,
essentially what real radio is about.
Oh, and old stuff was hot. And no one better exemplified the movement. That raw angry funk.
Slice still.
We even plug a little fun at ourselves and the world. This whole steroid thing in baseball is
the inspiration behind this show. You know, I figure if it helps a baseball player hit a ball
farther or a pitcher through the ball harder, I'm going to do it to see if it'll make me a,
uh, a big voice guy. You see these big voice guys, they make a ton of money. All they do is
sit around a microphone and talk into a microphone for a living. With syringe in hand, I am going to
administer, I think I'm saying that correctly administer. Anyway, uh, here goes.
There, all set. Now we'll just wait and see if it takes and I become a big voice guy.
You see what they're doing now? Have you seen these people? I mean, I love them all. You know,
members, I'll turn out low. But when you who tell me that Malcolm's mom orders trying to sell
you, uh, attempting to sleep or see, I invite itself out.
He bought heads radio, check us out online at podheadsradio.com. That's pod.headsradio.com. Thanks for the
plug-time Adam. We're now returning you to the daily source code. I got to tell you, I love it when
people put cool promos together. That makes my job so much easier on the source code. So melt
coming up this week. In fact, I want to do, I want to talk about it today because, um, well, you
in the, the whole nature of podcasting is that you probably are listening to this show on Tuesday
or maybe even Wednesday, which is good because this coming Wednesday, the fastest 10 minutes on your
iPod, the skinny on sport who talked about this before. Um, of course, you can find that at ipod.org
directory where we have now. And what was it, like, 43 hundred or 42 or 43 hundred podcasts
at last counts, unbelievable. Um, they've got an award show coming up. I think we talked about that,
and they sent me a promo haven't heard it, but I trust him.
On Wednesday night, the weight is finally over. The skinny on sports and iPod lounge
proudly present the skinny's. This is the first ever podcasted award show for sports. We've got the
top podcasting talent, along with musicians presenting the awards for categories and a way that
only the skinny on sports can. So tune in on Wednesday, enjoy the show, and have a chance to win a
one gig, iPod shuffle, or any modics six eye earphones courtesy of iPod lounge. You won't want
to miss it. Check out www.skinnyonsports.com for all the details, and the skinny goes to
you'll have to wait until Wednesday to find out. Skinny on sports, the skinny is the first
of what will probably be an annual event, I guess. And I am one of the presenters, very proud to
to be one of the presenters on the skinny's, the skinny on sports. Skinny on sports.com.
And remember, I told the well, of course, the U.S. trip, I went up to Microsoft,
really on invitation from Erika Hers. Good buddy, but well, good buddy. I know him for a number
of years, Dutch guy, but we actually hung out. We never really done a business, but we have met
professionally a number of times in Netherlands, then he went off to Italy to Rome, I think, and now
he's running Windows Media Center, Player, who how building number 43 or whatever it is on the
campus, and we met with a whole bunch of really, really fun people. That's actually was, it was so
different from, oh man, was I last there, like in 96 or something. It was, you know, like a totally
different company, at least that division in that building was just, yeah, I was kind of rocking
and rolling, and there were a couple of the MSN people there, and you know, we were talking a lot
about, obviously some of some of this is under the no-dam announcements rule, right? But we talked
about a lot about podcasting, also video podcasting, I actually had some video, cut some cool video
to show them kind of deliver the vision that I had on, on where podcasting is going and what we
can do, and also to help educate them a little bit, and they were very open about that, you know,
saying hey, we don't, we don't really know everything, and we want to learn, so it was a really
good experience, and today, DHL showed up. I just got to get up for a second, hold on.
That's what I grabbed this. Actually, it wasn't, I wasn't going to talk about this, but it's so
freaking cool. So this box shows up from DHL, and in it is a little mini flight case, you know,
a little metal case with actually more like a briefcase flight case, but totally protective case,
and in it is something I've never, and you're on a big fan of the Samsung, yep, you know,
I used to record the show on it, and in it is this little, it's like, what is it? 10 centimeters
by 10 centimeters, let's say, it's the Samsung portable media center, and essentially what this
device is, it's, it's pretty cool. I'll turn it on here for a second. It's like, it's a portable,
when those media players, it's the whole center, and you turn it on, looks very much like the media
center, you might buy for your living room, and it has a menu, my TV, my music, my pictures, my
video, and then the settings. Basically what it does is it has a really nice screen, you can plug
in headphones, you can sync it up with Windows Media Player, which of course I immediately did downstairs
on Christina's machine, and I was like, well, I mean, this is like Jesus Christ, this is what
what a beautiful thing to send, and I didn't quite get it until I turned it on, and of course,
I can't show this to you, but you know what, maybe I'll just, let me think what I can do,
maybe I just plug the plug the headphones, and I can at least play the first bit for you,
because it totally blew me away. These guys basically put together a 17-minute video, the MSN
guys, just for me, so I mean, receiving a gift like this, which they did say I could keep,
actually has Brent from not just Brent, but the portable media center team, Microsoft Studios,
MSN, everyone pulled together, and they probably stole this from someone, and we're saying
this to Adam, but it wasn't, it's not even that, I mean, that was really nice, but what they did,
the work that went into the 17-minute video, and I can't play it all for you, but I do want to
play just at the beginning. What I'll do is let me just, sorry, that was me pulling the plug out of my
out of my computer, out of my powerboard, now plug that into the, uh, into this portable media player.
There you go, okay, here it is, for Adam Curry, play from beginning, this is going to trip you out,
let me just turn it down a bit, in case it's too loud, this will trip you out, listen to this,
here we go, okay, it starts off with a little animation there, now listen to the first thing
that you hear, here it comes, this is going to, this is going to trip you out, it trip me, this is video.
Hey Adam, it's John Taylor, this is Nick Rhodes, we remember you Adam, whatever
I have, what is this podcasting thing about, and why haven't you sent us something because we're
sending this to you, so basically that's John Taylor, uh, a Nick Rhodes,
from Durand, sitting there talking shit about me, and I was like, it gave me a gimmick goose bumps,
I was like, wow, you know, that was very, very cool, of course they're totally schmoozing me, but
fuck it, I love it, and then, uh, and here comes Brent with a little bit of a hole, podcasting for
dummies, you know, it can't be that far, I mean Adam Curry is getting ready, that's it,
let me go, maybe you want to watch Adam, it's a cool dude, so, um, totally totally, I mean these guys,
they got a going on man, I'm gonna plug that, so, oops, I will, uh, obviously be bringing you
a more information about this, and this is exciting, yeah, this exciting development, you know,
I've never thought that I'd really be interested in handheld video, and I've had this conversation
with a lot of people, in fact, with the, uh, with the blogcast folks, they were walking around with
what is it the, uh, is it the, uh, uh, what is it, or, I can't remember the name of it.
Archio, whatever it is, is that the, uh, the video player, um, I have to take some of that back,
I really, I didn't think that it would be interesting, you know, and who's gonna watch this mobile video,
but when you get this device that basically can play MP3s, and we know media files and, uh,
odd forbos and wave and you name it and MPGs, yeah, so it kind of starts to hit home, it really does,
no, anyway, uh, we'll be talking more about that in weeks to come undoubtedly, okay,
what time are we at now, like 33 minutes, perfect, oh, you know what it's time for,
I'm gonna turn it down a little bit, because people complain about how loud this always is,
oh yeah, all you casting with Adam Curry, three, two, one, it's time for the internet with y'all,
pull it, hey y'all, how you doing? Hi Adam, y'all pull it here again with another hit test,
right on, and again, there's always three intros for you to identify, and here's number one,
I'm ready.
Sound of time like human league in the beginning here, but that's, that's not human games,
this isn't a little bit of a name, I gotta say, I think I'm stunned, here's number two,
I know that one is, that's uh, my tie with female intuition, I think, Dutch band, Dutch trio,
and the final one, number three,
is that the SOS band?
I think it's the SOS band. Sounded like that little kind of like half cowbell thing going on there,
times up, and you're already answered, and so number one in today's in test, is Fox the Fox.
I never would have pressed this little diamond. Oh, it's a title of the song.
Actually, it should have known that.
Now I've got my breath. All right, I recognize the hook now.
Sounds like a time band, right?
Okay, we're all for one.
On to the next one.
And then to number two, and number two is a Dutch band called My Tie, and they had a
really big hit with this song, female intuition.
One for two.
That's the final answer.
It's orange juice. Oh, standing in the rain. The song excites the rain.
Damn, I should have known that.
What a great song, is it?
I can't hear the rain.
Orange juice, Jones, and the rain. Kind of a set song.
I'm going to touch it. You can always have up beats on. That's true. And up tempo song. That's all right.
Well, that's it for today. You know what you have to do with it.
Hit test at gmail.com, and young polette.nl, this is JNPLAT.nl.
And Adam, see you next time for the next week.
Test. Bye-bye. All right, y'all. Thank you very much.
Check them out. Definitely if you want the extended version of the hit test,
young polette.nl.
The finest blues you've never heard. The roadhouse.
Hey, Adam Tony Stygler, Denison from the roadhouse podcast. The roadhouse is a weekly podcast.
Featuring the finest blues you've never heard. Every week, I go out and mine the depths of
GarageBand.com. Looking for the best in the pin of blues bands. Now, the roadhouse just
celebrated its fifth edition this week on March 19th. And if you haven't been listening,
here's what you've been missing.
Tell your legacy that I heard and heard and heard you said.
Talkin' in your dream home, and I heard everywhere you said.
Very good.
I started learning.
When I was four years old, I've made it for you and this ride.
Let's go.
I gotta tell you, man. I'm a sucker for some blues. I love it.
Definitely subscribe it to that. I just wonder if it's podcasts.
Hey, baby. If I was single, I'd take you home. Treat you right.
Wouldn't be no sleep for the whole day and night.
Get up in the morning with a smile. It's wide and I just sit down a bit off.
It's all over the crowd, but I'm a married man.
Don't blow the past right off.
I mean, that's a long skip the end.
I'm a pro mom.
It's just a success.
Yeah, kicking up our heels and we've been doing it without you. So, come on out and join us.
It's the roadhouse at codemode.typepad.com slash roadhouse.
Or you can subscribe to the feed at feeds.feedburner.com slash roadhouse.
Come on out. I'm step away from the hits of the 80s for a little bit and enjoy that time once.
Classics are the blues. We'll look for you. And thanks for all you do.
Technically, even though it is for the 21st, something that Patricia and I were talking about
during what the PPP podcast. Remember the days when you would buy an album and the band would
actually put an instrumental on it. You know, these days seems like everything has to be a
freaking single, right? So there's never an instrumental anymore. And Patricia was actually joking.
I think that was in the podcast. Maybe it was just some random conversation we had, but she said,
oh yeah, I know we used to have to do an instrumental or two just to fill up the album because you
didn't have enough songs with lyrics. And then I run across this show. And really, my love for
instrumental music is just flow on back and I hope it does for you too. It's not April 1st yet.
But here's a taste of speeches.
It's speechless. We try and bring you the best of new instrumental music.
For the next few minutes, I hope you enjoy a few samples and selections of our upcoming shows.
We are a style independent here at Spichthus. There's as many styles as there are ears to hear it.
And we certainly aren't afraid to leave the planet.
You
After floating through the void, Spichthus will set you down on the back porch and take you home.
And if you're back porch is nothing like mine. Maybe you want something a little bit more
south and west. Spichthus can accommodate you too.
Maybe that style's not for you, but yeah, some days we're just going to sit back and chill.
I'm where young Homer might be by steam or might be a little bit of that.
There's just a ton of fantastic instrumental guitar music out there. Some of it's fairly acoustic.
It's some of it ain't.
Coming to a podcast near you April 1st 2005. Visit us at ComposerPlanet.com-slashes.
Beechless. All righty, and that'll do it for the source code for March 21st.
Hey, I want to thank you all for subscribing. If you're not, check out dailysourcecode.com to
get the podcast feed as we can also find the latest show in the archives. And if you want to leave a comment
www.curry.com or drop me an email at curry.com.
All righty, sorry this was so late in coming tonight and as I said tomorrow I'm traveling, but
maybe then TV Chronicles with Connecticut, get the time and work out. He's only eight hours
time difference between he was in Portland and actually the nine hours since he was in the
vicinity of my lawyers. Always add an hour when you're near your lawyers. All righty,
everybody helps you to tomorrow take care. Bye, bye.