I'll just share a journey, too, for you, save it.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
And today is Tuesday, September 27th, in the year of our lure, 2,000 fans.
Warning, everybody, from hate to say it. Once again, sunny, California, sunny Northern California San Francisco.
It's a great and beautiful day.
You know, it's true what they say. It never rains in California.
And not seeing it rain once since I've been here.
Funny, a fog, of course.
Alright, so time now is 9 a.m.
Yeah, it's nearly 1 for me.
But, you know, as I've said, I've got to keep it head of the eight ball being out on the west coast.
The Friday I'm going back home, then the shows will actually be there for you in the morning regardless of whether you're east coast or west coast.
Actually, even if you're in the UK, it'll be a general west in Europe at the end of the morning.
So I've got my coffee ready, I've got my line up ready, we've got a hit test ready, we've got pot-safe music ready, we've got a new sponsor.
Yeah, I'm kind of cool stuff to talk about.
I'm just realizing something pretty interesting.
I'm looking out the window here at the condo at the Bank of America building.
If you've been to San Francisco, you've probably seen this huge tower, well, it used to have the time on it for me, which I could look right across.
You know, right out my kitchen window here, it's the time and the tower time has been off ever since I got here.
The first night it was on.
And I look kind of down and realize they're tearing the whole fucking tower down.
The wonder they turned the electricity off.
I guess it's going away.
To the tower, all the doors, all the doors, all the doors.
Well, hopefully they'll put something up in his place that is nice to look at,
or if they take it down completely, I'll have an even clearer view of the marina.
Alright, kicking it off today with a mashup.
This is one that artsen me just this morning, it's can't explain, but the mashup explains itself, check this out.
Alright, now let's hear the number from your latest record.
We are setting out to achieve anything particular with this.
We were trying to achieve the sound which we get on the stage at present, you know.
Can't explain what's written to show what we're really trying to do, you know.
Alright, fine, what do you say about us now, would it?
Yeah.
And for the future.
Cause on the future you had to.
I've got to credit call a seed.
It's not mine, but it's okay.
I don't make it anything.
Let your back, let your back, let it leave.
Don't do it, I'm not a bad thing to me.
It's not mine, but it's okay.
I don't make it anything.
Don't do it, I'm not a bad thing to me.
I've got to do it, I'm not a bad thing to me.
I've got to go, you can't leave.
Don't do it, I'm not a bad thing to me.
But it's all ready.
And I've got to do it, I'm not a bad thing to me.
What you're in and where?
Said it was going up free.
And I've got to give both of you a good.
So I get to a dream,
Show up on your car.
Yeah!
Better, okay.
I don't make it anything.
Let your back, let it leave.
And don't do it, I'm not a bad thing to me.
It's so good, but it's so good
I don't want to be with you
I don't want to run too late
I don't want to be alone
And I don't want to be here
Was it really what you're doing up like that?
Time, time
See I'm moving on
And I'll repeat to turn back
It's so good, but it's so good
I don't want to run too late
Time, time
See I'm moving on
I don't want to run too late
That'll wake you up
Races tower, rebooted by Smash
Find it over at mashuptown.com
Can't explain
I've had you in the minute
I see
Thank you gentlemen
Oh, those who boys in the beginning
They were so naughty, weren't they?
I was just looking through my blackberry
That's where I take notes
For stuff I want to remember to talk about on the show
Which of course is not effective once you have 50,000 notes
But I saw a message coming from Devon, Austin, Dorf
Adam, fear not, you are not a pussy
I can't stand getting my blood drawn either
Funny you should mention it because I'm sitting here with a band
that jumped my arm for the very same reason
Result of completing my physical and your emailing me
The one thing I hate more
than getting my blood drawn is having my blood pressure
You know, this is funny you say that
Because although I of course know in my
In my intellect
Whatever's there of the intellect
I know that it's funny blood pressure freaks me out a little bit too
Ever had since I was a little kid
The constricted feeling
We got through it all, didn't we?
Yesterday had a great day at Apple
Did not see my friend the frog and silicon valley
With his baguette barray and ipod
But I did ask the folks who were meeting with
You out of him, oh yeah, we know that dude
Of course there's like eight million buildings over there
So not really surprised that I didn't catch him
Walking across the campus
But we had a great update
That's really what it is
We go over there once every couple of weeks and have an update
We basically share some info
Because they do have a lot of things that they're seeing
A lot of trends, they've hired a new guy, Pete
Who is really responsible for the entire podcast
It's actually of the iTunes music store
And he has a lot of really good ideas
What he's really mainly is doing
He's trying to streamline a lot of these processes
Of people getting into the Apple directory
And I have to kind of reiterate one thing
This is Apple's directory
So they're not going to put everything in it
They don't have to put anything in it
They don't want to just like any potter.org
I direct our directory and we put everything in it
That's completely their prerogative
But there were a couple of things that came up in our talks
Which are really interesting
If you're submitting your podcast to Apple
Make sure that you have a description of your show
In your RSS feed
That's really critical
Because believe it or not
The people who take the submissions over there to Apple
They look at the description in the feed
They're not listening to all these shows
Which you can imagine
So if you've got a music show
And you file onto the music category
Which has been probably the biggest gripes so far
As that it just takes so long to get approved in the music category
That's probably because you didn't say
Dude, this is what kind of songs I'm playing
If you're playing like RIA license music
You're not going to put that in your feed
And they'll probably figure it out
And they won't list you in the directory
However, if you're playing potsafe music
Say it in the description of your feed
And also if you want to be featured
And I think that they just post up out
They think it's interesting
And probably kind of the way I do it here at the daily source code
You need to have a picture
No art
That's a big one
People do not have art associated with their feed
And because the whole iTunes podcast experience is also very visual
It boos you to have art
And it's funny because I don't like totally a green head nod
And by the way Adam, you don't have any art for the daily source code
And your feed
Sorry about that
And there was also some other minor thing that was wrong with the speck
I'm getting the new speck
Which I think was posted today or it will be posted today
So there were some things going wrong just in the feed by itself
No man
Hold on a second
Let me just see who's calling
I don't want to see who's calling me because I'm in the middle of a show
Screw it
But it looked like there might have been coming from home
So I'll have to check it out in a minute
So that was one of the big
Oh wow factors over there
And it makes sense
You know I ask people this all the time
Not just the metadata you're putting into your feed
Which is critical
I mean this is the stuff that propagates everywhere
This is how directories explain what's going on
And you just show this is how you are automatically categorized
But do that for your MP3 files as well
Please
Especially if you send off a promo
It really helps because you know
You have programs like I'm using MegaSeg
But you have programs like Cast Blaster
You have programs that even I tune
It pulls information out of the ID3 tags of a file
And displays it and that really facilitate
And getting the information out
So that was a big one
We talked about some other fantastic opportunities
Which
I got a voice mail
I'll tell you what
Let me play pod safe tune for you here for a second
Yeah
I thought you didn't need to be woken up
I only got checkers of voice mail see what's going on
This is Lee 3 Harris
Nothing to believe in
Pick it up on the pod safe music network for this reason check it out
I am TV and Vids 1
And I'm a little planet in Nickelodeon
And a net and a satellite dish and a
Big tanker Dr. Fish and a
You don't have this word you whisper
Nothing to believe in
Got a pretty good friend and a big new car
Everybody knows your name at the bar
All the design is sneakers
Terry O'Wit and she's speakers
We don't have just what you deserve
Nothing to believe in
Right to his right
When you say you're so old
Nothing more to silver go
When you know no matter not as the pain in
Then ain't gonna save you ain't gonna save you
Bucks and hooks upon the shell
Down on the corner there's a taco bell
Big max and two one sticks
And hot but stunned is and milkshakes
Nothing has just what it takes
Nothing to believe in
From the pod save music network
Check it out at music.podshow.com
More about that later on when
CC checks in
CC Chapman from accident hash
So I check the voice mail the phone call
Was funny
I kind of I'm happy I didn't pick up
Because I want to talk to these guys
But I want to take some time
It was the guy from the
Wiki base
That was the the Wiki that we had
Over the weekend that was so
Rockin and then kind of fell apart
Using it for show notes for the
Daily source code so of course
Exactly what I expected
What happened is we had multiple people
Working on Wiki show notes and there's
Another one which I put I actually
Linked yesterday show to that other
Wiki which Michael has been putting up
Man
I mean that we'll talk about your
Detailed show notes and footnotes
And correction notes and
Whoa that was really nice of course
I think he's doing most of the work
And the question is can we really
Keep it an open community
Wiki or do people come in and mess around
with it and I got to talk to these guys
About the the Wiki base
Whatever it is they are
To see if that you know what what happened
With the Wiki did it get taken down
Was it hacked the people mess with it
Is it not robust enough and these are all all questions
It's probably
I don't know I mean it would be nice if you
Can have some kind of permissions or something
I'm sure it has permissions in there
But I just got to figure out what the permissions are
It's got to be really simple
And I just like the whole idea of if you show up
There's the show notes and oh man
You know I want to add something
But still you got to kind of have someone
Keep it an eye on it because you know
Somebody can really come in and mess it up
And you know
There you go well have to kind of see how that works
As a community project
I'm still very excited about it by the way
It really it really kicks ass
And these I've never had show notes like this
So check that out
It's it's linked from yes
There's also linked to today's source code
I'll link to those show notes
And we'll see how Michael does on that
Maybe he can start giving us a little bit of feedback
As to how we can you know open this up to a wide
The community participatory event
You know what I mean
Let's see
What else did I have here
I got a couple of things
Oh, here's something really sucked
So yesterday I come back to the condo
And I can't find three com anymore
I mean this is
And for those of you who've been listening
Three com is the of course the three com is a device name
But there's been an open
Wi-Fi network
Am I building called three com that's just been nice and powerful
And I've been able to sit in at least four different locations in the condo and use it
It's gone
So all that was left now
Let me see I have Benbo 7
And Benbo 7 is not strong enough to make it
Actually is the only one spot that it works in the entire place
And it's kind of like on the couch and I have to turn it just so so I can get two bars on the airport reading
If I had an airport antenna and external antenna
I'm sure I do much better or even if I had the
I didn't bring the
The crap with me that does really well on Wi-Fi reception
So I kind of like had to prepare for the show last night
In you know I've contorted in all different
All different directions just to be able to get the Wi-Fi signal
So I guess I'm going to have to break down and actually have to go and
Call the cable or the 80s
80s
Yeah those guys
Oh it's we're talking to the people
We're talking to the people
Don't you want to say hello to the people
Yeah, how can you say podcast
Dang those reds are podcasting again
Almost live from Kirkland Washington
It's a bread abroad with Steve Lacy
Hi, this is Steve Lacy from my bread abroad
And the builders were fast here
Oh, do you know what they don't do tea breaks?
What they do back home?
Yeah, it's just down there
Back to Montana
Montana was grand
Sure, as I was the first time it was kind of similar
I was like there were guys with like a couple of cowboy hats on and I was like
They get to wear them because they're actually cowboys
Yeah, they're not front and because it's like
I can't hold for American companies doing business in the UK
Oh, she she could just do PR for me in a really small skirt
The fun now
You are listening to a bread abroad
Is British and he's not in Britain
That that's why he's a good name
So come and join this Englishman living in the Pacific Northwest of these United States
As I rant, rave, wax, lyrical, and place some fine music
You can find my blog on the web and subscribe to the show at www.steve-lacy.com
And don't forget you can find this and on a fine British podcast at www.brickaster.com
See ya!
Pod Show
Content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother
Hello, Adam, it's me, Mad Weinstein, your favorite lesbian from the internet
And the pod shows
I have a wonderful, wonderful, exciting announcement for you
And for all of the podcast turds out there
CubeHodder.org
The exclusive not exclusive
I don't know what the fuck I'm talking about
The gay and lesbian podcasting community
Which is of course open to anybody
You don't have to be gay, lesbian, transvestite, transvestite
Or a wander wisdom to join
In fact, our own PW Fenton is a member
Even though he's not well, he's a male lesbian
Anyway, we just reached our 100th podcast turd
Our 100th queer podcast turd
On the CubeHodder
And I'm so excited because just a couple of months ago
When iTunes was released, there were only 13
CubeHodcasters
And now we have over 100
And we've got 300 members including listeners, fans and contributors
So I'm very excited, Adam
And now, what does this mean for pod show
And the community in general?
Well, but it's why didn't you tell me Adam
But I have an idea, why don't we start?
Well, maybe it's your idea, I don't know
But maybe we can give up some free hosting
Away to the CubeHodders
And then they can work with us
Provide advertising for them
And then they get money, we all get money, we all get happy
I don't know if that didn't make any sense
You can cut that out, I don't fucking know
I'm a lesbian
Anyway, thank you, Adam
For all you support on this pod show
It's been a dreams come true for me
And I know that the other pod cast
Herds out there are just as excited
To make money doing what they enjoy
Doing
And I hope we can make this happen for them
And I know that we can get some common
Manufacturers to advertise some of these
Boo's, manufacturers, these Kenneth Coles
Type of companies, computers, whatever
You know, we're here, we're queer, we ask
We tell QPOTA.org
And this is Madge Weinstein
From yeast radio, you have favorite lesbian
In the bloatosphere
Have a nice yeast infection everybody
On yeast radio
Madge, that's an entrepreneur
Sorry, I can already tell from my equipment readout
Here that we had a skip during a
Just a little diatribe there
That's because God, I hate this
Ever since I installed Tiger
I'm sure there's a way to turn it off
But of course, I keep forgetting to do it
The dot mac, icing just kicks in
And of course, since I don't
I'm not able to reach a network here
It's trying to mount my eye disk
And it freezes the finder
And then all kinds of bad stuff happens
But I think Madge, fantastic
You blew me away with it with that
I totally totally, they've over 100
Podcast in the QPOTA.org directory
Which of course is also linked
From the indie potter.org directory
This is the cool thing
Where you can have subcategories
That are created somewhere
Completely different and still link into the same place
That really is pure genius of that system
But talking about advertisers
This is something that we've been working on
Very hard here at Pod Show
I came up with what I thought was a perfect idea
And I've really been trying to hit it on the show
But I got a big, a big no from the Pod Show
Sail staff yesterday
Although I still think they should try it
Volkswagen has been very interested in advertising on Podcast
And I kept, I had to test that
We're on a way to Apple with Chris
And I'm saying Chris, dude
Get me a Volkswagen
And we'll do a couple things with it
We'll broadcast from it
But also we'll do my biodiesel experiments on it
That was the part that he had kind of a reason
I don't know how I'm going to pitch that
To tell him man, it'll be the coolest thing ever
Everyone's going to be buying these Volkswagen
And crapping in their tank to make it run
I'm telling you this is going to be a revolution
So I don't know
I mean that's usually how it goes
Then we have to go through the agency
And the agency has to go to the client
So I wonder how revolutionary the agencies are
It's just a thought
So we have been looking to a whole bunch of other advertisers
And sponsors really
And it's cool when you get a sponsor
Because sponsors usually want you to talk about a certain product
And that's really easy to do if you'd like the product
So yesterday I was given product to take home the test with
And even though we're not even starting the promotion
I want to, you know, first of all
You got an iPod, maybe you're listening to this on an iPod
Or another MP3 player
Look at that iPod for a second
Now imagine
Just hold that and you hold it in your hand if you will
Now imagine that
Out of each side of the iPod
Something started to grow
Towards the right and towards the left
Hmm, 50
Great, I've programmed you yet again
It is the MM50
From a logic tech
What the hell is it?
Well it's something that I never would have bought myself
Because you know
I've seen these things laying around
You know, docking stations for your iPod
Because that's what this is
But this one really blew me away
First of all
It works with both iPods and with other MP3 players
So that's really styled for the iPod
But you can plug in an external source
Just a mini jack
So I actually had it hooked up to my computer last night
And I don't know what these guys do
Do it logic tech or how they do it
And what are they from different like Switzerland I think?
Yeah, I've actually visited them before in Switzerland
But the sound that comes here the whole second
Let me just it has a little remote control
You see which is very very nice
The sound that comes out of this thing is just unbelievable
Let me see
Are we on here?
Hold on
There we go
Wait, that's not what I want to see
Now this
I don't want that
Okay, this is from my iPod
Listen to that man
This is based tone
She all turned the mic a bit
The sound is unbelievable
This is exactly what I've been looking for here at the condo
Because I didn't want to put a huge stereo system in place
You know it's like all kinds of wires and shit
And I'm not going to use it anyway
Because everything I have comes off of the
Computer or off of the iPod
So this thing has a
A plug so you can connect it to your computer
So we just drop your iPod in it syncs automatically
And here's the thing that really blew me away
It has a little case and it has fold out feet and everything
But it's really sturdy it's not like a some plastic job
I wanted to take it into the bathroom last night as I was preparing for bed
And so I'm already to take the adapter with me and then you know move it over
And I unplug it and it keeps on playing
So when you have it plugged into it has a nice little white wall adapter
This used to be
When you have it plugged in
It charges the iPod but it also charges
Maybe it's running on the iPod battery
I don't know but it ran for a real long time last night
And I'm very very impressed
This is the thing by the way that I've been looking for
For the shows that Ron and I do
And we talked to advertisers and marketers
Because we always have to plug into
We always have to plug into the house system
In someone's media room and sometimes well know
I'd say most of the time
The sound really sucks and you can't control it
So now I'm just going to put this thing on the fricking desk
It's loud enough to blow up a whole room full of sounds
So it's very cool
It's the MM50
From from Logitech
Soon to be a sponsor of
The pod show podcast
I'm at CCH1 to drop you a quick note
Because I heard you talking about the pod show
Music rewind show today
You and your listeners a quick update on what it is
Pod show music rewind is hosted
And produced by Marcus Couch of the scenes
Check it out at buscinesine.com
Great pod cast in a proud member of the pod show music game
Anyways, what we wanted to do and what Marcus came up with for the idea
Was you know to kind of highlight all the different
Seven music shows that are signed to pod show
I'm giving people a flavor of what each of them is like
So every week we're going to a recap
Playback clip from each show
Every week what we're doing is each pod gastric
Gives Marcus a clip of a song and an intro
All that from the pet previous week
A record something brand new and gives it to him
Then he puts it all together and puts it out every week
And for those listeners you want to check it out
Surf on over to pod show music rewind.com
We're going to be it's it's it's in beta guys
Working it all set up getting all the servers and everything set up
But there's both a regular feed and an enhanced feed
So you can subscribe to either one
You know the hands has all the cover art
The album art the links all that jazz
But we realize not everybody can
Support enhanced pod cast
So we put out a regular one as well
And we put we submitted the listen to iTunes
But we all know how that goes so hopefully it'll be there soon
And so check it out and kudos to Marcus couch
He kicked ass and really stepped it to the plate
And knocked this one out of the park
So Adam glad you're enjoying the show
And the seven-headed monster will be that can do that
He's out guys totally rock do it
I really like listening to that last night
By the way CC make sure you got in the description of the feed
Saying that it's all pod safe music
That'll help with getting it listed in iTunes as we now know
Rolling this out off the pod safe music network
It's a good example of no ID three tags fly highs
What I see right here. I like it kind of a reggae vibe
What we need love
Beyond my kind why they know what we're going to get
Why they know what we make
No Jedi why they want
Keep it shoulder later that's where we are
Be keep on post-selling
Not fight
Maybe I need to
I'll be ignited
To the open up the plan
Make your hear from the make it go down
Drain the vibe with room in
To put it in your brand
Good know
To the sister
She must feel
Yeah
I'll proud
That.
drought and
What the
2.
Made a fool myself, it's a stumbling long
Like if you'd like to lose you to throw up a song
All I did was finish think about the freaking extra
Spending 80% in dollars every day of the week
It was our deal, some trouble
Shampoo, we won't
Shampoo in the corner, yeah, you know
The really was no other
It made me feel better, any time and any weather
I was an angry man drunk and I didn't know no better yet
I didn't mean to do it, but I still think it was suited
Yellow and ma'am, I could only like a Puerto Rican moon kid
No, hold on, go on now
Est on the Westoma, I'm not the same person
No, hold on, he's not the one I've been
He's a lost track of what was those days
But now I'm blind, high, cause my ramen paid
Like, right
You can't stop what you got
When it takes I've ready for it
They like it, you did, ma'am, I lost me
Stay a cool bar, and then you can't stop it
Reyes, open your leg, live from from my beloved
Me, they've been through the alley, but they can't catch me
Them can't see me, me, I'm a scar
And me, T-B, we fit that line, you won't need a shine
No player here, sure
Then step into the next, let me shine a fly
We're young, fit fly
We're slim, for your end, to the sky
We're the young partner, earth
Our only fit up, minutes, little hell
Make your feel, more minutes, away
I'll pick it, wind it, settle a bit
Drink the Bibleыш, mark ya neverstanden
Have an old dictionary, make a Away
Nadaie famous, Salme P Filmet,nie, it's Tebot Your Life
Come on, take their backs, come on, we're Turder things out
Set then them our black, damn our home
A win with you, I love it, bye
Time, our memories are your night
Ye, you, United
Bye, I live, T'you
I touch when it Essa
Now we're back, we're ramen pay
I've been to Jamaica about 17, 18, 19 times of vacation, started off with a documentary
I did once with a good Jamaican, I loved it so much that we just kept on going back
on vacation.
I love it.
I haven't been in a couple of years and it's time to go again.
We always go to a place called Round Hill, which is just fantastic.
It's great because you can go there for 20 years and the same staff is there and they all
remember you and I've become good friends with some of the staff over there.
If you go to, I'm not really like, I'll leave their stay in the house because these are great
houses that other people own that you can basically rent for a week or so.
They're fully furnished and you come with the staff with three, three people staff and it's
really nice.
But if I'm not hanging out with them, then I'd like to go into town but hang out with
the locals and some of the guys who worked out the beach and I teach them how to do stuff
on the internet and they teach me other important things in life.
And I've been to a dance hall a couple of times actually and so you hear the DJ of
the sound system.
What am I here?
Oh, is that the MM50? Is that still on hold on?
Yeah.
That would not read a Hayworth music.
I should be joining the Q-botters.
So the toaster or the DJ from the sound system will invariably say, LITA!
And you can actually buy these plastic disposable big lighters and they turn them up.
As far as they can go, in fact they rip the metal off and turn them and you know, so
that we can push the flame level even higher and they just blast these flames into the
air and sometimes they bring along aerosol cans and spray aerosol and ignite that.
And that's the whole bit of LITA!
So good news.
Well, funny news actually. I finally got a hold of the trucking company, JC Penny.
So here's what happened.
I never really told you the whole story, but I really got into it with JC Penny.
And they had said, if you don't hear anything by Tuesday because the shipping company has
14 working days since the, since it was invoice, that was August 28th.
That was two weeks after we freaking ordered.
They have 14 days to call you for an appointment.
So by Thursday last week, I'm like, excuse me.
They haven't called yet.
And you know, so then it took like 15 minutes and then the person came back.
I called customer service, JC Penny.
Well, here's the number of the shipping company.
You got to go call them and make an appointment.
I'm like, whoa, that's not going to cut it.
You know, I'm your customer.
I'm not the shipping company's customer.
You got to take care of me.
And just, you know, well, yeah, we can't help us.
Look, give me a supervisor.
I just want to talk to somebody.
So I got a supervisor on the phone.
And I said, look, you know, if I had known that I had to eventually call the shipping company myself, you should have emailed me that information.
Email me the name and number of the shipping company.
Well, yeah, I know, but, you know, she just wouldn't understand that I was not complaint.
Well, I was pissed off that I've been waiting so long for this stuff.
But at least tell, you know, send me some information through email.
Let me know when you complete your order.
Tell me what the process is going to be and that this is how it's going to go.
That basically I have to call up the shipping company to order something to make sure it's delivered or that it can just get stuck.
And it just went on and on and on.
I said, look, please, just put in a little tag next to my name in the database.
Have someone call me.
I'll tell them how they can make their business much better.
And then she said in the legendary words, I'm just a small person.
There really be a company.
I don't think I can help you with that.
And I said, well, I'm sorry.
Then I can't be your customer anymore.
And I finally called the shipping company yesterday.
Yesterday.
They had a freaking with JC penny shipping.
Like they're a part of it.
You know, JC penny is pretending like they're an independent company, which I'm sure they are.
Maybe this phone line just flashes and so with JC penny.
So they'll call me Wednesday.
They'll call me tomorrow to let me know what time they're going to deliver on Thursday.
Which, of course, is the day before I go, which means it's going to be this mad dash of unpacking shit and putting the bed together.
Ron is promised to come over.
He says he says he's good at that.
I've never seen him hang anything, put anything together.
I've seen him design stuff.
He's really good at that.
But I've never seen him actually with a screwdriver or a hammer or a wrench for that matter.
So that'll be interesting.
That's a sound seeing experiment right there.
Tell you.
So anyway, so that's kind of taken care of the day before I leave.
But I guess I'll be back in two and a half weeks and we'll be back here in the condo because it's just really heating up.
Also, I figured out that, you know, now that I know that I kind of live here in San Francisco,
three blocks from anywhere.
And there's a big block.
And you've got to walk under highways and pass bus stations before you get to a Starbucks.
Which, I don't mind that much in a year or two.
This will be a very bustling hustling community up here because they are really building.
After they got that Bank of America building torn down.
And so I, of course, I went to the best place for advice.
I went to the, you know, the dormant.
Mario.
And Mario, he switched on.
He knows what podcast things about.
He's a musician.
He's, he's, he's totally into it.
He's into the podcast music scene.
He says, hey, man, why don't you just order from Safeway?
What, they deliver?
Yeah.
So popped on Safeway.com.
And, you know, he just go through the entire store shop by aisle.
It was, you know, we've heard about these things and they do exist in places.
But here it actually does exist and does work, I guess.
So today between 4 and 6 p.m.
I have to be back.
Otherwise, it would have had to wait until tomorrow.
But I need so many different things just to survive here.
So I didn't put like a $250 order.
So they're going to deliver that today, including mobs and brooms and all kinds of stuff.
So, hey, yo, long live the internet.
What is comedy forecast?
It's a comedy podcast in four minutes or less.
Is it a rant?
Sometimes.
It's like those waitresses who ask you how your meal is while your mouth is full.
I'm sure they do it on purpose.
Is it a parody?
Occasionally.
Oh, there.
This is Paul Land.
And this is four minutes with Paul.
Is it funny?
Oh, I hope so.
Well, when I think we need to upgrade our computer.
What's wrong with the computer?
Well, the cassette drive doesn't work anymore.
And it's getting really hard to find pin-feed paper for the dot matrix printer.
But I love that Commodore 64.
Yes, I know.
You can check us out at our website, comedy4cast.com.
And that's with the number four.
Okay?
We're done, done, done, done.
Bye-bye.
The motor tools went forth and cast their pods in the direction of all who would listen.
And casting their pods in this manner, they were henceforth known as podcasters.
We're getting your ear.
I've got you podcast right here.
Hello.
This is Doug K.
The Executive Producer of IT Conversations.
Poptech 2004 was arguably the most popular event ever published on IT conversations.
And this year's Poptech held in Camden Main October 19th through 22nd looks like it's going to be even better.
Well, have I got a deal for you?
For the extraordinary cooperation of the folks at Poptech and Limelight Networks,
we're going to be broadcasting a free live audio stream of the entire Poptech event.
That's right.
I'm going to be getting up at 5 o'clock Pacific Time every day,
dragging my butt into Studio 2 to host the program via the remote ISDN feed from the Camden Opera House.
But wait, there's more.
During the breaks, we'll bring you the greatest music of all types from the podsafe music network.
Hosted by the various musical hosts of the Podshow music shows,
including the host of accidental hash and the manager of podsafe music network CC Chapin.
So mark the dates October 19th through 22nd on your calendar.
Check IT Conversations.com for the schedule.
And thanks for listening.
Doug K. Man, he's got it together.
He's got a great network, IT Conversations.com.
And the way he does it, and it's a non-profit organization that he's put together with just tons of volunteers.
And people willing to really capture this audio.
All these great minds and great speakers and great events.
Poptech, of course, is also, I guess, kind of an open source type of event.
But it's a bitch to get to, it's held up in what Camden main is that it?
So really exciting this year is that during the breaks in the live feeds,
we'll have the podsafe music network gang rolling out podsafe music.
So this is great, man. We're really doing it.
We are creating an entire new universe without any help from the outside.
But, of course, I have to admit, I do miss my non-podsafe music once in a while.
Yon, help me out.
I've been one girl in casting with Adam Curry.
I suppose you think you know me or me.
So yeah, what did you add?
The hit test.
Yon, Polet.
Come on, Yon, Polet.
Try as me, baby.
Hey, Adam, this is hit test number 61, it's Tuesday morning.
And I just get out of bed, so my voice is still a bit low.
I get to.
Can be an advantage, of course.
I wanted to let you know that I updated the hit test track listing page.
I added a lot of iTunes links.
Oh, cool.
So if anyone was going to buy tracks from the hit test and would use my links,
I would appreciate it very much.
Yeah.
Okay, three intros and three answers and this is number one.
Oh, man.
I give up.
And this is number two.
Robert Palmer, can we still be friends?
At least I got one.
And the final one is always number three.
Oh.
It's a lovely thing to do.
I think that's what it is.
Okay, I know number two for sure.
I'm not sure about three and one is tough.
And times up and this is answer number one.
It's a song from 1984.
This is Stinssel Town in the rain.
To the Nile.
But every ever comes so far.
Yeah.
We're not a goddamn one.
I give up.
I've seen it all before.
I know that.
Love was so exciting.
Tinssel Town and Lorraine.
Oh, man.
I'm not.
Here we are.
I've been this way.
Tinssel Town in the rain.
Answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
Let's Robert Palmer.
This is can we still be friends?
I love this song.
We can play this game any moment.
Can we still be friends?
Things just can't go on like before.
Madam Missing.
We have so much to learn.
Now it's time for the winter time.
We're going to the winter time.
Robert Palmer has answered number two.
And can we still be friends?
We're going to the situation I'm in right now.
And that's because I'm going through a divorce.
Answer number three.
I was right.
It's a love thing.
Answer number three.
Man, I love music.
And I really love these music.
Expect a lot of it in the coming hit test.
Okay, this concludes hit test number 61.
It's Tuesday, September 27th.
And of course, I hope it'll be played soon.
Adam in your daddy's source code.
I hope you did well.
I hope you enjoyed this one.
Two out of three.
Always.
Feedback is welcome at hittest.gmail.com.
And you can find all sorts of info on my blog.
Yampolet.com.
J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T.com.
And as I said earlier, there is a page with all the tracks in the hittest.
And now I edit almost all iTunes links.
So if you're going to buy a track from the hittest,
please do it using my iTunes links.
Well, thank you for listening to you for the next one.
Hopefully tomorrow, so until then, bye-bye.
Notice I'll single guys have a much higher output.
Yeah, and I'm sorry you're going through all that, and that sucks.
I don't really does bike.
I head on over to hittest.com or hittest.nl,
so that you can find out more about the tracks played in the hittest
and actually go purchase them.
Nothing we talked about at Apple yesterday.
I reiterated I said, dude, come on.
This is perfect two years.
I wish there was a G5 or some other model that I could...
I would have upgraded a long time ago, but there is no upgrade.
This is the biggest one you can get.
You know, the fastest.
I think it has the fastest processor,
but I think it's just it's had it, man.
The mouse, the trackpad, doesn't work anymore,
and I've been through a million,
I've been through this for like a year,
where the trackpad will also go screw me on
and then you have to reset your P-RAM
and do all this stuff and shake it like an etchist.
Another pop show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.
Thanks for watching.