Delta Sierra Charley 2-6-2
On Show.com make no claims regarding the quality of its hot chillers or the sanity of its producers. Listen at your own risk.
There are no secrets.
Only information you don't get out of.
Adam Curry.
A $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky and greasy.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
This is Adam Curry.
It's the 19th of October in the year of our Lord 2005 good morning.
First time in weeks I could say it ain't all that sunny.
Everybody how you doing.
Right in early here, Northern California coming to you from the Curry condo.
It is the Daily Source code.
It's a bit of the week. It's Wednesday.
Cloudy, rainy and the sun is just coming up over the horizon.
It's a little bit before 8am.
Of course means that a lot of you.
A lot of people listen to the source code.
It's enough for hours.
These codes.
You pay.
Other parts of Europe.
Oh man.
Sorry about yesterday.
Apologies.
There was just no way I was going to be able to make a show.
I spent a lot of time.
Was it Monday evening talking to Andrew Grumman?
Andrew was leading developers on iPod 11.
Just talking through life and stuff.
You know when you get talking through life and stuff like that before you know it's 11 o'clock.
Yesterday.
I think I told you that we had to go.
Ron and I were going up to Redmond to pay a visit to Microsoft.
And the flight left.
I think the flight was like 7.15.
So I was up at 4.30.
Oh man.
It's just a way to early for me.
So of course I'll tell you a bit about our travels.
Beware.
Of course I'll have to shoot you after I tell you everything right.
So a show full of things to talk about.
Promos.
Plenty of European promos as well.
And of course pod save tunes and a mashup.
This one I've been kind of holding on to for a couple of days.
It's titled Fat Boy Betty.
I can't help it.
Oh yeah.
This is a waking up.
Nothing else.
It's Fat Boy slim versus.
Be polycliffer.
For mashup town.com.
Yeah.
Right.
And tell me where it's coming from, what you're making, everything's gonna have so much time to try to get it out
And tell me where it's coming from, what you're making, everything's gonna have so much time to try to get it
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all
all right, all right, all right, all right, all right,
all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right
all ready, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, you all have an awesome comic screen, our favorite leather advertisings's design, well, all right, we'll see you next time.
There you go. I apologize. I hadn't put up the the picture of the beautiful sunrise yesterday that came up over the MM50
I'm a logitech speaker set. I just had no time. Yeah
Yeah, I have one of those
What's it one of those is it a Casio camera thing of a Casio camera doesn't it I wish it had blue tooth because
You know to hook up hook it up to the Mac and get it into iPhone
Oh, and then export it and do all that stuff is just too much. I got to set that up. Well
So here's the thinking I've been through this. I told you that I'm you know, just struggling along here with the power book
I think hopefully before the week and otherwise in the weekend. I'm gonna get TV's
I got to get an I Mac up here
Which you may actually turn out to be one of my TVs at this thing can maybe just get one of those adapters you can go from the cable box into the
Into the Mac so I'll might do that and
Somewhere between five minutes ago and
Four hours from now the cable guy's gonna come so I'm kind of well
I hope he shows or she shows up
Before 1030 because I really have to go Ron and I I'm gonna go see
Ray Lane one of one of our investors. It's you know, we try to do that actually we try to do that almost every week. There's so much going on and
And it's kind of cool to go get advice on stuff
So yesterday we went up to Seattle. I have to say when Ron and I travel. It's actually it's actually quite nice because
Once wheels are actually once we're in the plane
There's no one that can interrupt us. You know, there's no phones. There's no one saying you kind of just ask you one question
And it's great and especially if flight like that which is under two hours, I guess it would like an hour and 20 minutes or something like that
Oh, man, do we get the jam? We're like we're like like we've been married for 15 years, which is almost truth
But oh, man, it's great. We bigger each other the whole way and now this won't work and how about this?
And I think it should be this and it's so it's very very it's early
But it's it's an extremely creative. So actually everything went pretty smoothly flight was good
got up to Redmond and of course the person we were seeing there the
Was my buddy Eric Hirsch
he is
I don't even know his title actually, but he sits at the head of the table. So so I guess he's in charge of something and we got a demo
And we had a lot of conversations of course and met a couple other people who were part of the windows media team and got a
demo of the new windows media player and
I'll tell you
If I could tell you, I would but I'd have to have to shoot you later on
So that was without a doubt very interesting being up there. It's still it's just not for me. I'd kind of tell you
Redmond is no
Now that of course is not too far from from Seattle and before we left we had a couple other
couple other people to see couple other Seattle company. So all in all it was a very
Very fruitful day and of course when we got back to the airport typical if you're flying out of sea
Tag, you know, I was like well, you know, the flights delayed for four hours
So
Switching around jumping from carrier to carrier and you're supposed to go in Alaska and airlines and and wound up going on United and it was really cool on the way home
And I actually saw I was looking out the window. I'm like man is
You know, above the clouds, of course, and it was a full moon which is absolutely beautiful
Just blanketing across you know, this beautiful glow of the moon across these clouds that we were flying above and underneath the moon
I thought at first it was
It was a star
But I could look at it. That doesn't make any sense and there were no other stars to be seen strangely enough
And sure enough the the captain came on the inner com and
Said, you know, if you look out the left-hand side of the aircraft you'll see you see the moon
Okay, duh saw that but underneath that it's a planet. He said that's planet Mars and apparently
This is the closest Mars
Got to or has been to the moon and I subsequently I guess the earth in 60 years
I I'm I really should
I'm hand maybe this lack of astronomy podcast that's more info on that was you definitely find out because
There was some kind of
Astronomical phenomenon going on that's for sure, but it was really really really beautiful
Let me see I wrote down
a whole bunch of things here in
In my blackberry to talk to you about
See we talked about
Oh, yeah, yeah, they're telling you that safe weight. Did I tell you that safe weight delivered?
They delivered all of my
Actually that was that was Monday night so I haven't told you yet
They delivered my my groceries which I'd ordered from the UK which was kind of cool. You know, so I set up the delivery time
And
Once again everything went well, I think somewhere someone else has milk had burst open and and it leaked a little bit on my stuff
But that was okay nothing. I mean, you know a little bit of milk won't harm anybody
But what they do is if they don't have a particular item then they'll make a decision the decision is whether they'll
Replace it with a different similar item or if they'll just say hey, sorry
We didn't have this and we'll credit your account for that
So what I'd ordered was some lovely even nilla French vanilla roast coffee
Which was out of stock now here's what they did
instead of
Giving me a different flavor or
Well, I guess that they could have said well, we don't have it and you know will hook you up next time instead they gave me
decaffinated French vanilla roast now
If you're not a coffee drinker, you know stop for two seconds before you do something like that
There's a big difference between the taste and what it actually the drug itself does for you, right?
Huh
Hello, what the hell was that?
There we go. Welcome to the capital radio podcast here. We plan to keep you up to date with all the things
You don't have time to listen to on the website like jingles interviews and much more
We plan to keep the content fresh so please make sure you always keep your podcasting software up to date
This is capital there's nothing like it music power
All the hits and more and now stand by Durban East London
Maritsburg the wild coast and all of capital country for the most music power and if you have an already
Subscribe to the capital radio podcast
Now
Hi Adam my name's Paul. Do you remember this daily source code for Tuesday April 26 2005
I sure do that was the first podcast I ever listened to I know you bought my
Many I bought about two days before and I wonder what all this podcasting was all about and that was the first one I listened to
I've listened to every single one and when you don't do one I feel like something's missing
I'm walking to work in this like
No, bloody DSC
What's he up to so where's my DSC?
It should be a song shouldn't it? I'm not going to sing it for you. Don't worry anyway you've made me make my own it kind of starts like this
Fletchy flashy
There are warnings of gales in biking north of Sierra south of Sierra 40s cromotty fourth time dogger
Climbers fits Roy's soul lungy fast neck Irish seat Shannon rock-holt malin
Hebrede's Bayley fair-al-fair-o-s
The general synopsis at one three double-low
You might be asking yourself what is a flashing 12 podcast what a podcast is a
Radio show on the internet my name's Paul and I'm the one that does it
And a flashing 12 is someone who doesn't get technology someone who when you walk into the house and you see their VCR
The number 12 is sitting there. They're so technically a net they haven't been able to program the VCR clock to say the right time
Now your keys were on the outside of the vehicle. Oh my god. Now those are kind of automatic blocks over
What I need to do take hold of the inside of your door handle there. Are you doing this?
The shiny thing grab the shiny thing
Okay, okay, now give that a touch
Okay
It open
Oh my god, thank you. Okay, now what is that noise?
Oh, that's a door alarm
Yeah, but that only happens have the keys for the ignition
Oh my god, you know what
Your keys are actually a mirror ignition
Yes
Oh my god, thank you so much
That's why we're here. Do you need anything to get a gun star?
Always on because you're always blind. I'm sure I'm gonna get a billion emails from bombs all over the world over that one
But hey, what we're about is telling people about technology and when it goes wrong
It's called the flashing 12 podcast flashing number 12 podcast and you can find me at parkylandon
dotlipsin.com as PARKy London dotlipsin.com
You find the latest show the first show the only one I would actually own up for two plus a couple of primers
Which I thought were unbelievably often I kept them to the record and
You'll find the RSS for you there. You can email me at flashing 12 at gmail.com
That's flashing number 12 a gmail.com and thank you very much
What you do because I think it's great pod save music. Thank you very much Adam. I'll hand back to you now
Hello, I would like some of the Udron keys
bull or air sewer
No, I wanted for my armpits
I
Was going to a pentacosal church at the time hold my hands up
Brandy I was ordained I had become an ordained minister. I'm pouring them down rumming coke
Marjorie in beer everything. I had no idea. I started working in Christian radio. I was preaching in assembly of God churches or as I like to
Preface them ass of God churches. I am flying high to room spinning. I'm still way loaded. I was hardcore about Jesus
But not in the way that you would think they start she grab as a plastic bag it starts throwing up in it
I got involved in board again Christianity because I desperately wanted to lick this girl
And I begin to laugh as hard as I've ever laughed before the blind leading the stupid
I'm in shack off del
I'm Harry short-rear. What you come with a Michael Antony shut up Chris pool us that I cannot help myself and
I already have become an ordained minister
You guys are nuts, man. The stuff you're putting in these promos these days out of control
What is there a lot of UK promos that I got what happened what happened over there was there
something that that made that everyone go and make podcasts and make promos? It's just it's amazing
My Gmail box was full of them
Speaking of promos, this is one of the things that that Ron and I you know as one of the the duets of
Of arguing in the air. We know we are the Kenny Rogers and Dolly part of conversation
Is about the podcast Expo the portable media Expo and because we have a couple of damn announcements we want to make
And you know we've we've got some information and we're looking at this and
We just don't think it's the right venue
To do that so we're
Gonna think about how and when we're going to make some of these announcements
Which we're very exciting we got some some pretty awesome stuff and leading up to that though
I'll tell you now that
Within the next two weeks maybe three weeks
We'll be ask I'll be asking you actually
Podcasters out there for I'm gonna call it an audition
And what we need you to do if you're interested and of course
I'll tell you more about what that is in in the next couple weeks
Be kind of gear up for it is we're going to be asking for promos
Because we're going to be
Listening to just as many podcasts as we can for for this thing that we're going to be doing and
Obviously the best way to hear about a show is not to listen to an entire show and see if you like it
Or that is a great way of course
If someone recommends it to you, but perhaps it's a little easier if you make a promo what you just heard and and of course
That's that's an art by itself, you know, and
If you're not quite sure what to do you know you can just
Record a minute or two minutes
I don't really care how long it is as long as it's entertaining and and and talks about your show and explains what you're about and
And we'll give you a special email address to send that off to so if you're gonna if you're interested
Then oh here comes the sun do do do do do I'm not gonna take a picture because I just won't put it up on the show notes anyway
So you could start working on your promo so information on that forthcoming for sure
What else was I gonna say about that
Man, I am so fuzzy I really am oh I can't wait until I have my my connectivity up here
This is just killing me you know so last night when I came back I was you know
I have to put the power book on a on one section of the couch and kind of lie down and only then
Do I get the connectivity because all of my free networks have gone away?
So and I think I did mention that that the idea I had about
If you have a Wi-Fi
Access point and you want to leave it open and have people connect and you could put up a web page and put up some instructions and control who comes in and for how long and for what reason
That actually it exists it exists in the open source firmware of links is
So if if you're interested in in doing something with that
I'll make sure that there's a link on the show notes if you're new to the daily source code by the way the whole concept of show notes is that
When you hear something on the show whether it's about whether it's a promo or a mashup or a song or just something I was talking about
You can go to daily source code.com and you'll find a link there
Which will take you to the show notes and so you really have have to remember one URL one internet address and anything else that you were interested in will show up there
And the show notes of course are done in great detail by Michael and and anyone else
That's kind of the cool thing anyone else who wants to add any piece of information to the show notes
So they got in pretty detailed
Including time codes when when I start talking about something or when a particular segment played on the show and the ending time codes
It's gotten very very detailed
One thing we're not doing though is is giving away the answers to the backtracks podcast or the hit test
Because of course if you look at the show notes first and you kind of blow the surprise
I have hit test number 66 lined up and ready to go is from Jan Paul out of course in the Netherlands and
Obviously haven't listened to it yet. He said I can see that it's it's longer than usual
He actually sent in his email. He said Adam this one's a little bit longer than usual so
That either means Jan has got something to say or he's done something freaky again. Let's check it out
I suppose you think you know I do
Hey Adam this hit test number 66 and again it's a hit test in which the three songs have something in common
And so I hope you can figure it out because is number one
For my shirt right said Fred by the way I'm wearing my white beater today. So it goes along with the test and this is number two
Do you remember and Michael Jackson do you remember and the final one is number three
What are that? Well the three have to do with each other and time stops down did you figure it out?
These are the answers
Hello Adam. It's Dave Fox your old accessories are from the Adam Curry top 30 hit list
I'll hold on a second hold on a second. That's great. Oh, Jan you've done it again
Dave Fox is he works for Z100 in New York actually he works for he's a clear channel motherfucker
But he's one of us really and oh man that's so amazing. Well I'll tell you more about day five
Let me listen what he has to say
These three songs were number three two and one on the weekend of March 6
1992 oh my god you predicted that right said Fred would be heard from again as he had fallen from number one to number three on his countdown
Recounted the story of Michael Jackson offending certain countries in
Can you hear listen to his voice man? Dave has got some pipes on him. He's the guy that does
Podcasting it's wait a minute. Do I have that here hold on I think I have I think I have
Let me see if I can let you hear that for a second here we go
This is this is who Dave Fox is I think yeah. Oh, okay. That didn't work
Oh, no don't scan for missing files. Oh, man. Why am I doing this?
Oh, stop. No, no, no, no, no, skip all go away cancel cancel. Oh shoot
I'm sorry I never should have done this. Let's just continue with Dave if it'll work even
Africa by touching his nose and predicted big days for the group missed her big and they're so into be with me
It's getting the crunch time on his list. I'm Adam Curry and the closer we get to number one the
Tess you can tell my testicles had not dropped yet in 1902 tougher it gets last week's number one
Smash drops down to number three this week falling out of the top spot. I'm 260 it's right said Fred
I am 264 my love 264 my love love's going to lead
264 my shirt
Laughing all the way to the bank right said Fred. I'm two sexy number one last week
Downs number three this week. I don't think we've heard the last of right said Fred
hanging in the Hitler's day to cue. This is Adam Curry looking for the new number one song of the week and playing another
Smash that came very close
This is the latest from a superstar who cut his trip to Africa short because the people there thought he was
dissonant and Michael Jackson was visiting several places in Africa shooting a video and just passing out some of that
Jackson goodwill but it turns out the people thought he was thumbing his nose at them literally
You know it seems Michael has a habit of touching his nose. Just something does when he's a little nervous seems harmless enough right
Now to the people of Africa they thought it was holding his nose telling them that their country smell
Oh, not so obviously says Michael's people Michael Jackson touches his nose and the people get upset
Imagine what they would have thought if he'd grab himself
Michael's up to where places this week to number two with remember the time
Time
Looking for a second straight number one Michael Jackson and remember the time all the way up to number two on the top 30 hit list
And for the past three hours we've been counting down to the biggest hit in all of the free world and we have finally arrived
At this song in the first ever chart hit for a band that once tried to make a name for themselves by using a pretty strange gimmick
You see they actually tried playing the guitars on stage with electric drills
Then gluing picks to the drills and then cut loose on the fenders produce some wild sounds the trouble was
It produced some flying guitar picks and often got their hair tangled in the spinning drills
Being a hair person that gives me nightmares so the guys decided to concentrate on making music instead and it worked
Climbing two points from three to number one at the top of the hit list is Mr. Big to be with you
Just to be the next to be with you
Yeah, I'm gonna get you for this man
What's your chop? They finally made it I knew they could do it to be with you for mr. Big the brand new number one
Smash in America on the top 30 hit list and can Mr. Big stay Mr. Big and hang on to the number one spot for a second straight week
There's only one way to find out, of course be right here next week same time same station
So how did you do really?
I have to say before I go that this was some of the most fun production I've ever been involved with and I want to thank you
For making it happen for me and to young for contacting me and making this happen on the hit test
Well, thank you Dave you made it happen for us today. Thank you for working with me on the hit test
Well, Adam I hope you enjoyed this one and oh yeah, I hope you had them all
Again, it's always feedback is welcome at hit test at gmail.com
You can find information about the hit test at yompolet.com j and b-o-l-e-t dot com
Well until the next one until then bye bye bye bye buddy
17 years ago it's unbelievable oh
My goodness that was a great show to do that was in 1992
FM radio was still blasted you know we had top 40 radio was just through all over the place and and here's how they're worked
I created a
syndicated program which means
Yeah, thousands of radio stations around the country when most of them were still independent or smaller entities
It owned a couple of stations because that was a law back then that's changed quite a bit hasn't it and
and
So the concept was and it worked very very well is and you deliver a show to all of these stations once a week a three-hour show
We were delivering on
CDs so every week we'd have you know thousands of CDs made up for all these stations a pack of three at a time
And then the stations can play it whenever they want for free and I didn't get paid and I didn't have to pay them these days by the way
I think for airtime like that for deals like this you have to pay the radio station. It's gotten so bad
And what they do is they could insert an X amount of minutes of local commercials in every single hour
And then I would go and sell national commercials to like Pepsi and Reebok and and companies like that because you know
It would be on on hundreds of different stations and so you'd have a fairly sizable audience all before the infrastructure in fact
We didn't have
Trying to think well of course we had the internet
But it was
Kind of like that was go for time, man. I was using go for and text and and die. I was at
You had to have a PPP or a slip connection. I remember those days and
So Dave was working at Z100 and he was the production director and he'd put together
Well he started putting the show together on tape. I mean, there was that was it it was
It was magnetic tape to track tape
Man, you can hear all the little bits and the things that you'd put in there. So he was splicing his ass off and it was just around that time that I had received
A I had a Mac to from from Apple
Excuse me Daniel Paul was the guy it was hand in those out Apple used to give machines away to people
I had a whole division which was
Which it's it's so intense was to give away machines to people in the media and there was this little company in
New Jersey
There was just starting up and
They had a product called pro tools and
And
Through I guess through what they'd seen me talk about stuff on MTV. They they found me and they said well, would you mind beta testing?
And that changed my life
You know overnight it changed Dave Fox's life overnight. I mean, he had never really even used a computer except for like a
DOS command line thing so we sat for hours and hours and optimizing you know
OS 8 to make sure that it wouldn't crash out on pro tools and
And then the way we would do it is I would tape all of my individual breaks
You know all the things I was going to say
Like Sunday night I think it was and then Dave who live not far from me in Jersey as well
He'd pick up the tape for my mailbox a dat tape remember those
He'd pick up the dat tape and he'd take it to the studio
He'd then you know have to spin that off in real time
onto onto his hard drive and then he'd start assembling the show
Great to hear from you Dave. Of course
We've been working with him for the past months once again
Because when we when we decided to put the pod finder together for iTunes
Yeah, the first guy that came to mind was Dave and you know Dave on the whole exactly what what to do and how we want to put it together
And so but we don't really talk all that much it's just like you know
We send stuff back and forth through email and FTP and it goes so incredibly fast these days and and Dave has become just a freaking wizard man on
I think he still uses pro tools which is
Obviously a great for the digital realm. So good to hear you man. Thank you very much. Y'all for embarrassing me. Love it
Hello Adam this is Mike Dell of the Benzoyed Report podcast
podcasting is made a really big impact on my life
It's pretty much got me away from listening to traditional radio sad light radio
I back sound that serious so I can't listen to podcasts and I'm sad light. No, that's not true
But the other thing that's made a really big difference in my life over the years is ham radio
And to that end my self and John Martin KF8KK are putting on a ham radio class
of podcasting
Pied class if you will and that will teach you everything you need to know to get your technician class
ham radio license from the FCC and such your in California part of the time
You've got a California mailing address the FCC would be more than happy to give you a license
And then when you get to England get your license here you can apply for reciprocal operating privileges in England
The Netherlands and probably Europe wide I didn't really sure how that works
But anyway check us out
website is www.camradioclass.org and the feed is feeds.feetburner.com slash ham radio
Next that it's w
feeds.feetburner.com slash ham class
There we go
Anyway, yeah, we're going to leave the bloopers in there
Play it as you leave the war it's on
Really hope to hear you on the air 73
Hello Adam hello podcasting fans my name is Joseph. I've decided to do my very own tech podcast
I know I know there's so many to choose from and podcasts is out there have inspired me to give it my own spin the MAC Pro podcast
I see you're not convinced well whether you're a MAC Pro a switcher guru newbie
We'll have something for you on the MAC Pro podcast
We'll get under the hood troubleshoot discuss share tips and tricks and talk about the MAC Pro apps and Max in general
You're still not convinced
Well, I'll have news and interviews with movers and shakers and other MAC pros talking about their
Experiences and the future of Macintosh
Okay, okay, if you don't listen, I'm gonna smack this puppy
All right, I'm just kidding. I'm not that kind of dude, but I promise you'll like the MAC Pro podcast
Subscribe and iTunes or visit MAC Pro dot blog spot dot com
No animals will harm the recording of this promo. Hi, I'm John
Iceland Eros is the biggest international music festival in Iceland featuring 160 artists at 60s under venues in four days
We'll be podcasting from the whole festival
We'll team up with various music journalists to interview bands locals and festival guests to give you an insight on festival
Episode from each of the four festival nights would be published the following days starting on october 20
You can find more info and subscribe to the podcast at Islandewers.com slash podcast
Thanks a lot
Is now we're Bjork is from Iceland cool got a concert going on there
I've I know couple pilots who've flown up to Island
Interesting very very interesting. I had no idea that there was a podcasting community in Island there you go damn
This thing is really global. Oh, there's something I want to ask if anyone's a doctor out there. Hold on a second. Let me just grab
I can't find it. Remember I had my insurance test
Well, I passed the test, but there was I got the results. It's actually is interesting
I first time I've actually received results back from from a medical now I'm looking for it
Ah, shoot don't tell me. I oh wait, it's here it is
I'd already show prep this um
So they gave me the results back and I had a question about it
So everything is normal normal normal normal normal normal then it comes to the cholesterol
I don't I just don't know anything about cholesterol so it says here so you can the the results can be low normal or elevated
So cholesterol 200 and three milligrams per dl whatever the dl is deciliter or something like that
I don't know so there I have an elevated level then you have your LDL cholesterol which has no result next to it
Then the HDL cholesterol is 34 mg's per dl and that is considered to be low
And then I have my cholesterol HDL cholesterol ratio 6.0
Okay, here's the
Okay, oh I got it here says the normal clinical range for cholesterol is 140 to 200. Oh, okay
So I have 203. Okay, so that's just a little bit elevated and then on the
HDL cholesterol normally it should be
Greater than 40 mg per dl and I had 34 so it's slight variations but it should I be concerned and is the HDL cholesterol the good cholesterol or the bad cholesterol
Doctors out there listening help please let me know if I'm gonna live
I want to try
Beyond play when you're asleep is my die
I need a little more tree
With your arms around me
And I feel better not your heart
If you get on my hip breathing a little too cold
But I'm all again thinking about you
I need a little more tree
With your arms around me
And I feel better not your heart
I feel better not your heart
I need a little more tree
With your arms around me
And I feel better not your heart
The muffs
Little luxury
Potsafe on the daily source code again that mega segment I really got to work on that it's fading stuff out way too soon
That's from the potsafe music network music dot pod show dot com and
And I'm just looking in the in the blackberry here because if you're listening to us on a serious satellite radio
Then there is
Shoot man maybe if I start to fire up the browser I'll be able to to let you listen in on this hold on a second
Shoot that's not gonna work anyway
We've got the match wine steamed dawn and Drew Steve Gilmore coming up C.C Chapman
And then I know that my good buddy Pete up has put in some kind of cool stuff in a half hour
There, so that's all it's all podcast coming up in the next
Let's see for the next three hours here if you're listening to us on the serious stars channel 103
New sponsor I'll talk about that in a second
Podcasting with the east side of Philadelphia. It's the groggy java show my name is Ken Irman and I am groggy java
Welcome to my show
You know Adam Curry my man you opened up number 260 Friday October 14th with my mash up
Bono versus Bono do you roll my stuff is so new my website. It's not even an exciting
Google yet, but you'll man your show's what got me so inspired to start making podcasts and mashups in the first place
And now you've let me know that I must be doing something right. Thank you listen
WWE WWW dot ruckyjava dot TV is the place if any of your listeners want to check in
The show was talked with pod safe music and as ostensibly about me being a work at home stay at home
Dad, but usually ends up being a sloppy mess of narcissistic drool doing a lot of yo
I'm making myself late for work to get this promo out the door so I got a jet but I'll be back in touch later
Thanks, dude. Escarggy java dot TV and tell you listeners. I said hey yo, thank you so much. I'm out
Okay, terrific
Hot show content that will make you squeeze the dog and burp your mother
Hi, this is fam from the Dutch band Dr. Flexito
We played a funk in our own language so we can say whatever we want without raising suspicion with our friends the Americans
With this promo we would like to share with you some of the beauty of our language
So if you want to feel all European and cool for a moment, I'll just teach you the number one pick-up line
Every tourist in Holland needs to know
So here we go repeat after me
The poscoose puts the poscoose met poscoose puts once again
The poscoose puts the poscoose met poscoose put
Well, that was it so hard was it now keep practicing that line and maybe if you did it right
We'll teach you how to order a beer on your next promo in the meantime visit
If you want to know more of the Dutch language or just listen to our great music see you and
Don't we don't we don't we don't we don't we don't we don't we don't we don't we don't we don't we don't we don't we don't
Don't know that's a great
So those guys signed up the pod save music now where you can grab their tunes
Offer there. I wanted to play you one of their songs because actually it's pretty very funky good stuff
But because of the connectivity I could actually get a song to download
They also put their promo up on the on the PMM music dot pod show dot com
Which is great because you get an instant feel with these guys are about so they have their own podcast
By the way
Suggestion I wouldn't use what they suggested as a pick-up line that might not get you very far
Happened to be able to understand Dutch it is now
Almost eight forty five still no word from the cable guy
So that's gonna be a pain in the ass for sure
But I can tell you that the weather is changed in in the past
Well during this show literally the sun is just you know is beating down from
This coming up in the in the east obviously and to the west it's still you can see over the mountains
It's it's foggy Jesus Christ. I need to do a video cast when I get the I probably here's what I promise while I'm here in San Francisco
I'm gonna do one of these and record it all on video so you can see
While stuff is playing you can see what I'm doing
Which of course has nothing to do with you with the podcast? I'm doing all kinds of other stuff
So you'll be able to watch I guess and then we talk about stuff
I'll just swing the camera on you be able to see it
I I could do it with my eyesight and the power book when I'm afraid that there's just too much data going through to the fire wire drive
So
Certainly by Monday if not earlier depending on when I can get the get all the stuff together
So when we were in New York
And we were meeting with the sponsors and marketers and advertisers and companies who were interested in getting into podcasting we
We met with the company well actually one of the the sponsors has bro and
I'm talking a couple weeks back now and has bro has this new product called an eye dog
I don't know if you've heard of this or if you've seen it
Unfortunately we only have one at the office and Chris McIntyre the Prince of podcast
Immediately appropriated it has a very unhealthy relationship with this toy and it's not really a toy because what it is
You plug it into either your you can plug it into your computer
You can plug it into your iPod or you can just keep it on your desk. It has a built-in microphone and
Essentially what this thing and helps us speakers in it. So essentially what it does is it
It's it's on your desk and it's it's a kind of a cross between a neopet
a
One of those Sony eyeballs, you know the robot dogs and
And yeah and speakers and and it's it's really cute. I have to say and I remember going back home to
To Guilford to the cottage and telling Christina about this
No actually I didn't tell her about it. She said hey dad
You know it's really cool. I said what you said that I dog and when I first heard about it
I was like is that really is that cool? Is that gonna be an interesting thing
But she thought it was cool and she'd never seen it she'd only heard about it or seen the picture and when Christina said something's cool
I usually pay attention because I am certainly not the not the thermometer of coolness
And it's really really it's really entertaining
You can pet it on its head and it responds and if you don't say anything then it'll start to bark and when they
It moves around the music. It's got lights in its head. Do you want to know more about it? Check it out at
In the show notes for today a daily source code dot com the Hasbro i dog
You know and it's it's like 150 bucks. I've seen it for like 30 or 40 dollars. So it's definitely something cool
Ah, okay, that will be the cable guy
All right. I'm gonna take this call. I'll see you guys later. Hold on. Hello
Yes
Who
Hey, Comcast how are you?