Hi everybody welcome to the daily source code. I'm going to do a little different type of show today
Actually, when you're here in the background is a
What do you call out a mix down of one of the pod shows for serious running in the background?
Have all the computers running at the moment and got a kind of a tight schedule today. So I didn't want to
You
I'm recording on two machines and I've got another machine that's queuing stuff up and
I figured well instead of waiting for it all to be done. I just grabbed the iRiver grab the the love microphone and
Actually, it's a beautiful day in in Gilford
This it started off kind of windy and cold this morning. I think the wind is still still there
But it's so beautiful and this whole week I've been indoors working my ass off
Yeah
Sitting in here smoking up a storm. Yeah, sure the windows are open and and and that you know
I got a lot of fresh air coming in but I've been in this
Well, I call it the studio, but it's really a converted bedroom work. No, it's not even converted
It's a bedroom without a bed. It's a bedroom with a desk and you know got my stuff over here. You know what what's really cool this
You know, I'll just turn this up for a second
I was doing
Probably can understand it very well, but that's the four one one podcast and
Doing an interview with Senator John Edwards about his podcast. I did I'd mentioned that on a previous source code
And accidentally actually said John Kerry
Well, that would have been too smart if he was doing a podcast I guess now John Edwards and his wife Elizabeth do a podcast
I think I've only done too so far
But it's really good and I'll put links in the show notes of that and the interview which is done by a Skype
It's awesome and he really knows what the hell is going on and he listens to podcasts and
It's really it's it's good stuff, you know, who would have thought that
In less than a year we would have senators not only knowing what podcasts are but understanding the
The community and and also able to to do one themselves is very very exciting stuff
So uh, let me see so we'll go outside we'll go out for a walk on the downs
Let me just do
Set everything up here. I want to make sure my wires don't hit my my microphone continuously
I'm gonna grab the
Hello, let me just take a look at the
At the crap let because I had a couple of things I wanted to mention before I have a piece of paper with some notes which I'll take outside
I just wanted to mention a couple of things here
This is by the way a sound seeing tour and you know
I get a lot of email people talk about two different things and and I guess it's because I'm not pronouncing it correctly
Or I guess it just kind of sounds it can sound like I'm saying sound
Seeing as an SE and E whereas I've always said sound seeing
So sound seeing tour is where you know you narrate the environment and walk around shit the sun just went away
Okay, I'll have to pronounce jacket. Okay, two bits of interesting news that came in today on email
See who's this from this is a message
From
Saro a secari arrow from Finland
Adam just want to tell you that I received reply from
Uncy von Yokee of Nokia's multimedia division
He said that inside Nokia they are eye-podding like crazy, which is good news because
To me that means that
Nokia or Nokia which of way one pronounce it is
Is thinking about this and that's great. You know and I've had conversations with them too
So I'm really happy to see that that's moving along and this was kind of a frightening
Kind of a frightening email that I got we're not really frightening but finally a statement from the RIA about the
Legalities and licensing of podcasts
This came to me from
Sarah Sterlin who is a
reporter for the national journal and
She got an official position a statement from the RIA about podcasts. I'm gonna quote here
I'll let me just turn off this
You just turn that off for a second
Here we go
So it doesn't say who said this at the RIA but the quote is
We are always supportive of new and exciting ways for fans to discover and experience music
Podcasters like the uses of any other sound recordings must obtain the appropriate licenses from the copyright owners or their
Designese
Appropriate licensing is an important part of the legal system set up to protect musicians songwriters songwriters and copyright owners
Podcasts are downloads and as such do not qualify for the statutory licenses that are available to
webcasters, simulcasters, satellite radio and other digital transmission services
Wow, okay, that's it. Be careful what you're doing on your podcast because
They definitely have a position and they're right. I know of course they can't really have any other position
on that
So I'm walking
Down the stairs studios
up on the second floor
Let me sit in here. I'm going to grab a coat
I don't think I've actually taken you out in the backyard have I?
Okay, hold on I have to go back up I forgot my
sunglasses
Which is uh
Wishful thinking
Okay
So for those of you oh wait a minute now the mic is kind of covered up on my jacket when they pin this up a little bit higher
There we go
Right there, okay
This is not the oh so the for those of you there are always emailing me and asking me about my setup
This is not the
stereo griffin microphone because it's windy outside and I don't still have a windscreen for that thing
So this is the the wireless set
Which I have the the transmitter on my belt and I have the receiver part in my pocket
I think can do probably like half a mile but I'm sure the four inches
difference between the two will be just fine
okay
No, let's try this again
You can hear the cat's bell
Is that you ginger?
Hey ginger, hey baby
You want to come outside for a walk this cat is amazing he's an orange orange colored cat and
He's just like a dog
He's a stray who walked up to the
The castle when we still live there in Belgium
Never one away here go baby
He's always hungry
Is it good?
So he's so funny because when you go out for a walk you'll come along and they'll walk along with you like a dog
Welcome for a walk
I was kind of stupid. I guess the fed him of course is not gonna come for a walk. Okay out the back door
Oh
It is still kind of windy
So the way the cottage is situated
We have a really decent sized backyard
Surrounded by trees if you walk all the way to the back
Gosh, it's nice today. It's really nice and sunny if you walk all the way to the back
There's a gate
And if you walk through the gate which I'm coming. Oh, by the way, there's a we have a bomb shelter
In the backyard want to go on the bomb shelter with me. I'm gonna put my notes away
This was built in the second world war
Let's see if I can open it up
It's a two-person bomb shelter
Which is kind of weird because we have a five bedroom house
I guess some people just want to support me now
It's covered up
Shit for the second world war it's hard to get into hold on. Okay. I'm gonna
Go down now
I have to kind of duck to get in
I should have brought a light
Let me see what's my lighter
Oh shit
Okay, she's in the animals there
Bring me out
Okay, so here we are
Light still in the good home
There we go. So here it is. This is a chair and
As you can tell from the acoustics
We're underground in a tunnel kind of the construction. It's um we call this this is uh
Like some kind of
It's all concrete. It's built into the ground. It's entirely made of concrete and it has that
Round roof structure so it can stand the forces of whatever's above it
And
Yeah, it's basically just
People in the second world war when there was an air raid and
There was lots of air raids over the UK
Then you know the silence would go and you'd scurry down in here and you'd sit here
And uh sometimes the neighbors would come in and have to sit with you and uh sometimes the people would be here for hours or maybe even an entire night
It's kind of funky to think about that
But again very very small I guess this was uh only for uh for the privilege for you who had enough money
of resources to have this type of
This type of shelter right near their backyard right right near their home
So
All right
Pretty boring otherwise so let's go on out again
Climb it up all right. Hey Jess
That's Jesse a big dog. Hey Jess
Wanna come for a walk
Let's cover it up again the reason why it's covered up is otherwise
All kinds of varmin might get in there
And
We have plenty of foxes
Well the perfect den for a fox but not really what you want
So here I am back at the
the gate
And now
From here close the gate
We're walking through a
A little bit of woods here into
The open field
Known as the downs and the downs
I really don't know all the precise history
But basically from where I am and gulford
The gut the down stretches all the way down to the coastline
It's just hundreds of miles of
Open field with trees
Sometimes is line the the borders of it and
What it's used for mostly is for people walking
Walking with their dog and also horse riding
Because you can
But Christina's pony is
Located I don't know five minutes drive down the road
So what's that like what 10 kilometers 8 kilometers
Yeah about five miles I guess four five miles
And I can actually drop her off there and then she'll show up
Right at the backyard when her horse for a cup of tea
So it's quite a bit of wind but it's
It's beautiful it's
It's actually the sun really is warmed it up a lot it's not cold
It's just it's quite a bit of wind that's I estimate
20 20 knots
Yeah
It's probably what it is actually
Not bad for flying but it's gusty so I'm not quite sure
Where it's coming from it's coming from the
Is that from the south
East I think is where the wind is coming from today
And you can hear uh
Aircraft overhead flying really high
Those are the jets
Going to Heathrow I can see one two
Three of them stacked up on their way in
Okay, let me just grab my notes a couple things I wanted to talk about with you
Okay, what do we have here number one oh
Yeah, I talked the other day about the podcast specification working group
PSWG dot blog spot dot com so I emailed so of course after
My comments from yesterday I think it was
I got an email and
So you know what I said was I don't like the fact that although I think it's a good idea that we're trying to improve
I should wrote my camera man. This is stupid
They're trying to improve the technology of of podcasting
Primarily on the on the iPodter side on the receiver side of the equation
And when I went to that site
I saw only three links to three iPodter clients and I say well, you know what's this either you
Link to everybody's iPod or link to no one
So that was apparently just you know they set up the blog spot and
Weblog and there was three links and they just filled in the links of the
The founding members of the group and so they invited me to come in and I said well, you know
So how's this gonna work is this going to be a
An open discussion or closed discussion and
The way they want to do it apparently
Is they want to
Discuss things behind closed doors
And then whatever they come up where they want to bring that out into the open
Hello
He wasn't too friendly
I walked past a gate there's some gardens here
I guess garden you can rent a patch of land
here on the side of the downs and you can have your own little garden
And
Some guy going through the gate there a smile to Adam say hello, but
You thought the hell is wrong with you must be one of those damn podcasters
So the podcast the specification working group yeah
So I don't know I mean I don't have a lot of experience with
Working on
Standards and protocols and stuff like that and the only the only time I really have had an experience with it was
When we started the iPodter developer mailing list
Which is where all the development was done initially on on the first iPodters
And that was all out in the open
I enjoyed that very much although
Well, we need to speak now
I don't know walk down a little bit and then I'll turn around on my back to the wind
After we've gone like up to the golf course here because of course as golf courses everywhere in the
Um
So I don't know if that's a good idea to have that closed off you know their point was
That they
They don't want the quote groupies showing up and making a lot of noise. You know like groupies
Yeah, I think everyone has a say in this and everyone's interested and
I just don't have a good feeling about it and doesn't seem to me the way that to you know open source projects work
So I'm still I'm gonna wait a little bit and think about it. I just wanted to feel you know on that
I got a
Shoot man, let me
Went around now horrible. I got an email from Garth Kidd who is
One of the developers on the iPodter lemon and
If you upgraded your iTunes
This past week. I think it's version 4.8
Guess what your iPodter doesn't work anymore
This is totally fucking sucks
I'm not quite sure what Apple did or what they changed that I presume it's something in the in the way that you talk to it in the way that
You know you you update the playlist and and given update command
Which doesn't make a lot of sense to me because
There must be
Thousands
tens of thousands of programs
that use
either Apple script or
What is that is it it's a calm object I think in on the Windows platform
to update
and basically talk to iTunes
So it can do stuff both in iTunes and obviously to your iPod
And
Doesn't make sense that Apple would release a fix that would basically break that
But it happened oh man
I'm sorry I'm just trying to find a
Direction to walk you know what he's events and you go over sit here for a second
So it doesn't make sense to me that
Apple would purposely break
All those scripts
I'm sure they didn't do it on purpose, but
Man, they don't know their developer community
Certainly not the iPod in community
So
There's a new a new version of iPod element available
at ipod.sourceforge.net download that and everything will be fixed
and I'm sure that
Information will be available very soon about what exactly was broken and what exactly happened
Now their interesting development this past week is the release of the
Yahoo music engine
Which is basically well it's two things in one
It's a music player which is free for download that Yahoo released
And at the same time they have their music service where you can subscribe for I think it's four dollars and 95 cents a month
And you can
Download anything you want from their music store
I don't even think they call it a store from their from their service
And it will play in the Yahoo music engine and if you have friends who also subscribe then you can you know basically make playlists and
And swap those out amongst each other and they don't have to pay anything additional they'll have to still have pay the 495 a month
This is the another way of looking at at legal music on the internet because this of course is completely
Managed by DRM digital rights management and what happens is you don't actually ever own those songs
You can use them on your computer. I presume that you can use them on multiple computers
if you if you if you use the same
User name or whatever your idea is and you keep paying your subscription
But once you stop paying your subscription then it all goes away
And I don't know that's a good thing or bad thing
495 certainly seems like a very good deal and they claim to have a million songs
So
You know that may be pretty good and of course you can also put them on to your on to your mobile device
But again, you're you're locked in right you have to pay the 495 for for as long as
You want to be using that music
So there's
Pros and cons to that
What's interesting about the Yahoo music engine is they have a plug-in architecture and
I'll have to find the link and I'll put that in the show notes for today's source code
There's a podcast plug-in. I think it's called podcast plus
far cry from from an iPod or basically you fill in a
You could create a list of RSS links podcast feeds and then you hit download and it goes out
You know searches it's kind of you know a little aggregator
Goes out searches the feeds looks of anything's new and if there's a new file available it downloads it and puts it right into
Your into your player. I don't think it even creates a playlist
Specifically based upon the feed title
It's certainly not that I could find it doesn't have any automatic checking features
And of course none of the management features that we work so hard on on the iPod or developers list
Which is stuff like you know download only the the latest podcast catch-up features clean-up features
There's a lot of stuff there, but it's a good start
Oh
This wind is crazy. It's a really good start. No start walking again. It's a really good start
But it it made me realize that we could be doing so much more
like this
Particularly in in Windows
Media player as well as an iTunes as far as I know both of those have some form of
A plug-in architecture and I think that would be really
Really quite nice if we could take some of these beautiful iPod or engines and just plug them into the player
Of your choice and how about the the windamp guys? I know they have a plug-in architecture
I haven't seen an iPod or client for that
Seems like such a logical choice because instead of having a playlist in my
In my iPod or and in my player I'd much rather just you know use the player of my choice and have it be
iPod or enable hey we could even create a little logo iPod or inside
So that's the Yahoo music engine
I wrote down here cast blaster beta
I quite sure what I was gonna say about that
Other than that we're up to
Beta 11 right now
And Microsoft has offered to help that's very nice
They've offered to help us out
With the sound issues. I don't know if they really can actually
But I think it's more a hardware problem than a software issue
And the problem is is that
Unlike with the with a Mac
Where they have their core audio and it's a standardized
You know they know what the hardware is that their software's gonna be talking to
On windows
You know you're talking to
a third party
device that is your sound card and
Wow, I didn't know this but there's a shitloader different sound cards out there and every single one specifies
You know there are their capabilities a little bit differently
So for instance if you want to
Tell the sound card
Well actually if you ask the sound card through software you say okay, well, what is the
The master
Volume control
The sound some sound cards will say okay, it's called master volume and
Some will say it's the red one
So it's pretty funky, but that's really nice so we're gonna see if we can
If we can work with Microsoft and there's certainly willing to help us and I appreciate that
If you've been sending the email over this past week, you know with the start of the pod show on serious
Forget about it. I just went through 200 emails. I have 3600
Unread emails and you know, I rarely ever
Recheck something is unread to go back later. I try and deal with it immediately. That's the only way I know how to manage the email
So I apologize if I haven't gotten back to you
Oh, remember I think it was last week
Maybe the week before the rocket 15 pod casts
I played a promo. I think a rocket 15 man's getting one when we open my jacket
They were gonna be pod casting and I see my mic has slipped a little bit
There we go. They're gonna be pod casting from the infield of the Kentucky Derby and there was some comment there
Like we're all getting naked on the infield and I said, oh, yeah, right
You know, like people get naked if they can tucky Derby. Well, I got an email from the fine folks over at
Rocket15.com. Oh, yeah
They do get naked very nice pictures
I don't know if any of that will be reflected in the pod cast, but it was really nice
Just I didn't know him when I think Kentucky Derby, you know for some reason I think
I know I just wasn't it looks like woodstock. Let's put it that way. You know
Girls on guys shoulders
Pulling up their shirts
Very funny
So we're at the top of the hill now
Let me see
Everything yeah, I've talked about everything. I want to talk about so just finish this up and
Just listen to a bit of nature for a second how about that let me here the birds
See if I can find a spot where some birds are really talking to each other
I wish Patricia were along for this this walk
She has an uncanny knack of being able to talk to birds and they talk back or are talking is a big a big statement whistles
She can whistle and they'll whistle exactly the same tune and then she changes it and then they change it
And there's a variation and she totally gets into sync and harmony with them. It's very cool. Oh
That's a nice bit of nature that hell is that
Leathblower too early for leaf blower
I think someone's doing some construction on their house. Okay. We're gonna walk through
The very narrow path here
Man haven't been up this
This high in a long time. It's really
The fields have grown
It's up to my waist
Count okay
To reduce some of the swing boy. I'm glad I didn't bring the the stereo griff and lapel mic that would have been totally
Electrical this is beautiful. I'm standing up here
Dude, I really I'm stupid. I didn't bring my yeah bring my camera
Standing at the top of the downs
So it's probably about a mile from the house and I can see
Obviously I can't see all the way to London but I can see what would that be all the way in the distance
I'm wondering
That's not Heathrow is it now is too close. I can see the gulfard castle which is a
Another spot on the sound seeing tour radar
Talks about that yesterday about the millennium two thought or the millennium two thousand time capsule
Which is apparently stored at the
Castle of Gulfard
Trying to hold my hand in front of the mic to reduce them with that noise out here's with it
Here's where the construction's going on there
Rebuilding a house here but on the edge of the downs. I must be beautiful to
To have it well. I don't know if you look out over the downs from your living room
That's kind of nice, but of course everybody can look back in and it's public so
Anybody can walk around here
I could easily land the sessina here too the wind is just perfect for it
Little downhill slope, but I could do it
And I know one thing for sure that would be completely illegal
I have a sneaky suspicion that my my buddies
The Dutch the pilots
We're over the other day who fly the shenooks and are training the bridge here how to fly
They'll probably do a low hover one of these days now that they've seen you know now
They know exactly what the coordinates are and where we are on the map and it would be perfect for them to
To come into a hover so I will definitely have the
The eye river and stuff standing by for when that happens one of these days
Okay
So
Looking forward to a great weekend
See how much what are going on the clock here? 29 minutes great. I'll take you all the way back in home
Back inside the home and then we'll go up to the studio and then we'll switch off so we'll have about
35 minutes exactly
Wow
I was supposed to go flying this weekend
I was supposed to pick Patricia up
In Rotterdam fly back and then do some major training but
If the wind keeps up like this I don't know about the training because it just doesn't make sense to
Do a lot of touching goes and
And another types of training with this much wind because you're not really learning anything
You're basically fighting the elements
And you can only do so many configurations and so I hope it dies down a bit
They're predicting more winds that doesn't look too good, but
Definitely gonna pick her up. That shouldn't be a problem. We can handle a lot more wind than this
Okay
Cutting through a little path to the right here
Oh man, so beautiful
So nice to get out for a couple of minutes. I appreciate you coming along with me
And I hope that you're gonna have a good weekend
Monday
We have
The first official week of the pod show on serious
Thanks for all the comments on the on the test hour
As we've been formatting P.W. Phantom and I have been formatting the show and and looking at
You know different ways to put it together and you know automating a lot of the process because we have so much incoming
Submit at podshow.com
Podsafe at podshow.com and mashup at podshow.com
We're figuring out new and novel ways to basically store up the bins and have the computer do some of the work
We're not really selecting anything on you know what's good or not we haven't this nothing's ever been rejected
You know just put whatever comes in we put it in and I have the feeling that if this really takes off the way I'm planning it to work
We
We might have a whole channel before too too long and that could
Really translate well if you can keep you get the automation part working. I could translate pretty well into a
A full channel very much like open podcast.org
You know because like I'd love
To have many more full length podcast
Being played right now. I can do about one an hour
And I you know that's anywhere from 20 to 30 minutes
And hi guys
I guess
Swabber are too doggy they're outside back doors open
Barbara who comes in the thing up to
If the house every Friday
Left the door open for me. Okay, so we're back in the kitchen
There's ginger what we missed you ginger you didn't come along for the ride
Hmm, we missed you
Hey
Right, uh, let's go upstairs
It's a much shorter walk and it used to be in the castle
Much shorter
Okay, it's only three flights of stairs to get up to the top
And here we are
Close the door. I didn't tell Barbara what I was doing. She gave me a really strange look
What the hell is he doing? I knew he was crazy. I didn't know he was that crazy
Okay, and we are
Back in the studio. Okay, so
Whatever you're gonna do this weekend have a good one take care of yourself stay subscribed please if you don't know how to subscribe if you're just listening to this
Straight from a download from the web
You know this is awesome little programs called iPodders
There's a whole bunch of them at ipodder.org you can go look for
Download software. It's a link on the right-hand side of the page
And you can choose for any type of operating system multiple flavors all kinds of
Great applications that have individual benefits
And
Basically what they all do very well is you subscribe to the show and it will automatically download the new show whenever there's one there
So you never have to go back to the website and see if there's a new show
That's what they're all about
Okay, that's it for the daily source code have great weekend and I'll be back on Monday. Bye bye