Transmators, we don't need no stinking transmittance.
Augustine, it's Adam Curry.
Hey, it is the 14th of March.
The power of the Lord.
Everybody, how you doing? Welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Coming to you from Curry Cottage.
And pretty much a typical gray English day.
A little bit of sunshine over this morning.
Not enough to classify it as anything really nice.
It's a start of a new week.
And it feels like that week really started yesterday.
Lots of exciting stuff to talk about.
If you may be heard about the new stuff that has been coming out.
I'm gonna start to talk a bit about what we're doing and see if we can get some of the usual stuff in there.
Special hit test today.
Still haven't found Michael Butler online at a time when I could record that we could do that.
Heavy metal guitar solo hit test.
But I'll keep my eye on Skype.
Before you go to the show, just a little bit earlier.
It's seven minutes past twelve.
Normally I don't start until like two or three in the afternoon.
But Patricia has wisely set me up for dentist appointment at 215.
wisely because she knows that if she doesn't set it up, of course I'll never go.
Alrighty.
Let's see.
I'm kind of a slow start today.
Actually.
I'm just going to the tune there.
I'd rather slow start.
Kristina although she got up early this morning.
I just couldn't, I couldn't light a fire under her ass.
Quick enough to get out the door.
So I got stuck in a lot of traffic on the way to school.
She was late and then everything just kind of got delayed a little bit.
To start things off today, an email from David Harvey.
He's from Auckland, New Zealand says.
Listen to the daily source code regularly.
And he wanted me to say hi.
I love this.
It's a long distance dedication everybody.
Say hi to my friend Jared Rimer who's in California.
I got a lot of actually kind of interesting where you would ask me to say hi to your friend Jared.
You know, where on the internet you could send that directly to him.
The radio used to be really handy for stuff like that.
But that's changed somewhat anyway.
David sent me a really cool mashup that I wanted to play for you.
It's a green day and well, you'll hear that with the other song.
It's a title Boulevard of Broken Songs.
I want to be the day that they've got to throw it back to you.
I want this empty street on the Boulevard of Broken Dreams.
Where the city sleeps and I'm late all the time and I walk alone.
I lie.
You should have somehow realized what it got to do.
I walk alone.
Leave it everybody.
The other words.
I want to be the day that they've got to throw it back to you.
I want this empty street on the Boulevard of Broken Dreams.
I'm sure you've read it all before, but you'll never really hide it out.
I'm sure you've read it all before, but you'll never really hide it's out.
We're the other, and we're the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world
the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world the world's the world's the world' the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world of the world's the world's the world's the world's we're the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's food's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world's the world
I walked this empty street on the boulevard of broken dreams two days
It's gonna be the day that they got a Broadway back to you
I walked this empty street on the boulevard of broken dreams
I know you should have somehow realized what you got to do
When the city sleeps and on the only one
I can't make the message
They won't be watching each other and she'll be watching each other
It's gonna be the day that they got a Broadway back to you
I walked this empty street on the boulevard of broken dreams
I know you should have somehow realized what you got to do
Yeah.
Wow.
Boulevard of Broken Songs.
Excellent.
Massive.
Thanks to David Harvey for sending that in.
I've got some kind of...
I don't know, some kind of...
Fucking hell.
My microphone again.
I don't know what that is.
If I seem to turn up the second mic, then the home goes away, and then you hear the birds more.
So...
I'll just leave it at that.
That's perfect.
You know, I get a lot of email about these mashups, and I've got to be honest.
Your people always ask me, oh, can you send me this mashup?
Can you send me that one?
I can't.
I mean, first of all, from a technical standpoint, this is going to become a problem pretty soon.
You know, these mashups, it's just not going to be possible to listen to them together.
And already what I'm doing is, if I get a minute, I trash him right after I'm done.
I mean, it's...
It's just like a piece of free flowing form art, you know, that I don't...
I don't think that you'll go back and listen to a mashup ten years from now and say,
Oh, you know, I remember exactly what I heard that mashup, you know, because it's probably a...
It's a combination of the songs that makes it work.
And I think it's just like a temporary art form, which just flows and, you know, it just...
It kind of is.
That make any sense?
Dig it though, especially that one.
I have...
I'm really building up a treasure trove of stuff that I have yet to play for you.
And as I was...
I actually had some...
A lot of time over the weekend to do stuff.
We got out of Triple P podcast, Patricia Pie Podcast, which was a lot of fun.
And I hope everyone likes it as much as the first one.
And as much as we enjoy doing it, and it really is quite enjoyable.
And in fact, there's something about kind of being in an interview situation with your spouse that...
It's...
Oh, it's cool.
Now I can understand Dawn and Drew even a little bit better, perhaps.
And I have to say, whenever we do a Triple P podcast and so far, you know, batting a hundred there,
we always have great sex right after the show.
Hi, I'm Michael Gohegan, the host of Real Reviews, films worth watching.
Now that Real Reviews is available to you on the DVD, Talk Radio Network.
I wanted to put together short introduction, tell you a little bit about Real Reviews and what you can expect from the show.
Real Reviews was the first movie review, commentary and discussion show available on the internet via podcast.
And we've been really fortunate to have become one of the top rated podcasts that are available.
We now want to work to bring that same commitment to quality content to you, the listener at DVD, Talk Radio.
In each podcast, I'll discuss one film that's available on DVD.
Now as the tagline suggests, these are films worth watching.
However, there's no boring academic talk here.
We'll talk a little bit about how the film was made, maybe some of the historical context behind how it was put together,
the people involved, and a basic outline of the story.
However, I worked very hard to make sure that I don't give away any spoilers.
In some cases, these are films that you've seen before, hopefully I'll encourage you to see them again.
In other cases, they're films that maybe you've never seen, and you'll get the opportunity to watch great film for the first time.
So if you love movies, you should be listening to real reviews, films worth watching.
Now available to you on the DVD, Talk Radio Network.
That's Michael Gohagan, who's been podcasting since the word was invented with real reviews.
And what I really like about Michael Gohagan is he's an entrepreneur.
He's like, he's always chasing, I guess for lack of a better term, we'd call the American dream.
But he really is, I think he runs a, I can insurance services company or something.
He's successful.
And he's just really picked this up, and I could, I could, I met him out in San Francisco.
And I could really tell that here's a guy who's going to really jump into this and really go head first.
If he sees that there's an opportunity for doing business.
And clearly, there is.
He's doing syndicated deals now with the DVD talk with Radio, and it's cool.
I'm very, very happy to see that.
Now, over the weekend, we launched, and we is a Boku communications, B-O-K-U with little funny slashes on top of the O and the U.
We launched podshow.com, and so immediately some questions sprung up.
First of all, what the hell is this? What's going on? Why does it look like you're selling soap?
Actually, there's something that Ron Blum and I have been thinking about for many months and working on quite hard.
During that, during that time period is really, how can we bring together the three real elements that are necessary to create a marketplace?
And, and what's been happening on the internet, what's been happening with podcasting is kind of automatically push me in that direction without me.
I really even even realizing 100% of myself, I think.
Let's see, where should we start? Let's start with making it easier to find podcasts and receive podcasts.
Now, there's a lot going on in search. There's a lot of people looking to set up specific podcast searches.
There's many directories, podcast alley, of course, is a great place to go find top rated content, which is based on voting.
We need to work on the voting a little bit. I'd much rather have an opportunity to vote more than once a month, but even so,
this is where the community goes and tells each other about the cool, excuse me, about the cool podcast.
There's also ipodder.org, and ipodder.org is one of the things that I really want to work on, not necessarily ipodder.org by itself, but the directory.
The directory at ipodder.org now contains, as of this morning, 4,08 podcast that it's tracking actively.
As you can tell, it's really, it's not much of a site. It's a category listing. You can go into the category and it gives you the XML fee.
It doesn't give a link to the site. It just gives you an XML fee for each of the podcasts.
Now, the whole reason, well, let me start backwards. The reason why that site was just kind of a bunch of RSS or podcast feed links is because it was really built from the bottom up, the bottom being the opml structure.
If you don't know what opml is, please take a look at opml.org. You can see there are all kinds of links to information about it from ipodder.org.
What's cool about opml is you can create distributed directories.
I maintain this top level node, or what I call my top level, at ipodder.org, and that's where you see this whole list ranging from agriculture down to wine or women, I think, is the last one on the list.
Literally the way I maintain that, and of course I've built some tools over time, but it's just an outliner.
You probably see an outliner, maybe you know how to outline from school, and maybe you've used Microsoft Word as an outliner.
I use Frontier, which is like a full version of radio user land, and what's cool about it is, when someone else maintains a node, so for instance, the, let's see, science fiction, node is being maintained by someone else.
All they do is they create their own opml file, their own outline of the links that belong in that category, and they send me a URL to that opml file, which I literally just copy and paste in, and then all of a sudden when you go to the web version, you click on what the link that I've now created, and literally is a link, it's just it's rendering on my server into a new page when you go to science fiction.
It'll, you know, bring up the nice, you know, the little world icons, and all the links as put in by the person maintaining that directory.
So what's great about this is you can really build this directory extremely quickly, and the content that's in there is of high quality because it's not an automated decision making process.
You know, you have to actually, when you want to suggest a link, you do that through the suggest a link feature, and then an email is sent to the category or node editor, and they decide if they're going to put that in.
And of course, they're also out actively looking for new, new podcasts to be put into their particular node, and a podcast can be in multiple nodes, obviously.
So what's great about that system is that the category editors essentially own their own data.
It's theirs, you know, if they decide to change something, they can change it, I can't stop it.
If they decide to go away, then they can just stop updating, you know, it's literally that simple or remove the file.
So it's, although I've been providing the central resource, everyone has has their own data built up which belongs to them.
None of it is stored except maybe for a cash stored on iPod.org.
So to make it easier through podshow.com, we are creating basically the definitive directory.
This is where we want to have all the stuff in there.
You want to have the great search, you want to have the great categorization, you want to have the voting systems, and we've been talking to multiple people about that.
The category editors, and I couldn't have been dropped more hints, you know, throughout the past couple of weeks.
Like, hey, you know, jump on if you want to be a category or node editor.
The way it is, I pired out of org, you know, it's nothing's really going to change there.
We just gave it a little bit of facelift and quite honestly, no one's really happy with the facelift, but it's better than what it was.
And we've been streamlining some stuff and doing some static rendering on the directory because it gets hit really, really hard.
That's still going to remain the central resource, and we make the output of the entire directory available for anyone to do anything with that they want.
You know, it's there for you to build applications upon, et cetera.
And that's linked from the XML icon on any of the directory pages.
So what's cool about this new world of business is that you can only compete on quality and speed the market, I guess.
So every single one of the node editors are going to receive an invitation to participate in a way to actually make money at what they're doing.
Because there's many marketing and advertising opportunities when you have such a wonderful resource to use.
And I guess anyone could essentially copy this idea, idea, and do the same thing.
I mean, it's no, no big secret here, which is what I like about this, you know, again, it's really down to quality and speed to market.
There will be new tools to maintain category nodes with.
There will be ways for you to participate in revenue opportunities or bring some of your own in.
I mean, it's really going to be a complete open forum for everybody to join in.
And that's one of the things that makes me really excited about about this new venture and about the first thing we're doing, which is podshow.com.
Boss, excuse me.
I don't know about this new stance.
If this is going to work, I'm sitting down behind the desk.
And it gives me, gives me gas.
What can I say?
Hey Adam, it's Rob from podcast NYC and I just wanted to say you tortured me all those years when you were on Z100.
But now I'm starting to feel a little nostalgic.
And I'm glad that you're back with your daily source code.
I want to thank you for that.
I also want to talk about my podcast at podcast NYC.net.
It's actually more than a podcast.
It's actually five channels of podcast feeds.
I've got my pop culture rant where I rip and ran on culture in the United States of America.
I've got Ali Cuts, a new music program where I feature a new band every week.
I've got podsafe music where you can download MP3s.
I've got my audio book.
Welcome to the BI.
It's a business advice book and I'm posting one chapter a week.
And then last but not least, I've got New York Minute.
The groundbreaking New York City travel program.
So please come to www.podcast NYC.net and add them.
I promise everyone's still going to listen to the daily source code.
They'll just spend a little bit more time at podcast NYC.
Take it light and I'll see you on the site.
Oh yeah, everybody take it light.
I'll see you on the site.
Yeah, right on.
Oh boy.
I see where was I?
Podcasts.
So obviously there is another wise.
We wouldn't have started this.
There is a demand for from podcasters to be able to make money.
And actually, I'm jumping ahead kind of to advertisers.
But let's say that even the top podcast, including this one right now,
really don't have enough critical mass to really sustain any type of advertising model.
Certainly not on what we call a CPM, like a cost per thousand.
And the M stands for meal in this case.
So we need a couple of bootstraps to be put into place.
And I guess I will jump over to the advertiser Marker's part.
That's the world that Ron and I come from.
And we really did a lot of work talking to many people on Madison Avenue.
Big brands, companies that are all in one way or the other.
They're interested in basically finding their audience.
And they're realizing now much more that the shotgun approach is retracting a bit.
And you know, if you're looking for a particular audience, you can,
Well, when it comes to podcasting,
you can certainly listen to a number of shows and already just intuitively know what kind of people
listening to that show.
But also there's just a lot more information available.
And there is a much closer loop between listeners of podcasts or audio based programming.
Distributed in this fashion than there is perhaps through traditional radio outlets.
And that audience, as we've discussed before, is moving away.
They're not really listening to the radio anymore.
You know, the iPod and MP3 players is definitely where it's at.
So there's some bootstrapping that's going to be done.
And, you know, the first thing that I really wanted to make sure we did is made an investment in the content.
Because we've already, I can, it's moving so fast.
It feels like first it was really cool just to have, you know, this concept of audio,
nugget showing up on your iPod and MP3 player automatically.
It's moved beyond that.
Now people are really into the content.
I mean, I can tell, you know, and it's, and I get just as much email from people who subscribe to the show
and listen to it on a portable player as, as do people just sit there at their desk or at home on the laptop.
And when the new show arrives, they click it and listen to it right there.
I mean, that's really moved much faster than I anticipated.
So we will be making investments in a number of shows and podcasters.
Really to make sure that, you know, that they can build and won't be, you know, stuck in this,
in this kind of, in irons, if you will, you know, where there's just no wind.
Because, you know, not quite enough, you know, critical mass to really make any money to even quit half of the day job.
And I'm an impatient motherfucker, you know, I like to move things along.
So we've kind of figured that out and, and how we can, and how we can get a number of people going
who in turn will be able to turn around and produce new shows with talent that they managed.
So we've got quite an interesting structure and business model set up for all of that.
We'll be announcing all this as we go along and hope in the next or in this coming week.
We'll actually be able to do a couple of announcements about some of the talent that we've,
that will be investing in.
Then the, back to the listeners for a second.
I believe that every listener is pretty much a built in broadcaster.
Just be, you know, for yourself to to test or to, you know, muck about.
It may be for your family, your friends.
It's more than likely it's not financially motivated at all.
But this is a very, excuse me, a very large group of people who we also intend to help really by making it easy for them to do a podcast.
And it can be with different tools, different interfaces, different means of getting it there as long as it gets there.
And that, by the way, will not all be like a technology thing that we're all building ourselves.
I mean, there's a lot out there, which is I think the most exciting.
The most exciting part about the moment that we're doing this, the timing 10 years ago.
I had to go places and explain to marketers and advertisers what the internet was.
And that was, you know, difficult.
And then when we talked about all the great stuff that could do, we actually had to go and build it, which is even worse.
I was actually Dave Winner pointed to a great, a great article.
Let me see.
This morning, boy, this is going to take a second here, but I really do want to get to this article.
It was by.
Uh, let me see, was it Glenn Fleischman?
No.
Wait a minute, no Brian Deer.
That's what it was, I think.
Yeah, it's titled the long trail.
And down here, somewhere at the bottom, he says.
He, he talks about episode of Star Trek, where Captain Kirk is, you know,
is, you know, is zapped off the bridge of the enterprise and deposited on a bleak planter of rocks, mountains and precipies.
And he has to fight off the metrons.
And he does that with abundance of natural resources.
And so this is kind of interesting here.
It says, the notion of available materials has kept with me for years.
Look around today on the way, you'll find all the tools you need to build whatever you need.
That's what I discovered was the case when thinking about EVDB back in 2002.
All the building blocks already existed.
Each built somewhere along the long trail of technology just need to be put together in a new way.
Amen to that.
Absolutely.
Uh, so there's a lot of that out there.
And every single day, it's like, you know, I think of something that we can do.
Because basically, you know, there's money to do this with, which is, is the good thing.
And then all of a sudden an email pop up or someone has that idea.
And it's there, you know, it's like, don't have to invent on anything.
It's just, it's, it's rocking.
So, uh, stay tuned.
The daily source code will be the main place where I'll tell you what's going on.
And also at podshow.com, that little player that now has, uh,
I should have a copy of that if you hadn't heard that.
Maybe I should play that for you.
It's kind of hokey, which was obviously a large part of the intent.
Uh, I want to say, do I have this here?
Oh, I think I have it.
On my, wow, I can't believe how much I can't believe how much came in from my iPod.
So many podcasts.
It's just outrageous.
Okay, I think this is it.
Yeah, let's have a quick listen to this.
We don't need no stinking trends, man.
Hi, everybody.
This is Adam Curry.
Welcome you to podshow.com.
That's right.
Get ready podcasterscuspodshow.com is getting ready to launch.
And when it does, you'll be treated to the next evolution in podcasting.
If you're a podcast producer, you'll have the tools and support to create new more powerful content
and learn money in the process.
You'll have access to a broader audience and have the support of an infrastructure that can handle your success.
If you're a listener, you'll be able to enjoy pod shows more easily and more choice and more style.
You'll be able to get involved in your favorite pod shows and take advantage of unique opportunities offered by your podshow hosts.
And when you're ready, you'll be able to make a pod show of your very own, all for free.
If you're an advertiser, archetypal.
Get ready to have access to the most desirable and elusive audience groups on the planet.
We can help you get your message to the right listeners to build your brand and build your business.
If you want to be a part of the podshow revolution, just click the link at the bottom of the page and we'll put you at the top of the list for our debut.
You can also sign up for our free personal podcast service and other specials.
It's a turn off that boring radio and tune in to podshow.com.
Your ears will shout, enjoy.
Click.
Here.
We had a good time putting that together actually.
Did a little bit of MIDI work to make it all sound just perfect, you know?
This is a great show that came through on openpodcast.org.
I can only play a little bit because like 8 minutes long, but it's an angry IT professional.
It's his rant.
Openpodcast.org's number 1310.
See the flip side of when your computer doesn't work and you call tech support.
There are people behind that, you know?
Hi, angry tech podcast, take one.
Oh, I'm freaking angry today.
Fucking angry.
Just go ahead and say it.
Look, that dead head.
Come into work.
One of the texts with the biggest business territories of north is gone for the day.
Changes of floater.
Floating day he had off schedule to this day.
Today, Friday, 11th of March.
Why, I don't know.
Reason wasn't made clear to me.
All I know was all of a sudden with all this other shit I got going on.
I got cover for this time with bitch.
And when feel so bad, if it wasn't such a goddamn habit for a couple of people that I work with.
So it pisses me off.
So, you know, I'm hitting them.
I'm banging them out one after the other.
Starting early, you know?
I guess it was a 14-point call.
Let's go pick a parts first thing this morning.
Get rid of somebody.
Actually, starting out is very light.
And I didn't know what the hell was going to happen.
But I'd say between nine and 10 o'clock, they just started just pouring in the calls did.
What the hell?
What's the do about it, you know?
Take a one at a fucking time.
Yeah, baby.
One at a fucking time.
You know, if that's not bad enough, the goddamn the way we got the Beijing system set up right now.
When a page comes in for this guy who left, they call me in.
I get one for him and then one for the group.
And if it's some kind of a recall or urgent situation, the people at FWSS want to send out two or three pages for some goddamn reason.
You really should listen to this whole thing.
It's just amazing.
You know, all of a sudden it's like it puts a human to the tech support line you call maybe at work.
And those guys don't have it easy.
Let me tell you, they really don't have it easy.
I know because I am one, I'm a tech support guy for my immediate family, my extended family, all my friends.
And I'll just say one more time, you know.
It's kind of the duty, you know.
If I'm a geek, it's my duty to help you.
And then you'll, it'll become your duty to help someone else once you know how to fix whatever that particular problem is.
But you'll learn that when something goes wrong, it really helps for someone to, you know, just jot down the error message or call you when the error message is still up.
You know, otherwise it's like, you know, it didn't work and something popped up, but it didn't read it.
That just really doesn't cut it, you know, it's not, it's not enough to say that.
So, be nice to your friendly technician, your IT technician.
He really wants to help you. He really does.
I was, while I was saying that I was trying to pop up a website.
I remember I talked about the, the ingenious idea, which wasn't my idea, but it did come to me through the show.
I'm going to copy the link here.
Oh, man, I'm doing this through a remote console. It's not very easy. Here we go.
To use two dish washers, so that you essentially take the, the clean ones out of one and when, you know, when it's dirty, you put it back into the other.
And you really don't have your dishes and it covered anywhere.
And I got a lot of responses.
Basically pointing to the same website, Fisher and Paykel, they actually make a two-draw dishwasher.
And it's built in. It's built into the cabinetry and you have a top-draw and a lower draw.
And I'm saying, yeah, it's totally cool.
Let me see that some of the blurb here, superior ergonomics fully integrated.
Choose your own finished environmentally outstanding.
Not just a dishwasher, but two dish washers in one.
Separately controlled units featured the unique yet delightfully uncomplicated concept of a sliding kitchen drawer, creating superior ergonomics and easier access.
But they haven't really latched on to the idea of, um, I guess that's ergonomics, right?
But they should just say it, you know, never deal with these fucking dishes again.
You know, you keep me the goddamn drawers, top-draw, bottom-draw.
Honey, what draw are we using today, top-draw? I say, I say, that would actually work.
Every beginning has an end, even for this.
Uh, it's a stale-hizer roll.
Stale-hizer bun, or bun, whatever you want to call it.
That's fine.
You'll tell me your heart's straightness.
Everyone, help me find a new good home.
I could do this.
starring Tim Henson.
It's not going to talk.
Friendships will be broken.
The stale-hizer roll.
Someone will die.
Why would you come in here?
Or at least be so lonely, babe.
Instead of a bitch.
Let me tell you that beat out to start a beat I come.
It breaks its 10th from the store-to-view show.
Join us on Monday, March 14th, as we learn together.
He's won the stale-hizer roll from eBay.
Every day on the store-to-view, we talk about crazy, bizarre news stories,
and then proceed to mock him through the kill them.
For the past several months, I've been astounded.
The amount of crap that's been sold on eBay.
We're talking grilled cheese sandwiches with the Virgin Mary burned into it.
A pretzel in the shape of the baby.
Jesus giving the thumbs up.
And, you know, the authors had on a trisket.
That's why for a couple thousand.
It's insane.
I wanted to get in on the axel.
I placed a stale-kaiser roll on eBay.
People have actually been on this stupid thing.
Toon into the store-to-view on Monday to see how it all ends.
www.distortedview.com.
It's 10 minutes of your life. You'll never get back.
Come for the news of the weird.
Stay for the audio pornography.
What?
It's just a distorted view show.
And, of course, everything mentioned in today's show
can be found in the show notes.
You can find those at dailysourcecode.com
or at www.curry.com.
And, even though I don't have a young pull-in hit test for today,
I've got something that sounds close.
Adam Christian, sir, is the Maccast.
Hello, this is the hit test for the Maccast.
My name is Jan Tualette.
I am the cousin of Jan Tualette.
You might have heard of the Mac, the Adam and Sir.
Adam Curry's.
And, uh, he is today's hit test for especially for the Macintosh.
Okay.
So, here's number one.
See if you recognize this one.
This is cool.
Oh, you've recognized his Macmill.
One more time.
And, here's your 60 seconds.
Oh, I actually had one of these.
That's a Power Mac 61.
I hope you recognize that one.
Here's number two.
No problem.
Oh, that's it.
I don't want to watch.
Hi.
Oh, this one's familiar.
Oh, it's quite easy.
How are we going, sir?
I don't think we'll see 50 seconds.
Uh, I'm going to guess a, uh, maybe a performer.
We're early performer.
And here's a number three.
The answer is a built-in school.
Oh, that's a G4.
I don't want to about time.
That sounds kind of familiar.
Um, uh, blue and white, uh, G3.
Oh.
So, how do you know?
I know.
Did you manage to guess them all?
I, I don't think I quite got them.
Yeah.
I don't want them.
Hey, distinctive.
That's the Power Macintosh.
60, 100.
Okay, see any of that one?
I'll run about March 1994.
I hope you got that one.
He was number two.
Ah, that one is the Macintosh performer.
Yeah.
I see it.
It's easy.
I think I can get the model.
Oh, no.
What about the third one?
Your guest is what I hope is.
He's the eye Mac for me.
Your wife.
He's your black wife.
All right.
My wife does it.
He's your wife.
No.
Shit.
He's my wife.
You're my wife cause something.
I'm, kind of I'm...
I'm Karif.
Anyway, I hope you enjoyed this.
And...
See you next time on D...
Cas4, Cas4,
He says...
You're welcome.
I've been waiting for some time.
Catch one..
Come on.
There's...
Look.
Uh...
Alright, come on.
I gotta tell you, when I have all my subscriptions rolling through all day and I just pop them up on iTunes, it's like the radio station.
My personal radio station.
And it really, really sounds good. It's just, you guys are nuts, man. I love this stuff. Let's go.
Alright, that's it for the daily source coming from Monday.
Tomorrow I'll be back. I'll be keeping you up to speed on the more developments as they come along.
It's going to be a pretty big week. I hope to be able to do one or two pretty big announcements talking about some of the stuff we're doing.
As discussed earlier in the show, so keep it locked in, subscribe to the daily source code dailysourcecode.com.
We'll find the podcast feed and of course the latest show and the archives.
www.curry.com is my web blog for comments and add them at Curry.com as we can see.
Have yourself a great week, everybody. I'll talk to you tomorrow. Bye-bye.
www.curry.com