Daily source code, February 6th, 2005, transmitters, we don't need no stinkin' transmitters.
Autastic, it's Adam Curry.
That's right, Sunday afternoon tied for a laid-back source.
You know, it's like a Sunday, we got to be kind of chilled out.
Hey everybody, how you doing? Sorry about Friday.
I'll tell you what went on Friday, why there was no daily source code.
But then again, not too many people seem to mind.
I guess maybe Friday isn't such a big deal if we don't have a show.
Anyway, we're ready for one now.
It's Sunday afternoon, it's about three o'clock in the big green horrendous chair.
I noticed when I was talking last time about the big green chair
that hundreds of people know this chair.
I forgot to mention that this big huge, gaudy recliner was used by lots of the server guys who worked for me.
But I work with it, thinking of ideas, because that's basically when they had to stay overnight or get some work done, they'd chill out in this thing.
And they'd sleep in it, and many a problem has been discussed while someone was sitting in the big green chair.
Trying to just my microphone.
I've got the music stand that my father and law made for me.
But it doesn't quite cut it when it comes to the big green thing.
Just a green position at there.
That's a little bit better.
Alrighty, so Friday.
Even though I posted most of the information to my weblog,
let's see, what started out Friday?
After I took her senior to school and all the regular bits, and did my email and check my aggregator and look at all the news and did a couple of postings,
I went up to Black push airport to get all the info on my FAA fixed wing license add-on.
What a scam that turned out to be, man.
Oh, man, there's just, I love this sensio coffee machine.
Have you ever tried, we've talked about it before on the source code.
It makes such a perfect cup of coffee every single time.
So I went up, to meet with the operations manager.
And if you look at cabair.com, cabair is this flight school that has flight schools at Black Bush and else tree and different airfields around the country.
You know, it's like with the number one guys, we do all FAA training and licensing and examinations.
Hold on, that's Brian, I'll have to hold on a second, let me.
This is a buddy of mine, hold on a second, hey Brian.
Brian?
I'm never going to be able to hear him, of course.
Okay, I'll catch him later then.
So the ops manager sat me down and he said, well, you know, about the FAA stuff.
Yeah, you know, we really don't have n registered airplanes.
We don't really have anyone to train you.
We have someone who might be moving into L's tree, which is an hour and a half from my house from the cottage.
And maybe you can work some out, but of course you could join in here with our jar ops program and not that hell.
Yeah, it's like that means I have to go through a whole bunch of tests all over again and then I'm, you know, I'm then I'm in the European system, which I don't have to be because that's if anything, that's one of the benefits of being a US citizen.
You know, having a US passport as you get to do the US FAA flight exams and and just be a part of that system, by the way, the United States did invent flying, you know.
So it's not like we don't know what the fuck we're doing. A lot of Europeans really frown on on the US way of flying and training and again, I think it's just because they like to keep tabs on everybody and.
Europe's you weird right now and and the UK of course is a part of Europe that you know.
But there's the right these referenda or referendums I guess it is that are being held in in the coming year about the European constitution.
I've been web logging about the European constitution for a while and it's amazing how few people really give a shit.
And I don't even know if most people understand well in the United Kingdom I think they are pretty clued into what's going on, but I know the Netherlands.
People don't know, you know, and this whole Europe thing this United States of Europe, it started out 25 years ago, I think.
They started planning for this and the whole idea was we're supposed to have a single monetary unit, the EU, the European monetary unit, which now of course is the euro.
And as a part of that we'd have, you know, it's all about economics and now we're seeing that it's not just about economics because, you know, it's about control centralized control from Brussels and not just Brussels, there's also Straussburg.
The European government is home on a second and we just reply to a shoot, I'll get to that Skype message later on.
Actually, I should turn Skype off when I'm recording.
So it's problematic.
There's a guy here who has, we had a talk show called Kill Roy.
And he became a member of European Parliament just to go and try and blow it up because what he was essentially saying, and there was a great documentary on TV the other day with the man behind the tan.
But you got to envision him a little bit of a kind of like a cross between Haroldo and Jerry Springer, I guess, but he's classy, he's a real classy guy.
At least he comes across as a classy guy, I don't know him personally.
And it followed him in the European Parliament and he basically was highlighting all these dickhead jibronies who are, you know, making important decisions and casting Britain's vote in European Parliament.
And what we're seeing is that this is not at all about just economics, these fuckers want to make the United States of Europe and they want to control it from Brussels and from Straussburg, like that's the old little mini Washington DC.
And, you know, people should be electing the parliament, you know, I think in most European countries they do elect the European Parliament members, but it's not really being taken that seriously.
And I don't think they understand the inhabitants of these countries understand that these people will be making up all the laws and the rules.
And they're basically, you know, they're fat cats, most of them, I'm not going to, you know, I can't just generalize and say all them are fat cats sitting there, you know, with an office in Straussburg and office in Brussels, great traveling expense accounts.
They've got all kinds of secretaries and people to take care of their correspondence and, you know, they just sit there and just pass laws and, you know, and often as is, we see even with the, with the, with the United States, if you look at what bills are passed without people reading them, you know, because they're printed up in the middle of the night with all the changes in them.
So I'm not, I'm not going to try to run off on this tangent, but it has been bothering me that people just really don't seem to understand that there's a snow job going on.
And I think it's going to be good at all. I'm really against, really, really against all this power that Brussels is pulling towards it, at least from what I've seen so far, the people who are in Brussels are losers.
These are second line people who couldn't make it in politics, in the, in the, in their own countries in the first place, or maybe they're, you know, they're part of old boys networks.
And sure there are a few who are really serious about it, kill right, you know, by being an exception defines the rule right there.
Anyway.
I love doing the Sunday podcast because I don't feel like I should be limited to 40 minutes and actually I want to catch up on all the stuff that I still have left over from the week that just been pushing off down the outline.
Like, yeah, it's good, but when I run out of time, you know, then of course I make decisions about what I'm going to put in what I'm not going to put in.
So a couple of things we just got to got to get through the number one thing is it's time for more cowbell.
This is the Chambers Brothers.
Time has come today as the definitive cowbell track for Sunday.
Can't put it off under other day.
I don't care what others say.
They've been with owners in any way.
Time has come today.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
And I don't know if I have to follow, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,Hey, hey, hey,
Time, I can't run the father's son
A time, a time, a time, a time, a time, a time
Time, I can go and put aside
Time, I can't run
But I can't make time, time, time, and my soul
When the cycle tells us, time
Time, out of time is lost
Time, there are things to real life
Time, I can't run for days
Time, out of time is lost
Time, I can't run
Oh, now the time has come
So I know the next you're wrong
So I don't mind if we're moved by the sun
But I can't mind what I'm looking for
I've been walking through the side
I've been looking for you
But I don't mind if I'm coming
Oh, so I know the next you're wrong
I know the time has come
I know all the things you're real on
I've had something to do
But I don't mind if we're moved by the sun
So I know the next you're wrong
So I know all the things you're real on
I've been looking for you
But I don't mind if we're moved by the sun
Yeah, good to the very last drop of Calville
Same as brothers Calville, but they song
That was a time has come today
Thanks to Greg Del Sesto for sending me that
And saying indeed this is the
He says that your listeners Calville
Some issues have been well very cute
But this is the seminal Calville track
I think I have to agree
Excellent to listen to that
Much appreciated
Michael Jackson, the big choraldo interview
I guess was last night we recorded it here
Because off of Fox News I haven't seen it yet
Expressly so because I wanted to
But before I see the choraldo interview
I wanted to just tell you my thoughts
On what's going on
With Michael Jackson, essentially what he's saying
People make shit up
And it's just not true
There's even more Skype just keeps on coming
I need to shut the hold on
Let me just kill Skype for a second
So that people stop
Instead of messaging me and calling me
So
He's saying that he's being framed
Which I totally believe he is
The question that it's all going to come down to
Essentially is
It's almost going to be a Clinton thing I think
Although of course, Clinton as we all know now was guilty
I have a hard time believing Michael Jackson
Is 100% well
I don't think it's as black and white as guilty
Not guilty in this case
I've met him a couple of times
Every single time I met him
There were lots of kids
And how he mandell
Running around
By the way
Lots of girls too, not just boys
I'm wondering where all the girls are
In all these stories that I'm seeing on Fox and CNN
And web logs and everyone's reporting on it
And it's amazing how big this story is
And of course, it's quite normal for people to
And people like you and I
To
How can I explain it
When there's a celebrity who makes lots of money
And everything's going their way
And especially if they're a little bit of eccentric
It's just fun, it makes you feel good
When they fuck up and they get hammered down
You know, it's like that
Guy has problems just like me
And I've been there, not at a Michael Jackson level
By any, by any means
But I've certainly been there
I've been on covers of newspapers and
In other words, falsely accused of
Cheating on taxes and
All kinds of horrendous things
Nothing as bad
Really as what Michael Jackson's being accused of
But I think this guy
Is truly just a really loving guy
And he likes to hang out with kids
And hug them
And cuddle with them
And play with them
And that is something that in the United States
Unless it's your own children
Is just not acceptable
It's not accepted
And European listeners I think
Will understand when I say
And lots of American listeners of course
You know, this is in some ways
Along the line of the Janet Jackson
Nipple gate controversy
You know, big fucking deal
We were laughing last night
We were watching this reality show
Called the casino, it's about the golden nugget
Casino
And I'll let me just
Reset my latency here
That sounds actually pretty sexual
Reset my latency
And we were laughing about the show
Because it's a US reality-based show
And in this you see
You see strippers, you see gambling, drinking, drunk people fighting
You know, just everything that is Las Vegas
And then on certain point there
These group of girls who have a batslet party
And they're walking around with an inflatable penis
Near the pool
And they have to blur this whole thing out
Like this is going to damage me
If I see an inflatable six foot tall
And inflatable penis
On the screen, you know, meanwhile
In America
Most people I know
And I'm an American myself
We're always thinking about dick
And how to get it sucked
Actually
Let's just call it spades
That's what everyone's thinking all the time
But oh God
Oh God
And that's something to do with God
And God fearing people perhaps
You know, let's not show that on television
Oh corrupt the minds of our children
Um
So in a way Michael
I think is a victim of his success
He's a victim of his corkiness
Which is lots of creative people are quirky
And weird and funky
And you know, excuse me
If you could please give me a definition of what is normal
Then we could all adhere to it
On the other hand
I also have to say that when
When folks say, oh, you know that
Like we have a secret
And we'll put it in this little box
And we don't tell anyone about it
That those are like the
The classic pedophile moves
And I don't know what's true
You know, that's another thing
What's true?
What is the real truth
And
Yeah
I
Until I see some really compelling proof
And when I see these kids, you know, all I see is that they're
They're cuddling with them
And many people that just may make them nauseous
You know, to see a grown man cuddled with
With a child, particularly of the same sex
But I'm sorry
I just as I know Michael Jackson
I do not believe
He is a pedophile
I think he really
Truly
Loves children
Loves having them around
Loves cuddling and hugging with them
And there's nothing wrong with that
There really isn't
And when we were in
Is something I don't think
I don't think I've actually ever told anyone this on the podcast
In 1999
I was just about done with
My tenure at the company
Ron Bloom and I took public
Think new ideas
And we had promised to a three year contract
And I was, you know, Ron stayed on longer
To actually merge with another company
And he did a great job with that
But I had to go
I was like I was done
I was toast three years of running Ron and suit
Was too much for me
And
But we really wanted to leave the states at that moment
And the catalyst for that
Was about a year prior to that
One of the mothers
Of the school that Christina was going to
Came over to our house
Knocked on the door
And I opened up
And Patricia was there
And she said well
And I really have to talk to you about something
Because all the mothers at the school
We had a conversation
And we feel that Patricia
You should wear baggier clothing
When you come to school
And Patricia's hot
She's sexy
She wears
Like a
A track suit
And she looks hot
Like J.Glo
J.L.
Whereas a track suit
Only Patricia's a bud egg
That big
I think goodness
You know, Patricia is
She's curvy
She's crevacious
She's sexy
She's beautiful
She's a beautiful woman
Which of course
I think part of the problem here
Maybe a bit of jealousy
But to then say
You have to wear bagier clothing
Because the boys are at that age
And they're looking
Like what the fuck
Is that all about
And that really
You know, set us off
And I have to say that
I would say to Christina
When she was young
You know, maybe like four or five
And we take a bath together
Or sometimes she's hopping the shower
Or whatever
And I said don't tell anyone
It's cool
Because they won't understand
And I truly believe that
And boy was I right
When after that episode
With that mother
And we said
We looked at each other and said
Fuck this
Let's get the hell out of here
For a while
I can't deal with this
And of course that may be something to do with
Suburban New Jersey
Where we live
But you know
Is it any different anywhere else?
So there's
There is
Some frustration
Particularly in the United States
Fed by the media
Even though we all love having sex
You know that
You're listening to this thinking right now
Like yeah, I love having sex
Yeah, we all think about dick
Whether you have one or one
Or need one
So I hope
My true hope is that Michael Jackson
Really does get a fair trial
I'll be the first one to say
I really misread it
And I've misread people before
And let me tell you
Big time
So it wouldn't be the first time
But if anything
I believe Michael Jackson is asexual
Just he has no sex whatsoever
And look at the guys
Look at his childhood
I don't believe he was abused as a child
So I don't think that
That would have any influence on
I just I cannot see it
The way I know what I've seen
And I've seen a little bit more
Than what you're seeing on television
So I'm going to watch the Haraldo thing now
I think that he's pretty much
Sticking up for Jackson
That's what I read somewhere
But I want to see the
The interview first
To see what his conclusion was
Haraldo's a lawyer
So hopefully he's looking at the evidence
On hand
And is making a qualified decision
Based upon that
And it's interesting though
Now you see Michael Jackson is really
He's really starting to talk straight
There was a time when
I only could do talk like this
And I'm really just
I'm really just very shy
And part of that's an act
Perhaps part of his creative process that he goes through
But he's talking pretty clearly now
And he wants his day in court
And he has great faith in the American people
Has great faith in our justice system
So do I
And so I totally hope that he gets a fair shake
And then after that
We should try and leave him alone
And just think also
Because this could happen to you
If it could happen to Michael Jackson
It could happen to you
And it happens all the time
Okay
Enough about Mike
By the way, no matter what you say
He is one talented mother fucker
I've been getting a lot of comments about
Embedding show notes
Into the MP3 file
And let me say I got a couple here
I haven't reviewed them
Here's
Oh yeah, this is a great link that I got from
Dan Carlene
There's a caption editor
On iriveramerica.com
The link of course in the show notes for today
Where you can drop your MP3 file in
And then you cop you paste your show notes into the text window
And then you start the MP3 player
And let's say your show notes are just one line above another
Right
And you can time it
You can say okay I want
So for instance right now
I'd be talking about the iriver show notes
And you'd look at your iriver
And across the screen would be
Perhaps the email from Dan
That would be streaming as a text scroll
And it works this actually works on
A number of different players
Of course not on the iPod
Nor as far as I can tell this work in iTunes
Or maybe a plugin to actually show
The notes because this is a part of the
Lyrics tag in the ID3 tags
Not amazing how everything about MP3 and ID3
Is all based on music and nothing generic
They really weren't thinking about
Anything other than
The music when all this was put together
Let's see what the next email was
Oh this is from Tom Scuding
He has some more technical information
He says the old synchronized lyrics
Standard S-Y-L-T frame
In the ID3 tags
In beds of file into ID3 tags
So it's included in the MP3
So you need to add an extra file
So there's no syncing problem
And again, what he's saying is
The biggest problem is there is no
There are almost no tools to create this stuff
With
Because doing it by hand
I mean that's going to be a nightmare
But I think what we want is
Just like that I river thing
Although it's windows
And it didn't work very well for me
And it would be a horrendous process
To add to the chain of things
That I have to do to get my podcast out
Obviously
But if there was an easy way to do it
Boy what I
And then all of our ran
Actually sent an email about
How this works
How the lyrics tags work
How you can encode them
So there is a lot of data about this
And there's just almost no tools
On the Mac there's certainly no tools
Whatever there's plenty of tools
For windows
And for doing stuff
Like Winamp
And there's a lot of stuff there
But I'd like to hear more
If you know of an editor that will work on the Mac
So I can start testing some of that stuff
And if we know how we can make
Lyric show up on the iPod
That we may as to get somewhere with these show notes
It could be pretty cool
See when I get here
This is from
This is from Kim
Of Shakespeare's Two Flay
And Home School Habitat
I played a bit of their weblog before
Their podcast before
There was some tool
Anyway, I'm stuck at home
When the flute today
I've been ego surfing on lines
My podcast is listed found in the link
Have you ever wondered
As Kim
Where all the lady podcasters are
Goes on to say I guess
Match counts
But really there are a ton of us out there
Amy over the blog content
Contentious
Has done us all the way
By compiling a list
So check that link
Out the women in pod casting
The definitive list
And let's add to that
I just see podcasters
Podcasters is podcasters
I don't see them really
Is you know, male or female
And we have
What is open source sex
Violet blue
And
Well
Let's just call them all Bitty
Shall we?
Which segway is beautifully
Into this track that I received
From
Bitty Lyann
When I say Bitty Lyann
Of course I'm talking about Lyann
From the
Lassidious Bitties
She came across a track
Which is absolutely
Larious
Certainly in the context of
Seeing the Bitties on the 16th of February
When I go to New York
They they
Check this one out
On the swiss
I see Bitties
Here they're everywhere
Browns go it's grey here
Trouble when they walk here
It's a Friday set of streets
A full of old gears on day release
You're not able to walk fast
But you talk fast
Body shape like a B glass
At the road crossing
So slow
When the lights go
Not even up the curb zone
This is my first
I slow back
Nice old lady and her best hat
I know you can't see me
Because you left the glasses
And off with the TV
Then you reach out
And touch my face
And say
There were one that came back
To your place
I would put the only button
For as I see
You're the I'm 18
You're 73
Oh
You know I see a lot
I'm not holding on
To be giving you babies
Oh
You know I see a lot
But I'm not holding on
To be giving you babies
I see babies
When I'm cruising in my box all over
When I'm cruising I got pulled over
Knit my jumper
No she's over
It's rude to dump her
Come with down the shots for some Benson
Down the post office for your pension
Into a little woods for a cup of tea
And a bit of touch
And at the launch of really
W8 speech lickin it's like
And the doctor replace it hits like
In will work
Shake it all around the floor
Till you forget what you came in for
You got your own home when you always eat out
But that doesn't mean that I don't get freaked out
See I don't have a problem with you calling me king
But I do have a problem with you having no tea
Oh
You know I see a lot
I'm not holding on
To be giving you babies
Oh
You know I see a lot
But I'm not holding on
To be giving you babies
You know I see a lot
But I do have a problem with you
So I'm not holding on
To be giving you babies
Oh
You know I see a lot
I'm not holding on
To be giving you babies
You know what I see in love
But I'm not old enough
To be giving you babies
Oh, oh, oh
You know what I see in love
I'm not old enough
To be giving you babies
Oh, oh
You know what I see in love
But I'm not old enough
To be giving you babies
Seeing nothing but babies
Wanting my babies
I'm living a baby's dream
You know what I mean
It's not right
It's not love
Oh
It's not good
So in the States there's 50 cents here in the UK. It's 50 pence. I see bitties on the daily source code
Today's Sunday. It's February 6, 2005
Then I said it was going to be seeing the bitties to the 16th of February. I am
Booking my trip. You know, I've met so many people so many old voices from the past have come up
Since the podcast in craze really has grown too much of big hype
I'm just getting emails from people I've been spoken to in a long long time and I just need to do a little trip
So the idea is that I will be in New York on the 16th for the bitties
Bittie cast the kickoff there
I really want to be want to be there when that happened
I'm going to meet a couple people like Steve Leeds when I told you about him from from the MTV days
My old buddies from Medi America Jones, Medi America who did my radio syndication
They're all over podcasting of course have questions
Then I was going to travel out west
Guy who worked at Microsoft in the Netherlands eric hookers
About five years ago. I met him when I was into the jamvy stuff doing all of the
Why actually trying to I guess do a version of of
podcasting only it was with video it was a Java and without artists and guess what didn't work
He is now
He just moved from Rome with his family to Seattle to become he's some big marketing mark now
Microsoft and
He's heading up the what group is it something with the Windows media. I'm sure and
So he's invited me to come out and
And I've known him for for a couple years so be kind of cool. It's like local boy makes good
You know now he's a big cheese at Microsoft so be happy to go over there and
Oh, maybe I'll get to sit in a windowless room with him
Which is what happened the last time I went to Microsoft
Then there's some people in San Francisco of course that I want to hook up with and with any lock
And this is what I'm trying to figure out I'd like to go to the rave awards
Of course have been nominated for iPodder
And that I think is on the is at the eight knows the 22nd I believe so
And then I'll probably go back from either there or from Seattle and not quite sure and I'm trying to hook up with
Don and Drew
I know they go out to San Francisco a lot so I'm trying to coordinate that and just you know
Steve Gilmore just
Lots of people lots of people to hang out with and talk with and see where we're at as as we move podcasting forward and
You know I do want to say about podcasting that because who sent me I got an email yesterday
So I'm saying hey, you know we could also attach you know I call invitations to RSS feeds
It's an apps of fucking lootably
You know and just because it's an MP3 file that's attached to an RSS as an enclosure doesn't mean it has to be
You know start with a show opener and have
You know all kinds of stuff in the middle it could be anything you want like what have been listening to recently
Surelock homes has been coming through and a little bit every single day. That's one of the podcast
I'm subscribed to if you want to see new podcasts that are updated regularly I potted out org
Has all the new podcast listed every single day. There's probably about 10 new submissions a day on average that come in and of course there's the whole directory
If you want to
Have your podcast listed in the directory a lot of people are looking for this
And I guess it's just not clear on the site itself going to the directory go to a node that you think your podcast would would fit and
On that page you'll see a submit a link
link you click on that and you should be your information it goes off to the maintainer of that node and then
It will be added into the directory also slim that down a bit the directory because it was getting a little bit
large to suck into some of the iPodder software like iPodder itself the lemon version
It was it grown to like 250 k and size and I shrunk that down to like 70 now by
Aggregating some stuff putting it into its own
Opml file which is a great way. I guess to kind of cut down on on the on the bandwidth and just sucking in the that that that that file which has gotten a little bit large in size and
The lemon guys said that the improvement is really good and as you know they're working on the 2.0 release of lemon
So I'm really excited to see what's going on there. There was a was a PC magazine review of that also of Doppler radio
So a review of that fine Dutch iPodder client so
Good stuff there. Let me see
Some more stuff we got to clear up remember I was talking about reality shows about the
Anatomy for beginners and then I came up with this luminous idea of
Doing a stop smoking reality show that it could only be moments away. Well, I got two emails again all this that in the in the show notes
This show already existed. It's already done. It was called cold turkey where celebrities tried to get quit smoking
Information about that as I said in the show notes
What's the second email I got from Todd yeah same thing packs tv pax tv dot com
Cold turkey and then there's also a link to the website for anatomy for beginners Mike which I have dubbed now anatomy for dummies
Well, what a great show that is I've also subscribed to the some new podcasts
One of them is the indie media feed
Indie media I've already you know been paying attention to what they've been doing for a long time
It's you've got some great websites great infrastructure
Different countries have you know the indie media dot org it really propagates out even the Netherlands has their own indie media
So now there's all these well not necessarily
Specific podcasts, but I think some of them are being made specifically as podcasts, but I guess there was already a lot of
Audio activism going on for instance audio activism.org. I found
This and I don't think it's a separate feed for it comes to on my indie media subscription jodie pulse and
Does these
Wonderful little stories and we see how long is this one this one is
Three minutes
Yeah, I want to play the whole thing for you actually because I was amazed even though I think I knew most of the information about the fed
Now you've probably heard this you know the fed the fed is
Basically Alan Greenspan and he you know talks about
You know the economy and where it's going and inflation, but also he determines if there's going to be why don't
Of heat determines he announces the the interest rate hikes or drops, et cetera and
It's really all has to do with central banking and
I don't know too much about it. I'm sure that there's some financial people out there who would be happy to jump in on the
Conversation and talk to us about central banking
But listen to this story. I'm going to play the whole thing. It's three and a half minutes if you want to fast forward
You can but I think it'll be very interesting to you to find out exactly what the fed is
Who's a member who controls them and what they do?
Hi, this is jodie paulson from Moscow, Idaho with what they don't tell you
Unlike general Tommy Franks who feels there exists quote the potential of a massive
casualty producing event somewhere in the western world that causes our population to question our own
Constitution on quote I feel the US Constitution is an extremely hardy document loaded with foresight
Unfortunately in 1913
Congress trashed that foresight and ignored Thomas Jefferson who said quote if the American people ever
Allow private banks to control the issuance of their currency first by inflation and then my deflation
The banks and corporations that will grow up around them will deprive the people of all their property and tell their
Children will wake up homeless on the continent their father's conquered unquote
Ignoring clause five of section eight of the Constitution Congress sold out its power to coin money and regulate its value to a group of private
Bankers by creating the federal reserve
What the fed isn't of public institution. It's a bunch of private banks
That's right. It's not owned by the federal government or the taxpayers of the United States
In fact, you could say they own us because we're in debt to them up to our eyeballs
The fed consists of Rothschild Bank of London Warburg Bank of Hamburg Rothschild Bank of Berlin
Laman brothers of New York
Lazzard brothers of Paris Koon low bank of New York is real Moses sife banks of Italy
Goldman Sachs of New York Chase Manhattan Bank of New York and Warburg Bank of Amsterdam
These guys print and led your money out of nothing and loan it back to us with interest
Obviously, we'll never be able to repay them in Dan Benham's brilliant article a phone call to the fed
We discover there are only 263 billion federal reserve notes in circulation
But we have a four trillion dollar national debt payable in federal reserve notes
How do you like them apples?
Congressman Ron Paul says quote most Americans have suffered a steadily eroding purchasing power
Because of the federal reserves inflationary policies
This represents a real if hidden tax imposed on the American people on quote
Here are some statistics to back that claim in 2001
$1,780 had the same purchase power as a hundred dollars in the year 1913
In 1913 a hundred and thirteen dollars had the same purchase power as a hundred dollars in 1776
Get the feeling we're being scammed
Maybe it wouldn't surprise you to know that Enron's infamous Jeff Skilling was director of the federal reserve bank in Houston
So anyway whenever the government runs a deficit the fed prints money to buy the debt and
40% of our income taxes pay the interest
Keep in mind the fed's books are not
Opens the public these guys possess almost unlimited resources to buy influence and power
Presidents Jackson Lincoln and Kennedy tried to rest control of this country away from the bankers by printing
US dollars without charging taxpayers interest
But as you can imagine messing with the bankers can often be a dangerous move
I'm Jodie Paulson and I just thought you should know
Well, I think that should be a podcast all by itself what they don't tell you Jodie Paulson excellent stuff
I opening stuff and I wish I fully understood what was going on
But sounds like we're getting
Sold a whole bunch crap by whole bunch bankers including some other focus from Amsterdam the warberg bank of Amsterdam
And also interesting to hear that even Kennedy tried to wrestle that away from the bankers and
Printed money without charging the taxpayers. I mean
It's some pretty heavy and heavy stuff
So if you've got an opinion on that of course, this is only one side of the story. I'm sure
There's probably lots of wonderful things that central banking is brought to us, but it sounds kind of weird
You know if that really isn't the constitution it says that that can't happen then I quite sure how it happened
You know that again lots of weird things happen look at a rack
So we're now at our 40-minute threshold. I'm just gonna keep going because I'm about three quarters of the way through my list
And I just want to get everything done. Maybe I'll play a whole bunch of promos one after another
That I've been saving up and just haven't had time to get to
I've also continued to maintain sound seeing tours dot com if you go to that site that is actually a feed burner
RSS feed so you'll see like
The listing of the sound seeing tours and whole bunch of other crap on the page
Really just want to stick that into your aggregator or your iPod or soundseeing tours dot com and and it should bring up
It should bring up the the sound seeing tour feed I've been adding to to this feed
Really with only the best stuff that I've got in fact I just added bicycle marks tour of the red light district and absolutely hilarious
But there's a beautiful sound seeing tour
combo
Called on the wing and it's a husband. I think it's husband and wife and they go around different to a parts of the UK and do some sound seeing
I just want to play a little bit of this Kent ponds sound sound seeing tour because they did something really nice
They split up the audio channels left and right and
The quality is just a step David Dawson with on the wing my wife Gail and I recently visited the green river natural resources area south of Seattle better known as Kent ponds
Great to hear it up there. I know how does that sound
It's
It's Sunday, January 30th
We're at Kent ponds
Is something a raptor flying low a raptor
Wait a raptor? Are they in Jurassic Park on the street now? We're just walking down that
So anyway, that's you can find that it's sound seeing tours.com, but you got the idea right it's really intimate
It's left and right and it really trips with your brain when you're listening to that on the on the iPod
Or your MP3 headphones a little ear buds
more
information about
My blind typing quest
Let's see Andrew says tape a
She to paper along the top of the keyboard drape it over your hands
See that that apparently works. I've been trying several of the
I'm getting better. I find that just forcing myself to look at the screen my fingers pretty much know where all the keys are
But you know, I still occasionally hit the X instead of the C and stuff like that and of course said the T instead of the Y because I've got like
Uncoordinated fingers and
Here you go shopman who we've spoken about many times before who is one of the pioneers in coming up with audio routing to record podcasts on the Mac
for an audio recording console
Has has really done it again. He's come up with a way. You know, I was complaining about being able to
Set up my microphone with a chain of effects and then separately set up
Audio tracks with a chain of effects. Well, yeah, you go did it again. I actually have to open this
This I haven't opened all of these files yet. Let me see if I can get to his oh here he is here's Hugo's
hijack set up message
Adam
This is who close up mum or you go shopping you go shopping you're speaking people
I have to whisper a bit because there's somebody sleeping in the next room
All right
a comment about the use of audio hijack pro
I've been playing around with that a little bit and
testing latency and
getting into all kinds of details
Which I'm intending to write up on my website
log.yugoshotman.com
I'm not using the
Voice over effect that you're using or that you described in your last podcast
I have a different set up and I've actually described it on my site and also in the test recording that I
I'm sending you the link to and I will also put the link on the website
Um, I can totally help you out with
In conjunction with the guys at a rogue or me, but if you want because I've been doing all kinds of
pretty technical tests and
So let me know and
Keep up to good work
Now Hugo, thank you you keep up the good work he's been in this conversation it's been ongoing
Dawn and Drew were in it. I'm in it. I think oh Michael gohagan is in it
Why man let me just check that because there's an email he only see who else was copied
Oh Dave Slushart right. I'm sorry. Now we could copy Michael on it
Anyway, it's a big a big Mac community using audio hijack pro and we're now talking to one of the
Creators of the of the software
Quentin and Hugo is really leading this charge it being a great guide through all the technical stuff
So that we could really start to explain what we're looking for and I think we're making headway
Because I really do love this company. I think they're making some great software
I use it every single day and just want to be able to use it in even better ways that are more suited towards the way I create a podcast
Which of course is by no means set in law as the definitive way to do it
So I'll keep keep you posted on that if you want all the details of Hugo set up
You can find that in the show notes at daily source code dot com
Hello Adam and all the daily source code listeners. This is John on from online podcast and yes online is spelled
oh and g
L i any
I like to wish you Adam and all the daily source code listeners are very prosperous and happy Chinese new year
The year of the rooster
Especially if you're Chinese or if you're celebrating the luda calendar new year
Go with tikton
Siwang Jingjidian
He will eat a lot of how you
Wait a minute wait a minute wait a minute
You know you know that what he's doing right now is saying Adam carries an incredible dickhead in Chinese or Mandarin
You know that that's not just saying happy new year
Go hit that toy
Dike Dile
So if you understood me any of the languages above English included
You are qualified to listen to my show. So go over to online dot john on dot com and check out my podcast
And that's ong li and e dot jho and g dot com
Thanks again Adam for being the source of inspiration and motivation for me to start my own show
By the way, I'm addicted to your daily source code
It's yeah, and that's see you in that breed. Bye. I want some boy or ong and Mandarin
Actually, thank you very much. What do they mention there's a brand new
Indy feed podcast feed for punk punk music and of course
That is listed in the show notes as well and it's on ipod.org the definitive
Resource for you to go and find all of your new podcasts
I had them. This is Rob from podcast 411
I do a podcast why interview other podcasters
Each show I pick one podcast and we interview the people that are involved with that podcast
To find out a little bit about what they learn doing podcasts some technical information their history of computers and then about their podcast in general
I think you'll really enjoy the show some recent interviews
Ken and Cindy from the Ken and squip show Chris from the daily download
CC Chapman from reality bitch lab radio and from eat feed and many others
So check it out www dot podcast 411 dot com and remember to listen different all right listen different
Ooh and a slogan like that the satellite bandwidth continued
Rob Frieden
Who is actually I we've talked about him Penn St. University he pioneers chair and
He's the pioneers chair and professor of telecommunications god. I love having these people listen to the show
Makes me feel so incredibly smart
Thanks for mention my email response your questions about satellite capacity as your questions about digital audio satellite
Examine series channel bit rates here some links of course those provided in the email that I posted
Also an economist article about it, but the unconfirmed view yet is that as so far as that each channel uses
16 to 32 kilobits per second, which is nothing
And I think that's I guess the 16 kbps is and we went its mono probably in 32 if they're doing stereo
But that is nothing man, so I think it's the AAC compression that they're using
Now of course it's not what was widely adopted as MP3, but there's some real validity to this format
That we should be looking into
And I wonder
What popular MP3 players do not
Support AAC and it's it's pretty easy to come up with lists. I guess which because a lot of them do, but which key ones did not
So the I river does that support it?
Excuse me. Oh, that was rank
Creative labs don't know
The iPod does support it. I just like to know you know check it out see if you're
MP3 player if it supports AAC files if it doesn't let me know it's interesting
Maybe we should start providing AAC files certainly will help on bandwidth constraints because it does create an actual smaller file size
But I'm amazed I'm amazed by the 32 kbps. That's that's actually I think that's uh
I think that's actually quite impressive those bit rates
Big fan of the source code been listening for a while and uh
I have a question for you about OPML. All right. I know you've heard you talk about this in the past and you know a lot of the other podcasters talk a lot about OPML
And
Never really quite understood what it was until I was listening to your source code
From Thursday where you were talking about how the iPod or directory is maintained and
It really started it really hit me as you were talking about it that it sounds like OPML is kind of like the RSS
of links
But I get a sense that it could be a little bit more so
Maybe you could talk a little bit more about that correct me if I'm wrong and
Keep up the good work. Love this show. Thanks. What I'd love to hear is a Dave Winner morning coffee notes about OPML because he of course is the creator of this format
Which is widely adopted amongst outliners and
Boy if anyone can answer that question is Dave so I'm gonna leave that up to him
The way I see OPML
Is or the way I use OPML perhaps a better a better way to explain it is
Well, first of all OPML stands for outline processor
Markup language so just like 18 mail stands for hypertext markup language
Or XML stands for extensible markup language the M and the L
our consistent outline processor
I guess we can talk about outliners
So you probably know what an outliner is it's something that is not taught in
As far as I know any European schooling system just the even the the art of outlining is not taught
Although we deal with outlines and outliners it every day life all over the place and I am a total outliner
Freak
I use my radio user land outline or for everything because it's just it's the way my brain operates. I love it
And Dave, you know
Totally it's turned me on to that with his software
And so the way I view OPML is it's a way to create XML
Without having to fucking know what you're doing all you have to do is create an outline document
And you know the software then outputs that in
Version of XML which of course can then be read by software and computers can do stuff with it very much like we're using the directory
So you know we don't have this huge complicated database or submission system or all this interesting
You know workflow that you can build for a
A resource like ipodder.org. It's just hey, you know, just maintain a list and that's what outlines usually are list of stuff
And and each list each entry the list has a link and that link is the link to the
RSS feed or the podcast feed of that particular show
And because it it's OPML, you know and you can create it in an outliner and then it's all
Consistent standardized XML which poops out of the back which then the directory software
I potted out org understands and can parse
It's it's used for many other things and I think a lot of the confusion if I just understood your question right
Is that it's also being used for something called
Reading lists or subscription lists in fact most iPodders and
Aggregators for weblog aggregators
We'll be able to either import an OPML file which is nothing more than a list of all your subscriptions with
The actual RSS file attached to it as as the link to each node and it also outputs
That same sort of list so it's again a standardized way of of coming up with subscriptions
But in reality, I think OPML is much much much more powerful than that
So maybe we're at a maybe just don't have enough examples of applications
Or it's almost like a marketing problem at this point to explain exactly
You know what can be done with OPML I think and this is the one of things
I you know I want to understand more I've been following Steve Gilmour's attention dot XML
Or what she just calls attention
And I'm not quite rocking everything yet, but
This all does somehow come together with
With routing information
Yeah, I think that's the best way to explain it routing information is standardized
XML like way
Okay, I'm now I'm getting into deep. I don't know. I hope Dave does an OPML morning coffee notes podcast because I think it's it's really needed
What we can do with this stuff and could I I feel a little stuck myself once in a while as to you know where we can push it on the directory side though
I'm very very very happy
Because people who want to maintain a note in the directory they send me emails. Hey, you know, I'd love to take care of that
What do I do and I just send them off to ipod.org slash
Documentation and it's all right there and usually within the same day sometimes today later they come back with an OPML file and say what here
It is you know just to copy the URL where I have this thing stored and boom they're a part of the directory
Okay, 56 minutes boy. This is I feel like I'm cheating almost you know I'm going way past my room
I regular 40 minutes, but I just want to get through all this stuff and and get everything
Getting out that I've been waiting to talk to you about
Oh, the young palette who is aren't number one guy for creating the hit test has a
Has a a page up where you can get the previous episodes number five is what we're up to today
We've been emailing back and forth of course. I want to him to get these hit tests up on their own
podcast feed as well
But right now there is an archive
Where you can find them and the URL obviously is listed in the show notes for today
All right
Young polette here
With another hit test
But first let me say that a lot of stuff is happening right now
Got a lot of great responses on the earlier hit tests and a lot of things are going on right now
First let me thank Kevin for his additional work
Some of the things he is making right now and already has made
Actually expected in a future hit test and also thanks go out to Tom Schuiting
You'll refer me to yesterday
He's already
made me and he's going to take some time to
Transfer a few air checks into MP3 formats. So I can use them more old bullshit radio
A lot of questions and comments about the sound processing about the set-up. I'm using
I'm not sure
I want to go into that right now
Because I think we have to watch out for the fact that this little item is
Transferring in a some into a podcast of its own. Yeah, a podcast
Now you're talking and I'm not sure that that is something that we want to do well
Young it's all up to you. I'm very happy any single time you want to challenge me with a hit test
I'm happy to do it. You are the original hit test guru. So feel free to do whatever you want
If you send them to me man, I'll certainly use him of course what it does do is it
It really puts a lot of other people into you know putting a thinking caps on and I have now
We're going to do trivia the big trivia on Thursday. I have one two three four five other different types of trivia
Test that I've received and I'm saving those up for for the Thursday trivia day
So maybe later about these things
Right now it's time for the hit test. All right. Are you ready?
This is number one
So Katrina in the way is walking on sunshine easy one
And number two
Manning their hauling notes
Oh kawanya
These are really
Number three
Uh, I know the song
Living in the box
Living in the box living in the box. I think and for the answers this is answer number one
Katrina in the way walking on sunshine
Yep
Mark got one right
Good answer number two
All in oats. This is man eater
And finally answer number three
Living in the box yeah, we're living in the box got it right on
This morning
I'm living in the box well that's it for today
Please keep sending feedback and air checks from Adam
So hit test that Jim in the other house
See you next time for another hit test by Adam
All right, thank you very much young pull-ins
All right hit test trivia dude
Oh, that's great. That's great
And of course, I'm receiving all of these these great new forms of trivia
Maybe that's what you should do young maybe you should make a a podcast of all different types of trivia
So not just your own but maybe you should be the the resource you know I make it certainly send you all this stuff that I'm that I'm getting
And I know I've mentioned on the on the weblog a couple times
But I'm really really really thoroughly enjoying the Gmail experience in fact
I have given up on my Mac email client given up on my Mac.com email
I'm exclusively using my Gmail account now one of the thousands that I was invited to open up again
I really appreciate everyone hook on me up there
Wow, I mean the way this functions and I'm not quite it must be some JavaScript or something
I don't know how it works, but you could turn on these keyboard shortcuts so if you want to you know open up a
You can actually use the J in the K keys which are pretty familiar for anyone who's used
Vi or pine or you know command line type editor or email client
To go up and down
In the in the list of emails
Then you hit oh to open it and hit y to archive it
Just art to reply you know, and it's it's fast, you know, it's like you just hit the our boom already you're in the reply box
You've probably seen it
So it's great it has this you know all the advantages of web bay system because all your email is somewhere else
It has the super mega advantage of being able to search your email
Through through the Google search engine and of course
I love the fact that you hit the forward slash which is the same in VI and that puts your cursor right in the search box
And it has so all those advantages without the disadvantages of having to use your mouse all the time
Just keep your hands on the keyboard you barely I'd like if there was one there's one key keyboard shortcut command that I'm missing
It's
To report spam so if if you open something up and it's spam there's a little button there that you have to press and it
Apparently a registers that type of email or whatever it is as spam and
And it gets rid of it from your from your inbox. I'm not quite sure what it I probably trashes it or something like that
But you still have to move your fingers off the key pad to a mouse or the touch pad to perform that function
Which I
Turns out I do that a lot it was funny Patricia
You know I hooked up with her laptop again, and she's she's been all over as you know we were looking at
I forget about that
She's no actually she was looking for something very specific. She was looking for
Handbags and she was having a real hard time finding which is looking for through Google and you know
I'm and I said how are you doing?
I'm on your computer stuff and she said you know, I feel like a total shit. She said I thought I opened up my email
And all I do is I just sit there and delete junk and shit that I don't want. You said there's very little
You know the signal to noise ratio is fucked up. She said I feel like I'm a tool. I'm just a
A junk mail deletion tool. Not a good experience. We got to get better at that
Okay, a couple more promos before I go today. We're already
Almost double our normal time my gosh. We will be punished severely
broadcasting from the middle of
No
Hey Russ, do you know who Adam Curry is?
No, I don't know who Adam Curry is. Well, he used to work for MTV when they played music on that
Can you believe that?
Long time ago. We're going to podcast now. We're at a national geek.blogspot.com
We're hoping to have a first episode up pretty soon. So yeah
So yeah, I'll send you a message when you have a first episode if you want to check that out
You need email us at national geek.gmail.com
If you want and thanks for playing this if you did and
If you have an idea of how to make money off of this type of stuff
Well send me a message because I don't really like to know
Hey vice versa buddy if you got any ideas send me a message
Adam Curry.com. Yeah, I really appreciate that one. Okay. Let's see what is
What do we have here? Hi Adam. This is Lance Love. I'll send you a radio show
Yeah, the day about iPodre clients and
Especially concerning the vacation mode you were saying that
That was a really good powder lemon version two will be coming up with a vacation mode
What do you can actually download?
There's just the most recent
Podcasts over the entire
Podcastman very beginning from whichever show just let you know I've been using a great new software program called playpod
It's actually open source in this free
It's a 0.3 is the version but I've used it quite often and it has
Type of
Feature that you're you're looking for
Anyways, you might want to give it a shot. You probably already know about it
Since you are the pod father
So again, enjoy your show keep it up by listening whenever I can which is almost every day
And talk to later bye all right. Thank you very much Lance. I think that was
Yeah, I've been noticing all these great new features that we're seeing and not just in the iPodres
But also in agregators themselves in fact, I'm a beta testing the net news wire
I think I told you about that
Which now supports podcasting and understands how to
Get a podcast onto your iTunes
I don't know if it works with anything else currently
I've always kind of been you know
Like I never really want to use any of the the client side agregators because I'm a one-paying
Agregator guy. I like one page that just has everything from you know with the new stories at the top just like a web log
All of it down to the older stories at the bottom and if you know
I don't want it to be like email where I have you know on the left-hand side
I've got all these podcast where all these
web logs I'm subscribed to and have to keep you know seeing
Just this number count grow and grow and grow on on each one like oh I have to go look at
You know
I've seen now go look at the New York Times because there's 15 new stories if I don't you know
I get this guilt feeling. I don't want any of that shit
I want it to go away. I don't want to have these big numbers of unred stuff and I figured out a way
To create a view and net news wire which gives me exactly that and it's it's quite good actually
Because you have you know the all the stuff at the top you can even have
The the actual descriptions or you know whatever is listed in each posting underneath each
Fuck it looks just like just like my my one my one pain aggregator
So pretty nice with the advantage that you just hit the right arrow key and it opens up a browser right in the
application with the with the page that you that you were looking at
And make it even cooler it integrates with the Mars edit so if you want to
Post something from the aggregator into your weblog it knows those two applications
Which come from the same company. I think it's ranchero software ranchero.com
Then they work together and I'm wondering
I'm yeah wondering
What how the development is going to move? You know we basically have three pieces. There's like the aggregation part
which
It's hard it's really hard and I see a lot of progress being made in aggregator land
I'm just only using this that news wires the one example
I know because I've really been using this for a week or two
Then of course there's the iPod or developments which are all about you know the media files and what I haven't seen yet is what I'd love to have in in my
iPod or any type of aggregator is the same thing that I have on my sky digital box
You know it's like how much of
X do we keep around so how either how big can all the podcasts be all together?
You know could it take up two gigs of space or
Maybe you can do that by individual podcasts so you know if you have more than three podcasts of
East radio for instance which are about half an hour in length
You know if you have if you're three or four behind you know then delete the the oldest one or something like that
So you don't have to continuously I find myself going in and cleaning up which by the way is a is a cool new feature
In the iPod or lemon which I test it a little bit there is a cleanup feature
But I want more of that automated just don't want have to think about it. You know if I missed off just like in the aggregator
Like my centralized aggregator after 12 hours it's gone
You know it scrolls off but that doesn't mean that I won't see that message again because if it's something that's it floats to the top right so you know a message about
Let's see what is something
For instance
The store the wired new story about
What is it it's titled a here comes bill hide your iPod so you know that's a story that even if I missed it from the wired RSS feed
You're gonna see it somewhere else because people point to it and it just keeps coming back
I like bad Mexican food and it's really simple
It's a real simple way of keeping track of stuff without the guilt of
My gosh, you know there's 15 unread messages in the wired feed. I better go check them out because I'm falling behind
You know
You turns out you don't it it comes back from different sources and different channels so maybe you miss it
Maybe you catch it 10 minutes later or 10 hours later, but you will find it eventually
So it's I think it if I'm just a much easier way of
Yeah, much easier way of dealing with information and boy am I am I amineering overload but
Right now with what net news wire does it deletes its articles after a day
In combination with my Gmail account. I'm getting a lot better at managing all my info
Diary of a podcast
February 14th
What do we got what do we got what do we got
bills
junk
rubbish
bills
magazine
I'm getting a sake
Nothing another year without a card
No cards no
Great stupid bloody thing you think somebody would send me something someone somewhere
Diary of a podcast
Coming soon to the Richard Vows radio show at wwww dot vows dot com
My name's habei and I bought a lily on this past cast that in the entire world
My show is a total mix of satoia a
political
Cabbage
Hello out of all chap. It's Harry's dad here
I'm just calling to tell you at the regular feature on podcast pool.com words of wisdom with Harry
Harry bless him appears to have a clips my a rather modest
Exposure
And he's writing the interest of mainly American women have to say
Start his yard that he's intellectual capacity
Let me show you what I'm talking about
Wait a minute show wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. What is that? Is that that? Let me hear that again
I'm just making sure I understood that right
It's wanting to throw themselves at his intellectual capacity
Let me show you what I'm in. I'll give you a couple of extra social merch
I'll whisper with habei
Well hello there are podcasts people. It's time for our regular feature words of wisdom with Harry and
Yeah, Harry and I were talking about Parliamentary sovereignty versus the European Union
And about the difficulty that they single European currencies facing at the moment
We're talking of course about the euro
And I was talking with Harry over the breakfast table saying to him Harry
I really am disconcerting young man about the single European currency
I can't ever see myself wanting to lose the British pound
You know it's been never centuries. What do you think? Well Harry strikes his chin and reply to his follows
My finger but instead never a blink wish a pound by a wolf is stinking to you
That's my finger
Why everybody
Britain should never relinquish the pound in favor of the stinking euro. I couldn't agree more
Okay, thanks very much indeed Adam
We look forward to seeing you on podcast Paul dot com
I seem probably podcast Harry dot com knowing him bless him. He's always trying to steal the line light
Stop pouring out your kids. Well, yeah, don't do that. Oh, that was pretty funny
Yeah, the euro Africa. It's not about the money man. It's not about the money. It's about the control and if you if you change the money then the next thing is the control
So I guess I kind of got agree, you know and by the way those those 50 p coins with all the all the
Different sides on it. It kind of cool. So I like I like the English money not wrong with that
I don't know shit about the economics of changing from the pound to the euro, but I'm quite sure
Having lived in two countries that converted to the euro
Belgium from the Frank and the Netherlands from the Gilder that they got fucked by the European Union
And there's more fucking to come with that constitution
Anyway, that's it for the source code an extra long double shot
In fact
Jeez almost exactly twice as long an hour and 15 minutes. Okay, that's it tomorrow
We'll have another regular source code for Monday. Thank y'all for listening as usual the common places to go
Leave your comments
our ad with curry dot com for regular email
MP3 feedback a Gmail dot com if you want to send an audio comment or anything with an empty free file attached
And of course check out the archives and all the brand new shows and the podcast feed a daily source code dot com
Hey y'all thanks for checking this out. Hope it wasn't too long. Maybe even
Use this on the
Monday morning extra special traffic commute
Instead of your Sunday evening go patriots. Take care everybody
Okay