Daily source code, episode 187
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear since radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
It's June 2nd 2005. Dammit's June already.
Everybody how you doing? It's Adam Curry back home.
It's right, I'm back at the cottage and the weather sucks of course.
What's always supposed to happen?
At the heat wave when I'm gone, I come back and it's dreary and gray and raining.
And just the way we love it.
It's what you'd expect from back home, isn't it?
Welcome to your daily source code.
Well plenty of stuff to catch up on today.
Of course it wasn't able to post a source code for it.
What was it the past?
Three days literally we had the Memorial Day weekend,
which was also a bank holiday here in the UK.
Which means that Christina's home.
She's off from school this week.
So we're going to be able to do some fun stuff, catch up a little bit.
We're actually planning on going to a play to show to London's West End,
which she of course didn't like the idea because it involves theatre and boring stuff, right?
I think we'll be able to convince her.
And I really must say it's nice to be back in front of the console with the familiar mixer.
Got my sound back, my microphone back, all the stuff that I can't take on the road.
I still got to come up with an even better portable set.
I still haven't been able to find it.
The most important part of the setup that I have now, I guess,
is the processing unit that I have in between the mixer and the recording device.
You know, that's my firewire drive crap and out.
I told you about that, that I bought another firewire drive.
That one's working much better.
Then these Lissie hard drives I have.
I've had so many Lissie external firewire drives fail.
It's unfunny.
And thing with Lissie is, you know, they'll tell you, hey, you know, they're kind of suck.
And, well, we'll replace it for you, but no, the data that's on the drive is what I really want.
Not a pleasant experience anyway, so the other drive is working well.
And hopefully we'll be able to get through the show with kind of everything hanging together.
I'm also doing the show standing up today.
I'm a little low on energy, and I've found that sometimes just standing by itself will give you,
you know, that little extra edge that'll make you feel a little bit more up.
It's been, see, yesterday I came home yesterday was Wednesday.
It was actually the flight wasn't bad.
It was nine and a half hours from San Francisco to London.
Flight left on time.
It was great. It was full, but not, you know, overly completely fully packed.
It was just nicely full.
And they feed you nicely on Virgin Virgin Lannick Airlines.
They keep coming up with snacks and plenty of drinks, you know, and you don't have to ask for it.
And if you do, then they'll be happy to help you out, so that was cool.
Although, man, nine and a half hours, you know, at a certain point,
I think that, and it's probably just, you know, it's just, it's all human, but my God.
Some people just let it rip, man, and the plane can really start to stank after a while.
It's so fucking disgusting.
And I understand that, you know, you're in the plane, and, you know, you're bloated.
You're not feeling, you're, you're rocking around.
It's five, six hundred miles an hour, you know, and you're eating food and drinking and whatever.
And so I understand that, once in a while, you may have to little, little, little gassascape, but please, you know,
get the fuck out of your seat and go to the bathroom and do it there where it belongs.
Jesus.
And it's guys, man.
Guys do that the most, and it's just, well, especially the guys sitting next to me.
I contemplated, given some of his own medicine, but decided, well, maybe I shouldn't do that,
because you never know what kind of bad shit you can run into in that case, right?
Okay.
We have a kid.
Mash up time.
Run DMC and a Reath of Franklin.
Rock steady in run-tiles on the source code.
Get the new kids with a feeling from the side side.
Sit yourself down in your car and take a ride.
And while you're moving in run-tiles, let's stay the day.
Let's go this way.
Let's go.
Let's go that way.
Let's go this way.
I don't care what it is, I don't care
I don't care what it is, I don't care what it is, I don't care
I don't care what it is, I don't care what it is, I don't care what it is, I don't care
Rock steady and runs house, a Reath at Franklin versus Rundee M.C.
Centos by Scott Petek has been sending in lots of cool mashups
If you have a mashup and believe me, I'd love to have more
responding, thank you very much, so if you haven't heard yet, just send it
off to mashup at podshow.com, same goes for promos, send it off to
Submit at podshow.com and that podsake music pod safe at podshow.com
I don't know what it is, it's like, you know, for some reason
it's got to be the LeC Firewire, because everything else is working, I've got the new tiger
OS10 release, which I'm actually pretty happy with, it runs very well
although there's a lot of conflicts now with the Apple Key Spacebar command
you've like this, now there are three basic processes fighting for that command, the first one
I was using this program called Launchbar, and Launchbar is pretty cool, I think the equivalent of windows
is called Hot Keys, where you basically issue a control, an Apple Key Spacebar command
you do those simultaneously, and then it pops up a little menu, you type in the first couple of words
or whatever you're looking for, first letters or whatever you're working for, looking for, so for instance,
if I was looking for audio hijack pro, I just type in audio, and it'll bring up a number of
different options, and it basically remembers what you select on certain point, you can get it down
to just the A, just type in an A, and it'll know, ah, he wants audio hijack pro.
It'll launch it when you hit Return, which is real fast way to get to your applications,
and it does the same for documents and shortcuts and email addresses, and you can configure that,
very nice application. Then Megaseg, which I've been using to record the source code
with, or basically to play back with by, you know, lining up all of the, all of the elements
and putting them, you know, in order that I want to plan back.
When you hit the Apple Key Spacebar, and when Megaseg is running, then basically it starts
the playlists, that doesn't work, or it actually it's segs to the next element, even worse.
And now Spotlight, which is Apple's fine feature in OS 10, uses the exact same command.
You can change that, but it's kind of disorienting the first time you figure it out.
And I like this Spotlight, because it works very much like Launchbar, but it doesn't seem as fast
and it also doesn't seem to remember the command. So, you know, if I search for, basically it's a search function,
so if I do audio hijack, or just audio, it'll bring up a whole bunch of different audio
search results, including what they call the top hit, which will usually be audio hijack pro,
but it seems like it still is searching every single time it's searching through your,
I guess it was on internal database, or whatever, trying to figure out what you want.
It doesn't really remember what you selected the last time you did that search.
So, it's a bit slower than Launchbar, but it does really get into everything, even PDF documents.
So, that's a pretty cool feature. I'm digging that. What else did I like about OS 10, I want to talk about?
Oh, yeah, the RSS of capabilities and safari. I'm kind of understanding how it works now.
Now, I'm a one-paying aggregator guy. I like to have all the news in a reverse chronological order,
so the most recent updates at the top and then just scroll all the way through, which Dave Winner calls it a river of news,
and I completely, you know, buy into that philosophy of that's the best way to parse all this,
instead of, you know, separated by feed and put it kind of like an email like client to view.
But there's, there's no way to import your subscription, so what you essentially have to do is take all of your,
your subscriptions, your bookmarks, really. You should be able to just drag an OPML file on it, with not be wonderful.
But you're not able to do that, so you have to take all your subscriptions, put them all into your bookmarks,
and then it'll go out and basically look at all of those, look at all those subscriptions,
you can set that to every half hour hour or a day or a week, whatever you want.
Excuse me. Do I need to tell you where the burps coming from? Do you think it's a sincere burp?
And it's working pretty good. I like the fact that you can expand or collapse how many lines of text are associated with each entry,
and I'm kind of playing with it still, so I was able to, through a clue, basically able to import all of my contacts,
all of my, my subscriptions, but it would be nice if they had some kind of OPML feature,
also an export would be nice, so you can take it out. But it is working, it's, yeah, it's pretty interesting.
Let's see, I got a lot to talk about. San Francisco, that's where we were, San Francisco and LA,
I basically the last half of our journey. I was going for 10 days, man. I'm so happy to be home,
happy to see the girls. It's nice to be back in, in the familiar environment, kind of get back into the swing of things.
But we had some great meetings in San Francisco with a variety of companies and institutions,
and a lot of people very excited to work with us on the commercialization of podcasting, as you know,
that's, that's entirely what we're doing, and there's going to be so much opportunity for everybody to,
to go along with this ride. It's going to be a lot of fun. So I'm looking forward to making some damn,
damn announcements in the, in the near future.
I wanted to thank all of the, man, I got so many emails and so much feedback about the ear buds
that I bought, the replacement earphones for my iPod.
And I'd gone out and I purchased the in ear buds from Apple and was very disappointed with, with the results.
First of all, it's kind of hard to stick it in your ear ear.
And yeah, and you really have to stick them all the way in your ear holes in order to get any kind of base.
Basically, otherwise it's, you know, it's all like high end, a little bit of mid-range sound.
It's just not shitty. And the, the most interesting comments that I got back were,
first of all, there's a, there's a way to insert these in ear ear buds.
And the way you do it is you have to lift your ear low up with one hand.
So, not your ear low, but your ear at the top of your ear.
And then open your mouth like you're going to yawn.
And then you stick the ear bud in and then you let go of your ear.
And then essentially it's in, in place.
And that does work, although it's kind of weird because you have to do it a couple times to reposition.
But the best advice came from Mad Weinstein.
She said I should go out and get the Sony in ear ear buds.
They come with three different sizes.
Because I know not everyone has the same earhole size, right?
And although they work even better probably with the ear trick, you can just kind of stick it in your ear.
And it works and those are really good.
And I'm digging those a lot.
Very comfortable. You can keep them in for a long time.
And they don't, you know, slip in or out or slip out basically.
And yeah, so those are pretty good.
Although it does have the behind the neck loop that we've discussed before.
So it doesn't, you know, the, the two sides of the earphones.
The earphones aren't of equal length, which means basically the wire doesn't go down the middle.
But it goes down one side.
So you, you know, the wire runs down the left hand side.
And then you bring the right hand ear, but around the back of your neck and plug it in.
Which has some advantages.
But I don't know, just this kind of like a, I guess kind of like a dyshockey thing that I've always wanted to have that.
Have it in the middle.
I like it hanging in the middle if you don't mind.
Hi Adam.
This is the Learn Out Loud.com audio learning or revolution.
Do you want to listen to a lecture from Harvard?
Do you want to listen to a history professor?
Talk about the Polyponetian War.
Do you want to listen to the speeches of Dr. Martin Luther King?
Do you want to learn the spiritual healing techniques of Deepak Chopper?
Any author, any publisher, anywhere, any time the resources are here.
We're going to teach you how to learn out loud.
Join the Revolution. Join it.
Learn Out Loud.com's audio learning revolution.
What do you want to learn today?
Fantastic kids, Adam Curry.
Adam, do you remember saying this about me?
The one that I promised you about that I think has a lot of promise.
And there's a lot of people who are totally into the Beatles.
The Beatles Dread of Hot Cast.
The new home of The Beatles.
I Adam, this is Mike Stewart.
The Beatles Dread of Hot Cast.com.
It's a new podcast that I'm launching because I am a certified Beatle Nut.
There's no more trivia than I care to tell anyone.
And I'm the guy that sent you that Beatles baseline trivia thing that you sing to enjoy.
But, you know, I didn't share it too well with it.
But hey, that's another story.
All Beatle Fans, all Beatle Nuts.
Go to my new podcast.
BeatlesTrivialPodcast.com.
Where we discuss the Beatles, their music.
You know, anything magical.
I interview people from all over the world that have either known the Beatles or been with the Beatles.
Or just people who love the Beatles.
One of my first shows that I've got a commitment to is Tommy Roe, who was a famous 60s artist
Buddy of mine from, you know, had dizzy and sweet pee and he tour.
He was the headliner and the Beatles were his warm-up act.
So we're going to have a 20-30 minute interview with Tommy.
Just talking about all the fun of that 1962 tour with Tommy and Chris Montez.
So check it out at BeatlesTrivialPodcast.com.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right on.
Very cool, actually.
Yeah, I sucked at the baseline trivia quiz.
We should bring that one out again.
See if I can't remember even though I know the answers by now.
No new hit test from Yon Polet.
So I guess he's busy in the rehabilitation.
I hope you had a chance to check out his hit test podcast where he goes into more depth about his condition.
And it's really, it's interesting.
And a very personal insight to Yon and everything that's going on with him.
And I hope everything's going well.
Yon look forward to more hit tests in the future.
He does have connectivity now.
Thank goodness.
So he's able to hop on Skype and email, etc.
Another thing, flying back on Virgin.
Yeah, it's hard for me to sleep on the plane.
I used to be able to do much better.
I don't know what it is, but I just can't sleep as long or as well as I used to.
I think it has something to do with the recline.
The seats just don't recline as far as they used to.
And if they went back just a little bit further would be okay.
But so I watched a lot of movies.
Virgin has an excellent in-seat movie system.
It must be 60 movies and television shows.
You can watch all the willing grace episodes from front to back.
Hello.
Ah!
Thank you, Hun.
What's that?
Yeah, I know it's food.
Thank you.
Oh, like her.
It's what do we have?
Chicken salad.
And...
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's not chicken that's salmon.
And fresh tuna.
Tuna salad.
Thank you.
See what I mean?
It's great to be back home.
Oh, yes.
So I check out a couple movies.
And I don't know how often they update them.
How often they refresh them.
It seems like I've seen most of them, or at least the ones I wanted to see.
So the next trip over, which undoubtedly will be in three weeks from now.
If not even less, I will...
Oh, yeah.
No, it'll be three weeks from now.
Because I'm going to nomdex.
Right.
That's the 23rd through 25th of June.
And it's June already.
How did that happen?
I watched this movie called Team America.
I don't know if you've heard of this.
And of course I'll put a link to it in the show notes.
But it's essentially, it's a movie with puppets,
done with puppets, really on strings.
But it's hard to see how they did it.
And I'm not on the screen, of course, in the seat back.
It doesn't make it much easier.
But it's part animated, part puppeteering.
But it's really, really...
It's a very satirical look at the United States being the police force of the world.
And Hollywood's involvement.
They have this funny bit where Alec Baldwin is the...
You know, he's going to change the world.
He's going to, you know, he's leading all actors in Hollywood.
And they're all members of the film Actors Guild.
So everywhere there's this big F-A-G or Fag logo,
whenever you see Alec Baldwin.
And there was a lot of irony, a lot of humor in it.
So it's probably out on DVD.
So I should definitely check that out.
Very, very cool.
And the big news came earlier this week.
After the French voted no in the referendum
for ratifying the European Constitution,
the Dutch did the same.
High turnout almost 70% turnout,
which is very large for the Netherlands.
Usually they don't do any better than 35%.
And 63% I believe of the Dutch vote in the referendum,
said no, we don't want to ratify the European Constitution.
I've had some time to think about it.
And had some time to read through many different newspapers.
And it's hard to form an opinion
because for every single country,
I think the reasons for voting, whatever they vote, are different.
First of all, I think there's a misnomer
here in calling it a constitution,
where yes, I actually actually look
of the definition of constitution.
But you'd expect this kind of like the US constitution.
And a lot of that stuff is in there.
Freedom's right to work.
And, you know, etc.
Across border, commercialization, trade,
all those types of things.
But it is a 450-page document.
And a lot is just very, very difficult to parse.
And it kind of looks like it's, I think,
well, let's just call that the main problem.
I think, well, I can only speak for the Netherlands really
because I live there for, you know,
the past four and a half, almost five years.
They did a bad job at explaining to the public
what this is and what it's about and what the benefits
will be or what the potential drawbacks could be.
And I think that the no vote really comes from an incredible
dissatisfaction from the general populace and the Netherlands
about their government.
The way the Dutch elections, the previous elections
worked, the basically the labor party,
had the most votes.
But they weren't able to form a coalition with other partners.
So, in effect, they became the opposition
and which is kind of twisted.
You know, the party that had the most votes,
it's a multiple party system, not to,
but really they have 10 or a god knows,
15 parties it seems like.
They weren't able to form a large enough coalition.
So, the party that the most votes went to is the opposition.
And I think that that really rub the lot of people
the wrong way and that this is much more protest against
their own government than against
the ratification of the constitution.
And I really don't think people understand what it is.
Quite honestly, I don't understand what it is.
I like to be educated before forming an opinion.
And I've really tried, you know,
I've gone through this document.
I've posted a link to it.
I'll do it again in the show notes.
You can take a look at it.
It's tough, you know.
And it's, I mean, the whole thing becomes
convoluted just knowing that the European Parliament
changes locales.
What does it every month or every couple of weeks?
They go from Brussels to Luxembourg.
And then they go, you know, so they have dual offices.
And, you know, who's responsible for what?
It's really, really complicated.
So it's going to be interesting to see what happens now.
You see the financial times in one second.
I just think that the financial times
is what I like to read over here.
Europe and turmoil is the Dutch vote.
No.
Here, massive 62% echo French and rejecting treaty.
So now it's going to be interesting to see what's going to happen.
Sure, rock will probably come out and say something.
He may step down or it's just tough, you know.
In essence, I guess the governments don't have to follow
the advice of the population, what they vote,
but it seems like they would have to take some kind of note.
And Holland is just angry.
That's what I see there.
Just really angry about what's what's been happening in their country.
Of course, they blame it on their government.
But at the same time, I have to say,
this country gets the government it deserves.
And maybe there should have come out
in more numbers to vote when voting for a government
instead of this probably reactionary move
against the ratification of the constitution.
But it is kind of interesting to see this little
pimple on the ass of Europe, this small country,
17 million people live there, land mass smaller than Rhode Island.
You know, making a big difference in this whole game.
And it is a game.
That much I know for sure.
Hello, everyone.
This is Madge Weinstein.
Your favorite lesbian on the internet.
And I want to tell you to try my newest
channel on the internet.
Like BBC 2, I have a second channel.
And it's called yeast2.com.
And it's different from regular flavoured yeast
because you get to hear
a mishmosh of different electronic hunt.
And all kinds of bizarre sounds you get to hear.
Children playing, noise, music,
freaky, Dutch queens going on and on
about non-existent pressets.
You get to hear all kinds of very strange things
and best of all.
You, gent audience, can submit your own programs to yeast2.
As long as they're very weird and hard to stir things.
So, serve to yeast2.com.
Okay, Madge, as long as they're disturbing.
And it's not your regularly flavoured yeast.
Another fine line in that promo.
Need more promo.
Send them off.
I'm happy to play him.
Not just on the daily source code,
but on the pod show on serious as well,
which is doing great.
The feedback is enormous.
And people are really, really getting into it
and starting to send in their own podcast or at least
recordings and asking how they can set up a podcast.
And we're going to integrate our production systems
in the next couple of weeks,
so that we'll actually be able to take
ID3 information from promos and podcasts
that we put on pod show and stream them right
through to the display of the satellite receiver,
which is a really a big part of what
the information series gives you,
can't flows through that display.
And I think they have multiple line displays
on most of the units I've seen.
So, this is, I guess, another plea
to get better information in the ID3 tags.
I know there's still a lot of confusion about
what goes where.
I've posted a couple of links to some really good suggestions.
Whatever you do, just please put it in there.
We need that information.
And of course, we're building up a little bit of editorial
staff so we can add more information.
So when you, you know, if you're driving in your car
and you flip on the pod show on the serious
148, it's every afternoon between
6 and 10 Eastern 3 and 7 Pacific,
you know, that you can, if you fall right in the middle of,
for instance, or what do we play the other?
Well, for instance, Mad Weinstein,
use radio.
At least the display will give you some context
and some information because, you know,
unlike the, you know, the radio,
the radio me where you determine where you want to play
something on serious, it's all linear.
So it just kind of rolls out, which is a great way to,
you know, just use your driving time to pick up on stuff,
which is why I like getting a lot of promos
and the more information you can put in the ID
three tags, the better.
And, and basically, a shorter pod cast
longer promos, you know, that, that seems to work best.
So send it off to submit at podshow.com
and I'll be happy to drop it into the show.
Hello there Adam.
This is Paul Nichols Podcast Paul.
Thanks for playing the promo.
And you can hear up the dance register
just on my voice.
There are new bands featuring on my new site.
Unsigned UK Music.com.
It's pod sake music of the highest session standard quality,
that's specifically hand picked.
I'm able to try to syndicate as many of these good groups
as possible around pod cast stations.
And no revenue is made from the site.
This is just to keep glory back
to some fantastic musicians.
Please check the site out.
Dynamo is with the main series.
Up for the dance track.
Currently figure.
And as I say, you're very welcome
to download the teaser tracks
and to use them in your podcast.
Thanks very much for checking them out.
Thanks again.
That's podcast Paul.
My buddy here in the UK promoting the British pod save you succeed.
Fucking fire wire.
Damn it.
Hmm.
Sorry.
Oh man, that's salmon.
It's good.
I love it.
I don't have to say.
Oh yeah.
I was interviewed by Rob over at podcast 4011.com.
It's an interesting guy.
He gave up his job.
He quit his job.
And he, as he says, he's leech it off the wife.
Power to you, my brother.
And he's dedicated himself entirely to pod casting.
And he's doing a fantastic job covering.
Everything is going on in pod casting.
Check my podcast 4011.com.
Did an interview with me the other day,
which he's actually split up in the two parts.
Sounded great.
I'll just listen to it.
And it's because of the first time I heard of podcast 4011
was when he interviewed John Edwards about his podcast,
which I just saw the latest addition of that come through.
I haven't listened to it yet.
But, and I think he's not also working on getting
another couple other really big names on his show.
So looking forward to that, something you should definitely
consider subscribing to.
Let's see what else I have.
Well, I think that's pretty much it.
I have a couple more promos and some pod save music.
Let me play one more promo and then we'll get to the music.
I'm going to get twisted.
Don't be a star, be part of the moment.
Don't allow you to admit it.
Two brothers across the continent.
They stood down down.
And you're way over there.
Don't stop.
That way.
Where do you want?
And the opposite.
What?
Hi Adam.
Did you know that in some tribes in Africa,
when two men greet each other instead of shaking their hands,
they shake each other's penises.
Which it splines the origin of the phrase,
hey Bob, how's it hanging?
What's they got to do with me?
Nothing at all.
But come to my side anyway.
Twist it little gnome.com.
Where a young site.
We're just starting up.
But we already got quite a few little podcast on there.
Come and check us out.
Twist it little gnome.
Yeah.
Daddy.
Okay.
Snapper Morgan there.
Twisted little.
What is it?
Twisted little gnome?
Did I say that right?
I love it.
Fantastic.
Okay.
So tomorrow, I'll have everything a little bit more together.
I'm still catching up on email.
Yeah.
We're about at 5,000 unread messages.
God has driving me nuts.
I just don't want to keep up with it.
75% now filled with my Gmail allocation.
Two gigabytes.
I believe me.
It's not just attachments.
It's just, well, it's still a lot of spam.
That comes in waves too.
It really does.
So for the next couple of weeks, I'll be home.
Looking forward to catching up with y'all.
Please.
You know what?
I haven't gotten in a long time.
Some audio feedback.
I'd love to have that.
So you can always send that to me at adamatcurry.com.
And again, well, you'll see on the show notes where if you want to submit stuff.
But we're always looking for great pod safe music for mashups.
And of course, the promo's pod safe music now.
This is from a group called Up for the Downstroke.
I love it as feeling side.
Nice and mellow for a Thursday on your source code.
You know where it's true, but you're trying to hide.
You turned that love like a thrilling man.
And you can't give what you never had.
My flesh's my soul.
You can follow you.
I know the truth.
You can follow me at the bottom.
Being chugged.
Being chuhled.
Being suction.
You can pretend there's nothing wrong
Girl, I look in your eyes and see you can
So while I stop trying to run behind
You won't bite out if you never try
Girl, I look in your eyes and see you can
So while I stop trying to run behind
You won't bite out if you never try
Girl, I look in your eyes
Girl, I look in your eyes and see you can
So while I stop trying to run behind
You won't bite out if you never try
Girl, I look in your eyes and see you can
So while I stop trying to run behind
You won't bite out if you never try
Girl, I look in your eyes and see you can
Girl, I look in your eyes
I don't know, it's kind of a Donald Fagan vibe too
On the daily source code, up for the downstroke, it is deep
Feet, I'm sorry, feel inside
That's the type, of course, all the information about that in the show notes
And that'll wrap it up for today's source code
What we do?
About half an hour, not bad
Again, shorter podcast, longer promo, that's what we're going for
Also, great news about cast blasts are up to beta number
Thirteen already, that means public release coming soon
I'm going to get back into that
Being on the west coast with basically nine hours
Time difference between
Development team and myself was a little bit complicated
I can't wait to get back into that
About to load version 13 on the craplet
Give that a whirl, so maybe I'll do tomorrow's source code from
Cast Blaster
And then I got to talk to Mike
Cast Blaster, Mike is we affectionately call him
And see if he's ready to do a wider public release of the first version
I think it'd be very cool, I'm excited
Feet back out of accurry.com
Comments can be left on my weblog www.curry.com
Cast Feed for the show notes and for the archives of the daily source code
Head and over to dailysourcecode.com
Audio feedback is welcome
Still looking for the perfect theme song
And I want one of those that match Weinstein has
I want a song
Adam McCurray.com is the address for that
So tomorrow the thank god of Friday edition
Maybe I'll be able to convince Patricia to do
Another PPP podcast with me this weekend
Which I think will be cool
Place some more of her tunes and have a little fun
Catch up with my wife, you guys can listen in
Thanks for tuning in, thanks for staying subscribed, take care