I'll ready hello everybody. It's another weekend edition of the Daily Source Code, which of course means it's not a daily source code. It is time for the MTV Chronicles. Part 3. Is that it Ken? Part 2.
Part 2. Part 2. On the Skype from Lovely Portland, Oregon, is my friend and colleague and MTV
expert at Fissionado extraordinaire, Kenster J. How are you doing?
Hello, I'm fine. It's actually a beautiful day here in Portland.
It really sucks here in Gilford. We've had high winds, gale force winds, cold, wet weather.
That's good for us though, because you'd be out flying. We're not for the follow weather, wouldn't you?
In fact, yes, I was, you're right. I was scheduled to have a whole weekend of instruction, but the wind commander said,
he said, Monday, he said, nah, it's going to be shit weather. You don't want to do that.
How about you know that? It's just a shit or inclement.
No shit. No inclement weather is fine. That's not a problem. It's not a problem.
I mean, it's not a problem to fly. It's just when it comes to instructions, not it's not very handy.
Well, you know, they say flying is safer than driving.
No, what they say is the most dangerous part of your trip is the drive to the airport.
That's what it is. So the last time we did this, um, Jesus, it's been like, what has it been?
Ken, more than six weeks or something like that, I guess. Maybe in longer since we've done a MTV
Chromome where around the holidays.
Christ, I was in Utrecht. Was that the one or do we do another one after that?
No, I was in Uren, you're in that place. Yes, that place. Utrecht. Right. I was with my mom.
You're in Utrecht. Yeah, Utrecht. Yes, correct. Correct.
So this is the MTV Chronicles. This is where Ken and I bring up old MTV memories, kind of like bad Mexican food.
Uh, we regurgitate. Ken worked there for Ken, how many years? 10 years.
10 years. I worked there for seven and a half, something like that.
Well, approximately that. I have the exact date you started here as to the exact date you resigned on the air.
I don't have that. I know what the exact date. I started on Halloween, uh, 1987.
October 31. Yep. Well, actually, they, they claim October 30th, but American born Adam Curry.
Where's this? Where are you reading this from?
I found a 10 year MTV timeline covering 1981 to 1990 on those put out by the press department on their 10th anniversary.
Oh, really? It's pretty much a blow by blow of all the big events.
October 30th, 1987, American born Adam Curry.
Uh, Europe's most popular TV and radio personality for three consecutive years, debut as MTV VJ.
And one month later, remote control was launched. Oh, that's right.
I'll never forget in that first week, um, they took me up to the offices and people should know that the production and the,
the corporate side were very, very separated at the time. I don't know if it's still,
even because they aren't they all in the same building.
It's all in the same building now. So I don't think they can possibly have that delightful separation that we had.
Yeah. So what, so they have to wang the scripts down.
Remember that kid? They would throw some PA in a, in a community car.
You come to script over with this script.
We're late, we're, we're blowing 20 grand an hour on, on crew because we're, our scripts are stuck in a town car in mid, down Manhattan.
Hey, can't, are you downloading porn again? Cause you're cutting out once in a while.
I, I moved my head. Maybe that's the problem.
No, I'm getting a little bit of, you know, a little bit of a, a little bit of a, a little bit of a.
No, I think unfortunately, that's the Skype issue.
Well, no, it's not Skype. It's a bandwidth issue. I'm also sitting on the backup DSL because British telecom fucked up again.
And they've severed my line. Yeah, they severed my, my fat pipe.
Has it severed it? Well, I don't know. It's like, you know, I, so I call up my provider.
You know, I have this four megabit pipe, which is really nice.
And then they say, well, you know, it looks like DT is, because it's, it's,
you know, the actual line that comes into the house is provided by British telecom. And of course, British telecom says,
No, it looks fine. No problems here.
Yeah, and so then the woman called up and says, well, we're going to send an engineer out.
Are there any security issues we need to be aware of? I said, yes, make sure he's wearing that.
Best of suit, a lead helmet.
Stop winding me up, sir.
So needless to say, we still have a delicious pets here.
Yeah, exactly. Very, beware of the vicious pets.
So, but I'll never forget that first, that first week, then they took me up to the offices.
You know, you go around to meet everybody. And then I sat down with the press department.
And they, and I'm sure you're going to remember this.
And then they, you know, they lined up a couple of calls.
One of which was to TV guide.
Do you remember what happened?
No.
So they asked me all kinds of questions. And they said,
So, you know, what do you think about Madonna? And I said, ah, she's kind of bitchy.
That was being honest. You know, I'd met her a couple times.
She's not one of my favorite people. You know, like her music, but she's kind of bitchy.
And they freaked out.
Oh, I was just going to say, I can just picture Tina Exoros and Cheryl Jones.
The press scales just fallen on the floor.
Oh, yeah, because that was the one thing you could not do.
You could not talk negative about any of the artists that we played.
Which God forbid.
Yeah, I mean, please be fake and lie about everything.
Which I did for successfully almost for seven, half years.
Well, you know, there were there were clips and bands that we liked.
You know, we didn't get to pick the videos.
You never had to say in what you got to play.
And you had to be as upbeat about the bad stuff as you did about the good stuff.
Although we didn't, you and I were both in the music meetings for quite a while.
Yeah, we were for quite a while.
Which was interesting.
I don't know if you lasted longer than I did or if I lasted longer than you did.
I stormed out of what and never went back over a clip.
They refused to play.
It was a fabulous clip.
It hadn't charted in the, you know, the top 40 R and R or whatever the hell they were looking in.
Yeah.
So they wouldn't play it.
And that was so counter to anything that had ever made MTV great.
I mean, MTV became great because they played stuff.
The known else would play.
And I said here, watching people consulting the billboard to.
Yeah.
Radio writer charted in top 40 radio before they'd even consider it.
I just was disgusted.
No, I walked out after, um, I didn't walk out.
I didn't go back after, um, uh, member Abby Conowitch.
Yes.
He was the director of, was he director of music program or something like that?
And hired a Matt Farber.
Right.
And so Abby is a, he's a guy, by the way, or that is questionable perhaps.
But then he went on to run Madonna's Maverick record label.
But so I'll never forget the meeting was almost over.
I think you were still in that meeting, can't.
Oh, no. Oh, we can't leave yet because we haven't added anything from Warner Brothers yet.
I was like, what the fuck?
So this has nothing to do with the music.
It's only about we haven't played political footsies properly.
So I didn't go back.
Oh, yeah.
You had to play a certain number of clips.
You know, and if you wanted to get an exclusive on the new motley crib clip,
the motley crew clip, then you had to play two pieces or crap at least three times a week.
Oh, and we put them in the, that's, that's how the, wasn't that how the basement bin was, um,
was created.
Something like the buzz bin.
The buzz bin basement bin.
The buzz bin.
That's, it was like, it would, if you were in the buzz bin, that meant your rotation was,
you were played once at 3 a.m.
Once a week at 3 a.m.
Like, was that the buzz bin or was the buzz bin for the hot clip of the week?
I can't remember all the various tags now.
I think they might have, they might have changed it later.
But I remember specifically people say, yeah, well, well, well, well, yeah, well,
they will throw them in the, well, throw those clips in the buzz bin if we can get them exclusive on this.
Yeah, that was through a clock in the morning.
That, that was always the best time to watch the channel because that's when they played the weird stuff right on right on.
Also in 1987, I MTV launched it.
No, Australia.
Richard Wilkins.
Yep.
Kevin.
See you'll join.
Club MTV debuted.
My God.
Right before you started the same month you started MTV's week in rock debuted.
I used to love doing that show.
Remember when the VJs would, would host it.
Yeah.
Well, Kurt came the year after.
So for just a period of time for one year, you guys actually got to host something news related and then they got Kurt.
It was a great.
I really liked doing that show.
That was a lot of fun.
Now did you do?
No, this was right before you joined MTV.
Did the motley crews, the motley crews to know where contest?
I wasn't a part of that.
Four winners were flown to Bermuda where they boarded a private yacht and went on a cruise of the Bermuda triangle with the four guys in motley crew.
There's not forts and enough to be a part of that.
Well, you may have been luck.
He frankly, can you imagine?
And that was after the pink houses.
Yes, it was.
But it was, yeah, it was the next year that Kurt Loder left Rolling Stone magazine to join MTV.
He's still there.
Dude, how old is Kurt 60?
He's got to be older than 60.
I really don't know.
He doesn't look like he's changed at all, but I please.
Please.
He always looked kind of tired, but you know, Kurt was always out of lot.
You know, scooping, scooping those news stories.
Oh, yeah, right.
Well, John Norse is still there, too, right?
He finally got what he wanted.
John is still there.
Well, when I was the John, I got a John started as a production assistant and then
If I could fuck this way to the top.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
I can't comment about that.
I wasn't certainly involved or privy to any details of that.
But I don't know it.
I don't have positive proof, but he always was such a jealous little queen.
That's what he was.
He just wanted.
Yes.
That's my, that's what I was doing.
Back on my overall experience with John over the years.
It's neither overly positive nor overly negative.
He was relatively easy to deal with from my perspective.
But he had been in staffer.
So he never, he never kind of got difficult.
Then you weren't that difficulty, but you know, you drove yourself to the studio.
And yeah, I didn't, I didn't want to have no forgot damn cars.
Take, pick him up.
That's a paid in the ass.
You picked your clothes.
Patricia did your makeup.
So when you walked in the door, you were ready to go.
And there were a lot of premedonists that required hours of maintenance.
And, you know, yeah.
But I was John was, John was never one of those.
He never, you know, if he didn't play games like that with me.
So you did some homework for the show, right?
You, you prep some stuff right there.
A few different things.
Speaking of news, there are two people that we worked with at MTV over the years that are both doing quite well for themselves here in the States.
I don't know if they're on in Europe.
Karen Bryan, two is one of the VJs that was kind of the third group of VJs after you and Julie and Kevin.
But she, what she was also news first.
She was in Karen Bryan was news first, wasn't she?
No, that was Allison Stewart.
Oh, Allison Stewart.
I'm sorry, right.
Karen Bryan.
And that was the other person.
Karen Bryan came in as a VJ.
She was a, she looked a lot like Allison Stewart actually.
And the two had known each other.
They had gone to college together at Brown.
Gorgeous black girl, light skin, curly hair.
Very, very similar to Allison Stewart.
I don't remember how that she looked like.
Because we hired after that whole next wave.
Then you were just kind of doing the top 20 video countdown and dial MTV.
But mostly you predecessor to TRL.
Right.
You would come in once we can do the top 20 countdown.
And they had Karen Bryan and Steve Isaacs.
Oh, my gosh.
Steve Isaacs.
Who else was in that batch?
Kennedy.
Let's see.
It was Steve.
Karen Bryan.
Kennedy.
Duff.
John Norris.
Todd.
One was a VJ for a while during that whole thing.
But Karen Bryan was in that third batch of VJs.
And she is now the entertainment watch reporter on CNN.
Hold on.
I'm Googling her right now.
I want to get a picture of her.
K-A-R-Y-N.
Oh, that's why that's why it's showing some horrible images.
Bryan, B-R-Y-A-N-T-I.
Would you end up with it?
You don't want to know.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Did she very cute?
There you go.
Yeah.
I remember her now.
Okay.
Yeah.
I didn't really ever hang out with her.
I don't think.
No.
Because at that point you were coming in once a week.
Right.
And Allison Stewart, who was Steve Leads assistant.
Assistant.
Right.
When you started it, and then Allison went to the news department and did pretty well
with them, TV news.
She did a lot of the choose or lose.
She used to do a lot of the political.
She was good.
campaign coverage.
Yeah.
She's been doing daytime anchor on MSNBC here in the States now.
Right.
Quite a period of time.
She fills in a lot at night.
I'm countdown with Keith Obermann on NBC.
Okay.
So those are two.
Too bad MSNBC is going to shut down.
Well.
Seeing that, you know, it's funny.
For a while MSNBC was really kick and CNN's button out for the last couple of years.
That's kind of changed back.
Yeah.
Well, it didn't turn out the way they wanted it.
They wanted it to be a total multimedia.
Don't forget what the M stands for.
Yeah.
Well, that's true.
Or the MS actually.
Sands from Microsoft.
Well, and then there's CNBC.
Well, yeah.
But that's just cable NBC or whatever.
So Karen Bryant and who else is doing very well.
Allison Stewart and MSNBC.
Okay.
Karen on CNN and Allison on MSNBC.
So we talked about the post life of a VJ and television not being too successful.
Those.
Which means two exceptions.
Neither of them are making any real money though because you know that's just like MTV pay there.
I don't know.
Oh, please.
I had to see an end came over here.
And one of those guys that you recognize.
You know, like forget his name.
Yeah.
I talked about one.
One of their big guys.
Yeah.
I forget it.
Well, it's not that gut.
Well, yeah.
One of those guys.
He was really nice.
You know, he said that.
It's fucked up.
He was saying he was really complaining.
I said, man, son, just like MTV.
So yeah.
It's very political.
And it's, uh, and there's not a lot of money in it.
It's, that's hard.
You know, it's very expensive to run a 24 hour date news channel.
I was talking not too long ago to somebody who was, uh,
is an anchor out here for the local NBC affiliate in Portland, Oregon.
And I could make more money at a Starbucks, I think.
As if I restarted.
Yeah.
Hi.
I'm Ken Stranger.
Yeah.
Is a really good barista in Portland.
And you can apparently anchoring the NBC affiliate news.
Yeah.
Also, since the last time we did an MTV Chronicles, uh, a lawsuit was announced between
Julie Brown and NBC.
No way.
What happened?
Oh, they probably had a pilot that they didn't, they didn't do or something.
No, this is, this is good.
This is really good.
You'll enjoy it.
Yum.
Remember about two or three years ago, Julie did that.
God awful show called.
I'm a celebrity.
Get me the hell out of here.
Oh, I know the show, but I didn't see her on it.
That would have been pretty funny.
I watched one episode of it.
And, and she was okay.
I couldn't stomach a land of Stewart.
She was a finding bitch.
Just like, a lot of, no.
Who was a lot of Stewart again?
Rod Stewart sex life.
Oh, geez.
Okay.
Was that the English version that just aired over there?
Was that a separate?
Because, you know, it airs all over the world now.
I think that was the same version.
It aired everywhere.
It was the first season they had done it.
And I can't even remember who all was there.
But, I mean, you know, these are all quote-unquote husbands.
Yeah.
I mean, a land of Stewart as Rod Stewart sex wife.
I'm not sure she ever really was, but.
All right.
Julie, Julie, hey, that her got some told her off on the program.
Julie shouldn't.
I mean, the minute you go in that, you basically labor yourself,
yourself as a husband, right?
That's kind of the whole deal.
That would be like a jump the shark moment.
Yeah.
Yes.
You're done it either.
Frankly, I think in retrospect, I don't know what the hell she was thinking.
I don't mean to do it if she doesn't either because here, here's the basis of the lawsuit
between her and the production company.
During the taping of the show, and I missed the episode fortunately.
Julie got into a bathtub filled with leeches.
And was completely buried under a pile of squirming leeches.
Well, that's apparently they promised her this was safe.
That's um, according to the lawsuit, she still has permanent scars on her body
from the leech bites.
Oh, I bet.
I bet.
Totally.
My goodness.
So that was the basis of the lawsuit was permanent scarring,
caused by being put in a bathtub full of leeches.
When the producers had assured her it was okay.
So is she suing NBC or the production company?
It was ABC and the production company.
We're both both named in the lawsuit.
Wow, has that come to court yet?
Or what's the deal?
Uh, I don't know.
Oh, man.
I saw it on the news and I thought, oh, that's interesting for the MTV
Chronicle.
Smoke smoking friend.
Our good friend Julie Brown smoking going should should get a hold of all the paperwork
and publish that.
That'd be pretty funny.
And and you and Julie always had a funny relationship.
There was a competitiveness.
There was a bickering that went on.
But you guys were okay in the end.
I think there was an abonding event.
You guys got put in the same limo going to like the.
Oh, it was a New Year's Eve show or it was MTV video music awards or something.
You and Julie ended up writing in a limo together,
which everybody had been very worried about.
The limo backed over some old woman.
God, can't I can't remember that.
Oh, dude.
Oh, wait a minute.
It was in New York though, right?
Yeah.
And the limousine like backed into some old woman.
You guys were out like helping the old woman up and everything.
And Julie was screaming at the limo driver.
Yeah.
I do remember.
And somehow you guys bonded during that limo ride.
And you guys were okay after that.
But you guys always had kind of a funny way.
And you know what I was because Julie had an excellent knack.
And it was really the British humor.
She had a very good knack of completely tearing you a new asshole on the air.
And I just had no recourse.
You know, I had no way to get because just I couldn't I couldn't do it.
You know, and and so anything.
If whenever I'd like tried to, you know, to the zinger back,
it always kind of came out wrong.
Yeah.
I've got clips of Julie.
There was a great one where she was talking about what she wanted for Christmas.
She wasn't feeling well that day.
I think she'd been out partying with Billy.
I told the night before somebody that she was and she said,
I I don't know.
I just maybe a new blow dryer.
I just want to look like Adam Curry.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Anyway, up next.
You know.
I didn't mind that.
I didn't mind the hair jokes because everyone's just fucking jealous of my hair.
Well, you know, do you remember the time Julie had those dreadlocks put in?
That was a great story.
No.
She was in the chair for, I think, 12 hours having dreadlocks put in.
And she came into the studio the next morning and she looked like an Asian woman.
Her eyes were all drawn back.
And she was an agony.
She was an agony.
And they had put like 14 pounds of hair on her head.
And it was literally pulling her scalp out.
I mean, I do remember that.
And she put up with it for about a day.
And then she got like a pair of hedge tremors and locked them all off.
It sold her length.
Is that their prime?
Yeah.
She cut them off.
Hair looked like shit then.
That was horrible.
You had to wear her hair up in a plastic bag.
I think they had to put wigs up on her.
Speaking of which, you know who sent me an email the other day from MTV management
from the early days.
Steve leads.
No, I've been talking to Steve a lot, actually recently.
No, actually.
I've seen him on Skype.
Steve, I always like.
I got him on Skype.
He, he, and you know, I told him in Stali's like,
wow, this is like a free phone.
Oh, yes, Steve.
No, Tom Hunter.
Tom Hunter.
Hold on.
Oh, Tom Hunter.
Yeah.
What was his gig?
He was, I think he was one of the in the music programming department when they were still running
at lingerie.
Or Abby was he?
He was before.
No, he was before Abby Connor, which, and remembered that prick John, what's his name?
Canaling.
That one.
He was talent and artist relations though.
I've got a good.
I've got two.
Well, Matt Farber came after Abby Connor, which.
I'll personally tell you about Tom Hunter, just a brief update.
He's divorced.
He's remarried.
He's been married for five years.
Has three.
I think three kids all grown up.
And he lives in Dallas now.
And he's teaching.
And, and he's doing like a weekend gig on the college radio station.
And he's lost like a thousand pounds.
I was just going to say as he lost weight.
Yeah.
He looks really good.
What's he teaching like broadcast or radio or something?
Communication stuff.
Yeah.
I'm just going to teach her that would be when I think back to my degree in communications.
If only I had teachers who'd been in charge of programming an MTV.
Yeah.
Because then you didn't listen to him.
Like, oh, this guy actually had no sum.
You know, I remember when I went to West Virginia to school for that entire semester.
Remember my communications classes.
And like, you know, if you really knew what you're talking about,
wouldn't you have like a real fucking job?
I suppose.
I mean, I had somebody at my college who had never been outside this state of Ohio before
to tell me at one point that I didn't have what it took to make it in New York.
Well, you're, well, you are in Portland, you know.
I am now.
But that was after I conquered Manhattan.
Yes.
You took the city.
Okay.
So that was after, yeah.
That was, this is, well, you moved to it.
So what can you say?
Yeah.
We all things change.
His life goes on priorities change.
So Tom skews me.
What a nice bit of philosophy there.
I love that.
Thank you.
That's true.
So he's doing good.
He's, he's all right.
And then John can only have a little win.
We easily cocksucker.
God, I hated him.
John can only.
Yes.
Because I'll tell you why.
And then you can continue.
When I had my good memo.
When I had my Richard Marx fall out.
Yeah.
Which I don't remember how that actually went.
But Richard started on the radio program.
No.
It did not.
It started on the top 20 video countdown where there was.
It ended up on the radio.
Yeah.
Well, that's where it escalated.
But it was something.
I can't even remember what it was about.
It was something so fucking stupid.
But he was such a goddamn control freak, Richard Marx.
And then he said, I do recall this all of a sudden.
It may come to me.
You had said something that was really, I mean.
But it was scripted.
It was like a quirky MTV joke that every other artist go like,
Okay.
You know, after you play the video for the 20 millionth time,
you know, you got to say something else.
And whatever it was, he really went off.
And he went up to the office and tried to get me fired.
And John Cannelly immediately went,
Yes.
Well, we should get rid of him.
He is like, thank you, mother fucker.
I was horrible.
I do remember we had to pull tape.
You know, we've got to pull tape and say.
What did he say?
Exactly.
The Richard Marx fiasco.
I don't remember what it was.
It was not, you know, it wasn't.
He obviously had issues.
It was unnecessary.
Well, I just saw him on TV recently.
He's got a new album out.
And it struck me even then.
The years later.
What is it?
10, 15 years later.
He still looked neurotic.
Well, he, first of all, he's a great songwriter.
No doubt about it.
Yeah.
Great songwriter.
Good producer, actually.
He's been doing some major hits.
Yeah, no.
And so I'll give them all that.
But then I was hosting a show called Hitline USA.
And so it's Rick Kalman has that tape.
We should get that tape.
Actually, I have a real, I have an original real to real of that as well here.
I don't have the tape.
And he goes off.
And he says, on the air, he starts saying, well, your hair looks like, what do you say?
I don't know.
But he was the last person that should have been making an air.
Really?
And then he said, I hope you, you know, oh, because I was smoking at the time.
I hope you get cancer.
He said, I hope your lips fell off.
No.
He said, I hope they got cancer.
That's what he said.
And your lips fell off.
It was horrible.
You completely went off.
It's very stupid.
Did that show ever aired?
Did you guys get it?
It was live.
It was live when that happened.
You kidding me?
It was one of the best.
It was one of the best shows I've ever done on radio.
It just couldn't believe what he was saying.
Everyone loved it, you know?
I don't think you did well with it.
I don't think you got, you just kind of laughed at him.
But you didn't really fling mud back.
And God knows you could have.
Well, you know, what do you say to that?
You know?
What do you say to that?
Well, he meant it.
He really meant it.
No, I think I said, no, he said, you're going to be out of a job.
And I'll see you on the unemployment line.
You'll be ahead of me or something like that.
I can't remember what it was.
But we all did okay in the end.
It was stupid.
But the cancer thing really bothered me.
That was an unnecessary and unfair comment.
He still looks really uptight.
And like he doesn't have a sense of humor.
Because he really wanted to be a rock and roll superstar.
And he just didn't have it in him.
You know, he wanted to be.
What was the band?
He was always hanging out with.
Well, first of all, in his, in his band.
Who was in his band?
Remember who played in his band?
Remember.
Come on.
Richie, kind of him.
Wasn't, no, not, not Richie, kind of him.
Or was it?
Who was the guy who went?
Yeah.
He had fucking happy.
It was, it wasn't Richie, kind of.
It was someone like that.
It was like some, some doork from some happy days.
Like grown up.
Yeah.
Who the hell was that?
He was playing bass in his band.
Wasn't somebody from the Parkridge family.
Well, Donnie, Danny Bonna, Doochie.
Danny Bonna, Doochie, and bass.
He's funny.
We had a good time.
I, I hung out with him a lot.
He was very funny.
Danny's funny.
Remember when he got, when he got picked up, and he was working for MTV.
Somewhere in, in Florida, he got picked up for, for soliciting a transvestite process.
Transvestite.
That's right.
Whoops.
That's happened to a lot of famous people.
I don't get that.
He's red.
You're gray.
There was some tiff with that Murphy, and it transvestite too.
Well, she males are very intriguing to straight guys.
John Cannelly.
I found, you know, I have a huge box of paperwork, funny memos and things that I saved
over the years, and at some point over the last five years since we did the last MTV Chronicles,
I pulled out my two favorite memos of my entire 10 year period at MTV.
Oh, man.
Oh.
These are the two.
John Cannelly's is actually my second favorite memo.
I know what the first one is, but I won't give it away.
October 18th, 1991, to all MTV staff from John Cannelly, subject hammer under
Oh, no.
The hammer memo.
That's the hammer memo.
The original.
Please be advised that effective immediately, MC Hammer is now just hammer.
All references.
I love this.
This is the clinch to all references, both on there and off air to this artist should include
this change immediately without reflection.
Violators will be shot.
Prosecute.
Does it say shot?
No.
It does not say that.
We'll be swiftly terminated.
Yeah.
I mean, I have a reference.
Both on air and off air.
So we can't even say MC Hammer in the fucking hallway.
I remember we used to go like, if you hammer.
Not all mighty.
I just thought of one other really funny John Cannelly story before we move onto the other
memo.
Madonna.
I can't remember what video it was, but they had made this huge deal about this Madonna
video.
Nobody, it was the church, the Pepsi one.
Remember the one that got like a prayer.
Like a prayer like a prayer.
Like a prayer.
It was like a prayer.
Yeah.
All right.
Because at MTV, we taped a day or two in advance and we had to tape that the world premiered
the video two days before the video actually was available.
The record label and John Cannelly made this huge freaking production about coming over
to the studio.
Oh boy.
Give us a VJs and the senior staff a private screening of the video so that we could
tape it.
And they brought the video over in a Brink's truck.
I mean, it was just the most ridiculous stunt anybody.
And this wasn't even a televised stunt.
This was behind the scenes.
Was this the one with the wires running to the next room, Ken?
Yeah.
There were a number of us downtown Julie Brown included.
I hate to malign her in this way.
I had no part of this.
I knew about it.
No, you did not.
I don't even know if you were in the building.
Oh, yeah.
I knew about it.
But I didn't want to have anything to do with it.
There was no evil intent.
We weren't going to leak the clip.
We weren't going to make copies of it and distribute it over the internet because there
was no internet at the time.
We only had one computer in the building and it was a wing.
We drilled a hole through the wall and we were upstairs with the officers.
I remember that.
Yeah, upstairs at Unitel behind the behind the whole rack with the VCR system was because
we knew they were bringing over like a three quarter inch humatic, you know, the big
tape.
And we drilled a hole through the wall and we ran the cables and we did a VHS machine
behind the couch in the lounge, the VJ lounge back there.
And before the record label even showed up, it was a two hour tape on super long
to play.
So it would record for like six hours and we all had to record a deck would record.
Record label comes in.
They play the clip, you know, big production and everybody claps.
Meanwhile, all this is going on speaking of Steve Lee's love Steve leads, but this
is the only thing Steve ever did that I really thought was an office thing to do.
I remember it.
Steve noticed the wire going through the wall and he went like, well, no, he quietly kind
of opened the door to the VJ lounge and went in there.
And I'm sitting there thinking, oh, shit, the gig is up, you know.
And then the door opens and Steve comes out and he's got a VHS tape in his hands and I'm
like, we are so buff off.
And you know, it's Steve should have done his weighted to the record company left.
Of course.
Everything was over and then, you know, said, you guys stay here for a minute and then
he should have come in and ripped this out a new asshole.
But he could have taken us to the cleaners.
And steady handed the tape to the head of the record label and said, here's somebody
was pirating this.
Oh, I do remember that.
Oh, it's lame.
Well, the shit hit the fan and can now he went berserk and Julie was sitting there.
She was laughing a bit.
She was laughing.
Julie didn't give a damn, I mean, and that was one of the things the MTV management
so hated about Julie is she didn't give a damn what they had to say about her or anything
out.
That's right.
She could care less.
And went off and at one point, you know, saying how we were all pieces of shit and
everything.
And Julie stood up and said, I hear it comes.
She said, you fucking cons, I remember it.
And then just went off at Cannelly, ripped him a new asshole and just like walked out of
the room and said, I'm not going to sit here and listen to you talk to me like that and
just walked out of the room and he turned like 27 shades of purple.
Yeah.
So what was he got fired?
No.
I had to take the wrap for that.
Yeah.
You got to apologize.
I had to go apologize to Judy McGrath personally.
He believes she's still running that channel.
That's amazing to me.
I saw Judy McGrath at JJ Jackson's funeral reunion service.
We had a New York.
And you were almost there, in fact, you missed, I think by like a week, you were going
to be in New York.
I wasn't invited.
Oh, yeah.
You would have been invited.
Judy was a friend of MTV, not to the cocktail reunion thing.
Yeah.
You definitely would have been invited to that.
Okay.
And that was a trip because I looked for my wallet.
I started at MTV when I was 19 or 20 years old.
A lot of the people that were at this thing were there at the time and they were probably
in their late 30s to 40s back when I was 19 or 20 years old.
So when I wallstained to this room last April, Jerry has been expecting to be walking
into like a geriatric convention.
Oh, man.
It was a trip.
But Judy did show up and it was actually really cool to see her and we chatted
for a few minutes and I said to her, Judy, it's so nice to actually have a conversation
with you when I'm not absolutely scared shitless because she was a frightening woman.
You know, I never, I found it.
I still find to be the most unhipp woman in show business, which is why, maybe that's
why she's good at what she does.
But she was always the driver behind.
I'll give her this.
She was the driver behind long-form programming and less videos.
That is completely Judy McGrath.
She was very icy, but I have discovered over the years that Judy really, or I mean that
Judy really does have a soft spot and she cares about the people that she worked with
way back then and when she was at the party and we were talking about, you know, she used
to write copy.
I mean, she was a copywriter for the very, very early days of MTV.
She was just one of the gang hanging out and I'm looking at her thinking she's this, this
is she's another president of MTV Networks, right?
Now that Kristen's been elevated.
Yeah, to Viacom corporate, whatever.
Yeah.
First, and yeah, and it was Judy that called me when I got promoted to manager of
on our talent and said congratulations, I know you'll do a great job.
You'd better and then hung up the phone on me.
Yeah, that was like power trip, woman on power trip thing.
But she, but she, she changed the channel to what it is today.
I do have respect for Judy, all right.
We had talked about Abbey Connoisseur.
Wait, you're going to do one more John Connelly memo.
You had another cannelly memo.
I don't, that was the, that was the cannelly memo was the hammer.
But that was your second favorite.
That was my favorite favorite wasn't it cannelly memo.
That was the favorite Jackson Farber memo.
What was that was that the Michael Jackson memo?
Yeah, timely, I guess.
Do you have the official memo there?
I do.
Would you like, would you care to share it with our, it still has my name?
It was still, it still has the original fax header on it, where it was faxed to the studio.
So let's see what we said it up because we had taped the Michael Jackson weekend,
which was a part of another deal because we had, it was like three things, if I'm not mistaken.
One, what was all about getting Michael Jackson to perform on the video, musical awards.
And by the way, if you ever said VMAs on the air, you were punished.
Yeah, it was.
You had to say video music awards.
You were not among TV.
The whole world says VMAs.
The whole world says VMAs, but we had to say the MTV video musical awards.
And as a part of the deal, was that the one where he got the award in his name that I had to present to him?
The Van Guard award.
No, no, excuse me, excuse me, that would be the MTV video musical award, Michael Jackson video Van Guard, the award of the year.
The Guard award.
Yeah, somewhere in this timeline and I'm kind of flipping through it.
I didn't want to bug things down here, but it's somewhere in here.
It talks about when you went and presented that silly ass.
That was a fun trip though, because I went with Freston, with Tom Freston.
I actually put makeup on Tom Freston because he looks up front and beat December 23rd, 1989.
MTV CEO Tom Freston and MTV VJ Adam Curry present Michael Jackson with the Michael Jackson video Van Guard of the year.
Artists of artists of the decade, right?
I'm sort of the decade, right?
In Los Angeles, that was where they, Michael Jackson had to stand on a box because he had to be taller than you and your like six and a half feet tall.
So that was difficult for everyone.
But so as a part of that, there was also, and you already mentioned that we recorded the weekends.
We recorded on Thursday, right?
So we do Saturday and Sunday would tape on Thursday.
Monday was usually taped on Friday.
Tuesday, Tuesday was Wednesday and Thursday.
Wednesday was Friday, Thursday was Saturday and Sunday and Friday was Friday.
Right.
So Tuesday and Thursday is where 48's and 48's, that's right.
So we did a 48 on Thursday, which basically it's like a whole day of work, right?
So that's 100 grand worth of, well, more, probably like $140,000 worth of production time.
Yeah, I mean, we're talking, you know, two full days of the programming had been taped in one day.
And then we were always happy because on Friday, we'd have a 24 because that meant we were only taping from Monday.
That was like a half day.
So, you know, as I was like, Friday was like, oh, yeah, you know, it's got a 24.
We can go home early and get the weekend started.
But then came when I'm during a 48, everybody'd have to run and change clothes, you know,
do the, and then, you know, come back on the set and pretend like it was a whole new day.
Yeah, just so you know, I mean, we never saw that.
Typically introduced the same videos over.
You're just introduced before and make it sound fresh.
Yes, exactly.
Come on, energy, baby.
So then the, then the memo came down.
Yeah, the Michael Jackson reference memo.
It starts off with, and you know, did you like Matt Farber?
I don't remember Matt Farber, particularly well.
Um,
Yeah, yeah, yeah, fun of him.
You know, I, I did like him because he was really trying to keep the music alive on MTV.
He was a radio guy.
Was he the guy that had come from karaoke?
Yeah, I was.
Yeah.
He brought Kennedy then.
I don't, oh, that was the reason why why I didn't quite like him that much, I guess.
All right.
Well, because we're about to make fun of him.
I just wanted to make sure he was somebody like him.
We like him.
We're honest here.
I like him.
Okay.
All right.
So the memo begins with here's a unique one.
We need to refer to Michael Jackson as the king of pop in quotes on air quote from time to time.
Here's how we'll handle this.
In VJ segments, each VJ should refer to Michael Jackson as the king of pop at least twice
in each VJ segment over the next week.
That's twice per segment per VJ for a week.
You had to say the king of pop.
I remember.
And then in specialty shows such as yo top 20 most wanted fade to black, et cetera, refer
to Michael Jackson as the king of pop at least once per show per week for the next two weeks.
Be sure to note exactly which segment you do this in as we will be sending dubs to the king
of pop himself.
I know this is a bizarre request, but Fox and BET are already doing this.
So we need to too.
But we can't play.
We can't play.
We can't blame him for that because that was a part of the deal that Michael Jackson made
with MTV for the video musical words.
Yeah, I know.
But you don't know how this sentence I know how bizarre this request is, but Fox and BET are
already doing this.
Dix in my cry.
How lame is that?
Fox and BET are doing it.
We've got to do it too, my God.
Can't let me ask you a question because so I met Michael Jackson out in LA and I'd have to say
that if anything he's completely asexual, that was the vibe I got from him.
Do you think that he really did any of the things he's being accused of?
You know, I have to say I'm beginning to wonder.
I had thought for years that there was absolutely nothing to this, Michael Jackson, because
of his free-cish behavior.
And because of the fact that he gets himself into situations where there is certainly
possibility of improprietous behavior, if you know what I mean.
He becomes, and because he was at one time incredibly wealthy became a sitting duck for target.
You're saying he's not wealthy anymore?
He's wealthy on paper, but he's got liquid financial problems.
You don't know that.
You can't look at his fucking bank account.
Well, I'm saying that the news have reported that there are funny polls.
Thank you.
The news.
The quote news has reported.
We watch entertainment tonight.
He has to live, you know, one of the most extravagant expensive lifestyles of any
human being on the planet.
Oh, please.
And aside from his holdings, he's not generating much cash other than his holdings of, you know,
the various...
Do you have any idea how much money he gets per year?
I mean, that it's an astronomical amount, believe.
I know, but I mean, I've actually seen reports where they were analyzing the spending
and how much they don't know.
But they don't know.
That race never lands.
Nobody knows that.
It's costing.
No one knows that shit.
You can't look at someone's mind.
You can't look in their pocketbook.
No.
Well, no.
And that wasn't the point of the conversation.
The point of the conversation was he was weird.
And he was a very obvious, easy target for allegations of his nature.
I look at this ridiculous court trial going on.
And it really has turned into a three-ring circus.
I think the judge is a lot of a whole bunch of crap to happen.
Yeah.
But the judge is media horny.
That's what he is.
You know, we got X employees testifying.
Well, these are people who were fired and have a grudge.
I don't know whether they're telling the truth or not.
But there's so much money out there to be had by people that anybody is going to say anything.
I think if they stand to make this kind of money off it.
I really don't know.
I just don't know.
I always felt so strongly that no, it's just wasn't possible.
But so many people and so many allegations.
And there's so much similarity amongst the theme that it just...
I don't know.
I'm starting to wonder.
Well, for me, he's innocent until proven guilty.
And if I agree with that.
And I do believe in the justice system.
And if he turns out to be guilty, then okay, I'll be the first one to say I was wrong.
But let's also not forget that this guy is one of the most talented musicians we've had in my generation.
And he's also...
He hasn't exhibited that in a long, long time.
I disagree because he's written a lot of shit for other people.
He's been doing a lot of stuff for other people.
I had kept hoping for him, though, that he would one of these days in the past ten years,
or so create another really brilliant record.
It's impossible to do that when you're going through this shit.
You can't be creative when that's happening to you.
There's no fucking way.
There's no way.
Well, this this shit hasn't been going on the entire time.
But he...
Long time no.
We'll see what happens.
I do agree in the criminal justice system as well.
And the difference is between what I think and that is that that's beyond a benefit of it doubt.
You can have a little teeny doubt, but that's not beyond the benefit of it doubt.
I think there's some suspicion growing in me that some there's something weird going on.
But a reasonable doubt is what it is, Kevin.
It's beyond reasonable doubt.
I still have reasonable doubts, so therefore I would that be enough to get him.
Nope.
Don't think so.
Okay.
He's also raised hundreds of millions of dollars for charity.
No, that is absolutely true, too.
I was always a staunch Michael Jackson defender.
It's just been the last month or two.
I've started to think that...
I don't know.
There was just...
I'm with Haraldo, man.
Haraldo's a lawyer.
He's seen all the documents.
He said his bullshit.
I'd like Haraldo.
Yeah, I like Haraldo.
He was normally, I think, he's a jackass.
No, Haraldo's only.
I've always liked him.
You used to like him, though, because he had it.
He'd be fluted in New York every day in his own helicopter.
I had nothing to do with it.
Nothing to do with it at all.
That wasn't until much later.
Nothing to do with it.
While you were sitting in traffic in the roles.
And you never had it in the helicopter.
I had nothing to do with it.
I always liked him.
I thought I love watching his show.
We still get fucked over here.
I watch him all the time.
He cracks me up.
By the way, the car that the garage door fell on.
You heard that story.
I actually was brushing my teeth while I was listening to that story.
It made me spit toothpaste all over my brand new high definition flat panel monitor.
Was it the CRX or was it the Camaro?
No, that was the Mitsubishi.
Oh, the Mitsubishi, right?
The Mitsubishi had about two months left on its lease.
When I bought my first new Camaro, that was the Z28.
That reminded me of a funny story.
The night I picked up that Z28.
And the Mitsubishi, I'll explain why the Mitsubishi was in the garage in a moment.
But you got in that thing in a bathrobe.
Do you recall?
Yeah.
And put that car up till like 75 to 80 miles an hour in a 25.
And like five seconds.
Well, I did it before, I think.
And I was just envisioning the arrest of you.
MTV and radio celebrity in a bathrobe.
For doing 85 into 25 in my Z28.
Didn't happen.
It worked out.
No, it was fine.
And no, that wasn't the car that got teaboned.
The car that got teaboned was in 2002.
That I had SS that I had replaced the Z28 with.
The car is at overlap.
I still had like two months left on my lease of the Mitsubishi.
And I only had one garage stall at my apartment in you for whatever reason.
I think you had sold the Porsche.
And one of the garage stalls there at the curry mansion was vacant.
Yeah.
The one that didn't work.
Right.
And so I had stored the Mitsubishi in the garage there for like two months until the lease was up.
Oh, you were pulling it out.
Was that it?
You were pulling it out of the garage.
That car was in perfect shape.
I was supposed to be taking it back to Mitsubishi.
The next day to turn it in at the end of its three year lease.
Patricia was standing there in the driveway.
I had somehow wedged.
I knew the spring and the garage door didn't work.
And it was a really heavy garage door.
I had wedged a piece of wood or something in there that was supposed to prevent it from coming down.
Yeah.
And I got about halfway out of the garage.
When Patricia, I heard her yell.
And I saw the door starting to come down.
I was in reverse.
I floored it.
I laid a huge smoker in the garage trying to like that.
And I didn't get back far enough because that like 200 pound garage door went right dead center
across the hood.
Yeah.
And put a huge dent in it.
And the funny thing is, is I pounded that back out with a hammer.
It looked awful.
I took it back to Mitsubishi.
And they said, thanks.
They didn't even come out to the lot and look at it.
Yeah.
They like wrote me a check for my security deposit and I was out of there and goodbye.
Nobody ever said a word about it.
Oh, baby.
That was the Mitsubishi.
Yeah.
I love that.
And it is funny because I think even that day when I got out of the car and there was a huge dent.
I mean, the garage door was stuck across the hood.
There was smoke rolling out from, you know, the patch I had laid.
I think Patricia.
She was laughing.
I bet she was laughing.
She was laughing so hard at me.
I bet.
Because I had a fit.
I really did have a fit.
I was like, oh, no.
But you're right.
You know me and cars.
Uh-huh.
I couldn't help it.
So do you have anything else we can wrap this one up?
Because we're already at, like, what are we at now?
Fort.
Oh, I think we should probably wrap.
That was the big stuff I had on the list for the day.
I mean, you and I could talk about stuff all the time.
We should do a theme next time.
Like, you know, we still haven't talked about Joni Abbott.
I promise myself.
We're going to do that one of these things.
We haven't talked about Joni Abbott.
So we talk about the dead people.
Uh-huh.
We haven't talked about Dabithis Ouron Burger.
Oh, my God, crabatha.
rabatha.
Ah, my goodness.
Nughoses up at five o'clock is it with Courader Crabby.
Yes.
And they say Cour'! Everybody be like, oh, I think God.
Yeah.
I call it.
I said it was with Crabby, everybody would be like, oh man.
There was someone else who I heard from the other day, um.
It was, um, God damn, I think another guy from the news department, he was kind of like a, he was a cool guy.
He, um, it was Dave Serolnik, and there was someone else, there's not a Dave.
I'm trying to think, Dave and Nupus, I remember Dave Serolnik.
Yeah, that wasn't the one I should have kept my notes.
So I don't know.
I've got it.
I'm sure on a memo.
So I'm wearing trust me, but I'm some of my memories of everybody.
You know, it's funny.
I remember so many people, but when you go back, you know, even when I did that reunion,
JJ thing, there were people I had completely forgotten about.
You know, Chris Kelly, the stage manager and Chris Kelly, yeah, Chris Kelly was the
stage manager for a long time.
Then Jenna Rossitano became the, the pretty regular stage manager.
She was cute.
Jenna still stage managing Saturday night live, you know, because she was Beth's buddy, right?
Um, yeah, Beth in this whole group.
She's still directing of sure, right?
But, saying Beth is directing.
Beth is directing.
Beth has been directing Saturday night live now for five, six years.
Yeah.
Um, but Jenna is there.
There's a bunch of old MTV staffers that have gone over and are at Saturday night live.
And I always say every time I go to New York, I'm going, I should get in touch with Beth
in those guys, because that was the one, you know, one of the great things about working
at MTV with all those years is that you get to go to all the cool places, you know,
you get to go to the show tapings and the concerts and all that.
But I never got to go to Saturday night live ever.
Me neither.
And we've got buddies there.
Did you ever go to Saturday night?
No.
No, never did.
So we should make a list of stuff to talk about next time.
Well, you and I actually haven't had a conversation, you and I since the last time we did
at MTV Chronicles.
So yeah, I just don't want to have to brainstorm.
That would require work.
Like either of us have time between work and accidents and you running an empire
affair from the English countryside.
Yes, indeed.
I'm glad you enjoyed the good at cheese shopping cards story too, by the way.
The one.
Oh, yeah, the good at shopping card.
The shopping card full of good.
Yep.
Well, the cast is off my arm, so I can, I'm back to the, you get into the weirdos
shit, my friend.
You really do.
Well, I, you know, but you, you said it yourself last week, I, I, I don't go out
looking for it.
It's just.
It comes on to you.
All right.
Well, thank you.
This is always fun.
It's been good.
Yeah.
Good time.
Tell me MTV again.
And thank you for the, the plug there for the Ken and script show this last week.
I haven't done a promo in a long time, but yeah, but something about getting an accident
is inspiring to my creative juices.
But I like it so much.
I'd like it when you just talk about regular shit that's happened to you.
That's funny, you know?
That's real life seems to be funny.
Typically it does.
And I think that's pretty much what's going to happen this week as well, because I've
gotten no big sticks or gigs, and we're not traveling, so.
Okay.
How's business out there, everything good?
Oh, I am swamped in real estate right now.
As soon as I booked an airplane ticket to Florida and gotten a car accident, I got swamped.
I got seven pieces of business on my plate, and I've been working like 14 hour days,
seven days a week.
Right.
It looks like it's going to be a banner, a banner spring from the accounting standpoint,
and I'll just have to relax somewhere down the road when business slows down a little bit.
Okay.
You want to do some more.
I'm having a lot of fun.
You want to do some more of that.
You want to have your Lord out.
I'm actually off to Florida next week to spend a week at the parents house on the
other side of Florida from where you guys go.
Okay.
Well, Patricia says hi, I couldn't get it to come up because Oman Opa just left and she was
enjoying his soul when I know.
Yeah, they were here for like while we were on vacation and they were here
For what week we came back what Wednesday? I think yeah, we came back home in opera
But Trisha's mom would always she was a very violent woman. She would always she still hits me like hit me
So yeah, she hits me all the time
I can just do his legs at first time. I met but Trisha's mom. She said you know can you look just like Jesus Christ
And then she hit you
All right, all right. Well, my love to the whole family back at you by and we'll do this again more sooner next time
Okay, dokey
Thank you. See you. Bye