Delta Sierra Charlie 2
Oh
There are no secrets
Holy information you don't even have
And I'm Korean
I'm proud it's
With $16 million worth of airplane strap to my ass
Trains, meters
Than the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need no sticky and crispy
I like to think I'm flying into the future
Fantastic
It's Adam Curry
September 30th 2005
It's Friday
The power of the North
Technically it's Friday
It's actually Thursday night
Yep
Welcome to with the daily source code
From the curry condo
My last night here for this day
With this particular stretch on the oil rig
And here this
What's this?
Copicina from a real cop
Power of the North
Oh yeah
I got delivered
I got service baby JC
Penny
Came through
I'm sure you're going to be very interested about that
So of course I'll
You're giving you all kinds of detail about the move in
But on the eve of departing after almost three weeks
I'm finally moved in
So
Let's see
One, two, two, I'd say music
Good tunes, hit test
Lots of feedback about some of the topics we've been talking about
Power of the North
And of course the obligatory promo here and there
I tell you the Bank of America building
All of a sudden it lit up
Someone was projecting
I guess the city was projecting a movie
It literally
Clips of air races and airplanes
For fleet week we just coming up next week
Of course when I'm not here
I can have the best seat in the house
Just from sitting here at the condo
So watch the movie was kind of fun
Doesn't really compensate
No, doesn't
Okay
I received a mashup
It's a hot shoot man
I'll have to add to my own week
You know, to I got it from
Not from art at mashup.com
But it was specifically sent to me
Is a perfect mashup to get the weekend going
RK 47
You got it yet?
Let's see if the liver I'm your slave in
Got my win, said good bye
Now I'm back and not a pain in the crowd
Woo, boom baby
I'm still alive
I'm alive
You're on your way
Oh, oh
You got a new ticket
Hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey
You got a new ticket
You got a new tickets
Do you got a new ticket
We're all gonna be there
We're gonna be there
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Wow, you are so lucky that we haven't done podcasts, DJ set up here almost, you know, I'm standing in the kitchen, looking out into the living room, you could, you know, it's a bar, so you could sit on the other side and we could have a couple mics there and I could have some speakers, so, you know, we could play some tunes and talk and it could be, it could be, kind of like a fun setting to do interview shows and stuff like that. I know, it's just, just hit me. Now, of course, that the place feels like home, JC Penny delivered Ron and I were,
in, what does it call there? Well, in Silicon Valley, I forgot what town it is. We were visiting with Randy Commissar, one of our board members, he's at Kleiner Perkins. We'd like to hook up with the, you know, at least everyone of our board members almost every week because we have so many things that they can help us with.
And just the road of decks is our amazing when that, when those open up, you know, we can get to almost anybody we want, so we're having just an amazing time here.
But we were late coming back and, of course, the Bay Bridge is right here next to the next, the Caricando. So, it's all the traffic, Jesus Christ, that's a humongous penis limo. Wow.
It's one of those, we're like the hot tub in the back. Fantastic. All right.
So I'm looking, literally, looking what's coming off of the Bay Bridge right now. So all the traffic goes right up my street, all the rush hour traffic home.
So it was about five o'clock, you know, that was great. So JC Penny was supposed to deliver between three and seven.
I've been in almost constant contact with Mario, my man downstairs at the front desk.
And I got in and he said, oh, look, you know, your neon's been delivered. I might show that was put in in the condo and I said,
Has JC Penny called yet? I said, oh, the shit's already upstairs. I hadn't put it in the kitchen, which, of course, he didn't know that was the studio.
So, you know, I got up here and there, yeah, for 12, 14 boxes, I located the three boxes that contain the bed and put those aside.
Ron has promised me we're going to do a bed cast.
Ron and Adam put a bed together. Uh-huh. Maybe we should have the pod casters over and we'll do like a pod squad and we'll have a mini party, what we put the bed together.
And then, you know, and I was like, oh, man, what am I going to do? I knew I wanted to record the source code and I still hadn't eaten yet.
I haven't actually made myself, you know, bacon and eggs and I had some vegetables and I'm eating up everything that's perishable, essentially.
And I heard Patricia's voice in my head, she's saying, make it make yourself comfortable, make it all comfortable for yourself.
She's like, since sailing me, sound baptizing me. I can just hear, and after 18 years of marriage, we're going to get to the 20 years.
It's finally working. All the nagging. It's paying off. I can hear it now. It's I've been conditioned.
And so that, you know, instead of waiting until I come back in a couple weeks, just screw it, I'm going to go do it. So all the boxes are open.
You know, everything was individually wrapped. Every single thing. I mean, you even have to put these lamps together. So beautiful, beautiful lamps.
We have the lampshade is in place wrapped in plastic and the lamp itself was wrapped in plastic and you have to put the the fitting, you have to screw it onto the base.
And just a lot of unwrapping and there's, you know, styrofoam and some boxes and that cracks and breaks and there's styrofoam balls all over the place.
So, and every and gosh, man, I don't know, I think Patricia made a mistake, but you know, I'd need like maybe, you know, so if you had four, four,
and four knives, maybe you'd double it just to make it easy on myself, you know, have eight of each. I think I've like 20 of each.
And everyone individually wrapped, I might have had. But, you know, I've got the full, you know, the steak knives, the regular knives, the dessert forks, the regular forks, the soup spoons, the vegetable spoons, the salad tongs, the whole freaking deal.
And linen. Oh, yeah. I gotta tell you something about my wife. She is a linen freak. Her linen colloset is kind of her thing.
And she washes her sheets herself and she has sheets that she's had with her for 15 years. You know, these, and she's that are expensive and, you know, they do last a long time and there's a special thickness to them. What is 150 something thread. Oh, yeah, threads. That's what it is.
So she ordered two sets of, you know, king size linen and they come in that I can, this is porn for her. This is totally porn for Patricia.
Like computer porn when when when I get a new computer and I unwrap it and this smells nice, you know what I mean?
So anyway, in her linen closet, everything smells fresh and all the towels are in there and, and by the way, the fold, the round side of anything that's folded sticks is on the outside.
And everything's perfectly aligned and it's straight. It smells warm and soft and fuzzy. I'm not kidding. It's really her thing.
And I'm down with it, man, because our bed at home is just like it's sleeping in a cloud. It's fantastic. So she's totally trying to set me up, but I can just understand how she's, and she's bum, she's bum, she isn't here to help me out and, and, you know, get a lot of this stuff up and running. I've done pretty good though. I think I've done pretty good.
So when I come back, we'll just do the bed and, uh, yeah, then I'm almost there. Oh, and, uh, well, I'll talk about the neonos. That's a whole new story.
Hey Adam, this is Chris Malkard from the top floor podcast. I'm standing at the window of my top floor in the middle of a thunderstorm. I'm taking pictures of lightning bolts.
I'm hearing that. This is life. This is not fake. And I'm doing a photography podcast, tip from the top floor.com, and, well, I'm just taking, this is amazing. You should see those lightning bolts here.
And it's starting to rain thunderstorms coming up, and I just thought I'd say hi from right in the middle of a thunderstorm and send you a picture with it. And, you know, maybe you can play this on the show.
Oh, are you just seeing the lightning bolt? Wow. No, it's starting to rain out. Remove the camera from the window. Otherwise, it's gonna drown. Oh man, this is amazing. Close that window. And, oh, I can't believe this is happening.
Wow. Well, you have to know when to end, especially at the point when it's getting too dangerous and I have to actually go around the house and close a few more windows.
I hope you'll be with us next time. I'll do another sound seeing kind of thing. Alright, that was it from the top floor. This is Chris Malkard. Thanks for listening.
Talk to you soon. Bye-bye.
Pod Show, content that will make you squeeze the dog and burp your mother.
Hey Adam, it's Omar, and I'm talking to you from your 70 National Park, and interestingly enough, the curry village campgrounds.
I'm at your 70 National Park, because I'm traveling across the country in my beautiful Jetta, and my friend P is along with me, and we are podcasting along the hallway, we're halfway across the country.
We started in Fort Waterdale. Now, we got the other half of the country to do in the Southwest, and Vegas, Grand Canyon and all that, but we've already been to Yellowstone National Park, the Badlands, Mount Rushmore, all those cool places.
And I just wanted to let you know, not just how much fun we're having, road tripping across the country and back, but how fun it is to record everything we're doing, then putting it on a podcast and letting our friends and family listen to it.
I look forward to doing another podcast someday. I'm getting in the videoography as a new field, and I was thinking, combining that with some of the ideas you've talked about, another podcast about GPS positioning and podcast and video might be something cool to try out.
So, check the website out, it's roadboreyourpodcast.com, and if you want like your listeners know about it, and I think it's real cool.
I keep up the good work for promoting podcast and getting pod show and everything else connected to it up and running.
Thank you.
I'm jealous of that. That's what I wanted to do with my girls. I wanted to take a, I tried to get air streamed to sponsor that we never could make that happen. It was a little too early in the podcasting success curve, I guess.
Maybe we'll still have that. I want to, you know, go do routes, well, not maybe in Route 66, but, you know, really go east to west or something and go to, you know, from maybe Texas to San Francisco or just to some cool route.
Camp curry where you are and where you recorded that in your semity national park used to belong to my family. Absolutely true. In fact, the curry clan as they're known really mainly from Kansas, my, my great, my great uncle. I think something like that was John Stewart curry.
Famous rural painter hangs in the metropolitan museum of art. I think one of those in New York.
And so the curry clan would have family reunions, a lot of them from Kansas, and they'd all go to Camp Curry, which is, I said, I'm not quite sure who owned it, but there was a, there's like firefall rock or something man, I'm bad at this. I really should know better. My grandfather less than he's probably yelling at me right now for not having the whole story.
He always maintained the entire genealogy of our family and I have it. I have all the documents, but it, you know, it's a lot to go through.
But there was, I don't know, I don't know which curry member that was, but they had built huge bonfires up on this cliff and then at night when everyone was, it was time to go to bed and they'd kick the embers over this cliff and I guess the main dude would say, let the fire fall.
There's some family lore for it. We also owned a humongous piece of land, what is today known as Flagstaff, Arizona.
So some brilliant light in the family sold that for a joint.
So I can't get to my Gmail, otherwise I would tell you who sent me this next clip. This is, I've been collecting some audio and this is, oh man, we have, we have so much to learn yet about what you can do with sound and what is exciting and what radio is.
This is actually a piece of real radio. I think it's from CB2, which is not Australian radio station. Now, I played you the piece from the fly with me podcast where we listened to the air, actually was not air traffic control, but it was maintenance talking with the jet blue aircraft that had the nose wheel problem, the gear was down, but the nose wheel was cocked 90 degrees and so they basically had to, you know, blew out everything because the wheels don't roll that way when they landed.
Beautiful landing. I've received transcripts or writings from people who were on jet blue and they're experienced because they actually had direct TV and they were watching themselves alive on television through direct TV, making emergency landing. How twisted is that?
The writing of that is just, it's beautiful and everyone was high-fiving and jumping up and down when they landed safely and the whole vibe is described very, very well.
But I don't have any audio of that. I mean, that's the final piece that I want because what I have now is, and this is live radio is good for this.
You know, in podcasts, of course, are good because you'll see even though you're getting this live, the excitement of how this Australian broadcaster, I have a window open. How this Australian broadcaster was reporting on this landing live in a real time.
It's really, it's like a sporting event. It's great radio. No matter what you're saying, it's great radio. So I'm going to play that for you. And if anyone, or if you know anyone who was on that jet blue flight, of course, there was no podcast or who actually recorded it.
Man, you know, I would have flipped on the eye river. I don't care. I'm sure I would have remembered to do that part.
I know I would have. I hope I would, and I hope I would be able to use it. And of course, yeah. Anyway, so here is, here's the recording from that Australian station CB2.
That you really enjoy. This is great. Great audio. As the plane comes in on descent, the most crucial time, obviously, as it hits the deck, will the nose will twist round to the way it should be.
They're on approach now. The captain has made the decision that they'll go in. The jet blue flight 292 with 139 people aboard is attempting the emergency landing at Los Angeles International Airport.
I guess the people on board are hoping to God that the captain will be in control by the time they come to the end of the runway.
They'll deploy the shoots, no doubt the slides out of the side once it does come to a halt. Emergency services are on standby now. You can see the tops of houses now on the tops of trees quite clearly in the background.
As this airliner makes its final approach to Los Angeles International Airport. The vision is coming from a fixed camera on the control tower now. It's over the top of the airport.
The captain is bringing it to the ground now. It's not too far above the ground. It's about to come down. He's continuing the descent in Los Angeles International Airport with the landing gear problem of the A320.
139 people, the lives and the hands of this man landing the aircraft. He's over the top of the runway now. He's still coming down. He hasn't aboard of the landing.
So obviously the decision has been taken. Another freeway is left behind him and now he can see the ground below him. He's about to touch down.
The A320. It's about to touch the ground and then the hearts are in the mouths of the people watching across the globe and listening as well. He comes in. He's just meters above the ground now.
The captain brings it down very gently. The back wheels go down first and now they're on the ground. They're about to touch.
And the nose wheel is about to come down now. Will it turn around? The back wheels go down. The puffs of smoke come out. The captain tries to slow it down. This is unbelievable.
The A320 is on the ground. The nose wheel still hasn't touched yet. He's easing it down ever so gently. Ever so gently.
It touches now. This smoke comes up. The sparks fly. It hasn't straightened down. But something now. He's done it. He saved their lives. They'll emerge. Get out of there straight away now. The A320 is on the ground. He has done it.
This fellow has done it. The crew would now be getting to the emergency slides to open them as well. They still haven't opened on either side of the aircraft.
But the jet blue flight 292 has made a perfect emergency landing. There is no fire at all. It's stationary now on the center of the airport.
Stationery at LAX. This is unbelievable. Quite incredible. The first of the emergency crews arrive on the scene. They still haven't opened the doors. They still haven't put the emergency slides down.
There are now many, many emergency vehicles surrounding it. They're watching the nose wheel which sparks were flying. Smoke was coming from at cascading back below the aircraft.
But they still haven't taken the people off the aircraft at the moment. I expected they'd be doing that immediately. They haven't done it. There is obviously no imminent danger to the nose on board.
The captain has decided to leave them on the aircraft for the time being. The aircraft is now surrounded by emergency vehicles.
And they're all trained on that nose wheel. This is absolutely incredible. You'll see the vision later tonight. My God, it was frightening sitting in a studio watching it.
What would it have been like on board the aircraft? What would have been like for the captain who's done an unbelievable job along with his crew to bring this aircraft to a safe halt at the end of Los Angeles International Airport?
Oh, man. Oh, man. Is that great or what that to me? It's a classic, classic piece of audio.
And I just wish I had air traffic control in that jet blue aircraft, which had a recording of that. It exists somewhere. I know the tapes do exist.
Maybe Mike is minute, which of course the podcast doesn't exist anymore, but he used the podcast from the control tower in I think was Toledo Ohio.
I was a great podcast. Maybe he'll be able to get the tapes to us.
And then of course, just anyone who can send in a recording of what it was like. Wow. What a great collection that would be, huh?
Wow. We could package that and sponsor it. But,
Prius? Prius? Man, everyone's correcting me on that. I don't know how to pronounce that either.
It's the car that Madge Weinstein wants for free. One of those hybrids get into her willia.
She'll promote it. It'll be worth it. It will be worth it. Imagine Madge Weinstein and Chancy in a golf cart.
By the way, I apologize. Oh, man. I can't believe I'm so freaking stupid. I actually uploaded the Thursday's entire show from the condo early.
Because I need to get everything done because we're simultaneously casting on serious now.
And so I kind of have to have stuff done before, well, before like two or three PM East Coast time for it to go into their system.
Just go from an MP3. They take my podcast and it goes, uh, Pete up does and turns it into an MP2 or whatever their format is for the satellite.
Are we in stereo, by the way? We used to be in mono. Are we in stereo now on channel 103? I don't know. I haven't received my complimentary boombox yet.
So I've been using the MM50 with the sometimes with the iPod. I find now I'm sinking the iPod up more and then it's because it's really convenient just to take it.
No wires attached. You know, just take the remote control into the bathroom with me to the bedroom. It's like a little iPod boombox.
And so I haven't heard the show yet.
But who was kind of confusing the cousin Bruce you was on between six and seven, which was the start at six are our maiden voyage.
And we had to wait an hour for cousin Brucey.
He's unbelievably popular though. It's really, that's about three things when people call up at serious. They ask about how we're stern.
They ask about, okay, I think I don't know if they ask for cousin Brucey next or the pod show and Adam Curry after that.
I have a feeling it could be because it cousin Brucey, but that's okay, where when you're laying on the ground, my friends, there's only one way to go and that's up.
Podsafe music now from a buddy mine from the Netherlands. I don't think it's in the Podsafe music network, but I will definitely reach out to him and ask him to put it in.
I've received permission to to play it on any podcast any time. I think he had a, he, this is the guy Roger with his, I don't know if his bands exist in twine.
And he, the first season of idols of pop idol, it's called idols in the Netherlands. So this is two years ago, I think.
Two years ago? Yeah, maybe two years ago.
He was really smart. He had already had a band and he participated in the band in idols and he got through the first or second round, whatever.
And then he had to sign the contract and he said, oh no, I'm not because I'm quitting because now I've got the attention I wanted for my band.
So, you know, that works because he got attention, but it doesn't work that way with mainstream media because then everyone's like fuck you man, you don't want to play our game, you think you're going to get a shortcut, no way.
So I'm happy to pick it up here and now that we have a lot of traction going on with this Podsafe music thing, it's time.
It starts off mellow, but it really starts to rock out at the end. I think that this, this could be huge.
This is a song that I think would be great for an American audience. I don't think they've ever really been exposed to it. So here it goes. This is in twine and happy.
You know what you've done? Could you confess your face with me? Isn't it strange that you told me and won't think suddenly change your mind?
Isn't it strange that you'd come here for me turn away and leave me behind? Now if he's like I'm drowning, please like I'm drowning away without you.
I know the feeling, because I felt real so bad for. I hope you don't feel just like me. I hope you don't feel just like me. I hope you don't feel just like me.
I hope you don't feel like me. Isn't it strange that the world seems to turn away when I try and explain what's so strange that you can be as one.
If he's like I'm drowning, please like I'm drowning away without you. I know the feeling, because I felt real so bad for. If he's like I'm drowning away without you.
I hope you don't feel just like me. I hope you don't feel just like me. I hope you don't feel just like me.
I hope you don't feel just like me. I hope you don't feel just like me. I hope you don't feel just like me. I hope you don't feel just like me.
I hope you're so free with just life and fuck I hope you feel much more
than me, maybe not so I'm in
Not so I'm in, not so I'm in
Not so I'm in, we'll go to my will
Not so I'm in, not so I'm in, not so I'm in
We'll go to my will
Man, that song sounds so good, I love that song
In twine, happy pod save from the daily source code
As determined by the artist himself, that's what makes it really cool.
I see on my console here that I've had two skips in the recording of the show.
I don't know what the hell is going on. This Mac has had it.
And I've had, and I have had this Mac for three years. This is a power book G4
Three years, I think, yeah, you can't get any more powerful than this one.
And usually with the Mac it's like an etchist sketch man.
It's like, if it doesn't work, you just shake it, close it, shake it, and then it's all good.
But after a while, I think they just get sick.
Windows machines have that too.
So a lot of people ask me what I'm using to record the show
When I'm on the road to I use audio hijack pro.
And I use megaseg.
The megaseg is a real good scheduling program.
You can segue stuff into each other and line stuff up easily.
Yeah, it works really well for the way.
As Ron would say, I'm a line guy.
I hit record and I go, there's no editing.
And all my processing, my mixer, my effects
is all external on a Yamaha workstation.
And so basically just feeding the headphone output goes into the mixer.
And the mic goes into the mixer.
And so anything that play on megaseg, anything I play on my Mac basically
will be then fed to the mixer back into the line input of the Mac,
and that is hijacked through audio hijack pro.
So it's a pretty simple system.
It really makes me my whole computer soundscape.
So I realized I didn't even finish my story about why I'm such a doofus.
So I had everything uploaded.
I had to run off to the office because it's 10.
No, I'm 12, I thought it was 12, 30,
but 12, we had an interview with Entertainment Weekly.
Because oh yeah, Hollywood's coming and knocking my friends.
Oh man, part two of the plan is about to go into effect.
Now we're going to misuse the mainstream media for our own promotion.
At first they were in control driving it with the interviews.
Now we've got audience now.
We're getting pretty powerful here.
I found out that if my information is wrong, please correct me.
But the numbers that radio stations typically have of listeners
is measured in the quarter hour.
How much time do I have here?
Is measured in the quarter hour.
And that is done by arbitron.
And it's typically done by people feeling out of diary
what they listen to.
Forget about all that.
Statisticians will argue with you for years.
Whether it's a good sample or not, doesn't matter.
So it's a sample of America that does this.
And for a number one market,
a big market like New York or Los Angeles.
That's a big market.
P1, I think they call it.
A typical station successful station in that market will have
10,000 listeners in that quarter hour and a 15 minute period.
So, and really they do that because the audience changes
every 15 minutes, particularly during drive time.
People are popping around.
They're not listening to the commercials by the way.
That's when we switch away.
That's your 15 minute reason to switch.
So it is possible that someone who was in the first 15 minutes of a
first quarter hour of an hour of the first 15 minutes of an hour comes
back in the third quarter of that hour.
But in total, Q, as they call it, they'll be 40,000 listeners in that hour.
Well, we have some podcasts.
This one included that are well into the hundreds of thousands.
And people aren't popping around.
They may be, you know, programming the show the way they want it.
I know lots of people that go right past the mashups.
But that's a pretty sizable audience that we have.
Bigger than a major market radio station.
That freaked me out.
So, if you have any other statistics on that, let me know.
But that's what I was told because I've been asking around.
And, you know, I know a lot of people aren't really here still.
Remember, radio, the lowest rung of the show is latter and podcasts hanging right underneath it.
Oh, yes, my friend.
Wait a minute.
Did I even finish the goddamn story yet?
No, I haven't.
Okay.
So, the story is that we had the interview and then we had to run off to go to San Hill Road.
And I forgot to post the show.
And then I went through all this unpacking and completely forgot.
And also, oh, my God, man, the show is uploaded, but never posted it.
So, you may be listening to this show on Saturday or Sunday or whatever.
So, that's all cool.
But if you're a serious satellite radio listener, then you're listening to it on Friday.
Okay, it's back to the hit test now, sir.
What did you hear?
The hit test.
Hey Adam, it's time for hit test number 62, but before we start, I would like to address a question that's been asked
a lot lately and it's about the processing I use and how I make it sound so so good and so clear in post production.
Well, let me say that I like Adam use cast blast time record live.
The only difference between my processing and Adam's is that mine sounds good.
Just oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, man, I'm going to get you for that.
Yeah, sure.
It's time for hit test Adam.
All right, three intros as always.
And this is number one.
Hit me.
James Ingram, Patty Austin, baby come to me.
You're going to put your arms around number two.
Okay.
Well, I'm going to know it.
Knowing it to you, John, I'm going to say that's the original.
That's going to be Rick James and super freaky baby.
Number three.
Hit me again with that.
Jesus.
And time's up.
This is answer number one.
Patty Austin and James Ingram, baby come to me.
When you know that nobody's standing by your side.
Come to me, come to me, come to me, come to me, come to me when I'm so close to you, come to me, come to me.
Come to me.
Because I can't go back to living without you, come to me.
The first answer in this early 80's edition of the hit test.
Betty Austin and James Ingram and baby come to me a song from 1983.
And this is answer number two, from 81.
It's Rick James. This is Super Freak.
Very cheeky girl.
The kind you don't think will do my best.
She will never let your spirits down.
Once you get it off the street, I'll go.
That girl is making it easy.
Girls are super break.
I really like to chase stuff.
Right timing me.
James alright.
Yeah.
Make no more drama.
Yet no more mistakes.
It's me.
Come on.
It just isn't me.
And then it's me.
Come on.
It's just isn't me.
And James.
Me.
One, two, three.
Come on.
Yeah.
A one hit wonder.
Stacy let us saw and jump to the beat.
That's answer number three in this hit test.
This concludes hit test number 62.
As always, feedback is welcome at hittest.gmail.com.
And you can go to the website and the blog.
It's yompolet.com.
J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T.com.
And you'll find a page there with the answers to the hit test.
And also the iTunes links.
So if you want to buy some tracks from the hit test.
Please do it using my links and my blog.
Yompolet.com.
Okay Adam, I hope you did well.
Again, great music to be playing here.
See you next time for 63.
I guess somewhere next week.
So until then, bye-bye.
I love those songs, yom.
Stacy let us saw a man that was 1980.
I was working at the pirate radio station at Amsterdam.
You know, that's what I miss about not being able to play.
You know, we just haven't quite figured that out yet.
How we can play a lot of that back catalog.
Oh man, skipping again.
I know what the hell is going on.
Damn.
It just shows up that it's skipping.
I got to reboot this Mac every single time I before I do a show.
And now now iTunes is like just popping up and starting by itself.
Making me angry.
So I was going to say it's too bad that we can't play a lot of that back catalog.
Because the story that goes with every single song,
I could tell some awesome stories about the Stacy lattice top period.
And we'll have our stories later on about the cruise box.
And the brother loves and the lascivious bitties.
And you know what, we'll have those days too.
I'm sure.
Let me see, well, so I have written down here.
We're going to talk written down.
It's on the Blackberry right.
And it says now that this is the cool way.
The cool way to maintain what you're going to talk about.
Of course.
You got it.
Oh, the neon.
I'm going to talk about that.
The pod father neon that Greg Lawley gave me.
So I put it in front of the window is exactly the right dimension for the window.
And I was really excited about it.
And then I went downstairs.
And 24 stories is just way too much.
I mean, I have pictures.
I tried to take pictures of it.
It was really hard because it's just too high up.
And it's not big enough.
You know, it would have to literally be across the whole wall of windows in order for you
to be able to see it from anywhere.
I mean, you can see it.
But you just can't make out what it says.
So now it's in the corner of the condo here.
And I turn it on.
And before I record, I turn it on.
The pod father in green and purple neon is fantastic.
I'll post pictures of it once I get back to the cottage.
Um, now I screw it to promos.
Do you guys remember?
Pom, Pom, Pom, Pom.
The first podcast for the French-speaking Mac community?
Well, it's me, Steph and C.
And I'm back with a German version.
So it's called Pom, Pom, Pom still.
It's just at Pomcast.com slash DE.
Because I have to rework the website at Pomcast.com
to make it in French and also in German.
But also in English for the presentation side.
But basically I'm also on iTunes.
And for the French part, I'm on the iTunes music tour French.
I'm already, I'm always in the top 20.
I follow the German.
It's a little bit complicated.
I'm not in the top 20.
You have to search for me.
You just search for P.O.M.
The hell was exciting.
And you're going to see directly Pom, Pom, Pom, Pom, Pom.
And the variant in German, Pom, Pom, Pom, D.E.
Which you can't listen directly in iTunes.
Subscribe to it.
Listen to me every week.
My name is Steph.
I'm also reachable under the email stuff and see at Pomcast.com.
And that's what I do.
I do it in French.
I do it in German.
And I also listen to the daily source code, for example.
I'll show a dot com.
Recommend listening with at least one foot firmly planted in reality.
I'm finding yourself up all night looking at inappropriate things on the internet.
I don't know if you're going to reach it forward.
Do you find yourself repeatedly showing up late for work?
French fries.
Do not make themselves.
You need to be here.
On time.
Every day.
Luckily for you.
There's an answer.
It's the drag me out of bed.
Wake up call from one wisdom and lucky to trade you.
dot com.
Yeah.
Who is it?
That hell out of bed.
You dirty horror.
That's right.
Wake up calls aren't just for hotel stays anymore.
Now you two can get a personalized wake up call from America's top podcasting drag queen.
Want to wisdom lucky to trade you.
dot com.
If you don't get your fan ass out of bed right now.
Mary, I'm going to come over there and smack you.
Still.
It's one wisdom's drag me out of bed.
Wake up call coming soon.
Head over to luckynitzradio.com for more details.
If you wouldn't have sat around on the internet all night looking at porn.
I wouldn't have to call your sorry.
Now what?
You've never had a drag queen get you up quite like this.
Check it out over at luckynitzradio.com.
I play that promo.
I wanted to play that last time.
It was a long, long time ago.
And that's because you lazy ass podcast.
There's got to make more promos.
Make some fresh ones send them off to me, man.
Promote Podge a submit.
Sorry.
Submit at podshow.com or send it to me.
Add them at curie.com or add them at podshow.com.
And make sure that you put it up on a server somewhere, put the, you know, do your homework,
put the ID3 tags in.
It can be some promos.
I love it, man.
It fills up all the time that I just spend here wasting through my blowhole otherwise.
Hey, I checked out the pod take music network.
These girls are one of the top pod plays at the month.
I know a girl named Betting who wears patting leather shoes.
She just moved from Missouri and she's feeling caliposed.
She says, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, I know it's a damn dashboard game.
That's a damn dashboard game.
That's a darn before me.
the last.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Cut me.
I know it is.
I should promise, I could all get.
No, no, no, no, no, no man better
Who wears my stumbling shoes?
She gets her head on Thursdays, and she dined.
Robin' fools!
Because as hair, hey, hey, into the mirror
Lookin' inside you will burst
But I still watch say you wake up as the sun lives through the sky
But I still watch say you wake up
And she knows that you could die here
You're happy and free, and all that she could be
But I still watch say you wake up as the sun lives through the sky
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Oh, I love him.
Lissivey is Bitties and Betty, big pod play
That this month in the pod save music network
Check it out at music.podshow.com
I'm really sorry, it skipped again
So you've got now five skips
Episode.
So that's where pod castings all about.
We give it to you as it is with the wards everything
All attached to it.
Apologies for that.
I'll have it all fixed.
Usually, strapping the power book to
60 million dollars worth of aircraft
Take it back to the cottage.
It seems to work.
Get it back in its own environment.
Yeah, these are actually a little testy that way.
Okay, that's it.
Have yourself a great weekend.
I might do something over the weekend depending on
the welcome home sex.
I'm going to have with my wife when I get back home.
All right, have a good and everybody.
Have a great Friday, have a great weekend.
Bye-bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.