How are you doing?
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It is Thursday.
What do we have?
January 6, 2005.
Once again from sunny South Beach, Florida.
This is your daily source code.
I'm not, I'm current.
Using the bellipers parting together here in the sunshine.
And I'm not kidding.
It really is true.
Having a great time.
How are you doing?
I want to give you an update on stuff.
But not too long because you're going to do a special type of source code today.
Since, well, I guess basically it'd be just boring to boring or boring.
boring, boring, boring, boring to tell you that we had another great day.
Really got somewhere.
I had some breakthrough moments.
I had some fun.
I had some coffee.
And I guess that would be kind of boring to get it over and over again.
Hey, guess what?
This is the broadband at home.
Apparently actually really works.
I haven't had the balls yet to try and walk Christina through it all.
Because what I'm worried about is that it's not going to work or something will happen.
So I won't be able to get her back up and running on the modem connection.
But someone from the easy net called the Patricia today and said, hey, you know, everything working
okay.
She said, well, I haven't actually plugged everything in yet.
So maybe a little bit later.
Christina also had her first full day of school today at the new school.
She went kind of like an orientation the other day.
And I just spoke to her and she said she's having a great time.
And that makes that puts a smile on my face boy.
Let me tell you because when your kid goes to school and enjoys it and comes home smiling,
that's great.
Particularly after my god.
She was out of school for four weeks.
You know, if you take a Christmas and New Year's in Do account and a week for the move and everything.
Yeah, that was, you know, to have your kids in the home going, I'm so bored.
Please send me to school and when she actually goes to school, she likes it.
That's the kind of stuff that, well, that's the kind of stuff that you want to celebrate with the drum cadence.
Yes, exactly.
That's what we got to do.
Ha ha ha.
Ha ha.
Ha.
Oh man, I love it.
And it looks like we're actually going to get the drum cadence of the day set up on its own feed.
had a little email exchange about that and we're working on that.
I'm not going to do, by the way, you can get the drum cadence of the day through openpodcast.org.
So if you subscribe to that, you'll get it automatically and the whole point is just to get
it on its own feed so you can subscribe to only that without getting anything else.
So I'm not going to play that today in the source code because we have a different type of show.
We, even though it's Dave Weiner, Ron Bloom and Adam Curry here in Miami, we're, you know,
hanging and figuring stuff out, having talks and it's also, you know, don't tell Patricia
or Christina, but, you know, I'm really enjoying the sunshine and the rest and it's kind of like
a little mini vacation in a way, not that I needed one, but it is kind of nice to be totally
involved with yourself and what you're doing and not have any responsibility for anyone else.
That's kind of quote, except for my partners in this case, which is different than my family.
And throughout the week that we've been here, Madge Weinstein has been a part of, you know,
a lot of what we're talking about, Madge will be often used as an example and it's really just
because Madge Weinstein's yeast radio, I don't have to tell you what it is because you've heard,
you've heard Madge Weinstein on this show before, I'm sure you've listened and, you know,
like it or not, Madge Weinstein would never work on traditional broadcast, would not work on radio,
it does not work, you can't do that, not anywhere in the world really, I don't think.
The outrage would be just too big because air waves are not controlled by URI, you would think so,
you would think that we own the spectrum in the air, airways, but we don't, not really,
or we don't have, we may own it, but we don't have control over it. It's other people who control that,
and there's lobby groups, et cetera, and it's very hard to keep stuff on the, look at the United
States, you know, freedom of speech is one of the most important things that we value in the United
States, yet there's all kinds of stuff that you can't say, and this is Howard Stern's major,
you know, I don't think, he's not in for the money, you know, that's basically that's his,
if he had to go out and say, no, I think the money is important to him, but it's, it's not the
number one thing for him in this satellite radio deal, and we're just having breakfast, just got back
from breakfast, and we saw a news item running in the, in the restaurant with Howard Stern,
and he had the whole crew there and Robin, and you know, they were handing out these these
serious radio boom boxes, which is apparently the only way you'll be able to listen to Howard
Stern, if you're not in your car, you know, you have to say, so he's now hawking the boom boxes,
which are ugly, ugly, fugly, and he'll be doing that for a year, you know, he's also getting
stock in the company, so of course it's logical, it's for his own pocket, but he's concentrating on,
now he's selling devices when he wants to be passing along as a message, so anyway,
when when we stumbled across East Radio Madge Weinstein, this to me was like,
yeah, this is the kind of stuff that belongs in our world of podcasting, as an example, because
you don't have to only do this, but Madge has ideas, Madge has thoughts and Madge communicates,
and Madge is probably, or no, I know that Madge does what she does because she wants to try and make
the world a little bit better, so you have to kind of look through the delivery mechanism,
and there's the wonderful payload that she carries with her message, so it's important that
we recognize this, it's important that it's important that you know that she's been a part
of a lot of my thought process over the past couple days, so of course, said, well, why don't I just
call her and have a chat and just see if I can get some more information and share that with the source
code listeners, so I did that, and I did it, well, we tried to set it up a couple of ways,
try to use Skype, I don't know what the fuck is, it may be my computer, but something is very wrong,
I still can't get my email, which makes me think that it is actually, well, something's wrong with
my computer clearly, because other people can get email on this network, so I just haven't had
time to troubleshoot it, I'm going through the web interface, which is a lot of fun, Skype blows,
Skype blows fucking chunks, what on missed opportunity? You know, it still crashes, now you can
select a different sound input, but it's still crashes, you know, so I have everything set up the way I
want it, I want to record and it crashes, because it, and it actually, for a nanosecond, I was able to see
an error message before it crashed, but I've just haven't gotten into it, it's not working right,
it doesn't work for me, it may work very well on Windows, but it doesn't work on the Mac,
so I resorted to my cell phone, which you can use to record conversations, so the quality won't be,
you know, 100%, but still, it's quite amazing that all I had to do was hit a button,
I was recording my conversation, after the conversation, hit a button, it blew too through
my laptop, then what I did is I actually did some processing out of trying to make it sound a
little bit, a little bit better, so a little bit of compression and a few tricks that I put in,
but it's bar like two edits when I had to stop the recording, it's the whole conversation I had.
We're going to get to that in a second, there's one other thing I was really happy to receive
an email from Barry Coral who starts off with saying that she's happy with the things when I
mom are better, you have no idea how good they are Barry. She knows in my Miami, but she said,
I want you to know, oh, it says, I know so much about, okay, oh, I miss Reddit,
maybe it's just read it to you, they'll be easier, of course it's in the show notes, but you
don't have those, next to you, not do you, or most of you don't. Hey Adam, glad that things with
your mom are getting better, I know you're in Miami and hope you're doing okay. I know so much
about you because I've been getting so many emails from your listeners and selling many CDs to
them since you started playing my record every day, there are more. So I want to thank you,
thanks for the support wish you all the very best and 2005 for you and your family, thank you for
making a difference, regards Barry Coral. Well, you know what, it's working and that, I've had
a smile on my face since the moment I saw that email because it's working, the loop is closing,
we're making it work, you know, you have people creating Barry Corals a software developer,
she's creating software, she distributes it on the CD and the, in digital form on the, on the
internet and I'm a user and I'm sharing that and other people sharing it and guess what,
without digital rights management, without, you know, without fucked up contracts that
leave Barry Coral with nothing, she's making money and, and it's working, it's fucking working
and I got to tell you, I'm proud of that. You guys should be too, to me, so we could do some
shit here. So let's play some Barry Coral before we get to Madge Wine, so here's the world you
call home. Let's run for out new confessions of an indie girl and you can buy it Barry Coral.com.
Yeah, you locked the door until you buy some comfort from your old booths. Have your listen to you,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, there's a lump of good music, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Jan ona, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I sure do, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I, yeah
Yeah, if you know you found a found someone to speak up for you
Yeah, I'll wait for you to elevate away to get you through
It's as if somebody's somewhere low close were twice
When you listen to you
I put an up stereo out of you and I need you
All out of the world you come home, you listen to your own
All out of the world you come home
All out of the world
Hello, Matt Weinstein, how are you?
I'm good, thank you
I'm so happy that we could jump this call because I wanted you to know that I've been waiting for you
And I'm so happy you have arrived
Okay, are we on the air yet by the way?
Of course we're on the air
Oh, but I think that's what you're trying to call on the other one
If you're hearing a beep, that's probably my phone
Beeping to let you know that I'm secretly recording our conversation
Okay, so you started you used radio in 1996
I had no idea so and was it the same format?
Were you doing the same type of show?
It was actually mostly about vaginal use
We had a show called East Talk
Is this a big problem, vaginally?
Oh sure, you know, it's amazing because 95% of the women in this country suffer from vaginal use
But you hear all you hear about is that fucking breast cancer with those dodgy and yellow ribbons
vaginal use just as deadly
vaginal use is more deadly because it can cause vomiting, diarrhea
It can cause all kinds of terrible things and it itches
Cancer doesn't itch
vaginal yeast itches and it causes a burning sensation and it's very annoying
I mean cancer, you got it and that's it
You hardly even know you haven't half the time, simply you're in chemo
Well, you're such an expert on this thing
I have been campaigning in my crusade against vaginal yeast
with my first perennial match once again, yoga against yeast it's on
We're going to yoga nonstop until starting earth day and so there's a cure for vaginal use
Okay, well, you can count on my support, you know that
Oh, thank you very much
So I saw that you I don't know how long you've been doing the video
The video clip
Now the video journals I've been actually doing video journals since the 2000
So that has been doing for about 40 years now
And I started doing that because I was doing video advocacy for an art for a friend of mine who was an art students
And she required that everybody do a live journal
Right, live journal was first learning in order to keep them sort of journals of the filmmaking process
I was lazy, I was too lazy to make a written journal, so I did a video
Yeah, because that's what I preferred to do
So I'm glad to hear that that's sort of taking off as well, but in a slow at a slower pace since it's really nothing to play those things on
I got to tell you imagine the yeast radio that's your platform
That's where that's where you need to do it
You don't understand
I'm sitting here, I'm sitting here in Florida with Dave and Ron, you know that because you're smart, you've been following
Right, sure, sure
And by the way, you're totally right about Dave
That he's kind of a pot
No, you didn't say he was a pot, he's not a pot
No, I didn't mean that he's a pot so I meant that he's very smart, but you know that he can be a little bit overbearing
What you said was pretty much right on
And we love him, I love him for it
And by the way, he really likes you
And he wants many more of his psychic reading, and he wants to know
He wants you to be compared again to Nicole Kidman that really helped
Well, I would think it could do so, but he hasn't been podcasting very much lately
And I'd be happy to comment on it if he would put something out there, you know
Oh, you need to love back, because what you're saying
Yeah, I need something, I need to hear and talk about something
Oh, for the reading of the big B
Yeah, I just need to hear him, I got to do the second reading
In order to do it, I need to hear him talking
That's some crap, talking about the McDonalds, for example
It's looking for Wi-Fi, when in fact we all know all he really wanted is a goddamn double-season
Looking for Wi-Fi and a McDonalds
That's bullshit
That looks for Wi-Fi and a goddamn McDonalds
Or a goddamn hamburger
Oh man, I'm a flurry
I love you
I remember that somebody told me in Holland, they called it a McFlurry
I'm a flurry now, because that's learning means like masturbator
Something you know about this, no, no, no, no
A slurry is a slut that does that, no, no, no
What's your background, man?
You know, I think you said, well, I was hurt
Yeah?
Well, I was going to say, I mean, you sound like you have a technical background, I mean, certainly it sounds like you got it
Either you're doing the gusses doing, but someone's rigged up your stuff
Well, you got nice equipment
I do it all myself, bless you doesn't do anything
She's got the early Alzheimer's, early on set Alzheimer's
She's lucky if she can get onto the toilet without self
So I have to do it all myself, plus she lives in Florida, she's actually very close to where you are
And God, I don't have to see her very often, yeah, I'm down there in Miami
At least once every two months, it's a shame we didn't cross heads this side
But I'm here through throughout the weekend, I'll get you a hotel room, come on
Listen, listen, not all of us are, you know, early retirement baby boom.com millionaires
Bruce Harris, which is helicopters in your airplanes
Some of us have to write a goddamn bike chair
No, it was bare feet
Yeah, bare feet is clogged
So technical background
Yes, so I do it, I do it myself, I was a DJ for what, you know, I'm an old lady
I was one of the founders of the little fair, I am a lesbian, lesbian, and known to be technical
And I'm very technically competent, so I do work for a record label and I manage a girl band
God is my excuse
Can I play that on my podcast?
Well, no, they're kind of sucking right now
So I'm really embarrassed to let anybody see of them
However, I do have another girl that I manage, her name is Patty Elvis
She is the best Elvis impersonator
I don't have to be recording
She's a female and she's a lesbian
I'm a lesbian, don't worry, we're a month lesbian, sure, man
So I'll be with her, I'm Saturday, and be doing a podcast with Patty Elvis
Excellent, she's a very hot guy
And so yes, I'm very busy, but basically the label gives me my technical background
I do a lot of computer work on my own, and I'm just an old guy
Anyway, as I said earlier, I've been waiting for you to show up
I knew that you were coming, I knew that you were coming to podcasts
I didn't know who you were or what you're going to be like
But I think you belong in solidly in this community
And I hope you stay, and whatever I can do to help, let me know
Thank you very much, well you can keep listening to me
And you can keep talking about me because I need more listeners
Because this thing is going to grow
I'm still waiting for the big explosion when I don't have to explain to people that a podcast is
And then they treat me like it's my burden to tell them how to click a dog there
And mouse and download a fucking MP3 file
Why everyone on earth can't do this as easily as they can change the channel
It's completely beyond me
You know, you need to get a lot easier
Okay, so what do we need to do to make it easier
You know, you need to be able to stick the iPod in and you get your
You know, to tell you the truth, what it needs is it needs to be part of iTunes
It has to be part of iTunes
How about, how about it has to be part of the iPod itself
Beyond iPod itself, I don't know
But it needs to be, you know, have an interface
But if you have to load Linux in order to get it to be an interface
Forget it, that's not going to work
Somebody needs to talk to Apple is what I'm saying
I realize they may not go for it because they need to sell more content
Apple is not going to want to talk to us
They're not?
No, come on, you reviewed the inside
Well, I hate that set
What about a plug-in like those native from the screen savers
What you have iTunes plug-ins, why couldn't it be that?
Yeah, I will, you know
I think it needs to operate differently
I think you need to deal, it's sort of like mail
You want it to be able to show that it's in red
And you want to know that you've heard this already or not
And you want it to be able to be disposed of automatically
Oh, really? I wouldn't want that at all
Unless they talk about you or me, of course
Well, that should be flashing
Right
Well, I love to talk to you about this stuff
And your input is really important
And your podcast is incredibly
How long are you doing it every day or five days a week
I'm doing it every day
Sometimes I want to do it more
But I feel like I'll burn out
Yeah, I don't know if I'm going to, I do any more of it
Do you think I should do any more of these talking while I'm on the toilet
Because it seems like there's other people doing that
Well, first of all, I really like
The lovelier microphone
I do that in the beginning
When I, when I still was rich and had the castle
I gave way half of my fortune
Oh, I don't know
And I really like when you're, you're walking around
You're doing, you're in your space and whatever
And you know, the shit cast, you know, I, yeah
I mean, what I like is you'll be, you know, unclogging your toilet
And all of a sudden something really beautiful
It's like, you know, the opposite of software
You know, you're, you're dealing with shit on one end
But something beautiful comes out the other
That was the sink that I'm clogged
And you know, I, I wanted to tell the general audience
I suppose I can make this announcement now
But I get unclogged the sink
Right after I ended the podcast yesterday
I successfully unclogged the sink
I knocked down the room where all the night
And it's meant we're sitting and smoking and spending my assessments
My $400 a month on assessments
If they were altering their smoking for they
Generally enough, gave me the plunger so I could plunge it myself
To avoid the $15 charge
And I did, right?
So, yeah, as long as you keep, you know, talking about the political stuff
And the social stuff and, right?
I love that, you know, that's what it is
Yeah, I said today on my podcast
It's like, as his Joan Rivers Howard Stern
And Rush Limbaugh had a massive orgy
Like, you could be the result of that
That's so sweet of you to say that because I was thinking
I feel bad for Howard, because Howard is one of my role models
But I know, if he ever heard my show, he's going to be so goddamn angry
But I got to say, come to him already
Exactly, exactly, and you know what?
I hate to say it
I said today, if I had $500 million, I would, I would
Ask Howard Stern to come to podcast immediately
Here, here's $500 million
And don't have that, but he belongs here, he belongs here
But okay, so he can't talk about it
What's that, what's that beeping?
What beeping?
Hello. Hello.
I hear a beeping, I don't know what the fuck that is, do you hear it?
No.
You know?
I'm not going to like a bomb.
I can't hear what you're saying, I'm going to hang up the phone
So you can call me back, I don't know if the interview's over
If it is to buy, but can you hear me now?
I can't hear you.
Okay, how about now?
Who do you want to tell the phone, and it goes off every day
It's technical office, I never changed it.
Okay, no problem.
Are we still recording?
Yeah, I just wanted to finish up for, and just say,
Thank you very much for coming on the source code
You know, keep being mad, it kills me every single time I hear you.
You also need to be anything else but mad.
But thank you so much, it is a profound pleasure, especially having watched
You all through middle age.
Now I get to see you through menopause too.
I can tell you how touching it is.
We can hold hands together, we can do it.
Yes.
You know, are you older than I am? I'm 40, are you older than I am?
I am actually, I'm in my 50s, but I don't know.
I don't know what my age, and I don't really talk my age, but if you saw me, you know, I don't look at the
Pictures, I saw. You used to date at the moment, what?
I used to date at the moment in 1967.
He doesn't really consider it dating, but we had a short affair in 1967, so that's
to give you an idea of all day. Now after why I look young, that's because I'm timeless.
You are.
And I don't drink, I don't drink at all.
I don't drink either, that's what makes, that's what keeps you young, looking at your skin,
keeps looking beautiful, drinking.
That's true, but you do love the reference, I don't do that neither.
Yeah, but you know, one of the days, I'm not going to kill me.
It's fine, as long as you don't end up with a bad lady like me, because I ended up in a mental hospital
because I, indeed, I'm tired of pills and became morbidly obese at the same time.
No, no, no, that's not my plan.
Yeah, that's a warning to certain people to stay away from the McDonald's.
I have one final question.
What do you want to be when you grow up?
A big fact like.
There you have it.
The Madge wine steam on the daily source code.
Madge already created a did a podcast after we did this, and that's the current one that's up.
And of course, you can get that from the show notes, but it's magic underscore Weinstein dot live journal dot com,
which I guess will soon be six apart or something like that.
Okay, so maybe we have a little bit of idea about magic.
There's a couple things as I listen to this again.
That I realized one, I don't think Madge actually knows about iPodder.
Because as I listen to her describe basically iPodderex or any number of iPodders.
It sounded like, you know, either she doesn't like the replication or the duplication of having the same interface in iTunes as in iPodderex or.
I'll have to ask her about that.
And also that this really is Madge, you know, it's hard to be anything but Madge.
I heard her actually say that, and that's what works.
Folks, it's a reality, it's real life, it's why it's the power of pure intellect every body.
Internet.
Oh yeah.
And that's it for your source code for today.
Maybe we'll interview an artist tomorrow.
I've been thinking about talking to maybe we'll get Leanne Westover from the list of his videos on the on the phone.
I talked to her about what podcasting is doing for her.
But we know it's selling some CDs, which is really, really cool.
And maybe we'll talk to very cool one of these days.
I want to thank very much for tuning in.
Of course comments are welcome through Adam Curry, Adam at Curry.com, sorry.
Or my weblog www.curdie.com.
I'm going to go find my compatrails and we're going to go hang out some more here in Southern Florida.
We're talking soon. Take care. Bye bye.
Thanks for watching.