Daily source code 1 25 2005 transmitters we don't need no stinking transmittance
Autistic it's Adam Curry and it is Tuesday January 25th
Oh man always gotta think about that for a second what is the date today
Hi everybody welcome to the Daily source code coming to you from the affluent
Surrey suburb
It's kill for that's right. It's curry cottage. My name is Adam Curry
This is your Daily source code for Tuesday January 25th
Good stuff to talk about today some techno bits. We're gonna be looking at
Looking at the cast blaster got some pod save tunes for you
And of course some promos some some wacky stuff all the stuff you'd expect from the Daily source code for the next 40 minutes
Taking you down on a journey from nowhere leading to nowhere
That's right as a constant we call it a show
I tell you um yesterday I got three calls from different news organizations and publications
It seems like we're going through kind of like a 2.0 round of press the press is not done with pod casting
I thought that we pretty much had everybody and and everybody had written their piece but
Seeing as this probably is not a passing fad they're coming back for more
If the BBC asked me for one more thing I'm gonna ask him to put me on the payroll
And BBC has so many different radio stations and programs and they seem to be
Rather poorly co-op coordinated actually
Because they don't know you know one side doesn't know what the other side is doing and who is doing what show for what reason?
It's okay though because I don't mind the BBC is pretty much figured me out now
All you got to do is call Adam send him up to the
BBC SCR southern counties radio. That's it sirry university
They've got an ISD and set there. I sit down and and off we go
But even actually let me look on my calendar even for for this week and next week there's all kinds of stuff scheduled
But the angles are a little bit different you know now it's not how to this happen how this come to be now
They're looking for angles
Future you know where is podcasting going what are the big industries saying are they affected by it
So let me see next week USA today and
What did I have here?
I had something there. I think
CNN international
Hold on actually got to type that into the calendar there
CNN international this week
We still have
Hold on I call it a little slow
Yeah, BBC technology show
Aramaica that's tomorrow afternoon that'll be a telephone interview that I try to turn them on to using the ISD and set
Because I know that the BBC rents it out commercially and I don't think we'll be able to do that
But so Aramaica that should be fun
And it just keeps on coming and unfortunately next week USA today
Also wants to take a picture. I'm really worried about that if you heard yesterday's podcast you know why
Because well, I look like an idiot and I'm not I repeat I am not going to post a picture on
The weblog it's it's frightening if if if you want to have frightening just check out yes, there's podcast at the end there
We're Patricia was basically talking about
Well, how ugly I look
So I can hear that the dogs are barking which means that something's going on hold on
Okay gardening services are here
First things first yesterday Scott sent in some trivia. I completely sucked. I only got one right
Let's see if for those who're keeping track chili whack gone gone gone was the first track
Marty balan hearts should I should have known that would go west we closed our eyes. I got that one right and the fourth one
I can't believe I didn't get it of course. I knew this song, but it guess it was like the album version of something that I wasn't
familiar with at least not on the snippet of course prints and
Controversy and as I guess correctly ABC look of love
wound that up love the trivia stuff keep sending it in because
I love looking like a dish
Hello Adam. This is Ted here from TedPod.phone.ms podcasting from Ireland and I was just listening to your show and
Was listening to the guy given out about you trying to earn money and all that kind of oh, okay
This is about the
Was this Sunday show where I played this show has no name. I think is is the name of the show
I got was totally railing on me, but
And there you were trying to explain yourself. What you thought you don't have to explain yourself. So we all want to be the money if you get it
We all want to be the money
And
But at the same time you was right that your show can be an oin
You're right
Like anyone else's show can be and sure you can just turn it off a fast forward or maybe like
Exactly, but show mine can be an oin and if you want to take out how an oin it is
You know come to my website and have a look choose Adam
Excellent, okay. That's a good way to get a promo on the air
But wait did you actually mention your promo at all is Adam? I don't think he mentioned his um his site
Hold on a second I've been
Getting all these through mp3 feedback at gmail.com
Let me see what was this
Was it Chris? I can't remember I'm I'm searching through this now
Uh
Well, shoot
You know what I'll put that in the in the show notes. That's what I'll do
So you know who that was and you just make a note right there that I
Sight address
I'm really starting to get better at the show notes
You probably notice now that I have a link to a real HTML page if you want to take a look at the show notes
The next step
Really should be putting those in the actual post itself I guess instead of providing a link
And I'm just gonna keep on providing the opml file
Because I got it, you know, it's like the raw data so it's XML so it's totally parsable
So there are things that you can that you can do with it. I'm the way we're gonna listen to
A bit of a podcast from event lab where one of the pod squad showed up and
And
Another promo here hold on saying a
Hawaii atom this is John from legal sound check
Where we feature law plus music in less than seven minutes
I'd like to add a bit of the lawyers voice. Oh, last second
Lawyers who do anything that lasts only seven minutes this is a podcast I must hear and by the way
Do you charge by the minute or just by the hour and chop it up in a 10 minute chunks legal equation
We also throw some music into a sort of boardroom mix and type things up rather quickly before I commit corporate career
Hericary
Legal sound check is available under the law category on your ipodder.org directory
You know you really set the bar high on the daily source code atom many thanks for your hard work and innovation
And if you ever need any kind of legal help
Let me know
There are three things I'll send you straight away
My
That's right send lawyers guns and money. That's all we need that'll see
Most action
That's good to see
You know some
Professions some
Legal profession coming into podcasting indeed
I think there's two podcasts listed in the ipodder.org directory
That's where you can find
We'll find any podcast basically categorized by
By topic man. It's a lot of noise in the studio here today people
Talks barking people going nuts. It's a one 42 by the way in the afternoon
Patricia and I went to the doctor this morning
Bright and early she has to get some prescription for her meds
And so I figured I'd go in as well, you know, and the peed in the little cup and everything
Mys will sign up with a doctor here although I gave I get a annual physical for my pilot's license
So I know that I'm pretty much okay in fact
My next checkup is due. What does it do? July. Oh, I also got in touch with the guys from cab air aviation
They're the ones that have the flight school up at black bush
So next week I have an appointment going to go up there going to drink some coffee going to kick some tires and
Hopefully work on you know
Finding the right instructor to help me complete the add-on for my
PPL for my pilot's license. You know, I have the helicopter license just want to get the fixed wing portion now
It's a lot easier actually
If you already have one license because you don't have to go through all the theory again
Don't have to do the test for that
I have to be signed off on have to do the check, you know, I have to demonstrate that I can really fly
And then it's just building up experience, you know, it's renting a plane and going going
Not stopping
until well just not stopping flying take off landing
Navigating
Navigating is not a big deal because I've well I have a GPS
But you know, I've flown I have like six or seven hundred hours that I've flown
Many of which solo so navigation is not an issue in fact in in helicopter navigation sucks because you've got
Basically your hands and feet tight up all the time you can take your hand off the collective
And you know and lock the friction down so you can you know basically
Have one hand free to touch controls or whatever you need to do but
In an airplane it's like you know metal to metal get that fucker in the air it rotates speed
Just pull back on the stick it goes up you flip on the auto autopilot and
That's what the asteroids are for after that, right?
Anyway, so that's that's next week. I'm sure we're doing some sound seeing or something from there
And I came across a podcast from event lab
And it was interesting because there were a couple of people in this podcast who I knew Eric Rice was on this podcast
And I've actually
Drop this podcast into a new feed which we'll be talking about in a second
Because you should really listen to the whole thing. It's it's like an over an hour
But in this show on the phone or on I think it was on the phone or on Skype all of a sudden who shows up?
But our good buddy member of the pod squad Michael go hey gohagan
They even started off the show. How do I pronounce your name Michael gohagan
You know him from from real reviews and I'll just play a little snippet of it just to go to wet your appetite
And of course you'll find a link to
To this actual show in the show notes because he was saying a lot of really good things
We're talking about
Making money with podcasts
What you have to do to evangelize it. How you actually record your podcast what you need for a podcast and also just telling other people what podcasting is all about
I also though and aware that that means that it's gonna take a little bit longer
to explain to somebody
Exactly what's going on
And so if I if I meet a friend as a Japanese yesterday, of course you go through the podcast thing
Oh, I have to have an iPod and you know, eventually they get it once they got it
You're set but at the same time if you you use radio
Even though there's that word
Okay, I get it so it comes to me. Okay, you know then maybe you explain that it's stored on the computer and that type of thing
So as an example if I go to call a movie studio to ask for a screen or DVD and I'm real reviews from MWG blog a podcast
I'm gonna get one reaction as opposed to I'm calling for real reviews radio. Yeah exactly exactly we've talked about this before
I think even when it comes if you're doing stuff
on location for instance and you and you want to interview somebody
Part of the whole deal is you've got it, you know
You just got to have the right equipment. It has to look right doesn't have to cost the same as what the pros use
But essentially if you're gonna stick a mic in someone's face make sure it kind of has that professional look
You know, because that's you're gonna get a very different response from from some people
And of course you you may decide that you want to very you want someone to treat you as you know
Something not important and perhaps amateur or it's in that case. You might use a different type of microphone
Specifically for that reason the big thing though is the mic cube you gotta have the mic cube
Which slides up over the microphone and you know and the the big TV and radio guys have have their channel number on it or their call letters
Whatever
And so indeed if you say real reviews radio, you know, that's a
That's a sounds like a much bigger deal if you're dealing with people who need to hear that
It can also be very advantageous
It to get a different type of response
As I think Michael was pointing out by
You know showing up with a good quality perhaps, but maybe more like a mr. microphone type deal
You're gonna get someone will you probably able to catch unawares you know and say things that you wouldn't expect him to say normally
Right that was part of my idea behind creating
KSS X I mean I have a small studio built boutique studio of that kind of is responsible for doing you know anything that I
Essentially do is just okay if it needs to be more professional sounding I have a studio name on it
And I found KSS X kind of my accident because I have a lot of friends that do traditional pirate radio
And I have had friends that are you know on the air that work for clear channel and so I love that podcast and kind of puts everything in the middle
You know it's a little bit better
Than pirate, but it's also you know a little bit more real than what you might hear you know that wacky morning, too
Kind of think you mean everybody get bored of this the crazy morning
All right event lab podcasting challenges the title of that show do check it out
And I show also put that in this new feed that I'm gonna tell you about in a couple of minutes
Let me see where was I here
What's all that racket oh man what they're doing outside
So I still don't by the way haven't seen anyone actually connect the wires now that the pipe is
Has been tunneled through the garden up to the house
And you know today I'll hook up that router and see if the the big mega line is working
I thought it was those guys for second outside, but no, it's definitely the gardener
Yes, they were talking about the OPML
That's a part of the I potted out org directory that people are using for the applications and other directories
And I've got an email from calum who says that there is
A great essay that Joel Spolsky wrote about double byte encoding it's titled the absolute minimum every software developer
Absolutely positively must know about unicode and character sets no excuses
Now calum sets it's very readable explain the subject to him more clearly than anything else you'd ever come across
And I have started to read that and yes, I'm starting to understand that
It's not trivial stuff
That's not trivial, but give that a read
It will explain some of the issues that we're that we're running into although really I found that
You know there's this OPML stuff, which is great because OPML is really it's a four hey on
Is it the gardeners?
I thought they came on Thursdays
Yeah, so we can clean up the poop the dog shit
He closed the door from me, huh?
Thanks
It gives me much better acoustics in the studio
Okay back to the pod squad or the OPMLs what I was talking about so I use an outline I use
The outline of your find in radio user land or frontier and I use it for almost everything I got it
Got to tell you it's great. I'm my brain works well without liners
So when you save an outline document, that's what the format is it's OPML outline processor markup language which is
XML essentially and this is adopted far and wide particularly for subscriptions
But when it's an RSS subscriptions reading list if you will as an OPML file
These are the types of files that you'll see almost every single aggregator and I believe
Most of the podcasts though I iPodders
Also are able to subscribe
Through OPML files now the file that I've currently if you ever seen this the pod squad there's there's links to it
I did it a little differently
But I think that's kind of confused everything in everybody including me
So what I'm going to do now is I'm going to create a new pod squad
OPML file
Excuse me, which will include like you know the 12 or what 10 or 15
Podcast that I listen to so it's you know it's a personal thing obviously, but
It's people that you know we've been working with and pod casting for for a while
No, I think it's great and you know it's it's my my personal pod squad, right?
It's whatever I think belongs on that list. I'm going to make it into a traditional OPML file
so that
You can actually just download this file drag and drop it into your iPodder and it will subscribe to all of those
Feed so I'm not going to make it too big obviously
There's something else for the iPodder
Guys to think about you know if I deliver an OPML file that someone wants to subscribe to and you just by dragging it in
Perhaps we should have an automatic only get the first pod cast from each feed setting or something like that
So we don't swamp people with you know hundreds of megs just from one single
Swoop of the mouse to subscribe
Additionally in the iPodder.org OPML of the directory. I'm going to put
The same pod squad file in there only it won't be RSS links. It'll just be linked to the RSS files. I think
Oh
This is a call actually I want to take hold on cool. I put you on pause again. I'm getting pretty good at that
You didn't want to hear that call. I did but you didn't show
Back to pod squad right so I'm going to put a pod squad node into the iPodder.org OPML
Which will be the same as all of the other
iPodder.org directory nodes so that you can actually auto you know subscribe to that to each individual feed
From your iPodder software. I think I've gotten all the buggies out now
so that
So that it's not breaking the directory browsers in the in the iPodder software
So you should be able to then just you know click and subscribe to those then of course
I want an HTML version
So you can sample sample those and I guess
Maybe maybe there should be one feed for the pod squad so you just that's actually an interesting idea
I don't know if that's the right way to do it
What yeah, let me know what you think about that if I gave you one feed for the pod squad and
Essentially whenever a new show comes out from any of the pod squad podcast you automatically receive that
I don't know if that's a good idea. I guess it's the same thing if I guess that has more power if you
Subscribe to all of them because then if you don't like something you can unsubscribe. Yeah, that makes more sense
I guess okay, so anyway I'm working on that really been thinking a lot about cleaning up
pointers and stuff
Getting the show knows working a lot better
You know just so we can I just got to keep my head straight and you know be able to see everything also another
little test that I did
I
Started a podcast feed which I pointed to yesterday from my weblog grade calm
For sound seeing tours and
This is my first attempt at a feed burner feed and I got to say they've got some pretty interesting shit going on
The most exciting I guess is that you can actually look at statistics and see
I'll pull up the statistics right now so I released this yesterday
And it's essentially no more than a
An RSS feed that you can subscribe to and whenever I come across a great sound seeing tour
I'm going to plug that into the RSS feed so it'll auto download to your
To your PC or to your iPod or your MP3 player
On the stats side if got some you know, it's good. It's exactly what you want to see as a as a programmer
I mean as an audio programmer someone who's you know wants to know what what you know how many people are subscribed
What they're using so I'm looking here at these stats
Pretty interesting
So they have something they call circulation
And circulation is their attempt at saying well, okay, these are the actual number of subscribers
They also give you hits how many times how many times the feed has been hit, but so since yesterday
I have a 446 subscribers to the sound seeing
Tour what's interesting though is this pie chart that tells you what type of iPoders or
Aggregators or what they call here readers are actually subscribed to your feed
So check this out for some stats
Interesting to see that fire fox the live bookmark so that's the RSS functionality that fire fox has bundled in with their with their browser
accounts for 22.4%
iPoder is
Percent that's I presume the lemon version. Yeah because iPoderex is 3.7% that's about right for the mac market
Thunderbird 2.0 8.1% so I guess that's just a regular browser
Excuse me 8.9% is unidentified
net news wire 13.4% and other readers account for 25% so
From a browser perspective
fire fox
is
higher ranked
Then internet explorer wouldn't have expected that really
And of the readers and agregators
Fire fox live bookmarks is the top followed by iPoder followed by net news wire
Follow by all the unidentified followed by Thunderbird iPoderex
And then it goes down to oh this and more here feed reader universal feed parser intro v news
CFN network this is cool. I got to check these out these like all iPodd
Variants my god there's a whole list blog matrix yager feed demon news gator
nimic pluck sharp reader
Someone's actually using curl
Which is a command line
HTP glide I guess on the mac i Potter v a j Potter. I'm sorry j Potter v cool. That's a 2.0
No, oh dot 8.0 a wasu what the hell is a wasu?
A wasu is a free windows news reader that runs in the background on your computer. Okay blog lines kinger
A kinger has a little
exclamation mark next to it, which is interesting kinger says
So web based blog aggregator, but kinger does not currently report the number of kinger subscribers to your feed when it
Request the feed meaning I guess that others do
But I see my yahoo is way down on the list so I guess they're not reporting either or just no one subscribe through my yahoo
I'm gonna keep my eyes on this see if I can pick up any trends
It's definitely cool to have the you know some more expanded stats than then what I'm normally used to which is basically just an access number so
Cool stuff and
Give that feed a try
You know whenever I come across something they have a little bookmarklet
If I see an MP3 or I'm listening to an MP3 that I like I just click the bookmarklet and it brings up the
The feed details. I just have to add a name and a title and it goes right in
So yeah good stuff now. I know why so many people are using feed burner and it does really allow you to
You know add enclosures to your feed that normally you might have if you're using a web blog system that doesn't support that so
Let's talk about class
Class blaster for a second. This is
Was it was it Sunday or was it yesterday only that I was talking about you know wanting something very simple
Well, I can just you know have a folder on my desktop drop a file into it and have that automatically be part of an RSS feed and
I got tons of email all kinds of pointers and ideas and scripts and you know
Everyone has has thought of this
I am certainly not you you can coming up with this idea
But none of them really
Would work or at least wouldn't work for me. I could not get them to work
It seems that if you want to use Pearl the Mac has a very
Typical Pearl installation
Now anyway Craig Meyer hook me up big time he created a special install of the podcastmatic that I can Bradley wrote
Did I play the promo for yesterday?
Basically setting it up so that it works in you know the default Mac and Tosh install whatever it is
That was really cool that he did that for me and this is great
So here's here's the way I have it set up
I set up a
Separate directory on my dot mac account so I basically just drop a file in there drop an MP3 in there
It uploads and
I still have one manual step that I do right now, but I'm gonna make that automatic
You know then I just run this one command and basically what it does is it goes in it
checks out how long the file is it parses the ID three tags and then creates an HTML file as well as a
An RSS file which to me looks validated perfectly
So it works
You know it's
The system is there all I need to do now of course is just make the the magic folder that I that I like so much
So I drop it in and from there copies it over seamlessly and once it's copied over it then
Triggers the the update the feed command so that'll be my a little project for this afternoon
But this is good. This is really starting to get somewhere. This is the type of podcast functionality
I think that we need to make for the masses because it's so fucking simple it's like an inbox and outbox
You know just drag this into the outbox all you have to do all you have to know is how to fill out the ID three tags
You can do that in iTunes on the Mac or Windows and there's a whole slew of programs that will let you create those
So essentially once you've set up your configuration file, which of course no one in the right mind really wants to do
But let's say that your your file is configured so that your feed reads what it should read
You know in this case I've called up my test cast blaster feed or whatever
Everything else is automatic all you have to do is fill out as much information as possible in the ID three tags
And you're good to go. So I will be experimenting with that and of course. I'll have the feed to the cast blaster feed
I have like three MP3s in there now. It's just going to be stuff that I think you should listen to
it's
Stuff that I may have exerved in the source code, but can't play the whole thing so for instance
What I just played for you that that bit from
The podcasting challenges with Michael Gohagan that's in there
So check out the the show notes for today's podcast and you'll be able to subscribe to that feed let me know
You know what you think and if anyone else is working on more of these
Simple dragon drop creator podcast systems
Let me know you know this is this is cool stuff and this is the way to get more people
Indepod casting which you know and of course I was just thinking not only here's his a feature that should add of course
It should ping audio.weblogs.com
Once it's updated the RSS file so many different things to think of
And of course thank you all very much for pointing out to me. Yes, they have to have played the mix of the the biddies with you
Don't owe me
With that was the mix
That young pollette did in in Holland the mix with the Dutch singer on the rehauses
I of course knew that it was a cover version and I
Not only did I know this because I'm a disc jockey and have all the Lawrence welka albums
Also, it was reiterated on cover bill to show that the biddies were on recently
So I don't know if if you knew that if he was just like surprised or thought that there was some plagiarism going on
But a lot of people were really friendly enough to send me the original which you'll be probably remember as this one done by
Leslie Gordon
Here's you don't only on the daily source code
I
Oh
You
r
I don't tell you what to say I don't tell you what to do
So just let me be myself That's all I have to do I don't care, I love you, I'm free, yeah, I love you to be free
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
Now I know who I'm doing the best, I love you
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
lives in Amsterdam, and he did a walking tour of the Albert Cup market in Amsterdam.
It's really funny because of course I can understand everything that's going on
on the background. You should see his setup, he's using, I guess it's I think it's a
Bluetooth wireless headset and it looks just like, you know, he would be talking
on the telephone, he's walking through Amsterdam, but besides it being an excellent
sound-seeing tour and of course you'll find it in the show notes for today and in that new
sound-seeing tour podcast feed. He also, he did something really, really cool. Let me see if I
can, I'll fire it up, let's do the beginning of it and he explains how, you know, it's basically
it's more than just a sound-seeing tour, why it's a multimedia tour. The bicycle mark audio
I'm sorry it's a commuter K actually, it's what I meant. So it is Saturday, January 22nd, 2005,
and I'm bringing you our first sound-seeing tour in Amsterdam, and one more thing before I go,
thank you to no coins for leaving me a little tip in the tip jar, funding the podcasts for a
couple of more months, and here we go. Okay, check this out.
All right, good morning from Amsterdam, or whatever, good evening, wherever you are,
it's morning here, about midday, and I'm in the pipe neighborhood of Amsterdam. Of course you'd
be in the pipe neighborhood, it's my favorite neighborhood, which would be in the south, just behind
the Heinrich and Brewery, which you may know and love so well. Okay, so you didn't know it,
this is, yeah, like the sweeper says, the bicycle mark audio communique, and today I'm going
to take a sound-seeing tour of the Albert Kite market, where basically I intend to
describe everything to you in words, maybe describe the smells, the feels, and I hope the sounds
will just come across pretty well. Just listening to him talk about it, I can already feel the
fresh air and all our stuff and shit go away. I'm busy, please, can't you turn on podcasting?
Here for yourself. A lot of people running around, so a lot of people are going to be looking at
me when they're going to what I'm doing, but it's Amsterdam, so we don't, we don't tend to really
give a shit. Also, I brought my digital cam along, just to be taking photos, which you can
follow along in my flicker photo show. How cool is this? And he does this really high-tech thing
in a really old school way. Check it out. And what I'll do is I'll play the law in order
sound, and that means change pictures. And so that reminds me of, when I was a kid in school,
you know, and you'll be listening to some audio tape, and you have a workbook that goes
along with it, and you hear the, and that means you had to turn the page. In fact, I think it was,
maybe that was with the Bonsio-Line Bonsio-Missio-Lip Professor,
turn the page. Anyway, you got to check it out, some great photos. He actually forgot to
continue to take pictures about halfway through, but totally new way of listening to a sound
scene tour. It works perfectly well without the pictures, by the way. But it's, I did it with
the pictures. I didn't, you know, skip ahead, although, unfortunately, in the flicker slide show,
it already shows you what the next frame is going to be in a little mini previews. That kind of,
yeah, that kind of ruins it a little bit. But awesome. Awesome. Looking forward to many more
communicates from our buddy bicycle mark. You'll like this. It's like an MTV slamer. The
ballot of Carson Daily. This is Master Pierce Weirder. Tony Goldmark brings it to you.
Here's the tale of a cowboy. I'm sure we all recall. We all know about his rise,
and we know about his fall. He was raised in Santa Monica, but he moved old and why,
where he'd host the daily countdown. The time squares through the owes so high.
Carson Daily. He was close up to your nail Carson Daily. He heard the man's all screaming
Yale. He didn't introduce his attendant videos from the time first studios and soon into
obscurity. He failed. Just like in a tea and Martha Quinn and other names at Bailey Carson Daily.
Every day and three on MTV, it's see him on the tube. When his head awful,
a hairspray just a smile and lack of food. Playing videos by boy bands and going to bleed up the
wise doing if you wanted steady paycheck. He had to pretend he liked him too. He would interview
celebrities and play their world for me or playing everyone from antsink all the way to Britney Spears.
He would make a lot of votes no longer want their MTV by making intellectual observations written by
next angle child of three. Carson Daily. He was close up to your nail Carson Daily. He heard
bands all screaming Yale. He introduced his attendant videos from the time first studios and soon into
obscurity. He failed. Just like Julie Brown and Jesse Camp and other names at Bailey Carson Daily.
But his fame was very short. About a year 2005, he assumed that he could get most any woman
dead or alive. And so after a failed marriage to actress Tauri, he got caught up into what
Kales Ever Cowboy. Here on a screen. Yeah, pretty soon. His rhyming star came plummeting to Earth.
Now he's worth less than eight Italian Lera. It happened one day when he wasn't at the studio.
And they realized he was late. They finally found him in the suit. He ordering his birth
in a closet with Christina Acculara. And they locked him up in prison on the charge of violating
jail bakes. So he spent the next five years in Santa Pino Institution every morning in the
showers. He received his retribution and meanwhile TRL was taken over by Tom Green. And since
then Hollywood squares his own the place Carson hasn't seen Carson Daily was close up to
Carson Daily. He heard the fans all screaming jail. He introduced his top 10 videos from the
time for studios and soon into obscurity. He failed. Just like Kennedy and Martha Quinn and other
names at family Carson Daily. He was the host of TRL, Carson Daily. He heard the fans all screaming
jail. He introduced his top 10 videos from the time for studios and soon into obscurity.
Too bad it kind of fades out. It's like a cop-out should have ended that song.
The ballad of Carson Daily just want to say a couple things about that. First of all it's funny.
You know it makes me chuckle but it's really not fair. Carson actually had that job. I did before
it was TRL total request live. It was MTV's most wanted and before that it was dial MTV.
And the same format. You know you call you vote you vote through the by the phone lines
that used to be free by the way when I was still there. It was free free call or just like a regular
toll call. And now of course I'm sure you pay money for that for voting and you know well
rightly so but that's how much has changed. So I had that job and you know when you leave MTV
and I'm not quite sure why he left or if he's even gone I guess I guess he's gone.
I don't know him personally. Although he probably still works with the exact same camera
people that I used to work with. A lot of people are they have been there for 20 years at least.
It's been 10 years since I've been there. But you know people are it's hard when you leave
a gig like that you know MTV it's like you're you're so fucking pigeonholed you know if you think
it's a springboard to anything oh that's just not certainly not in show business. I mean MTV
is weighed down on the ladder and of course you make no money and that's very relative. I mean
of course you make money you make good money by all standards you're in the richest one
percent of the world. But it's not like showbiz crazy Hollywood fucking money no way no no no no.
I see when I was at MTV until what I made I made the first year $150 and the second year
$175,000. Great money don't get me wrong don't send me feedback that you know I'm fucked up for
sake but it's not the 10 million you know Tom Cruise gets for a movie of course it doesn't
require the same type of talent either. But it's the best money you're ever going to make as you
know as a VJ because from there I don't think you really can go no one's really been successful
at moving further in show business and what I'll do this is a good idea I'm going to get Ken
Clark on a Skype call Ken was the talent coordinator he does a podcast with Cindy who who I also
worked with it's the Ken and Squip show and I'll get Ken on the honker and we should just have a
chat and let's just run down the list and let's see what everyone's done because he keeps in contact
or knows pretty much what everyone is doing and they're actually doing some interesting things so
that's a promise for a future maybe we'll do that tomorrow he's I think he's on tour now or whatever
but maybe when he gets back home or when we can work out the time differences between West Coast
and London we'll hook that up. One more mention before I go remember Craig Patchett's daughter who
read the Bible verse couple months ago I had it on the playdown the source code
she is now doing her own podcast which probably makes her the youngest podcast or eight years old
which actually Rick from ICM Ross and me the Zemois says that beats out Matthew Bishop by six years
so there's a link to her show at it's a part of the godcast category and the godcast network
actually and you can find that at godcast.org of course through ipod.org in the directory
that's it for the show 43 minutes little longer than normal actually I think I've been running
consistently over 40 minutes so I think got to keep a tight I'll be back tomorrow it's going to be a
real busy day not quite sure what time I'll have a show up for you gonna try and get it up in the
morning hours for me which means it'll be ready for everyone's state side even before you go
or in the comments add them at correct calm if you're going to send me an MP3 file send it to
MP3 feedback at gmail.com all the episodes of the source code and the podcast feeds subscriber
at dailysourcecode.com the weblog www.curry.com is that enough fucking information to rewind and
replay if you need to hear it again I'm out I'll see you tomorrow right here on the source code
bye bye