Delta CR Charlie 2.0 9.0
16 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hello everybody.
The source code for July 15.
I've been rebooted.
Well, it's what you get for not using the cast blaster.
It's the daily source code.
Today we have the studio set up in super configuration mode
because we're going to have a guest on the show.
Joining me in about eight minutes or so will be CC Chapman from Boston.
I see she's got some exciting stuff to talk about,
which I've been hinting at more or less for the past couple of weeks.
So we'll find out about the pot-safe music network on today's daily source code.
Sorry about yesterday's a snap-hoo.
Many of you may have gotten the file or maybe had to download it manually.
I guess the short-term memory that goes first, what I had done
as I had done the show notes and published everything,
but forgot to upload the file to the servers.
Me and help one of my friends.
I suck.
It gets even worse than that.
Since we're using Akamai, what Akamai does, it goes in and says,
okay, I've got to get this file,
dsc-25-o7-14.mp3.
And it says, oh, it's not there.
Then it returns an error and then I start uploading,
then it starts giving the cash-basically pieces of the file.
And I learned a lot about the content distributed distribution networks
last night's experience, so won't happen again.
Alright, let's kick the weekend off just right.
A dog from mashuptown.com sent me great one to kick off today's daily source code.
This is something that we're kind of bringing the right mood for the weekend.
I got sex and drugs and rock and soul on your daily source code.
And I got sex and rock and soul on your daily source code.
I got sex and rock and soul on your daily source code.
You know, it's going to be outlawed.
man is going to come down on us. I wish that there was a way to actually, you know, really
do something with those mashouts, but it's, uh, it's become just impossible in the record
business to do this. You know, it would take months of clearances for every little sample
that's used. And, well, so let's just enjoy it as long as we can. What you hear in the
background, of course, is the lovely Converre. It's on, uh, on low today. Since, uh, we have
a nice, uh, son, but there's also about, uh, 10 knots of wind coming out of the west, which
is basically blowing, uh, some cool air in, so it's much, much nicer today. I'm so happy, uh,
just the past couple of days have been unbelievably hot here in, uh, in the cottage, uh,
which has been, I'm not, I'm not complaining, but, you know, it's like, and now you have to
record something, which means, you know, it's hard. It's hard to get motivated when it's really,
really hot. Video extreme is positively proud to produce and present Professor
Pee's porn panorama, a podcast featuring adult movie and novelty reviews, erotic readings and
assorted brands and raves from Professor Pee, and the staff of Washington's premier porn palace
that our experts do the dirty work for you. Really, we don't want, we watch bad porn, so you
don't have to, and play with wimpy vibrators, and crappy lube. Professor Pee's porn panorama
at video dashingstream.com, don't forget to dash.
Hi Adam, this is Father Oadric. I've launched a new podcast called The Secrets of Harry Potter.
In this podcast, I'll answer all sorts of questions about the magical world created by JK Rowling.
Is Harry Potter good or evil? Why is there a unicorn in book one? Did the philosopher stone really
exist? Why is Harry's alcohol had weak? And did the Pope really condemn the Harry Potter books?
Will the role of evil lord Voldemort be played by Bill Gates in the upcoming movie?
If you want to know the answers, subscribe to The Secrets of Harry Potter on www.CatholicInsider.com.
Ah, the good father's at it again! First it was the Da Vinci code, and tonight at midnight in the UK,
the new Harry Potter book is being released. Kids are going to be lining up in
fun of bookstores in the middle of the night, and unbelievable, and they've had a lot of press
moving up towards this release. Particularly here in the UK, of course, because JK Rowling is from
the United Kingdom. I don't know if all the Harry Potter movies, I think certainly the first one,
she insisted that it was filmed on location and in the studios here in the UK. So she's pretty
much a hero over here. Estimated worth, I think, is 750 million pounds. Because I read the
financial times, the newspaper I'd like to read, and so they've always had the financial angle,
and about this Bloomsbury publishing company. It's really quite an interesting story. They've
really done something great, and I'm so happy because kids are reading. That's pretty damn
important. Who cares if it's Harry Potter? Now, of course, there's been this big controversy about
what the Pope supposedly said about Harry Potter, and if you go over to Catholicinsider.com,
Father Rodrigues, not only these two Harry Potter podcasts, and I don't know if there's going to be more
in the series, and he really should listen to him. They're really good, but he also has links to stories
about what the Pope really said, et cetera, and there's also, he was, he just sent me an email about
how podcasting has revitalized Vatican radio, and there's a lot of cool stuff that they're doing,
and they seem to be re-energized, and it's just nice to see that. He sent me a press release through
email, asked if he had an online source, that I could point to. So if it's there, I'll put it in the
show notes, obviously, for today. Okay, so let me position the mic a little bit here. I've set
up the studio so that we'll hopefully be able to get a good connection here on CC through Skype.
So let me just get him on the phone on the Skype's. Hey, CC, how you doing? Good man, what's up?
Hey, home fries, it's all good. It's all good. Today it certainly is. That is for damn sure.
So, where were you born, man? Where was I was born in New Hampshire? Really? Born in
born and bred raised up in a New England. Oh, man, was your family's rich? Yeah, not boy. No,
not definitely not a privilege of bringing in all of this. Okay, damn sure. All right. So, CC,
I've been talking about about, you know, this pod safe music network for for weeks, maybe months,
I guess. Yep. And, you know, today, I guess, is the day. Why don't you want you to tell me what's
happening? It's funny. I've been talking about it too. I was listening to an old interview. I did
two months ago that just barely got put up on a podcast the other day. We're at at no sack.com
with no stacks of dot com. Yeah, N.O. S. A. C. It's the one in Bergek show. Love it. And there's some
friends of mine. So I talked, you know, they're good buddies of mine, but I talked about this like two
months ago saying, yeah, this has got to go live soon, blah, blah, blah. And I listen to it this week.
And I'm like, yeah, it will be absolutely. So it's very cool. I mean, the pod safe music network.
I guess it's safe. Yeah, by the time this goes out, I mean, pod safe music network.com,
it's going to be the place to make it easier for podcasters to find pod safe music and for artists to
submit their music. And, you know, right now it's tough. I mean, you know, you've got these podcasters who
would love to play pod safe music if they can find it, but they got to take time to go to, you know,
great sites like garage band and my space stuff and go around. But it's tough. I mean, I've done it.
It's not easy. But not only do you have to search through stuff by downloading things or that
everyone has a different way of looking at it with real player or whatever, but you also have to
see if they give you permission to play it on your podcast, because officially you need permission.
I mean, it's not like every independent song out there. You can just grab and play on your podcast.
I mean, exactly. And you see it all the time, you know, people hear a song on one person's
podcast and assume that they can play it. And it's not the way it should be. And you do have to
get permission and it can take time and you're running around and we want to make it easier. And what's
great about this is so from our disposition, I mean, our just comes to this website and they say,
you know what, I want to share these two songs for want to share this whole. Right. Whatever they want.
Right. And they upload those songs and by uploading it, I mean, they're telling the world,
hey, if you're a podcaster and you want to register for this site, which is free for everybody,
you know, sign up, you know, I'm submitting these two songs in any podcast or who registers on this
site, can download it and play it, you know, as long as they, you know, play the usual rules, you know,
they link to the artist, they give, you know, the proper plug to the artist, so the artist gets to credit.
Right. And on the flip side, I mean, an artist, a podcaster comes in, they register and they get
access to all this music that's just sitting there that they don't have to ask permission for, because it's
already been granted. I've been, I've been working on, I've been working with the beta for the last
thing, two daily source codes. And I'm, I'm signed in as a podcast. I don't can actually sign in as a
listener as well as a podcast. Not yet. It's coming. Listeners, though. I mean, anybody who doesn't
register can come in right now in stream, it's funny. Oh, I've already got emails from the artist
asking about this. They can stream any of the songs. They can't download them, but they can listen to
every, every song you see hasn't really played a little flash play right next to it. Streams it right
down so you can listen to it. Listeners, we'll be able to register soon and be able to, you know,
sort of devote and plug their artists, you know, and show their love for it, but not yet.
So it was, it was really, what I liked about it, and this is the part that I provided my input on,
is so I go and I have my own little area in the PodSafe Music Network, which was also my show
information, which I just, I got highlighted on one of the refreshes that I did on the home page,
which was nice. And I can go into the library into the database, let's say I just call it a library,
and I can search for different types of genre of music, or if I'm looking for something specific,
or I can browse through it, and then I can listen to it sample it, you know, just by clicking on a
button on the page, and then I can add it to my playlist, and then I downloaded it for playing it
on my show, and then next time I go back, I just, you know, it's like a little bit of admin,
by saying, you know, register, what does it, what does it actually say? It says, uh, we can actually
say that I played this track, which is important. You don't have to do that part, and the other thing
too is you don't actually have to download the track, you can actually play it live right there,
if you're set up. Exactly. Exactly. But what's cool about coming back and saying, like, hey,
I just, you know, I just played slim on episode, you know, 40 of accident hash. And it's a form that
takes you through that, right? You don't have to fill out all this stuff yourself. All you do is you put
a name of it, name or number of an episode, it's just a text field that's up to you, and you say the
date, and what's cool, what's why that's cool is because then on the artist page, if I go to look
at slim or, you know, if it's a Van Gogh, you go to that page, it's going to show the last five
podcasts that played that song. And it's going to link over and likewise, if I go to, you know,
the daily source code profile, it's going to show the last five tracks that I played exactly. Right.
And the listener could just be an invention. And very soon, we're going to give the artist
the ability to actually, you know, go in through there, you know, login and see the actual dates
and link to the shows. So that way, they can, you know, because artists want that stuff. They want to
put in their press kits and send it out to people. And so we're trying to make it easy for everybody.
So, um, so that there's this data, obviously, that, um, that is, you know, being a mass that
can be used for some great statistics, which are right there on the site, such as what I have here
I had hold on a second. It was, uh, most listens, uh, top rated and most pod play. So I presume that
that's coming from people, uh, coming and checking out, listening, just by clicking on the play button.
The pod play one actually comes from the thing I was just talking about where the podcaster says,
I played this song. That's where most pod play comes from. Most listens is how many people actually
just clicked on that little streamer and listen to the, to track and top rated is we're going to have
the ability so that you can come in and give a one to five star rating on any, on any, on any track.
And then there's also the ability to click on, you know, show me top 10 artists and he'll show
those categories in one big, long list. So what I like about this pod play thing is, um, in the,
and I've talked about this many times, but I might as well do it in, uh, in the quote, real radio
business and which is completely, you know, they're, they're joined at the hip to the music business.
The way it works is, you know, a record comes out, but it's carefully scheduled with promotion,
predominantly radio promotion and the way it works is, and you know, it's not like everyone's all,
you know, in cohoots with each other, but the guy in New York who's making the music list for
the radio station there is definitely looking at what the guy in Los Angeles is adding to his playlist.
And they do that through a number of, of different ways, but the, the main, the main publication
for that is radio and records. And in fact, on the back page, and it shows you exactly what each
station is playing, what they've added, what they've dropped from their playlist. And then,
I guess, eventually we could go on to like charts, right? We could do, um, the data's going to be there.
Yeah, we could do lots of that. I love that. And one thing I want to stress because I know
there's been lots of talk about this in the podcasting world is when, when people see this, I know
the first thing they're going to see is around the front page or if you go to profile page of any of the
podcasters, you're going to see links like subscribe, Vx, and now you're going to see an iTunes link.
And I just want to stress to the podcasters that the podcasters are entering all that data.
So there's none of this locked in stuff that people have been worried about. I mean, in your profile,
you actually say, hey, I've got an iTunes link. Here's the one I want. Yeah, I've got updates,
which is crucial. Yeah, I did, too. But when iTunes went live, we had to add that iTunes excited.
It takes you right to the iTunes page of your website. If you're in there, hopefully,
hopefully Apple is getting everybody in there. Yeah, and we're talking to them. We're trying to,
we're trying to help them out and fix some stuff. Yeah, they need some help. So let me,
I'll tell you, I have lots more questions. Let me play podsaic music right now. This is,
actually, I went to the page today. You know, I got to put this stuff closer together.
I went to the my most pod play and let's see. I don't know how to pronounce it. We need a pronunciation guide,
phonetics next to it. To your, I'm not sure. I'm not sure. I'm going to say it either. Yeah,
I'm not sure. Anyway, the most pod play on podsaic music network. I'm going to give that one a play.
This is a filled and we'll be right back and we'll talk some more. Okay, so you see. Cool. All right, stay with me.
We've all four is the same thing that has us yearning for heaven in our youth. I'm the same
pain that has elders wishing for more time to find the truth. Yeah, truth will never be found
pure in the mistomber life. Do this spirit is to live in liberty and be bound to earthy
treasures that cannot please and divine soul of man that learned to be free and constrain the
flesh and learn and can make a tendency. In a world filled with every pleasure that we can
continue. It's a replacing of arrangement that happiness we can achieve. What is it with trying
to where what is the pain we try to appease? Where's the source of this unknown inch that has
us bent on self-destroying? You don't have this spirit. It's to live in liberty and be bound
not to earthy treasures that cannot please and divine soul of man that learned to be free
from constrain the flesh and learn and can make a lot of tendencies. Yeah, there's a good time
and maybe it can't just let's true six, two, two, right, and let's donate and take it
hot so high you're now going to do a cry. Oh, there's no holy thumb up, do some respect for most
do the plummet, the key to bear life down in the promise to comfort that God said.
Will we know physical satisfaction will never feel a spiritual void? Much like a square peg while
it make other will never feel around how much like speculation will never
concretely answer the question post just like you'll never know who you are without seeking
the source of this spirit is to live in liberty and be bound not to earthy treasures that cannot
please but divine soul of man that yet to be free from constrain the flesh and learn
can make a lot of tendencies to be filled with his spirit is to live in liberty
and be bound not to earthy treasures that cannot please but divine soul of man that yet to be free
from constrain the flesh and learn can make a lot of tendencies to be filled with his spirit
is to live in liberty and be bound not to earthy treasures that cannot please the divine soul of
man that yet to be free from constrain the flesh and learn can make a lot of tendencies
man the ending especially was unbelievable to era i think it is titled that is filled
CC Chapman on the Skype talking about the podcast music network which is now in beta launch
we're going to keep it in beta for like a year
yeah we'll be like Gmail and flickering exactly pretty damn good hold on a second there's something wrong
of my oh shit hold on CC okay there we go yeah i'm sorry the patch bay was out of whack
oh man yeah i was just thinking about that during that song i was kind of
actually i started celebrating the weekend early if you know what i mean nice and yeah i mean it's
already uh quarter two over here and i was just thinking it's how unbelievable is this what we're doing
you know i'm standing here i've got like computers hooked up to each other and mixers and we're talking
through Skype and we're playing music the people have made maybe with garage band i was just like whoa you know
this is this is something big happening here yeah it's it's so it's so damn cool i mean it's funny
not to keep plugging bands but that's what we're about um as reading this article the other
day and uh Mitch Alden from now is now is doing an interview and he talked about how some listener
on my podcast heard the show and checked him out and saw that he had a gig and they actually
extended their vacation a day and hung over in Maine so they could check out the band live because
we were on a podcast and i'm like that's the story people need to hear i mean that's that's
what it's all about i mean that's why i'm doing this it's all good it's all
all right one thing yeah i think i don't want to forget about the site i i just want to i'm
totally gonna abuse the power i've got at the moment i want to thank Chris Rockwell from the daily
download it's two nine thousand from extra super action show right around the Chris did all the
PHP program and ensued it all the design work and these guys worked their asses off and i want
to personally thank them for all the hard work and the headaches they went through to get this up because
it could have been half as good without both of them yeah big boys big big big boy mega boy yeah
i know that and and it's unbelievable and how this has been going on for how long will be as
everyone been working on this two three months maybe at least two three months has been a lot i mean i
know this is the fourth complete different looking feel of it so it's it's been going through lots of
revs and there's a lot more coming and we've got a shopping list of enhancements that are still
to come so okay and and and and if you have feedback there's a contact i've already over the past
couple nights got feedback from artists who have found it and put in their music and ad
hey can you have this genre or you know it would be nice if we could act you know whatever it is
i was also thinking what i almost missed there is i can i can feel the community but there's no
place to leave a comment that that's actually it was funny we've had two artists actually say hey
you know why don't you have a forum in here so you know we can all network together and meet each other
exactly i think so yeah i think it's all done yeah like on the artist page so people can
can just provide feedback just doing you know like a maybe just a comment thread right there
right on just a single simple thread i don't know if you have to go into a big forum and all but uh
yeah and we want to give we want to give artists a bunch more you know access you know plug their
shows you know the calendars and blogs and all that jazz so it's it's much more to people can say
hey i love you know chance or i love you know whoever who's the else is on here i'm looking
and let's create bless on you know who that is but people can say hey i love these guys and get
updates from them and everything so yeah so i can totally uh here's someone out there going oh
but wait a minute the evil pod show was behind all this of course so i'll wait a minute this is uh are
we paying you CC not yet how are we gonna make money with this that's a good question
do we have any sponsors coming uh yeah and and there would they be anybody what why would
someone want to sponsor something like this would anybody have heard of these sponsors?
well uh if you go to pod safe music network.com you can see already that we have the sponsor
absolute is uh is really underwriting uh the launch of this project and that's mainly because
you know first of all it it really fits with uh with their brand and with their product
but also you know it's the summer it we've got the they want to be involved with a lot of music
it's uh you know it's just it really it was a good fit for their strategy and what i thought
go ahead what i thought was cool about them was you know they said hey we don't want to be labeled as
a sponsor you know because we're we're supporting you guys we think it's a cool thing and you know
i mean they you know call it say that you know pod safe music network is flavored by absolute i'm like
yeah yeah that's great and good i like that too and now they got peach vodka which i'm excited about
i don't i'm not a big vodka fan but peach vodka's gonna go really good on my iced tea for when i record
that stuff is actually pre mixed it's it's absolutely it's called absolute a peach it's
your latest flavor uh it's peach vodka so sounds pretty good in me uh and now i believe and although
i don't know if it's working yet but um so the concept is um if you play a song uh uh the you've
downloaded from the pod safe music network compalking is a podcaster now um then do i i have
believe i get like a referral code and i can put that into my show notes and then if you click on
that it'll take you into the artist's page is that how it works it's coming that that's one of
those states that's why we're in beta right um yeah we're gonna have the ability so that you know
if the podcaster plays a song but one of the artists in the network um they can actually put
in an affiliate code and link to the artist and link out to uh you know place to buy the CD or buy
the digital download and get a commission for that link right okay so you'll be able to buy the
music yes you will oh that's really make money okay it's coming and um and that's but but one
thing to stress is that's completely optional because some artists you know don't have a CD they've
got one track or they don't want to sell it on this network and that's cool they can still be
put their stuff in here they don't have to sell it there doesn't have to be any money change in hands
right um this is cool dude I really like this this I'm I'm excited yeah in many ways for me this
is you know I was like oh man this is this is this is the dream now we finally have closed the loop
we've got all the pieces in place it's gonna make my life easier that's for sure i mean i'm actually
built it for you cc that's what's all right yeah nice i feel better no it's great because i mean
it's hard work i mean going finding music and now i just go here and go okay i want to play something
acoustic tonight sort by genre oh sweet i'm gonna play this band it's great right well cc um
i want to thank you for all of the tireless hours that you put into this as well and uh and really
for taking charge and leading this revolution for no money apparently um yeah but that's it's really
important you know you you're doing some great work not only with accident hash but really in
building a community and letting people know what's going on and you're you know really a great
promoter of uh of the independent music uh which i just from now on can only see his pod safe it's
really cool well thank you it's it's been fun it's gonna get even more fun i can't wait all right buddy
so you uh you actually sent me an MP3 i i look for this and they're not listed in uh they're not in there
yet and the pod tech music network now uh hopefully they will be soon because i'd like to add them
and report on them they are if i can talk about it for a second you know wallfam um they're on
raco disc and so the raco they actually contacted me um to play on the on the accident hash they said
what's this podcasting thing and they get what podcasting is they've actually started wallfam put
out eight single podcast as a promotion um but they said i'm totally getting up a wallfam uh
they've got a CD coming out on Tuesday that it's just it's it's good old fashioned 80s rock and roll
and i'm so addicted and i've been getting cut i got a comment from some guy in London yesterday
saying i got caught playing air guitar while listening to this on my iPod in the office like that's
awesome i said it to the band and they were all static they were loving it cool all right um will you
make sure you send me a link then to uh to their page or whatever so that i can put it in the show notes
definitely all right buddy CC Chapman um now the uh what we call you the uh what you have the god
father of the podcast music network man there you go what did you call me one time the music
ambassador something that was hysterical whichever one you want i'll have the uniform made tonight
thank you sir all right CC do we're gonna play this uh this song this is uh Cheryl right
yeah Cheryl come and take a ride by wallfam
come and take a ride
i knew this girl couldn't meet my face i'm trying to run and she thought i was trying to
me i'm freaking out cuz i've been learning for a while baby you win the first one can i say
and she said what that could do now side he broke her heart and took her feelings for a ride yeah
now we're gonna be up for me and don't care baby you're in the first one can i say
call me take a ride
bring me someone else
call me take a ride yeah bring me someone else
and i'll just be what i like to train i believe it's because of you i couldn't make
i need you not to treat the keys of for a while baby you win the first one can i say
call me take a ride
bring me someone else
you said you've been had not tried anyone else i guess to my show
call me take a ride
bring me someone else
Oh yeah, man, that goes kick out.
Oh, welcome, and Cheryl on the daily source code CC, you still with me?
I'm still here.
Yeah, I had to move the shit.
This is so incredibly unprofessional of me.
Oh, you must be an indie podcast.
Yes, that's exactly what I am.
I love it, God damn it.
I hate that shit.
No, I can't know, no, no, no, I actually, I think it's good, let's say.
It's all station.
It's awesome.
At least, you know what you're getting then, you know, you're going to get what I think is
the good stuff.
Right.
So I'm going to get the good stuff.
You're not going to get morning show banter for me, do you hate indie music?
Obviously not.
So yeah, if there's indie, I wouldn't mind being the indie of anything, you know, shit.
Hold on, CC.
You're still.
You're home.
You're home with me, man.
Very a humor.
Yeah.
Thank you.
That was very good.
Featured artists on the Podsake Music Network.
I see there are also shows that are featured, including this one.
I know because I put myself in, who's on there?
How do you get on?
What's the deal?
Well, there's two parts.
I mean, one, any podcaster out there, anybody, even if they're not, if they're going
to play music, if any sort can sign up and be on this site and get music, there's, you
don't have to be a music, I mean, we've already, I saw, I don't know how we found
now.
I saw Senator Edwards podcast is on here already.
Really?
Yeah.
I know he's going to, because I actually got an email from the producer a couple
weeks ago saying, hey, you know, can you, they're playing like a song at the end now?
He's like, can you give me some music that would be appropriate?
Which I think is, I was psyched on a very cool, yeah, I'm that, very cool.
So anybody can sign up, but then on top of that, what was cool is, you know, Podshoe
wanted to sign some more, uh, ban, uh, more music producers to Podshoe.
And I, I had the, the happy, happy pleasure of helping find them, and I just wanted
to take a second to plug them all and, and let the world, you know, do one of these
damn announcements and let everybody know who's on board.
Yeah, go for it.
All right.
So, um, first up, everybody sort of Michael Butler, uh, he, uh, I'm sure people don't
know, wait a minute.
He doesn't always play Pods, you know, traditional Podshoe music, but he started another
podcast called the Rock and Roll indie cast, and he's playing nothing but Podshoe
music.
It's great stuff, um, Michael's great.
So he's on board, uh, Mark from the Tart and Pod cast, the single, the best music
podcaster in Scotland.
I don't know if there's others, but he's the best in Scotland.
Mark's a great guy.
So that's it.
The Tart and Pod cast.
We've got Canis Lupus and Renum Reef from ban tracks, yeah, ban tracks out in, uh, Boise
Idaho playing cool mix in music, uh, Julian Smith from in over your head radio, uh, he's
up in Montreal.
He plays a lot of cool laid back hip hop, emo, and Julian has just got a killer look
out looking on life.
I love the guy.
Mark is couch with the scenes scene out of Chicago or that one shot, really cool guy.
And I left him to the last because this guy, this guy is a personal personal friend of mine
who we've been through shit together that no one could ever stand big mic with the
extra super action show, um, playing the best hardcore and punk coming out of San Francisco
and beyond.
Um, so those guys altogether make it up this little music and for Pod show that's
going to, you know, really push and make, you know, make a lot of noise when music out
there.
And, of course, also accident.
Oh, oh, yeah, I'm part of that.
Yeah.
Oh, the other plug everybody else didn't, you know, yeah, no.
And what was, and it's funny because I know people are going to go, well, why these
guys and blah, blah, blah.
And, you know, we, we went out, look, I mean, I know you said you know, go, go find some
people C C and it was, you know,
find, not just great podcasts, but also, you know, cool people who are looking, you know,
who are embracing podcasts when you want to see your community. That's exactly what you do, of course.
Yeah, I mean, that's what it's about. This is about building community all around and, you know,
anybody who thinks otherwise is just on crack because that's why I'm in this, I'm sorry.
I mean, I haven't gotten too much shit, but I know I'm going to get some, and it's just,
you know, I want to get the music out there here and get these emails from people ever since
iTunes which live saying, oh my god, I had no idea there was all this music out there
I've been sick of radio for years. I'm like, that's the person why I'm doing this because they get,
they get the listen to, you know, brother love or Mike Chappellier, they get the listen to these guys
and go, holy cow. This is great. It's good stuff. Awesome. All right, CC. Well, you should be very
proud because I certainly am. Thank you Adam. I'm psyched. I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm very happy this is finally out.
I mean, everyone's been well. What's you working on? Like I can't say. So I had an over to
podsafe music network.com and start enjoying. Definitely. Okay. All right, CC. I'm actually, you know,
like, I don't have time for anything else because it's like I'm up to my 40 minutes. I'm just going to end it.
Sweet. Okay. Hold on. Let me, uh, let's get the rock money off in there. Roll the credits Adam.
Yeah, that's right. DailySourceCode.com is where you can find the podcast feed for this podcast,
the latest episode in the archives. Of course, what we've been talking about today, a lot of
it will come back in the show notes, but it's podsafe music network.com or music.podshow.com.
Thanks to my special guest. CC, Chappellier, but I'm still there, man. Head of blast. Yeah. All right,
don't, don't see this is the bummer part is that I can't, you can't hear the music, right?
Nope. Okay. Well, we had a call with cast blaster mic and Skype today and they're going to
help us out so we can put that in the cast blaster. She actually report and you won't have that annoying
echo. Beautiful. All right. Have a great weekend, everybody. CC, thank you very much. We'll
proud man and catch you in the film. Sorry, don't hang up. It's all here. All right, feedback,
Adam and Curry.com. I didn't get to all the promos I wanted to play today, or some of the
excellent voice mails that I've been receiving. So, keep it up. I'm now 99% on Gmail. So,
I'm still waiting for my infinity plus one to show up yet again. Last time it was right in the
nicotine. If not, I'm going to have to go in and start deleting stuff, which is, that wasn't
the promise. Come on, you're going to promise me. I'll talk to you on Monday. Take care, y'all. Bye, bye.