Pot show, no one knows how it makes it so creepy.
Delta shared Charlie 2-9 or 6.
Oh, I dreamed.
I was rich if prior.
Running up higher than the sunset strip.
As the flames burn brighter.
My head grew lighter.
And I watched the flesh fall from my fingertips.
Ashes to ashes, trust to dust.
I don't know what it means.
To be burned by something that you love so much.
I think I must be living the dream.
I think that I'm living the dream.
Who I dream?
I was the pilot.
Oh, the ship lost out of sea.
That's my eye.
You're not hurt.
My youth reigns forever in the end.
Ashes to ashes, trust to dust.
I don't know what it means.
To be burned by something that you love so much.
I think I must be living the dream.
I think that I'm living the dream.
My birth grew from my mouth.
I melt to my knees.
I could hear those hollow bones.
I'll echo back to me.
Ashes to ashes, trust to dust.
I don't know what it means.
When you try to hold on my side.
I can't touch.
I must be living the dream.
I think that I'm living the dream.
May he rest in peace.
Prior to Fem, Chris Mills from the wall to wall.
Fem, CD, of course from the pod tape music network.
I was just looking through the network and there it was.
Just waiting for me.
I think it was a new submission as well.
Everybody, how you doing?
It's the daily source code coming to you from Curry Condo.
I'm completely jet lagged.
Although everyone keeps saying, boy, you look really good.
You look really well rested.
And that, of course, is as usual due to virgin airlines.
Nice 10 hour flight from London to San Francisco over the weekend.
And saw two movies.
A typical trip on the way over, you know, slept a couple hours.
I saw four brothers.
Wow.
This is a lot of...
There's a shitload of echo here.
There's a lot of echo, baby.
How do I change that?
One, two.
There we go.
Ah, much better.
Now we're all intimate.
I'm not in the hallway.
Okay.
Here we go.
Yeah, that's the movie.
I think John Singleton directed four brothers with Mark Wahlberg.
And was it Andre 3000?
Andre 2000?
Andre 2000.
I think John, man.
Violent, but really, really good.
And I saw the 40 year old virgin, which is just perfect to watch on an airplane.
Particularly if the airline is virgin.
So that was all good.
As I posted on my weblog, got in and immediately set about mopping off the floors here.
It's condo.
I kind of left in a rush last time.
And also not having been here for three weeks.
It's dust everywhere, man.
I really got to figure out someone who couldn't who can come in and clean that prior to my arrival.
So I wouldn't have been okay with all the jet lag.
Hadn't it been for a whole slew of phone calls that I got Sunday morning.
The first one.
And it must have been around I'm thinking 2 a.m.
No, maybe even earlier than that.
Maybe around 130 due to the explosion near Luton in the United Kingdom, which is quite a ways from where the cottages.
But of course, the minute the news came out, it was north of London and everybody was freaking out.
And it was very sweet.
Everyone was calling and saying, hey, is everything okay?
If you're spoken to Patricia, close the doors as a huge cloud of chemical crap coming your way.
I don't think it's going to pass anyway.
It basically the cloud is going south east.
Oh, my goodness.
That was almost a disastrous mistake I made.
I didn't bring the Heil microphone.
I have the AKG and I have the portable sound board.
And I had to, well, so I don't have the Heil microphone.
But I am using the Heil box to prop up them.
I have a little mini mic stand.
And on top of that's about.
Let me see one, two, three for about eight CDs.
So it just barely is high enough for me to, you know, rest my hands on the bar here where the setup is in the kitchen and talk directly into the microphone.
Anyway, so we're south west of London.
So no, no problems there.
But apparently you could hear this explosion, which was three fuel tanks I believe.
You could hear it as far away as the Netherlands.
That's one big freaking bang man.
I'll tell ya.
Lots of stuff to talk about today.
A lot of music stuff.
I have a couple of pieces of audio feedback.
And of course, some interesting promos that I've weeded out from the enormous amount of submissions that come in through email and through promos.podshow.com.
This is, and also a lot of things about iTunes.
You know, stuff from the palm cast, palm, palm, palm cast in France.
He sent me an email with just a quick report as he calls it star academy,
which is a production of end em all and famous certainly in Europe.
It's kind of like an idols, you know, like pop idol or American idol.
It is now also podcast.
And in the French iTunes music store in the podcast top 100, this is interesting star academy.
It shows up at number one, number four, number nine, and number 20.
And they're planning to sell those shows in the near future via iTunes.
I've been getting so many reports about iTunes.
I don't normally look at the, at the podcast directory in iTunes.
And I went over there today.
And, you know, I just clicked on music, thinking I would find some interesting music.
I've really been on a big music trip here.
I think I would find some interesting music podcasts.
And everything I clicked on seemed to be a podcast, but it was a mainstream podcast.
So there's the rhythmics podcast.
There's the, actually, Roger Smalls mentioned the Madonna podcast.
And let me see.
If I open it right now, let me just see what's in iTunes.
Hold on a second.
Because it seems like very little indie podcasts are represented anymore.
Now I can hear some of you including Madge Weinstein going,
Oh, well, now you're finally finding out, aren't you?
There we go.
iTunes music store.
I have to go through podcast first, I guess.
Okay, podcast directory.
Here we go.
Let's see.
Because it maybe was just a one-off that I hit it.
And I got a whole bunch of what seemed like certainly not independent podcast.
Okay.
So they've divided into new categories.
And we have music here.
And so click on music, accessing music store.
Something's wrong with the wireless connection here.
I think it's because I have one of those television transmitters.
You can transmit the TV signal from the cable box wirelessly across the room to a little receiver.
I think that's definitely interfering.
It doesn't seem consistent, but it certainly is interfering right now.
Oh, here we go.
Okay.
So these will be the music podcast.
What do we have?
Indy feed.
Okay.
Indy feeds a good one.
John London bus exclusive music videos.
WXPN musicians on the record.
Amy Mann, Music and Interviews, Bruce Springsteen.
KCRW, CVS, Radio 3, podcast.
You ridnix the ultimate collection.
Bono, the Rolling Stone interview.
So those don't really seem to be indie podcasts.
Some actually don't even seem to be podcasts at all.
And there was a comment on the show notes that I was just reading before I kicked off today's show.
Let me see, let me just go to these.
Let me just go to the notes for a second because it was a really interesting comment about iTunes top 100.
Now, I think I've explained before how I believe the top 100 is still compiled.
I don't know if they still do it that way.
But it's based upon new subscriptions to a podcast.
Of course, done to the link for the music store to subscribe to it.
Within a certain period, which I think it's 24 hours.
I'm not quite sure. Okay, here it is.
So here we go.
After listening to Rogers and this is from Paul, which Paul is not at home on his podcast, Paul.
Yeah, I think so.
After listening to Rogers' funny, but mad contributions regarding the witch magic,
I went to iTunes to look for her podcast.
That would be the Madonna podcast.
To cut a long story short, I got sidetracked into looking through the iTunes top 100 subscribed podcast.
Okay, top 100 subscribed podcast.
There must be something wrong with the way they calculate this list,
because radio force in business, which is the fabulous show with Peter Day,
is listed at number 34.
Strange is there have not been any new episodes of this cast for well over two months.
What's going on?
Well, I don't know.
I think that, well, it must be based upon new subscriptions.
I mean, it's kind of a self-fulfilling.
If you show up in, I guess, what can you actually see on the page?
You can see the top 20 podcast before you have to click through or scroll somewhere else.
Let me see, I'll just look at it right now.
So if you're in there, yeah, exactly shows the top.
I don't know, it shows the top 25.
So if you're listed in there, people are obviously prone to clicking on it
and subscribing to it, which, of course, keeps you high and list.
But right now, if you look at it, man, it is really, it's mostly mainstream.
So, um, glad we changed the name of, uh, I potted out org to indiepotted.org, you know?
We still need a good place to go and look for independent podcast.
One more thing I had here about, uh, we were talking about lyrics and how, um,
the RIA is now going on after websites, um, that publish lyrics and guitar, uh,
tablisher.
It's pretty serious now.
The music publishers association, which isn't the RIA.
It's the, uh, it's the organiser.
It's like the RIA, but they represent sheet music companies in the United States.
Uh, they're going to launch the first campaign campaign they're calling.
It's war.
Ladies and gentlemen, the first campaign against websites offering unlicensed song scores
and lyrics, um, and who's this guy?
I'm sorry.
Lauren Kaiser, the music publishers association president, said he, I guess it is a he.
Wanted site owners to be, check this out, jailed.
Mr. Kaiser said he did not just want to shut websites and impose fines,
saying authorities can throw in some jail time.
I think we'll be a little more effective.
Holy crap.
Stay away from it, please.
Oh, man.
That is outrageous.
I mean, surely they're, of course, first of all, yes, it's a copyright violation.
Totally, but, you know, evaluate what you're going after here.
You know, it's not like so, not when no one's printing books.
You know, this is not from music lesson.
I guess you could print it off a website, but I find, you know, I've studied piano
and I find tremendous value in a book that has all the printed information, you know,
all the printed lyrics in there.
Perhaps with, you know, whatever music and sheet music companies that.
Those are really good compilations.
I've never been really able to find anything as good on the internet as I would be able
to find in a music store.
And quite honestly, I think it's, it just, it really helps spread the music and helps
people understand what's being sung.
And how long have we heard people say, I think Jimmy Hendrix was singing.
Instead of kiss the sky, I got to go kiss this guy, you know.
Okay, but they are serious, so, before warned.
I wanted to mention the podcast or con, which is coming up.
There's just so much happening.
This is, I guess, in a way, like the portable media expo,
it's much more like a blogger con.
And it's taking place in Chapel Hill, North Carolina on Saturday, January 7th.
I'm sorry to say that I won't be able to go because I'm definitely going to be home
through that first week of January.
But you can check them out at podcast or con.org.
And if you're driving along, can't remember that.
Then, of course, you can always go to the show notes later on.
And, and pick up all the links mentioned today's source code.
And, and, oh, man, you're going to love this one.
This is really cool.
This is about mainstream media versus podcasting.
If you're listening to this on the serious satellite stars 103,
how you doing everybody, this is podcasting.
We just talk about ourselves.
Oh, don't tell me this.
Oh, here it is.
Emiss, okay.
This is, um, was this an interview?
Now, Emiss radio division president.
Now, Emiss radio is, uh, I don't know if they're owned by anyone in particular,
but they are definitely a radio group.
So, they have a number of stations.
The division president, Rick Cummings,
recently told a group of Wall Street analysts.
And this is coming from mediabuyerplanner.com.
Recent told a group of Wall Street analysts that is own research
of his own research of college students
is picking up what he called iPod Fatigue.
This is going to get so much better.
Coming said that this is his own survey amongst college students.
iPod Fatigue happens when younger listeners have 100 songs on their iPods
that they're sick of dealing with.
The opportunity for radio said Cummings is to continue to lean on content
and to bridge that technology with the radio audience.
In other words, perfect,
like God, this is so fantastic.
In other words, professionally produced content
can be the bridge to reaching younger listeners.
For example, coming said that Emiss is starting to offer podcasts
and that podcasts produced by radio professionals
can eclipse the quality of independent sources.
So, let me hit you with that again.
Because, you know, let's remember this guy.
All right.
What does this guy look like?
What a dark.
So, podcast produced by radio professionals.
Lots of these people who are above that.
Produced by radio professionals can eclipse
the quality of independent sources.
Okay.
Well, that all depends on what you call quality
and then also depends on quality of what?
Quality of sound?
Quality of content?
Dude, you are so incredibly awesome.
Hi, my name is Douglas K.
I'm a singer-songwriter from Edinburgh in Scotland.
I put three of my songs up on the podcast
music network about two or three months ago.
It's been great.
The response I've had from it.
The podcast from music network
have been sending me emails
to let me know when I've been played on podcasts,
which is really handy.
They seem to have been coming in pretty much daily
and sometimes twice or three times a day.
Tell me that I've been played on podcasts
from police like Japan, the States, Canada
and so on as well as ones here in the UK.
And a lot of the people that put the shows together
have also been in touch asking for either sessions
or interviews or things like that,
which, again, is great.
And in addition to that,
I've had quite a few emails from people
who have heard me on these things
and quite a few sales of
downloads and CDs and so on.
And it just makes such a difference
when you know that you can get your music
out there without having to go through the regular channels
of radio-airplay
where you're sending stuff off to places
and maybe two or three of the radio stations
will pick up on it.
The podcast thing
and through the podcasting of music network
is just a fantastic way of getting things out
because your stuff's up there
for all the pod show producers
to produce at their leisure.
So I think the podcast music network
is an invaluable tool for bands and musicians
and with the way the music industry seems to be going
I think it will become increasingly important
for bands and artists who want the stuff to be heard.
Douglas, thank you so much.
Now besides that, I'd really like what Douglas had to say.
I just love hearing someone speak in a Scottish accent.
Fantastic.
Just keep sending me feedback
without accent, man.
That's great.
And thank you very much.
That's exactly the way it's supposed to work.
That is exactly what it was created for.
And we're smoking our own dope over here, man.
We love it, too.
And Michael Butler has been kicking some major
CC Chapman, of course, as well.
Just spreading the gospel, man.
Just making it happen.
And every thing, there's not a day that goes by
that I don't get email from an artist
or from someone who's used the pod safe music now.
We're going to make some show incredibly happy.
Really does.
This is what we were missing
to really get some good ass music out there.
And again, every single day, I'm just amazed
by what's being submitted to the pod safe music network.
When I'm helping the limit
really kicks in.
I'm sorry about that.
And you know what this Frapper thing is.
FRAPPR.
It's a combination of,
really it's someone put something really cool
together with the Google Maps API.
And you can essentially mark yourself
on a map, like a pin map.
You know, like a region and Kathy Lee used to do.
And does region still do it with whatever her name is?
Newgirl.
It's a pin prick on the map when they call someone.
So I have one.
I have a Frapper map, which is linked from somewhere.
I think it's, you can find it at curry.com.
There's a link in the blog roll on the right hand side.
But there's also one for the pod safe for piece song.
If you haven't heard that, if every day we're Christmas,
it's currently the most played song,
pod safe tune from the pod safe music network
on any podcast anywhere.
Almost overtaking the all-time spot.
Now it's definitely it's moving up even on brother love.
So the Frapper map was created
so that if you have a pod cast, you enter your pet,
your little flag, your little little pin prick there
to show.
So that you have a, we have a,
it is, you know, I'm doing a horrible job of explaining it.
But it's actually really cool.
Even though there's only three people on it so far.
CCC Chapman there and DJ AJ and Greg Turnbull.
I got to add myself to it.
But eventually, if we, if we get the attention of all the pod cast
just playing the song, we'll have a really cool map of
every single region that it was played in.
And yesterday, I was over at my friend Greg's house.
He will live here in San Francisco.
It was his son's birthday two weeks ago.
So I brought some presents over and had a nice home cook meal,
which is fantastic.
And I played, pod safe for piece form.
I played actually about about 20 different pod safe tracks.
And he said, Adam is not a single track that I wouldn't
hesitate going to a record company in New York
and representing it and pitching it.
And I said, you know what?
I don't think there's a single artist of any of these 20 tracks
that would let you do it because they're so happy with what they're doing.
Who wants the bullshit of a major label at this point in the game,
man?
I think this is just hanging there guys.
It's going to happen.
You know, people are going to be able to just buy stuff from you.
They're going to hear about it.
We're going to pop it.
It's going to happen.
Anyway, so the pod safe for piece,
Frapper map is, of course, available at the show notes.
If you go for the daily source code.com,
but if you want to go directly,
it's Frapper.com FRAPPR.com.
And it's pod safe for piece promo is the URL for that.
Okay.
Let me see.
I already talked about the iTunes stuff.
Let's see.
This was Chris.
I think he was right in the book.
He had a big epiphany moment here.
Adam, how's it going?
My name is Chris.
I'm the brother of Jay Mac.
The main dude behind Hood hype.
You probably heard of him once or twice.
Yeah.
Whatever.
I don't know.
Listen, you guys,
between you and my brother,
you've both inspired me into my own podcast project.
And one of the things that came up when
was tossing ideas around was the concept of taking some of these
sci-fi books that I've been writing.
And put them out in an audio book format.
And I thought, hey, you know, why not?
So here's what I'm doing.
I've got a site set up right now.
Temporary release site at children of the gods.blogspot.com.
And basically the concept behind the project is I put together scripts that are adapted
from the books that I've been writing on.
And I get these voices together.
Put some sound effects to the whole thing.
A little bit of music background.
And create a whole sci-fi adventure that's just mind-boggling and mind-blowing, right?
So here's the thing.
Recently, I saw the success of Podsafe for Peace, which brought all these people together to create a big track
from all over the world.
And I thought, you know what?
That's kind of the concept that I'm looking for
is in terms of voices for my own project.
So I'm wondering, what does it take to do something like this?
How do I get all these people together?
They have some talents or maybe they're an aspiring voice actor?
Whatever.
They've got some good acting talents.
And they want to get it out there.
I think I've got a possible outlet for some of these folks.
I want to get together with these people.
And see what they can do to kind of bring this to life.
Because the fact of the matter is I can only fake so many myself.
And we've got quite a few characters, of course, in the script.
So check it out.
You can email me at deadweaselallonewordatgmail.com
and saying goes for any of your listeners.
And I'd be more than happy to forward a copy of the latest script.
You want to take a look at it.
If anybody's interested at all a taking part of it.
Please do send me an email.
I'll send you the script.
Let's see if we can hook up.
Let's see if we can make this happen.
Thanks for listening.
And I'll keep doing the same.
Have a good one.
Yo, man.
I thought footballer boy at gmail.com was weird.
Deadweasel really takes the top spot there.
See, I like that idea.
I think you'll have no problem at all getting people to jump on that.
With all the stuff that I saw go on with podsafe for peace.
We're going to see a lot of freaking collaboration in the next just in the years to come.
And I, you know, please definitely keep me up to date on this project.
Let me know what's happening.
Let me know if people have gotten in touch with you.
She got your actors.
And, you know, keep us in the loop.
Maybe create a podcast of the creation or whatever.
This is exciting stuff.
And what are the chances of you being Chris being Jaymax brother from hood hype?
Of course, one of the few shows that features R&B and Urban in hip hop music.
What are the chances of audio feedback coming from Chris referring to hood hype?
And then all of a sudden, there's some interesting audio feedback from Julian Smith.
One of our very own podsafe music podshow podcasters.
Yeah.
And without this as Julian from in over your head dot net.
And obviously the podshow.
I'm just a gang along with CC and extra super action show big mic.
You know.
And it's, you know, I thought I'd let you know.
But something that I thought of while I was listening to your show 295.
There are no good hip hop podcasts out there.
No good podsafe music hip hop podcast.
And I thought that was pretty funny.
And still the truth, I felt kind of bad for you man.
I mean, I mean, I, you know, it's not a big deal or anything like that.
And I don't want to make you, I mean, nothing to freak out over.
Except for the fact that, you know, I kind of do one.
And I have kind of been with podshow ever since July.
And in fact, we kind of announced it on your show in July.
And I remember you doing that too.
And if anyway, I just, you know, I was thinking maybe that you've been high the entire time,
like the full four months or perhaps I suspect high even longer.
But I mean, don't get me wrong.
I love drugs.
I do.
I take drugs daily.
I love drugs and alcohol and all sorts of really fucked up things that you would probably also like.
And I also love hip hop.
I do.
I don't know man.
And I was thinking maybe I'd give you an idea of what it is that I played.
I know you don't listen to my show or anything like that, but that's okay.
You know, I mean, you run a company or whatever.
And I'm sure that you're really busy with that.
Let me give you an idea.
And this is kind of the sent me an email this morning.
Where is it?
Oh, yeah.
She got to find the freaking email.
It's always gone.
I'm never organized.
It's crazy.
Sound like me, man.
Oh, yeah, here we go.
Alex.
In over your head number 94.
Yeah, it's, it's, I've been doing shows for like a pretty crazy long time.
Like almost as long as you have since November of last year.
So it's, I've gone past my one year now.
So I've been around for a fairly long time.
In fact, you played a comment of mine.
And then like, maybe December or something like that before the new year.
I was really excited when I have it.
It's pretty cool.
He says.
So do specifically to you and your great show.
I'm listening to more hip hop.
Great.
I dug that Jedi mind tricks and just attracted you play the other day.
So much that I snagged the album.
Excellent.
Also picked up brother Ali.
All right, excellent because of an earlier show.
Very nice.
Thank you, Alex.
And I'm sure they appreciate it.
Those two led me to find atmosphere.
I played him too.
Murders.
I played him.
A stop.
Ideal.
Yeah, I played both of them and felt.
Yeah, I've, I've played.
God, I've played a lot of hip hop.
I throw out 94 shows.
That's pretty crazy.
So what you're hearing Julie and say besides spanking me silly.
Is that once again, this stuff is really working.
It's good thing you owe me on my side man on your side.
I mean, good thing you have me on your side.
Yeah.
That would be pretty fucked up.
You know what I mean?
Like the only really crazy good hip hop show.
It's really unbelievable.
I mean, there are other really good shows as well.
But it's good that you have not on your side.
I was just thinking.
So, you know, it's really good that we're, you know, I just, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I.
I'm down.
I just think that, you know, maybe we could do good things together.
You're looking for a good hip hop podcast and maybe even run for Pod Show.
And I am a good hip hop podcast with Pod Show.
Okay.
I was thinking that it might work out maybe.
Anyway, I'm really busy right now.
I'm going to go see a hip hop show.
Interesting.
Enough.
But I thought I'd leave you with a track that I played on my show.
That's got a lot of good comments.
And that I think you really might enjoy.
That's called Slow Down Gandhi.
And it's with Sage Francis.
Check it out.
I'm sure you'll love it.
Right, I'm bro.
Thank you.
I was looking for some good hip hop.
Gosh.
There once was a song called The Rest of President.
Contemporary music.
It was the kids.
It was a top 10.
I wasn't popping.
So I missed the bus a bit.
The politics was on everybody's heart this summer list.
And the cool kids were all rockin' votes.
I shit you knuck.
I was pistol whipping cops for hip hop.
I'm a slow box.
Yelling into mega phones.
The killin' hard rocks.
Shoes and cartons.
And the stepping stones.
And a famous addicts.
I pulled him on marches.
The day the criss-coil on biscuit.
Who's the final goal in marches.
My penistores.
Two pull the clown on.
And in fact, that's the reason for the high horse.
And we're not here.
I seen the rings and I'm not trying to cause the wind.
I'm the door to wonder pros.
And I push a carton.
All for the sake of military reproving.
They feel they can't stake the way they target it.
The students.
I got a thought.
Whistling Ohio.
The rest of them.
They should stop doing a stay in a banner.
Cricket convention.
Who was they thought?
No, no, no.
Who was they thought.
Who was they thought?
Who was they thought, who was they thought?
Who held it?
Who was they thought?
Paws?
Why did you cut them?
Why did you cut in a plane that?
Paws?
All you two had continued to do this.
But this is what I've got to do.
What I've got to do?
The four one is your own.
Detailing crumbs...
It's definitely aywat.
It's death penalty versus suicidal fantasies
All I wanted was a fucking Pepsi
Institution
Making you think you crazy is a billion dollar industry
I could sell sanity in a bottle
They'd be charging fucking press air
They're not getting help
They'd be immunized welfare
middle class eliminated
Rich get richer till the poor get educated
But some of y'all still have been grown into your face
You face something quite match your head
And I'm waiting for a brain to fill the dead space that's left
You're all giving me ethnicity or give me dread
Trust a funny in-reppin' with that a cause for a long
Cause when push turns the shove you jump into your forefathers on
Seize a banker
Your part of the system
All throw the tread of blocks and comes in
Come the briefcase
The sickness is sent to the camera start rollin'
See the fuck out of the picture bill
Reaching briefcase
The sickness is sent to the camera start rollin'
Pull down, run to your killin'
I'm Mr. Save the world
Spares the details
You save the females from losing interest
You miss saved the universe
You're a damsel in distress
Tight down to a track of isolated incidents
Generalize my disease, I need a taste of what it's like
Living off the fat of kings, I play the scape at your hunger strike
I'm the strike, the strike, the strike, the strike
Slow down, gone to your killin'
One love, one life, one too many victims
Republic, rat, Democrat, one party system
Media goes in a frenzy
The stripped of their credentials, presidential candidates
Can't debate over this instrumental
Let them freeze down, winter takes all
When the music settle, have Ted Nugent head hanging on my wall
Kill one of ours, we'll kill one of yours
Some friendly fire
That's a funny turn
Like civil war
Six in the morning police have my crib
Now my nice consist of two, two things in violence
The cruiser fixing vitamins
Music that is spirited
New flavour food made of mutated high bridge girl
They tell me that it's not that bad
It fucks you up good
But it's not that bad
They hold on to these tales to lift the door that wax
God save us all, let be less the cattle the bad
Bad news for what I blame for the strain
Of my vocal cords
Who can kind of hate for threat but can't hold a sword
It's the same who can pray in about the global war
But can't hold a global joke
But that they voted for
They call the shots with the nine the line of fire
I call the cops but they break in the line of duty
Let's call a stop to the abuse of authority
Truth keeps calling me
And I'm a lift to tell the story
So let's not true
Crits begin to give us
You need to cut the news
But you don't believe in scissors
Use the blood that troops
Don't wear a yellow ribbon
Just bring home a mother fucking brother
Just because they don't hold a shot
But they're in the line of fire
I'd like to call the cops
But they break in the line of duty
And I'm a call a stop
You abuse of authority
Truth keeps calling me
And I'm a lift to tell the story
Yo
Special thanks to Julian Smith
In over your head
Dot net
I really appreciate the feedback Julian
Really appreciate the track
I only have one question
Do you know of any really good hip-hop hardcasts?
Such a strong hip-hop
Hey my name is Josh
Nervous name to the just Josh and podcasts
On my podcast you can get an insight into my life
If I was linked to me rap on pontificate once a week
We did intervals on this Roy Hilly place
Which is fun but kind of hard at the same time
I got my glasses like an actually read the music
And if you're a good boy and you vote for me on podcast alley
You might just be also lucky enough to have the opportunity to hear me play Trombone or jazz piano
Do these kids like 13?
And for all you geeks out there
I will occasionally completely nerd on you
The photos were great on a little postage snap size screen
Then this last one
There we like this photo app called aperture
Oh there's computer hacking is making me thirsty
And, last but definitely not least for the music lovers
I'm gonna play some awesome pod safe music
I'm talking about the good time times
I look like a man on a mission
I know a girl named Betty
So why don't you go check me out
You can find me at justjoshin.org
That's JUSTJOSHING.org
See you there
Hi Adam
Last March
I started listening to your show
I was so excited about pod casting that I actually quit my day job that very month
That I haven't had a steady income since
I've just been pod casting and getting poorer by the day
Well you can imagine how excited I was when I heard about the un-dition
A chance to quit the day job that I didn't have
And I was all over that
The problem is that while I was promoting my podcast I unbeknownst to myself was
Promoting myself all at the same time
Now I've been offered several jobs that are truly tempting
None of them however is in pod casting
Please Adam
Don't make filthy lucre the thing that loars me back save me
Let me un-dition with my show the car cast
You like listening to shows that are recorded while driving that's what mine's all about
It's one of the original shows it was recorded regularly while driving
So check out the carcast.com or search for carcass and iTunes
I'm not mad as hell yet Adam, but please don't make me turn to road rage to prove my point for the love of all that is holy
Adam do the right thing
The carcast.com
Thanks Adam
I know that you've been looking for a great place to catch all the top pod save christianism
Well the stride music show is your podcast
Come on over to www.scribemusicshow.com and subscribe
The majority of the program is dedicated to getting you with an ear shot of some of the best independent christian artists
But I need money
The scribe music show
Radio when you want
Welcome to rough mix. Did you ever wonder how music is made?
I'm not talking about the finished product but about the process that is involved
How do ideas turn into a finished product what comes first the words or the tune join me Brian Kelly at rough mix
The podcast where I share how my music is made rough mix can be found at camp ruffner.automatic
The ODOMATIC.com
Hey Adam this is saves to DJ
In DSC 292 you post the question what is truth well you'll find the answer on the PMN
Don't want to type what is truth into the search box
When you don't check out my podcast at saves-to-space.com and let's see why we STM and our STP
We'll be cb.com
Can you lay it like this is Terry from the hogcast the podcast that's all about the Harley owner's group
In the adventures we have a we'd like to wish everybody a very merry christmas
We're hoping that all the guys out there get shiny new Harley Davidson
We're hoping all the girls get absolutely gorgeous leather boosty a's and Adam
We're hoping that you're finally gonna get yourself a vehicle worth rat and two. I mean you know
Nice car nice airplane. I haven't heard anything about a motorcycle
Merry Christmas to all and thanks again for listening. Yo Terry. Let me tell you ma. I am definitely a rider. I have been all my life
I have had so many different motorcycles. I was it was ever since I saw Marlon Brando in
Was it the wild bunge was that it where he strapped that you know that that trophy to his handlebars and had to have the black leather jacket
So that I started off with souped up mopeds
You know we did all kinds of stuff man. We you know we drill out the carburetors or as we say in the UK
carburetor we'd bore that out. We'd get oversized pistons and oversized cylinder heads and take it from 50 ccs to 70 ccs and just
Unbelievable shit. We had machines running so fast and so hot of course all air cooled and there were tricks you could do with the with the Honda 50 cc
For stroke engine you could jam the
Something with the ignition that I remember or the
Yeah, something it was something with the ignition you could jam the the points or something
Then it would run faster and we had always of tuning it and then I moved and I actually did a lot of motorcross and
trial riding and I had for one of the motorcross is one point ahead of Java a Java
Which is a is that a Yugoslav it was made in Yugoslavia. I think and
It was the weirdest thing. It's 350 ccs going in the one open pipe
Custom built frame and you actually would push the
The gear shift into the engine block and then turn it back and then it became the kickstarter
No electric start. You know always fun to try and crank 350 ccs when you're 16 years old and you know have the weight of a feather
And then later I owned two sportsters. I owned a fat boy the limited edition fat boy
Which I really really loved and that was one of your living in Jersey and
At a certain point, I just didn't have time anymore. I sold the I sold the Harley's and
Tooth was now it's almost it was two years ago
in
July, yes like two and a half years ago
Every year I would participate in this
Celebrity race for something called the black motorcross with black meaning illegal
Which is put on by these guys who have abandoned in the eastern part of the Netherlands
You know very very rock and roll crowd and everyone will dress up and wacky outfits. I once went as in a prisoner outfit
I once went as a as a priest
You know and we'd always participate and it was a really it was a professional course
They had professional riders professional heads
All kinds of stunt exhibits et cetera and
On the last one which was that was two years ago last one I did
They put me on a KTM
450 cc motorcycle and I and you know I would drive once a year during this race
And the year before they gave me a 250 I think was it that this year was a 450 and I went up on one of those
One of those jumps and yeah, I we weren't jumping all the way over the jumps just you know
hook a little bit of air and then you land on the flat top surface and then you go down on the other side and
It was
Probably the third
The third lap and if you don't train for the shit man you have no idea what you go through your stomach is killing you
You just want to puke your arms are killing you. You can't feel your shoulders
I popped up on top of the jump and then as I as my rear wheel came back down
My my throttle hand hit the throttle because you know my hands my my wrist just kind of collapsed underneath the
The shock and
Boom that bike went just
Left right underneath me and I landed flat on my back
In fact, it was nothing wrong in my elbows or my arms because my my back absorbed the entire
The entire shock wave and
To this day that's still bothers me two years later
And I really kind of gave up riding after that and besides Patricia says look how many dangerous things do you want to do?
I she said I'm okay with the flying you know, but not but you got to quit something so
There you go
Don't ride anymore
Which is a shame because I really did like it
Really did
It's Russell. I'm just hasn't commentary for you on a Delta Sierra Charlie number 288
So don't you get the new Jaguar?
Thought those really cool. What you're doing with the
The interface system your hand where you could talk to the computer and let's tell it to do things
I'm just had a few thoughts on that. I'm just be careful. You know don't record anything like that
Messing with the buttons and stuff
But I saw as I was just thinking about that and I've been looking for a iPod and
Migration system for my car and I haven't really found anything
I've been happy with Tradeff and transmitters, but also I was looking at
Bonna new hate unit to replace my CD player in the car that would interface with the iPod with their system
You know like from Pioneer Alpine or something like that and
Really as it's kind of thinking about it and you don't see a stereo with you know a nice screen like the iPod
You know, especially like iPod video or even in the nano has
I'm you don't have a color screen like that. It's just a kind of a
You monochrome or you know very few colors kind of thing
So I was actually thinking I've been looking around internet. You could find some
Car installs with a Mac mini and I was actually looking at that and wondering if there's a way you could plug in your iPod
Have like a iTunes type interface, but simplified so that you could you know use a touch screen and push buttons
to navigate around your iPod and download you know play the music on there
to listen to it in your car this that'd be a pretty cool idea
Enjoy listen to your show and keep up the great work
I'm trying to think why I played that there was a reason for that because I'm really starting
I'm really trying to select this stuff for you
I can't remember for the life of me. I was gonna say something about that. Oh, I know. Oh, oh
Okay, yeah, that was about the the Jaguar indeed
Boy man that thing was good on Patricia. Let me tell you hot night
So what I was going to say about it is
That you know, I'm now in San Francisco and even though we bought the Jaguar the Curry Cruiser
For over in the UK I still really want to do the biodeasy look experiment and I put out a shout out
Earlier last week that I'm really looking for some kind of diesel that we can just you know
Fuck around with an experiment with what I'm out here and we'll pour vegetable oil in it and we'll see what works and you know
We'll see we'll see how far we can get and I specifically want to be something that we you know no one's really gonna care about
So that you know if we mess it up then you know, we'll just be toying expenses
But I'm good for a couple grand for for the right diesel and today
Ron his
his nephew
Adam Bloom and
Ron's wife Marta and I went over to the new office. I think we're going into the new office
Tomorrow so I'll keep you up the speed on that, but you know just looking at the final
Final bits and pieces and as we're rounding the corner
There it was I could it was standing right there
Part by the side of the road
It was I I don't know what year it was from it looked like it was from you know late 70s early 80s
Excuse me
Mercedes
Station wagon
300 turbo diesel
It had it had six seats in the back so the station wagon, you know, it's not a payload
But it's a person load or maybe that's foldable. I don't know, but basically you have a kind of like a jump seat all the way in the back
Which is facing uh towards the rear
It was it was kind of a it wasn't quite lying it was it was a
Hmm, it was a kind of a beige yellow type color. It was really ugly really dirty and on the back window
It literally had a sticker that said bio diesel. I'm like this is there's a reason for this god is talking to me
Fanta it was it was exactly the car. I wanted I could see with just a little bit of finger paint
We could make it in the perfect pod show mobile
Apparently there's no conversion no adaptation necessary
Maybe it even I guess it runs on biodiesel already
So I got really excited you know I'm looking around then some guy was walking down the street
Hey, uh, is this your car? I wasn't so anyway I left my business card and I wrote on the on the back of the car
I said and you know will you please sell me this card this car and and I wrote down my phone number
So hopefully we'll hear from this person and of course
I'm still entertaining offers if anyone has a really cool clunker that we can mess around with
I've got an empty parking spot right here in in the in the basement of the condo
So and I want to get all over this and and start some experimentation if you're listening to this on
Serious satellite radio and then you're wondering what the hell is going on this show is the start of the four-hour daily lineup on serious
This is the daily source code. It's a podcast and actually it's kind of cool the podcast continues
After we're done here on serious specific host hell why hell way hell way is up next
Follow by Madge Weinstein Dawn and Drew and we're gonna continue here on the podcast
So if you want to hear more and find out what you're missing
Well, you just have to learn how to subscribe and download it now won't you okay serious people. I'll see you tomorrow
And meanwhile back at the ranch here
We've got my favorite
And GB welcome back to California atom it's and you be with some feedback from DSC number 294
It was really sweet of you to mention love spirals is an indie success story and I really appreciate that
But as comic strip blogger pointed out in the comments of curry dot com
Yeah, our cities were yeah wait a minute
Angie
When that now we're talking about comic strip blogger in in our little love messaging
Oh, no, no, no, no, I think we're going off track here definitely sold before podcasting in fact
to much of them before in be threes and a lot of them before the internet
Yeah, somewhere actually released on cassette and
They were all released on the indie label projects. So I just wanted to give them their props
Now I joined the band in 1999
and
began a lot of all my promotions
Created MP3s
Put them up and that started in a radio station and just explored all the
The new avenues that we're coming into being at that really exciting time
And tell eventually I realized that we could do most of what the label currently does for their bands
Into these radically changed musical environment. I mean everything is so different from when
When Ryan first started the band. So that's why this year we decided to put out our CD
Completely independently on our own label
And it's really exciting but coming from an old school background like that, you know
We have some questions as to whether some of the new inventions are really better than the old standards that we're used to and
Wonder in which way we should go and you seem like a really great source for advice
It's been so awesome to start this topic about
Whether artists with songwriting collections agencies can
freely podcast or not
And it's been cool to hear what everyone says all around the world
Anyways, I'm really looking forward to the full launch of PMN
indefinitely include love spirals in your digital sales experiment. We'll be right there with your baby
In fact, I put up a new song last week in the jazz section
And I'm hoping that you will help us pick out the new song from free and easy to add to PMN next week
So get back to me tell me what you want you like
It's always great to talk to you. You know, I love your throaty voice too, baby
And all I can say is I wish I was up in San Francisco partying with you guys this weekend
uh
Party
We need party. Hey Angie. I got
I got your envelope. Thank you very much and thank you very much for the CD in the personal note and
I will certainly
I've been playing the CD here in in the condo and I need to hear it all the songs a couple of times and I'll tell you what I like
Yeah, I like them all
Obviously and by the way the panties really smelled nice
So
Roger smalls. This is starting to have a little life of its own
I play it a couple of comments from Roger. He's been around for a while actually he's been podcasting for
Probably about a year now and I got an email and I followed it up
I'm not going to tell you who the email was from because he specifically asked me not to not to mention it
But he says dude check this out and he
Posted a link to a page on Google base
Which will we'll put in the in the show notes he says I think you should be worried
So if you read this out please don't mention who I am
I told Roger that I wouldn't tell anyone but I thought you should know about it
What's I of course he knows exactly what it is that was really dumb
Anyway, so I didn't quite understand what it was I'm gonna go to this page now
Uh, at base.google.com and here it says Roger smalls items
And it's based here's rare hair wax tub as used by Adam Curry description and it has various pictures here too
A real treat for fans of the podcasting pioneer pod show millionaire and former MTV presenter mister Adam Curry
Show the podcast enthusiast in your life how much you care this Christmas with this unique partially used tub of hair wax as used by
Guilford's very own star of the airwaves and so it goes on to describe it and
Now I don't use hair wax, but then I realized that I had cleaned up
The office and for some oops shoot
What about thing just kick dashboard just kicked in I hope that didn't screw up the recording okay?
I realized that I cleaned up
My you know the second bedroom the studio at the cottage and from some old television shoot
Someone had brought along some hair gel and that had wound up in my little personal makeup bag and of course
It was you know like old nasty hair gel so
You know real creamy even I think I was it was really like totally wrong product to we toss that out
And now all of a sudden some things are starting to fall in place for me
Because I was here I was thinking that
Well hold on let me read the second email and then you'll probably understand even more
um
So actually so this guy has been talking to Roger over Skype and
Says Roger thinks you're more famous than Michael Jackson
So I don't know about you oh
Here he seems to open up to me in my girlfriend over Skype and he just said that he was at your house at
230 this morning. I guess he's going through your trash and trying to sell your stuff. Well
So he's getting this shit out of the trash. I thought it was the foxes who were who were rummaging through the trash
That's pretty
This is a little bizarre, man
Roger don't come over to the house. Okay. I think
Madge as email the couple times the Roger. I'm gonna get into this and find out what's going on
This is just kidding a little bit too weird. Okay. I have one more pod save tune
I want to play for it's really beautiful
It's comes from a Russell Wolf who sent me emails says I'm a performing touring musician who also does max support for Harvard
Emboston of course it makes total sense
I listen to your podcast Friday you really reach me with the civility thing
You were talking about human nature about being human
Anyway, I've been loading a ton of my songs on the pod safe music network
Including a song from a new album karma co called human
I think you would really enjoy what it has to say about human frailty and the things we do to each other in love and war
Okay, Russell
Here's your spin man. Let's listen to human
What do you see me looking at you?
I must be
Because I never looked that way and anyone else
I
Went out for some coffee
We stopped in that restaurant
I put on my best pair of shoes and my sweater
Thought I could be what you want
Sitting right up across from me
It could have been you that I didn't see
Because I never
Real and noticed anyone else
In what else wouldn't hate the town would make you put you down
Try the long way home
Somebody else wouldn't hate you or pie and leave you
Crying all alone
So take off that makeup
You're skin tries to speak to me
You're wearing all of the paint like a horse and a doll
It's a mystery
Inside your eyes there relies a hole
Into the scale 10 of your soul
And there's only room for one
Not anyone else
I
I think we should just close out today's show with that, and just think about it.
We all are human.