Delta Shara Charley 2-0-7
Hi, this is Rachel from AudioCollective.net.
You're listening to Adam Curry on the Daily Stories Code.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass.
Transmaders?
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need noss.
Think in transmere?
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Fantastic.
This is Adam Curry.
And it's your Daily Source Code for Wednesday, July 13, 2005.
Alrighty everybody, how you doing?
It's first of all apologies for yesterday.
No source code and I'll get into all the gory details as to why that happened.
Man, I've been through the ringer as it comes to...
Well, the ringer, the cell phone,
explanations about that and more in today's Daily Source Code.
Had a long chat with Casplaster Mike today.
He's rightly, I guess, been pitching at me
that I haven't been using Casplaster when I'm at home.
And I explain to him why is because I want to be able to hook up my stereo valve process
or on my external gear.
And that's when the big light bulbs start to go off
as Mike explained exactly how to wire in through Casplaster.
So, shoot, it's working.
And it sounds great as far as I can tell.
We'll really find out, of course, after the show's over.
Mike suggests that I might not want to do an extended long version.
Unless it'd be no good.
Yeah, so I don't have to go into too much details to how it's actually done.
But the only issue now is I have to figure out a better way to sit
because I've got the microphone and the windscreen is just blocking out the view of the crap
actually, maybe I can.
Wait, why don't I turn it tablet mode?
Oh, Eureka.
Now we're talking, okay.
This is a bit of a big thing.
Okay, so now it's all in tablet mode.
All right.
So this is going to be kind of a partial beta test,
partial talk about shit, partial play some stuff show.
We've got podcasts, music on the way.
Something different and a mashup from mashuptown.com.
Yeah.
Jicky Boys.
Switching the live.
Okay.
You know one of the most important things
I guess it's kind of obvious but
when you're doing a podcast you've got to be sitting right you know.
I haven't quite found the right pose right now.
Now, I'm in a big office swivel chair with a rather high armrest and a mash-up tub for you.com.
Okay.
A dove, where to go, man.
Thank you.
He's been supplying me with the mash-ups mash-up town.com.
And of course, as always, everything that we talk about here on the source code you can find in the
show notes at dailysourcecode.com or on www.curry.com.
So, I've had the crapplet on my lap now.
Recline just a little bit in this office chair.
And so, I've got the mic kind of, you know, swivel downwards toward me.
And that's also because I have this fucking weird hum here if I turn the mic towards the ceiling.
I don't know if you can hear that.
It's really faint now, which is a good thing, of course, because we don't really want any hum.
Okay.
So, everything should be working.
I'm liking the way it sounds.
This is the cast-blaster.
You can find that at cast-blaster.com.
If you want to more about it, there's a version you can use.
I think a perpetuity, a little record ten minutes, and then you can purchase it.
It's still in beta, but already I'm seeing just by using it again.
And it's only been, what?
Like, a week and a half or two weeks since I used cast-blaster for the last time.
Already, I'm seeing more things.
I think we should, we should have the could possibly go into, into the one-point
no version.
I can see mic just groaning.
Like, no groaning, as we speak.
I don't know.
No more features.
Anyway, it's still hot when the middle of our heat wave here in the UK.
About 33 degrees centigrade, which is hot.
That's in the, what is that?
That's got to be in the 90s, far in the 90s.
Hold on, maybe.
Don't I have an OSX widget for that?
Hold on.
Let me see.
I think I do.
Here we go.
Comvert.
Does that have temperatures?
Uh, temperature.
There we go.
We want to convert it from Celsius.
So it's 33.
Yeah, 91.4.
Hey, 91.4 degrees outside, everybody.
Um, so you can hear the fan in the background.
Very lightly.
It's actually outside the door.
Patricia put the bedroom fan there.
So again, this house definitely not equipped for this type of weather.
But we aren't enjoying it, not complaining whatsoever.
Um, this shit I was complaining about was what started Sunday.
All of a sudden, um, when I use my phone, my cell phone.
And I have a virgin mobile over here.
And I really liked that because I wanted to pre-pay it in necessarily.
In fact, when we moved here, didn't even have a UK bank account or credit card.
So that would have been hard anyway.
But I didn't want to email, basically.
And I also wanted to kind of know what we were spending on, on phone costs.
Um, so, and I'm pretty happy with virgin mobile.
Um, it's, uh, it's way too expensive when you're roaming overseas.
Um, so I have, uh, a team mobile, again, a pre-pay team mobile for the US.
But anyway, um, whether, if I tried to call out on Sunday,
I would get the three tones in succession that goes, do, do, do, do.
Um, and it wouldn't do anything with just this connect.
And if I tried to call myself on, it would, uh, a message will come on saying this cell phone
is currently not accepting connections.
Now, this was a new one.
I've, I didn't know what disconnect notices are.
And you know, there was plenty of money in the account and all that was set.
Um, what happened is my phone got blacklisted.
Now, I've posted about this a couple times.
And, um, I think I mentioned it in the previous source code.
What that means, essentially, is there's a centralized database that the networks all used together.
Um, and we'll have access to.
And if your phone is lost or stolen, you report that to your, uh, network carrier.
And then they put it on the blacklist.
So it gets, uh, a checkmark and it's put into this database.
And so then you get the result.
Um, if you try to use it on the virgin network with a version SIM card, it won't work.
But it's a centralized database.
So it'll also, um, uh, happen, uh, or it'll also will stop to function on any of the other UK networks.
It may work in other, in other parts of the world.
But that's pretty much what they want to do.
Um, is, and I, and I think since team mobiles on it, they're probably covering the states as well.
So, uh, effectively, um, it's trying to deter, um, cell phone theft.
Duh.
Okay.
Uh, so that's great.
But somehow I got on this list and I hadn't reported it.
And, uh, that identified that I was the owner of the account.
And, you know, the problem, because of course I call them up.
And, you know, a member of the team will be right with you.
It takes 30 minutes every single time you call and want to get a live person on the phone.
Um, at Virgin.
Of course, this is kind of logical because Virges, what we call, um, it's a virtual mobile operator.
I think it is a VMO.
And they actually ride on team mobiles network.
It's, it's team mobiles antennas.
Uh, in fact, often, um, if you go to select network, you select team mobile, but it'll say,
Virgin on your phone.
So they're just basically helped us.
That's all they have to do.
And, you know, and, and the cash register part is, uh, is also probably handled through
team mobiles infrastructure.
So all they have to do is really have a couple people who, you know,
stand for the Virgin customer promise and answer the phone promptly.
You know, it's, they don't have enough people.
So, and they can kind of understand.
But to anyway, after we figured this all out, um, no problem.
Sir, in 24 hours, they'll be back on.
So Monday, of course, it wasn't back on.
Another 30 minute wait getting through very tedious.
Um, oh, okay.
Uh, it'll be unblacklisted now.
Turn your phone off for half an hour.
Then turn it back on and then it should be fine.
Of course, it didn't work then.
I waited a couple hours, didn't work.
Um, called again went through the whole process.
And you have to explain everything new because you can't, you know,
you can ask for team member Gareth.
But, uh, he's on lunch break or I can't find him.
Of course, the answer.
So you have to go through the whole thing.
Explaining how it all works.
What happened?
Uh, often telling them where the black list is.
So that didn't work.
So then I decided to go down to the virgin store in the high street.
And you didn't know how I love going anywhere called high street.
Um, uh, and so virgin has a store in a store.
Guess worst.
In WH Smith, which is kind of a general purpose, uh, magazine store,
but also grocery store, not a grocery store, uh, household good store.
And they have a corner, uh, in the back of this store.
And it's a desk and they have, uh, I don't know.
Um, it's not very big.
It's, it's literally in the corner.
And so there's Ian and Ian says, Oh, yeah, okay.
I understand what's happened.
I've only been here for two days myself.
And like, oh, okay, this guy has no connections within the company.
So, but he tried to get through, you know,
same deal, turn it off for 20 minutes.
Now we couldn't actually perform that test in the store because, uh,
you cannot receive virgin mobile in the virgin mobile store in Gilbert.
Uh, which is, of course, ludicrous.
I've known about this, but this was kind of funny.
Because this Ian guy had only been there for two days.
He just discovered it as well.
And he was tripping out.
Uh, so I go outside and he says, No, wait 20 minutes.
Okay, I'll go down.
I'm hungry.
I'm going on to Burger King.
I'm going to have a hamburger, you know,
Burger, hamburger meal, whatever the hell it is with a coke.
So I'm eating there 30 minutes.
I make it safe.
And I'd say, okay, you know, this is it.
If it doesn't work now, then I'm, I'm taking different measures.
So, of course, it didn't work.
And then I just walked back to T-Mobile.
Actually, I had been into Vodafone because I figured,
now I'm going to go shop.
Went into Vodafone.
Um, didn't like the attitude of the people,
salespeople there.
So, you know, just, they'll have the same phones, basically.
Then they went to T-Mobile.
And there was a guy there who knew a lot about their service and
a lot about their products.
And he could tell me, you know, how, um,
you could get onto the Starbucks T-Mobile access points or
airports just by sending a text message.
And it'll be automatically added to your account.
Um, you know, so, of course, this is a contract that you have to,
uh, have to enter into to get all these wonderful services.
They have a, um, a discounted rate, uh, for international dialing.
So, yeah, it's still going to be kind of expensive.
And roaming in the states, uh, it'll still be 69 cents, uh,
pence a minute.
So that's, uh, way over the top.
So it looks like I'm still going to have to use a different account in the
states when I'm there because it's just crazy.
I mean, you pay for your incoming calls.
So you're paying almost a buck, you know, that's, uh,
actually you are paying a dollar for an incoming per minute for
incoming calls.
So that's not going to work.
Do you have a good data bundles now for the UK only, of course,
uh, one gigabyte of data per month for 90 pounds.
And then 75 pence per megabyte after that.
So that, I mean, it's crazy.
It's still ridiculous amount of money, but okay,
that's better than I've seen.
In fact, if you're roaming, if I'd be in the states and use this account,
it would cost me £7.50 per megabyte.
So that's like 15 bucks.
Oh, man, porn gets really expensive that way.
Does it sound familiar to you?
If so, domestic life.org is calling your name.
Turn into this family safe podcast where a young married couple
discuss ups and downs of raising two small children in today's day and age.
Again, that's domesticlife.org.
podcasting, it's Adam Curry.
Hello.
Adam, this is Pohaku from JediTrainer.com.
And I think we've got a very unique podcast that helps people improve their lives
by using the power of their mind.
Let me give an example.
Okay, you ready?
I want you to follow me on this.
Okay.
So back in your chair and I want you to relax.
I want you to relax.
Start from your head and move down to your shoulders.
Get your torso moved down to your thighs, your legs, and your toes.
Okay, now if you're all relaxed, here's what I want you to do.
Get mad.
Get mad while you stay relaxed.
Guess what?
You can't do it.
See, the mind and the body are one.
Getting angry requires muscular tension.
And if you stay relaxed, you can't get angry.
This is just a little tip, a little sort of a sample of the kind of things that we do
on JediTrainer.com.
People's lives are being changed every day by this podcast.
If you look at the comments on podcast, l.e.com,
and we invite you and your wonderful listeners.
I'm one of them, by the way.
To tune in to JediTrainer.com,
and I'll guarantee you your life will dramatically change
through the power of you and your own mind.
Aloha.
Oh, you hear that?
It's already giving away a part of the big secret that I wasn't going to talk about.
Shoot, see now I'm totally trapped in all these wires all on a second.
See, now there's that hum that I was talking about.
I'll wrap it off from my...
Oh, man.
What was that?
Oh, yeah.
That was Patricia.
Oh, man.
Hold on a second.
Let me just call her back real quick.
Tell her.
Doing a show.
She's probably going to leave a message.
Okay.
So...
Hold on one second.
Okay.
There we go.
So now I'm going to see if I can get rid of that hum.
Oh, hey.
The whole studio is falling away.
I got to do this differently.
This is...
This is not going to work.
I'll just keep it like it is for this show.
This is not the way to do it.
Okay.
I like the T-Mobile guy.
And he sold me something that I've been playing with for the...
Well, of course, I had to play with it because...
Well, it's an MDA, which is a pocket PC.
Oh, yes.
I can hear a mobile phone fan freaking out right now as we speak.
And this is...
What's cool about this is it had...
And I've had the XDA, which was our...
That was a heavy mod, man.
That thing was.
So this is definitely bigger than the...
Then the size I'd like to carry with me as a phone.
But as the guy in the store said,
It's big.
And it's powerful.
I said, huh?
I'll tell my wife that when she looks at being...
Because one of those, you know, like, what the hell did you buy now?
I'll say, huh?
It's big.
And it's powerful.
If you slide the cover up, it reveals Presto.
A nice little keyboard in Quarty format.
So you can use it with two thumbs kind of.
And yeah, I can get pretty fast.
It has all the pocket PC stuff in there and synchronization stuff, which, of course, does me know good,
Because I had to get all of my phone numbers from my Mac, from my Mac address book, into the...
Into the Windows world.
And those two definitely don't want to talk to each other.
There is a product out there that I'll point to on...
And in the show notes, which actually adds it to icing.
And we'll sync up your phone through USB, just like you do with any phone and icing.
And I was about to order it.
I was like, you know, it's like 50 bucks.
It's interesting because I thought, you know, that's like what castblast are cost,
But you know, man, I really want it.
So if it really is going to do the job for me, it'll be well worth it.
Certainly worth hunting around, for other ways, to do this, to do this export import.
And then I read that they hadn't yet come out with their tiger, compatible version,
and apparently an icing in tiger is all different.
So that was a bummer, but I'm going to keep my eye on those guys.
So what I wound up doing is I use this other program.
I forget what it's called, but I'm going to put a link to it.
That essentially outputs your dress book as V cards.
Then I was able to Bluetooth the V cards into the MDA, because of course it has Bluetooth and GPS,
and all that groovy stuff.
And then add them one by one into my dress book.
So that worked reasonably well.
And, you know, there's always loose some data,
or something gets messed up when you do that kind of stuff.
But it worked out okay so far.
And so then the coolest part about this is it has Wi-Fi built right in.
And if it detects a Wi-Fi network, it'll use any internet applications.
We'll use that Wi-Fi network, and it connects automatically.
And it's actually pretty damn good.
So what is the most exciting part about this?
Is that Skype now makes a pocket PC version available of Skype?
And it works.
I've had some issues with some people.
I think if you really don't have the bandwidth,
then you know, stuff starts to go a little wacky.
I'm quite sure.
And it's primarily on the receiving end, where it screws up a bit,
or maybe the process is working too hard.
I mean, there's a billion things that could be wrong.
I haven't quite figured out the perfect configuration for using Skype
with the built-in Wi-Fi.
But it's unbelievable how nicely integrated this is.
You can go into your address book, search for a number,
and then you can select, you can just hit the call button,
and it'll call that person to the cell phone network,
or you can say call with Skype.
And it'll use your Skype out automatically.
It's just fucking amazing.
So I'm very pleased with this thing right now.
And I will continue to report on the progress.
But right now, it's just great.
You know, my Skype is in my pocket.
I love it.
The web browser works.
Oh, no, it's all pretty cool.
All right.
Let's roll out some pod save music right now.
This is one that was brought to my attention by PW Fenton,
as he programmed it into the pod show on serious.
It's Christian Dozler and the honey Greek bookie.
Quick bookie.
Okay.
Great.
Wait.
What's your secret?
It's No secret, Dongkin.
It's Provisile.
I don't actually know, but as long as I'm shooting below par, I'm not going to ask.
Sounds great!
You think all that miscovee would prescribe some provisional for me?
Mind you, I'm no doctor, but the way I see it, provisils good for everybody.
So far as I know.
But as you said, you're not a doctor.
That's right, pumpkin.
I'm just an ordinary guy who takes a lot of drugs.
And gauze, like a son of a bitch.
Provisile is not for everyone.
Consult the physician before taking provisile.
Do not take provisile if you're just food on a daily basis.
Side effects may include nausea vomiting, headache, stomach rams,
business confusion, liver and kidney failure,
energy loss of mental acuity, diarrhea, shortness of bread,
chest pains, swollen testicles, irritated bowel pigeon toes,
respiratory inflammation, permanent blindness, loss of sexual motivation,
pancreatic dysfunction, googleize, polio, and temporary ducking of the stool.
I just found that.
On my hard drive, I was putting the show together,
and I got to play this.
I don't even know if I was supposed to play that.
I think that was, no, I'm pretty sure that was PWFenton,
but I think it was all PWFenton.
Him and his electronic bag of tricks, very, very cool.
By the way, I think I know what I want.
That I have to have some kind of work desk.
Pod, let's call it podcast desk build.
There will be a stand-up desk.
I think it's just so much easier.
I don't mind standing while doing stuff.
If I could just have everything, and maybe it's curved a little,
so I can kind of stand in it a little,
and then have a choice of operating the mixer.
The mic can come from high down instead of over to the right,
or over from the left,
and then I'd have high stools.
If I wanted to, I could kind of, like a bar stool, I could sit on that.
That's what I'll have to have made.
Maybe when it's a little bit cooler.
So all the news today, of course, dominated by the fact that,
and I predicted this, that the authorities know who the terrorist suicide bombers were,
because they were suicide bombers.
This was a simultaneous bit of news in the London bombings.
And this is what kind of your worst fear is,
these were British boys born and raised in the UK.
And basically, they were influenced by, well, we'll find out, hopefully,
whatever factors to do this.
But that came from inside the country.
And so I didn't predict that.
What I did predict is that they would figure this out
through the CCTV cameras, London is so wired.
So they literally were able to follow the route of this bus,
and see who got on and make a lot of deductions,
and they did raids on their houses,
and all this happened very, very quickly.
So, first of all, that's great.
I think that's an amazing bit of work has been done there.
And now we have to kind of figure out,
what was the background of these four?
What was going on?
How did they get so influenced to, you know,
basically, you have to be brainwashed, I think,
to do this one way or the other.
I mean, it's not human nature to want to kill yourself.
So, yeah, this is tough times.
And there's a lot of conversation going on.
And I must say, Auntie, the BBC is doing a great job
during all this.
They've got great coverage, great shows, great guests,
well prepared.
There's not too much drama footage, although it's there,
but, you know, there's not a lot of flags
and fighter planes shooting overhead with fanfare.
It's just real good reporting, and I'm very impressed,
and still very impressed by the Londoners.
See, update on the health situation,
still tingling in the index finger.
The shoulder still messed up.
I've got my exercises that I have to do.
It's definitely not spasming as bad as it was,
but oh, man, it's very, very irritating.
Especially when you are typing in the keyboard,
and you use your index finger a lot,
and you type on the keys, and it's like,
almost like there's a little bit of novocaine in there.
Yeah, I know.
None of this sounds too good.
Does it look low?
Oh, wait, sorry, is this one?
Okay, this is Jim from the Life of Jim Podcast.
A podcast for everyone.
Talk about everyday life.
Talk about exhaust gaming, photography, video, and computers.
I made it to a skid, play around with some music.
I'll have my family on, as yes, just to make the investing.
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
You can listen with Apple's iTunes.
Just search for a life with Jim.
You can also go to my website at lifewithjim.net
to listen.
You'll find show notes, photos, video,
and even post comments for each episode.
Can you turn that music down?
Listen to the Life with Jim,
a podcast for everyone.
Please, keep sending me promos.
I love it.
Submit at podshow.com.
The multitudes went forth
and cast their pods in the direction of all who would listen.
And casting their pods in this manner,
they were henceforth known as podcasters.
Take it in your ear.
One galley casting with Adam Curry.
Y'all done.
It's time for the hit to go.
With y'all, Polar.
Hey, Johnny Boy.
Hello, Adam. This is not a hit test.
I'm going to start right away.
All right. Here's intro.
Number one.
Right to the business.
Okay.
SOS Band.
Two.
I...
That... that... that...
Just be...
Man, it's too good to be.
Love is in the air.
John Paul Young.
Number one.
Easy.
Easy one.
And the final one is number three.
Oh, I love that.
That's crowded house during treatment's over.
Man, I think I got him all this time.
Somewhere we have a live version of that
that we did in one of our radio shows.
Back in the early 80s.
You're listening to the hit test.
Everybody.
John, Polar.
And this is the first answer in today's hit test.
This is change.
Oh, change of heart.
Oh.
All right. Same producers.
Shit.
I have four in my eyes.
Now I can't see clearly.
I've changed my mind.
I'm taking back my love.
Make it.
Change of heart.
Yeah.
Give me back.
Oh.
All my love.
Change of heart.
zrobić.
Everywhere around the ground
Lovers in the air
Every sight in every sound
Not even gonna attempt to sing along with this fun
Off is in the air as ancient number two
And this is answer number three and hit this number 48 crowd at house. Don't dream it's over
God, what do you ever dream
Come
And so number three crowded house
And
title don't dream it's over. Well, this hit us this over. I hope you enjoyed this one
And as always the address for feedback is hit us at gmail.com
And you can find information at the usual website
yompolept.com
That's J-A-N-P-O-L-E-T
That's calm. Well, thank you for listening until number 49 so until then bye bye. All right young poletta everybody. Thank you very much
Young hit test number 48 already unbelievable. Hey, um on Friday show special guest CC Chapman
He's got some cool stuff to talk about so make sure sure you are stay subscribed
Also
I'm talking to the folks at Apple
And we obviously there's a lot to discuss you know there's plenty of stuff going on with with the feeds and
With shows and
There's a lot of talk in the community
That would be the podcast in community help be as you know
And I think that we're gonna come with some
Solutions that maybe we can do to help each other. I think that's
How convoluted was that?
We're working on it. We put out some suggestions. I had some ideas to make it easier for everybody because you know
Directory building business is tough work. I know we have
120 node managers who are patiently working on my father dot org. So it's not trivial
But I think we got some solutions. Hopefully we'll be able to talk about this way
No damage announcements. That's what it's about. Okay
Daily source code.com is where you can find the archives for the show and of course the latest program and the
podcast feed www dot curry dot com for my weblog comments at Adam Adam at curry dot com you can send the
I had like 2% left on my Gmail account. Where's infinity plus one Google come on?
And
Anything else you want to submit promos send off to submit at potshow dot com pot safe music pot safe at potshow dot com
And the massive smash of a pot show on our car
I'll talk to you tomorrow take care everybody stay subscribed
Makes no claims regarding the quality of its pot showers or the sanity of its producers listen at your own risk