Delta Sierra Charlie 219er.
Something remarkable is happening here.
Video is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who managed what you can hear since
radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
Now you can have it all.
I heard it on a podcast.
Rock and fucking radio, you want it.
You got it.
Just download it and put it on a podcast.
No one's gonna stop you telling FCC to stick it, kick it,
the revolutions.
It's Adam Curry.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this short.
It's Adam Curry.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
Yeah, I got a source code for you anyway.
It's Monday the second.
Come on.
For you, okay?
It is the daily source code good evening from the UK.
It's almost 10 30 p.m.
Drastic mistake.
We had a really, really nice dinner and then I just kind of laid down on the couch and
well, I fell asleep.
Oh boy, what an interesting day, interesting evening last night.
That's right, Patricia and I had a night in Big Smoke.
In the Big London town, the big L, as we went to the playboy party and of course had
our own parties, then we got to tell last night in the lovely Dorchester Hotel, which is just
off the park.
It was a very chic indeed.
I'll tell you a bit about the party.
Of course, I also recorded a sound scene tour.
And let's get caught up on the stuff that's happened over the weekend.
And Monday, oh my god, my day behind.
So we actually got on the train around 1230.
We've taken a car out to London.
And it's just so much, and that was really because we were all kind of like dressed up
at a very departed year of last night.
And well, you know, I just didn't want to get a dress all wrinkled.
I don't want to get my dress wrinkled either.
We hopped on the train back today and actually started doing some editing on the way home.
It was a fine-risingly spiky podcast.
And I've kind of been indoors for the rest of the day.
So I missed all the beautiful weather.
But I got a lot of cool things lined up for you.
You've got a backtracks podcast.
We've got some pretty unbelievable pod safe music ready to roll for you.
Plenty of promo some news and lots of stuff to talk about right here on your daily source
code.
And this is new guy who's been creating mashups.
He's been playing a couple of his mashups on the pod show on serious.
His name is DJ Earworm.
And he does the most amazing job at mashups.
This is definitely one of my favorites.
Is this stairway to boot like heaven.
DJ Earworm on the source code.
Is anybody home?
Well, you don't know me.
But I don't know you.
And I got a lot of stuff.
And I've got a lot of stuff to talk about.
This is just a feeling
Feeling my rooms
One hour too bust
And my spirit is crying
Pouring in
Then my thoughts arise
brings a small duet dream
And before I see the ghost, I'll see the pain
Because of where it's gone
I know it's mine
In the city
This is just a feeling
It's just a moment
If we all call the time, then the fight will lead us
And the mood will go
With those who stand on, and before it will come
We'll have dinner
Because of where it's gone
It's just a feeling
Yes, it's a feeling
We'll fight for another moment
This is just a time change
If we all call the time, then the fight will lead us
What makes me want to know?
It's just a moment
If we all call the time, then the fight will lead us
And the mood will go
With those who stand on, and before it will come
It's just a feeling
We'll have dinner
Is that unbelievable?
What?
We'll have dinner
Can you eat it?
Can you own one?
Well, there's good news you can.
Go by bitjobs.net
That's b-i-t-j-o-b-s.net
For more information
Or download the latest episode of Bitjobs for the masses
It's an independent music podcast with a British accent
If you want to know what's cool
On the way to what calls call you
The song's cool
You told me you don't know
I don't care
It knows what's hot
And he's giving me a song
It's got a day
It's just cool
Next generation
Cathad
Thank you
Simon Tune
For the ode
To the daily source code
That's the stuff I love
That's fantastic
I really appreciate it
Also, they were just thinking they knew opening up
That's PWFrenton doing some arts and crafts there
And Tampa Florida
Love it fantastic
There was one more thing I wanted to say about the mashup
The stairway to Put Like Heaven
part and fascinates me.
She always has, and it's not just her appearance, but it's her whole background, you know,
this growing up in a hut, and playing with sticks most of her childhood, and then becoming
a big country in western star, and I saw this documentary, I don't know, and the living
UK channel or something, and I just blown away again by stuff she's done, you know, in
the past, she's given all the songs that she wrote with her partner, manager, she gave
them all back to him, all the licensing, everything, and you never hear about her with
anyone, do you?
You never hear about her love life, although in this documentary I saw, they did say that,
well, she actually said that in the early days she was, quote, very sexually active, and
I'm just wondering, you know, what, who was she done with, fascinating, just a very amazing
woman that is, let's see, what we're also going to talk about this, there's lots of stuff,
oh, we talked about on Friday, and thank you very much for responding over the weekend,
and the email is still rolling in, of course, the ACing Croni is nature of podcasting,
people consume the podcast a lot later than they're created often, and I posed the question,
you know, would you be interested in getting free hosting and bandwidth for whatever you,
whatever your podcast needs are in return for advertising, and you know what, not a single
negative comment. In fact, overwhelmingly positive, though there is, I'm learning some stuff here
about if we want to put a model like that together, what I'm learning is that people definitely
want to be able to choose what kind of advertising, and that ranges from, you know, I want
to be appropriate to my audience, okay, that makes a lot of sense, by the way, and people aren't
looking for spots, I'm not necessarily talking about, you know, spot advertising, but more like,
this podcast brought to you by, I think that's probably a good dip in the, you know, toe dip in the
water, but mainly people are concerned that, you know, they wouldn't have a, well, she's have some
kind of sex products show up as advertising in or around their podcast, so that makes it a little
bit more complicated, I certainly understand, it makes a lot of sense, so I guess there is some categorization
to be done, but everyone seems to kind of like the idea, so I guess we can still, you know,
we can still figure out ways to trade beads and murals. I'm tired, I tell you, I took a lot of
Adam, big night in the big city, everybody, I'm getting old, I'm actually going to be 41,
this coming September, September 3rd. Was this, I wrote something down here, oh yeah, this is cool,
my in-laws are here, I told you that, we picked them up on Saturday, and my father-in-law is,
he's like a fucking magician with his hands, now he's a musician, and he writes musical scores,
literally just from his head, and anyone who does that knows that that's pretty complicated stuff,
and you can do 12 piece orchestrations, just right on paper, and he's actually, he's sitting,
he's got a keyboard here, and he's, you know, composing stuff, and God knows what,
but he can also take, you know, match sticks and some gaffa tape and glue and create a fireplace,
you know, he's amazing like that, Patricia has a lot of those qualities too, and so I was talking
to him about the desk that we talked about, you know, I want to have a better place, because I
like standing when I'm doing my, I like just standing in general when I'm working,
I wouldn't mind having a working area where I could have my, my rack with my equipment, my mixer,
my power book, you know, kind of in a little more ergonomic configuration, and he's already drawn
it up, he's already got the blue print done with a nice little rounded edge, so it kind of fit my
stomach into it, and belly up to the, to the workspace, as it were, and tomorrow we're going to go get
wood, and it's going to build this while I'm vacation, this guy's phenomenal, so I'll be sure
to actually I should take pictures of the entire process, because what he's going to do,
I'll ask him to take some pictures, we can get the wood tomorrow, we've got the blue print,
and he's going to build it in the garage, and then we come back, then Patricia of course has to
okay it, because it is a piece of furniture, you know, and then we'll move, I have to empty like
8 million draws on the thing I'm using currently, and God knows we're going to put that stuff,
and then we'll move that to the garage and move the new thing in, and it's going to be really
exciting, so looking forward to that, and pod save music coming up, which will be pod safe, but not
necessarily works safe, so you are for warned. Good morning, CC. This is Dave Hamilton from the Mac
Observer's Mac Geekab, and okay actually I have to set that up, that was that was stupid of me.
This was a voice response that was sent to CC Chapman of the accident hash, and I was copied on it,
and I was so blown away by this story that I really wanted you to hear it, because it is about
pod save music, let me just go up one level here, let me roll that out for you again, so we'll
he'll introduce himself, and you'll hear this story, but this is Dave Hamilton. Good morning, CC.
This is Dave Hamilton from the Mac Observer's Mac Geekab, and no, I'm not here to plug my own podcast,
though, my PR guy would yell at me if I didn't. I'm here to tell you as a quick story as quickly as I
can anyway, that I just think is freaking awesome. Last night, my wife and I went to see now is now
here in Durham, New Hampshire. Now we just moved up here from Connecticut, and my wife,
because she's my wife, started listening to podcasts a couple of months ago, and
her now is now bought a bunch of their CDs, listened to it, and our first date night out,
now that we're here in Durham, we got a babysitter last night, two of them, actually,
to watch two of our kids, hey, why not, support the local economy, and went and saw this band,
and they were, they're great. I mean, you know this, right? But these are guys, there's three
guys in this band, they produce a ton of music, and they just sound great, they leave it all
on the stage, they rock, right? They don't, they don't hold anything back, they're not here,
just to go through the motions, they rock, and it was just so awesome sitting there thinking,
man, none of this would have happened without podcasting. We never would have found this band.
We never would have gone into sports with last night to have a, you know, a night out,
and it was all because of podcasting. So I just wanted you to know that, you know, it's
come full circle, at least for us it here, it has one, one family at a time, right? So, you know,
it would start it out, it's just something listening to in the car and checking out this new
technology, has now infiltrated our lives to the point where it's, it's helping to decide a
direction for us in our leisure time, and it obviously, that's exactly what it's supposed to do,
but I wanted you to know that it's working. So, pre-chon brother, rock-on, have a great morning.
So, how cool is that? This is exactly what I'd hope would happen, and it is indeed working.
We are picking up on new music, we're creating new superstars, our own superstars, and that's
not necessarily, you're going to be millions and millions of sales and records, but I think
we'll be able to make some good beer and rent money, you know, and I'll take that as a start,
and the growth rate over at the Poncec Music Network is unbelievable. We're approaching a thousand
artists now, we've got a thousand podcasts, and a thousand and close to a thousand songs that have
been downloaded of the catalog that is. So it's just unbelievable what's happening, and I think
we're getting the store together so that anyone listed on the Poncec Music Network itself
to the Poncec Music Network is going to be very cool. Okay, I warned you earlier about the content
of the Poncec Music for this particular episode of the Daily Source Code, but it's not, you know,
the mood on that, but, you know, it is still kind of the beginning of the week, so it might apply to you.
I can't pay the rent and my pockets are empty, but you box reminds me of all the songs I
lose when I'm too busy and while I'm in the blue, everything is so fucked up, everything is so fucked up,
bittersweet is bittersweet, and even your memories are a memory, with someone banned the
other drink, with someone banned me another whiskey, everything is so fucked up, everything is so fucked up,
and someone asked what you've been down, nothing is all I could say, it's hard to do much when
I'm always in pain, just getting awake the next day, every song already had its turn,
I hate music, that's a whole masterpiece, you think it's fun to be 31 and have ambition,
not the bullets for the gun, everything is so fucked up, everything is so fucked up,
everything is so fucked up, my fingers just ran, I love,
gentry bronze and then the night watchman from San Francisco, everything is so fucked up,
you know if you're listening to the source code in the evening, it's perfect, you know, I've got the
lights dimmed and I've played that Daldy Parton song and now kind of this lounge,
piano, bluesy, type jazzy stuff, which reminded me of the last night after the party,
Patricia and I went to the hotel bar and it was a very, very chic, very classy bar and there was
a guy in there, just playing the complete Vegas repertoire, you know, like Moonlight in Vermont,
they didn't stop and actually it was interesting, we were sitting there actually having a late night
snack and the Liam Neeson walks in, so we had a real close encounter with a major superstar, he was hammered
by the way, I don't know if he was in town doing some work or apparently he's a regular at the hotel,
is it just me or was there like some kind of meeting where Germany and England and France and the
US all sat together and the world leaders said, hey let's go out and tell the world that Iran is
doing nasty shit and then I watched the news on television about them doing something that could
give them apparently some kind of enriched uranium, which would allow them to create nuclear power,
which of course immediately is thought to be a nuclear bomb, but then yeah, the pictures that you see
just don't correspond with what they're saying, you know, you see like power plants and then
like a Google Maps picture zooming in on a couple of barracks, I don't know, I'm quite sure I'm
understanding what's going on, maybe we're getting ramped up for something. A couple of days ago,
I posted something on my weblog at curry.com, the actually wind commander William wanted to know
what the origin of the English phrase, Tutal Pipp, Tutal Pipp, and what the origin of that was,
and I thought it was Tutal Pipp with a D, and I guess it was it's Tutal Pipp with a T, and there's
no real, you know, defined source of authority on this, but some say it's a derivative of Tutal
Lure, which is a French kind of like a sea later, and it morphed over time to Tutal Pipp.
Some also attributed to the sound that horns made on cars in the early 1900s. Well, Tutal Pipp,
I guess that's it. Thank you very much. It seems to be no definitive answer to that.
By the way, I've been talking to a lot of people about this lately, about living in the United
Kingdom as an American. Now, I guess we all are kind of like chameleons, you know, and you kind of
adapt to your surroundings, and we lived in Belgium in the castle. Now, the Belgian speak Flemish,
which is at least the part where we live, either they speak French or Flemish.
And the Flemish speaking part of Belgium, it's the Flemish is Dutch, only it's with an accent,
you know, it's southern, and words and phrases are differently, somewhere it's a completely
different, some phrasiologies, you know, and really it's more like a rhythm of the way they speak as well.
And when you're surrounded by, you know, a culture and people in language the whole time,
you start to pick it up and you start to incorporate it into your own speech.
And I'm really afraid to do that over here. I think I've talked about this before,
because everybody, every Brit here, when you say Madonna, they roll their eyes up and they're
heading, go, oh God, you know, she's trying to be so posh and posh and she's trying to,
it's your accent, it's just horrible. And then I think, you know, and I, because I was reminded
this, I saw Madonna's in the Vogue over here with the pictures of her country estate and her
and the kids and they're really great pictures and she's really, um, she's wearing kind of
classic almost 1930s clothes and she's beautiful that way. She really looks pretty and it suits her
extremely well and then she's in bed with Blu-Pajamas and the kids from Blu-Pajamas and it's all
just really nice. And I think, you know, I know our little bit, I've met her a couple times.
I think that she really just wants to fit in and she really enjoys the United Kingdom and of
course we're here. I understand, you know, why? And I see all the benefits and the stuff that she likes
but it's so unfair, um, because she's, she's really, she lets herself be assimilated and she's
taken that step and she said, okay, I'm just going to go with the flow of my accents here and it's
and, you know, and she kind of slides in and out of it but it's really, um, speaking English, speaking
proper English is, it's almost more of an attitude and it's more like, you know, the whole rhythm
of the speech, you know, you're much more careful about the words you use and the phrase
theology and your whole vocabulary kind of expands and certain long words that we would skip over
in America, um, are still, you know, utilized here and it really shows, um, uh, a different kind of,
um, I'm not going to, I can't look at my finger on it but it's more than just an accent.
There's, there's an attitude to it that you kind of take on and that may be it that there's some
offense to that, but anyway, um, a plea to all you brits out there, you know, let, let us yanks
slide a little bit, you know, we, we really want to try and blend in. We're here, we're here to learn
we mean you know hard. Oh yeah, oh yeah, we'll hide everybody. This is Dr. Puff.
I'm the host of a Reggae and Dub podcast called Pumpcast. Here's a testimonial from
Drew Domkis of the Don and Drew Show. Man, I just wish somebody would do a Reggae podcast.
I sure enough, this guy's going to do a podcast, which is all Reggae and, uh, it's just great, you know,
I mean, if you're in the Reggae, that show is just awesome.
Each show, we try to feature the best pod save Reggae and Dub out there and we try to create a
relaxing groove, maybe the perfect thing for that post daily source code lighter flick.
So subscribe through our RSS feed at the website puffcast.com or we're also in the iTunes music store.
P-E-U-F-F-C-A-S-T. That's Puffcast.
Special thanks to Don and Drew to Rob at podcast 4 and one of that little interview's
snippet. And, uh, and special thanks to you at him for the inspiration for Puffcasting in general.
Reggae and Dub all mixed up with my own homemade electronica.
Oh, guys, Steve, Irene.
Yeah, Irene, I can't wait to go back to Jamaica. I think I've been 15 times in Jamaica. I love it.
And there's a virgin flight that goes direct. Okay, that'll be, that'll be, that'll be,
we'll do that in the winter when it's a shitty weather and we have some more vacation time coming up.
It's a daily source code. Let's, um, Y'am Polite is really busy actually.
Yeah, got a note from today that, um, hit test number 51 is on its way, but it looks like he's got, uh,
he's got a gig and he's got some stuff going on there in the Netherlands and I'm not
allowed to talk about it, but as soon as some news is known, I think it's very exciting and I definitely
want to young to come on the show and talk about it because it is something that's evolved out
of podcasting. Um, but I got your fix of trivia stuff. Backtracks podcast. So you think you know
your hits backwards and forwards. Yeah, right. You're listening to the
backtracks podcast exclusively on the daily source code without I'm curry. Hey, Adam.
Hey, how you do? Let's get right into this week's quiz. All right. Listeners ready?
I'm ready. Are you ready, Adam? Yeah, I'm ready. Okay, here we go.
That's number one.
Yeah, I know what it is. This is uh, uh, who's Johnny Eldebard.
Time's up. Number two.
It's the same rhythm, uh, tempted by squeeze. That was interesting.
So four number three.
Something really heavy.
Either I don't know the song or no.
Time's up. Okay, here the answer. Okay. Number one is a prize.
There you go.
Uh-huh, uh-huh. Johnny Eldebard.
And here's number two.
I love that song. That's right. It's tempted.
Number three.
I love that song.
What the hell is this?
Like Ronnie James D. Or something.
You got another thing coming.
I would not have guessed that one.
So how did you do Adam?
Uh, two out of three. It's my standard fair.
Thanks for joining us on this week's Backtracks podcast quiz.
You can visit Backtracks podcast on the web at
Backtrackspodcast.com.
You can catch it next time.
Backtracks podcast. Spin it back.
Man, that is just such a wall of sound.
It was a good time right here that I love the production.
All right, that's it for the source code.
Almost up to our 40 minutes for August 2nd.
Thank you very much for tuning in.
Sorry, I was so late with the show today.
So tomorrow, I should have time to either get it all done or at least start working on
a major portion of the Playboy Party sound scene tour.
So look forward to that.
I've got a little mellow or day.
Not as many phone calls as today.
Seems like there's another wave of press coming around as well.
So uh, beyond the lookout, be a look at an email if you have your own podcast.
Because that's the best way to get it out.
And I guess the press are back for more.
So, now they're looking for angles.
I have another angle on this podcasting phenomenon.
All right, it's Adam and Curry.com.
As you can send me audio feedback.
I'm still kind of staying ahead of my Gmail.
I deleted a couple of attachment-based emails and I'm done like 96%
so send it anything if you got it.
www.curry.com is my weblog.
We can always find a source code posting and also other stuff.
And daily source code.com for the podcast feeds of this particular podcast.
And if you have a side by radio receiver, stick it in your ear.
Man, I'm so ready for vacation.
And I gotta go line everybody up.
I actually, I gotta copy Doug right now.
I gotta tell him that we have all these villains coming next week.
Thank you very much for listening.
Wasting your time with me.
Stay subscribed. Bye-bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.