Delta Sierra Charlie 278. Good morning everybody. Welcome once again from Ontario, California.
This is a daily source code. It's Saturday morning, crack a dawn. You can hear the lovely air
conditioner here in my Sheraton hotel suite kicking in once again. I can think of me
up all night. Every single time I would kick in or actually when it would kick off, turn
off, then I would wake up in a slight sweat. I am definitely jet-lagged. I got my nice inroom
coffee going here. I feed it just give it a little update on what's happening here at the
portable media expo. A couple of things that happened yesterday and just give you my
impression and talk about some other stuff. We'll enjoy a couple of coffee this morning
together. I was looking for some cool music to play on the Pod State Music Network and I actually
wound up checking a couple of podcasts out, which is usually the way I find a new music or a music
that I want to play on the show. It doesn't necessarily have to be new. Some of that pod safe stuff
is years old and just now getting uploaded. I bumped into a Pod Show music re-wine number 7,
which I hadn't heard yet. This is the show. You can actually find that music.podshow.com
on the homepage. It's a 7 different Pod Show music podcasters and it's a selection. I think
Marcus from the scenes scene takes one or two songs and a little piece of a clip of each show
and puts that together at the end of the week, which is a really great way to listen to some
very diverse bunch of tunes. And CC Chapman played this song that I immediately went looking for
and maybe I'm just not searching right, which doesn't make any sense or maybe it's just not uploaded,
but if CC played it then I'm going to assume that it is Pod safe and therefore playable on the show.
It's a perfect Saturday morning song. CC likened it to the Beatles and
something else. What do you say? I don't know. To me it was more like a Dooby Brothers vibe.
I think he's a Massachusetts native. The name of the band, I think it's just one guy is the candy
butchers. And so basically what I'm doing now is I'm ripping a piece of the Pod Show music re-wine.
I'm cutting CC off and going straight into the song. Oh shoot, hold on a second. Dude, I didn't
have my, I didn't have a Pod about hold on now. I got to listen to CC for a second hold on. Here it comes.
That's what she said. And I'm like, okay, what is this? What am I in for? And the next one?
Yeah, so CC was very surprised by this guy as well when he said, I think he saw him play live.
Play the most amazing rocking set I had ever seen. Come on, CC, get to it.
Me away. It was a mix of like the Beatles and Elvis Costs. Yeah, there you go. He said the Beatles
and Elvis Costello, but I disagree with that. It's much more like the house, like the dubies.
Played and played play. And the reason they did this was they didn't have a drum set that they're
waiting for. And I had this on a queue up too. And they rocked the house. Yeah, they rocked.
And that showed the musical talent. And I went home and I couldn't stop raving about them.
And I thought, come on, CC, there we go. Check this out. What are we going to do about Michael?
I think is the title.
Dream the bottom and friends. Well, she knows what to do with Michael, she knows how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how
how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how, how,
Oh, try to make him feel
That he's the one
He's his mother son
Not like anyone
It just needs time to heal
Hey finally hooked up for the first time
The night before the fourth of July
He felt so awkward saying goodbye to the girl who just changed his life
Now my friend, they are in separate ball
She even gets that boy to go to the gym
Now if you don't think that's love
You must be cynical
Oh, maybe man
You're just dreaming in French
Yeah, because he knows what to do with my call
He knows I'm against him
He's his mother son
Not like anyone
It just needs time to heal
Oh, she knows what to do with my call
He knows I'm against him
Yeah, that he's the one
He's mother son
Not like anyone
It just needs time to heal
Yeah, he's the one
He's his mother son
Not like anyone
It just needs time to heal
Oh, that's right
He just needs time to heal
He knows
Man
Is that a candy putster
He's quite easy
Is that a Saturday morning song or what?
Oh man, I'm totally, totally loving that
The connectivity the hotel is not the best
So I wasn't able to download any other songs
I really just wanted to
Just wanted to do a quick podcast
Last night were the podcast awards
Not quite sure how they worked
I think the winners were announced a long long time ago
And this was essentially the award ceremony
Got a real nice, like Lucite thing here
For 2005 podcast awards
I received the People's Choice Award
The people have spoken for best-produced daily source code
I really appreciate that, it's very nice
Meeting all kinds of cool people here
And last night at the award show
Just unbelievable how many people I know about or heard of
Or recognize their voice
Oh, by the way, long with that prize
A long with the prize
Came a check for $250
Which I re-aworded to Doug K's podcast Academy
I think is fantastic
It's really it's for real, it's happening
I think the podcast Academy is something that we came up on
Came up with like an 18,000 feet flying back from Nomdex
And we were talking about that
Maybe it was the oxygen
But Doug certainly got that kick in man
That's very cool
And I also received
I think all the winners received a microphone
A brand new microphone
It's a
Hile
I don't know about the name there
H-E-I-L
The PR40
Let me see what they say about the Hile
Hile sound has established a reputation for innovation during the past 37 years
In the live concert sound market
Custom home theater industry
Building the highest quality microphones for the amateur radio and communications market
Okay, so this is apparently their top of the line
Should we try it out?
Okay
Let's do that
That's actually a pretty cool idea
It has a
Let's see, does it have a
Let's fit on my stand here?
Yeah, I think that will
Okay
Here's what I'll do
Right now I'm on the AKG
See 1000s
So I have to turn off the Phantom power for second and an unplugged switch over
So just bear with me for one second
You'll kind of hear it plop and around
And then we'll be on the new mic
Hold on
Right
Oh
It's actually sounds pretty good
Wow
This is nice
Hold on, let me put it on the old stand
It has its own
Shoot
I'm talking into the side of it now
There we go
It has its own
Oh man
My other mic stand is really jacked
I'm tight here
Hold on
Here we go
It has a little hold
Oh shoot
So it has its own holder
But now I have to unplug
I unplug the mic again to make it work
Okay, hold on
Let me
Let me see
There's something I can play for you
No, I don't
Okay
We're already committed to this
Stay with me
Wow
They even have a
Shoot hold on
I have to unplug it one more time
Bear with me
There we go
Wow
It looks very professional
I have to say
I think it sounds nice
Let me just
Yeah, it has nice bottom range
Nice bottom range
Yeah, lovely
Oh man
I got a cool sound clip
That somebody sent me
Check this out
This is
This is in regards to the discussion
about the curry cruiser
The jag xj
Superv8
That was sleek and smart
For men who'd like hand jobs
From beautiful women
They hardly know
That's from that crazy
Crazy movie
That's not again
I like that
That was sleek and smart
For men who'd like hand jobs
From beautiful women
They hardly know
Fantastic
Last night
As I said
I was in bed around
Around 1030
It was so tired
And I tried to listen to a couple of podcasts
And I watched a little bit of TV
Which is completely boring
I think around 1am
Someone knocked on my door
Because it did wake me up
And then this morning
I saw an email
From around that time
That there was
Let's see if I can find it for you
That there was a pajama party
Oh yeah
This is a rowdy bunch
Let me tell you
Let me see
It was from
Madge
Let's see
Come on Madge
Where's your email
Now here we go
Sexie PJ podcast party
We're taping the pajama party in our room
I won't give you the number
In half an hour
Soccer girl
P.K. and Jay chick
Nicole and me
And a couple of creepy dudes
It'll be videotaped for the feed
Nicole looks sexy in a 90
That's a magic stylus
Who's a long for the ride
And this morning
The PJ party didn't show up
But some of the stuff that Madge did yesterday
It's pretty wrang actually
I don't know if I'm proud of it or not
And some other people were up really late
Drinkin' around the world
Oh wait, this is not the one
This is good too
Today's podcast for October 20, 2005
Welcome back
This is something I found
Long absence
Today we have a celebrity inspired term
Maya Copa
Recently Bill Gates used it when describing
Microsoft's failure to dominate the online music industry
Maya Copa
Spelled MEA
Space CU
LPA
Is a Latin phrase uttered to accept guilt
It translates to my fault
I think people like using the phrase
Because it is psychologically easier to say than my fault
Bill Gates used it
Maya Copa is interesting
While I'm sure Bill Gates
thinks he can dominate
Anything he directs Microsoft to tackle
Apologizing for not dominating the online music industry
Is awfully presumptuous
I've also heard Adam Curry drop this bit of Latin
On the daily source code
My notes go
I first heard it over a year ago
Back on September 27, 2004
Back in the early days of podcasting
I had no idea what that was for
I didn't know I inspired a word of the day
That's pretty cool
Now here's what I actually wanted to play for
This is pretty funny
I was up at a really pissed
Okay, so it pissed by the way
Some of the blackberries to close
Pist by the way
In Britain means drunk
Not angry
I've just been listening to your podcast
From fuck knows
I just want to drop your line saying
Obviously you're in and out in and out of England
And around Europe
This guy is so here and we're listening to it
Which means you're going to spend some time
Time in our car I am pissed
I'm recording this to some my eye book
So I'm just using that little PC
Little speaker
Microphone
So you're going to spend time
Jettin around here and there
And all stuff
Which means you're going to hit centre of town sometime
I'm a TV producer doing some stuff at the moment
And I actually right now I'm doing some marketing bits and pieces for MTV
I know you know that company
The Viacom brand
People that do these things
That's not the exact
So basically
You're going to meet a whole lot of people out there
To do that podcast
Whatever the fuck that's all about
I don't know
You talk about it
What is your show about?
That is a very good question my friend
That is the $64,000 question
What is it about?
I don't know
It's about experimentation
It's about what's happening in podcasting
It's the way my mom keeps up with what I'm doing
Exactly
Because I've listened to it for like the last three months
Maybe less or two months
I don't know
What your podcast is about
I don't know what it's about
I listen to it
And I enjoy it
But then I listen to Brandon and Eric
Doing the MacGeek.com
When I listen to the Twit podcast
I like that
That's funny
Although they always talk about video
I don't know what the fuck they're talking about
The video thing
I think it's just very very
Americanized
I don't know
Is that the word?
Damn, I'm doing it
I don't know what you do
I'm an American word
And then say is that right
And then at accept
I'm not going to get feedback on this
I did love your
What was it?
GMT
No, no
What should be
Yes
It is standard time
Is that a summertime
I enjoyed that
It made me smoke
Because I thought to myself
He means summer
I knew what you mean
It doesn't matter
I didn't need to write it
Anyway
What are these anal people about?
So, basically, a long short of it
My name is Charles
I'm a person
I live in London
Right, I'm brother
Love them what you do
I'd like to meet you
Could you tell them I can interest in person
So, if you were very nice
Okay, then it goes on to give us phone numbers
Which are one play
That's what I like about the Brit's man
When they're drunk
When they're a little bit soft up
They're funny
They really are
There's a certain point where they
They can tip over
And they become a little aggressive
And angry
And unreasonable
Like most drunk people
But
Yeah, it's
And I'm not for it
By the way
Because drinking is a huge
Huge problem
And Christina's 15 years old
And the story she's told me about her friends
Getting just so drunk that their vomiting blood
It's very disturbing
But it's such a part of the culture there
Oh, that's my, actually set my alarm
The blackberry waking me up
You know what?
As I sit here
In this extremely depressing hotel room
By the way, what I think is a fantastic microphone sound
This is well worth coming to the expo
Just to get this free mic
The sun is just coming up
I can see it coming through
The palm trees
The shades are cracked open just a little bit
I think it's the perfect
Opportunity to play this song
Which I have played in my
Was it the curry condo video that I did?
Jimmy Bratcher
Restless for this song
Good morning
Nothing's wrong but it's alright
I lay me down to sleep tonight
Toss and turn
Sleep on call
Restless for the song
The dreamer dream with you
In view
Better times and dreams come true
As what open tell me where's the dawn
Restless for the song
The view from here
Don't darken
It's shout so clear in my mind
Don't break in through darkness
Dreams come true
Better times
So hold me close
Sleep to me
For the dreams we've yet to see
Can't wait to see you
When the morning comes
Restless for the song
So hold me close
Sleep to me
For the dreams we've yet to see
Can't wait to see
When the morning comes
Restless for the song
That's just one of the prettiest songs I've heard
It's such a long time
From his red CD
It's just one of the prettiest songs I've heard
My going purely pot safe and proud to be that way I might say that
It was a really good discussion actually
There was another guy on who I forgot What his name was
He has a streaming business
And he had some interesting information about that business model
I think at the end of the day we all agreed
That there's significant change of flow
And particularly in podcasting with consegu
We're just routing around
all of the licensing issues, you know, it's the music industry's problem. They're bad,
but they aren't able to license stuff to us. See what else regarding Podsake music? Oh,
there's a new digital flots amount, P-Dub did an excellent, and you know, I should play a little
piece of that for you, just the beginning of it, because it's so excited. You know, P-Dub, we hired him
before a Podsho was a company to do the serious show. And actually, I've never met him in person,
which is just a travesty, although Madge Weinstein thought that she met him on one of the video
cast that I saw, turned out to be Chris Kringle. Let me see if I can just bring this up for you,
because P-Dub has now also decided to go 100% Podsake, which unfortunately also means that little
that signature, beginning that he has, today, today, today, that's kind of his digital flots.
I'm starting thing there, his tune. I'll just play a little bit, because I think the, I think he
really sums it all up. And as you listen to this digital flotsome episode number, what is it's 20?
Oh, my second, this has 26, but I had 27. Shoot, I have to get it from the, it has an updated
yet, and I too, thank you, iTunes. Okay, I'll get it straight from his site that I'll work too.
So we start off basically pronouncing the, what is this? Man, I don't understand what's happening
with my website. It really fricking blows. I want to move this thing to WordPress so bad.
Okay, let me go to digital flotsome. I'll get it straight from digital flot. I thought I'd link to it.
Okay, yeah, it's the rest-in-piece edition. So it's just going to open it with iTunes.
What the hell is going on here? Oh, it's streaming? Interesting. Okay, let's see if that actually works.
Oh, maybe it would help if I, there we go.
He talks about the new revolution later on. One thing I do know for sure, it's over. There's no,
I'm not going to be playing anymore licensed music. If it's not registered through the
Podsafe Music Network, I'm going 100% Podsafe from this moment on. It's over. It's over. It's over. It's
over.
Dearly beloved, we are gathered here together on this solemn occasion
to mourn the tragic passing of two siblings, the recording industry and the broadcasting industry.
Any time a passing like this comes so unexpectedly, it is hard for us to understand.
We often cry out, why Lord? Why were they taken?
Often their passing seems so senseless, so unforeseeable.
But I am here to tell you that this is an instance where I think I can bring the grieving
some comfort in the knowledge that even this tragic passing can be explained in a way that anyone
can understand.
The idiots brought it on themselves. They sinned until they were punished for their single-minded
green and lack of imagination made ways suffer for eternity.
How cool is that, huh? Hello and welcome to another edition of digital flat out.
You really should listen to the show to get the full effect. While that was playing, by the way,
I opened another piece of my little prize package there. This is a shock mount for the microphone.
Built by those who care and fair few heights of Illinois, USA. I can tell you guys care because this is
some good ass shit, man. I like this. So it has one of those wire frames, real professional looking
and I don't even need a like a plop filter. Well, maybe a little bit, but I've got a really
like the sound of this mic. This is cool. Something else that I heard last night was a cotton
steam song podcast, KTSP and I was so sweet because she obviously also heard about me going
to a purely pod safe and she dedicated an entire show to me, which was just so beautiful.
The flying edition, of course, all kinds of flying songs. So I don't know what she's going to do
now that now that that is no longer going to be legal anywhere, but also not in the Netherlands.
I wonder she's going to continue with that show. It's too bad because the way she
aggregates those songs and gets all the right themes together. It's fantastic. It's my favorite
favorite podcast for a Sunday late morning. See who else did I want to talk about?
Oh, yeah, yesterday during the awards and the place was packed and still it's such a fun vibe
and there's so many different people here. There are lots of listeners who
sponsored their like the tartan podcast. What's his name? Mark from the tartan podcast.
He's from Scotland and one of his biggest fans, one of his listeners, co-sponsored his trip out here
and I talk with her for a while and she's just really into it and she's in a totally different
business and there were listeners who came up to me yesterday who were big fans of a podcast
heard about the expo and just wanted to come up and meet everybody and I hold on. I should get my cards
one second. Just stay right there, okay. Let me just grab this out of my. Oh man, where did I put them?
Oh, here they are. I think this is it. It was I think was Darren. He introduced himself as one of the
blind casters, which to me was very, very evident when he came up to me. This is the guy actually
who wrote me an email and pitched him on and was kind of mean in his approach. I don't have his
card here about some accessibility features, but we had a really great chat surrounded by
million other people which is what I hate about these types of gatherings as you can never really
sit down and just chat with someone which is actually why we have the the pod show lounge
is so we could just you know have a place where the pod show people can hang out and talk with
people and because you know there's like stars man, the frickin celebrities. Look at Dawn Drew is
amazing yesterday. It's like sunny and share on acid. More acid than sunny and share. So anyway,
so Darren had some really good remarks about the pod safe music network, particularly while
it's all about accessibility and I really want to make it our mission and this is a message to
pod show HQ as well. In all the building that we're doing, let's try and put these accessibility
features for a huge core audience of pod casting, namely people who are blind. Let's make sure we
put that into the DNA of our thinking and that we always develop with that in mind because there
are some things particularly about the pod safe music network which is really bogus that don't
work for instance the verification email. There's some flash is a huge problem and I don't know
if there's like alt tags or accessibility features and flash that you can use but I can certainly
see why flash interfaces don't work for the blind. So anyway so yeah he was going through this
whole list of things like dude you know I've afforded one or two of these emails that I've caught
you know that you sent to me but why don't we just give you a login to our bugzilla
database which is if you're not familiar with bugzilla you know look it up but it's essentially an
open source database where you can drop in bug reports and there's you know tickets are assigned
to them and you know it can go through a resolution path so that eventually stuff basically gets
done and of course it being open source and put together by a whole bunch of really smart people
it is very accessible so Darren was was completely you know over the just overjoyed with that and so
we're going to have him doing some QA and helping us out which I think is a great idea to have
your users those who are familiar with it and Darren is familiar with the with programs like
bugzilla actually you know I think that's kind of what was designed for wasn't it for users to
be able to feed back I think so let's see I had another message here let's just I'm just going
through the through the Gmail box and seeing what's up let's check this out for a sec well shoot
Steve Pender from karate cast nice the little like to have been there with you in Ontario
California with the media expo but the money hasn't exactly been there yet but we're working on it
and we have a chance in the near future to possibly make some money at this so that's good we're
working in that direction right on but I kind of wanted to talk to you a little bit about
what's been going on in your show notes I'm sure you've read it with some of the
just the crap and what he's talking about is the comments not the show notes but the comments
I think this is the thing if you've looked at the comments on curry dot com between
nightwise and Michaels in there who actually does the show notes and a couple other people even
I jumped into this thread and you know for 25 years now I've been studying the reality of
confrontations and what really amazes me is the crowing one could do on the internet the language
that is used here by some people would never be used face to face it's how bravely people run
there mouth online that is sometimes hysterical the internet has become a place where people with
zero confidence and spine can posture a bit by sticking their chest out and beating it like a
babbling gorilla I've met some of these internet critics face to face and they can barely get a
word out without wetting themselves the bickering in your show notes from Wednesday's show
about you calling someone out on your show was like comic relief I learned a long time ago
that one share critics will complain you know about how they're a life's treating them
and do absolutely nothing to change it so Adam if you don't mind I just like to say something to
these few one share warriors yes Adam Curry has a podcast show yes it is popular
yes if you're hearing this then you listen to it yes he has an agenda it's called the pursuit of
his family's happiness and yes he has that right in yes you have that right to voice your opinion
as does he and yes you're allowed to say stupid things to him and you should be happy he even
allows you to leave him messages and yes when you say something completely moronic he has the right
to publicly announce your stupidity hey man you should be thankful someone is recognized you for
your true calling in fact people like you should post their resumes on his show notes for possible
job opportunities you could sign it with a big ink stamp of a butt so people can recognize it as your
hi I'm Steve Pender the host of karate cast at www dot karate cast dot com
thanks Steve good pipes there man nice processing that's not really good
if you're here at the expo you've probably seen the t-shirts the unditioned t-shirts
if you go to podshow dot com you can also see kind of what that looks like there's an unditioned
banner that shows up a lot of people asking about that uh it is something that we're ramping up
wasn't ready to fully announce here at the uh at the expo I said and you know and it's also
not something you announce just something you do I think that if you look at the entire universe of
podcasters which is what 10,000 registered now I'm like very stuff that 10,000 registered podcasters
it's a podcast alley in any pod or dot org the the the 1000 most enthusiastic
shit man when we fill that thing on the floor um now let me rephrase that the people who came out here
who were able to come out not everyone who was it was enthusiastic podcaster and passionate about
what they're doing could come out but the people came out here are really very motivated and a big topic
of discussion is how do we make money on this and i promise you that that was uh what podshow
is all about and then we're going to um going to start answering some of those questions um as you
know there's a number of podcasters um which i lovingly call the pod squad uh who have uh essentially
been able to give up their quit their day job and podcast full time and it's not just their own podcast
but they're producing other podcasters and they're really working with us on creating what we think
will be uh the next set of tools needed for podcasters um and probably more importantly uh what
we need to grow our audiences and acquire listeners and uh having met hundreds of you here at the
expo and many hundreds more that i haven't been able to meet and probably won't just because there
is enough time um every single one of you seems really incredibly qualified and we feel that there's
a way and a process um to find uh people who we can basically help quit their day job if not just
say hey congratulations quit your day job. i think there's also a listener side to that by the way
of i've seen all these um these these really passionate listeners who were promoting their favorite
podcast uh i think uh that's a very valuable uh skill and and passion something else that can be
rural rewarded by allowing um great listeners and sponsors of podcast to quit their day job
that's really what this audition is about and stay tuned because uh in the coming weeks i'll be
explaining more about this and oh by the way everyone i mean everyone can participate and that's been
really uh pretty important point i think you're gonna like it the audition the largest promotion
podcasts about to hit you right between the ears
and the lips i'll either have your start tomorrow because i can't be around you and
i'll be with you if you refuse to come with me i'll go at a long
i'm waiting for a day when i can finally see
my dear sweetenos um fell for me
Because I can't be around you and I'm not big with you
If you refuse me to come with me, I'll go with you long
I'm waiting for day when I can't find a sleep
But if we blossom fair, my days we'd blossom fair
My days we blossom fair for me
Oh man, Robin Stein sweet blossom from her daydream CD
Played that on the source code a couple of times
One more thing about the audition, not only can anyone participate, but anyone who participate automatically wins
Because besides, I guess if you look at the steps in podcasting, there's really three steps
For a lot of you, I know because you're so passionate about what you do, the ultimate is to quit your day job
I think underneath that is G, I'd like to just make some money
Kind of like pod save music artists, you know, it'd be great if you had a hit
It's also nice if you can just get some rent money out of this
So I think that's a step that we can help a large number of podcasters with
Of course it doesn't involve advertising and sponsorship and doing business
But none of it will ever make you change what you do
That's kind of interesting, you know, all the shows that are now part of the pod show family
Just so you know there is an absolute rule as we have no say over the content
And it's explicitly stated that way, because I don't even want the opportunity to have the say over what's happening
And how many shows you want to make? I don't care, you do as many shows as you want
You know, you get rewarded based upon the audience size
So it's anyway, so then you have one more level, I think that's a vast majority of people who may not even be interested in
In monetizing their podcast, but we're surely going to open it up for everybody
And that's just give me some great, reliable bandwidth, let me map my feed to a service that is going to stay up and is guaranteed to work
And one that is not necessarily, you know, a new project, you know, and just access bandwidth from somewhere
And you'll be hearing about this just around the same time you hear about all the details of the condition
Is that we have teamed up with some great, great companies to create the pod show podcast delivery network
And I'm very, very excited about it
Man, I'm telling you a lot on this Saturday morning, aren't I?
Well, maybe one more thing I wanted to talk about, audible announced a service yesterday for podcasters
And you remember a couple months ago, I was talking about the concept of what I call soft DRM, actually Ron calls it soft DRM
We all hate the DRM term, and the fact that through DRM has such a negative connotation
Because when you say DRM, lots of people think, oh yeah, that's the stuff that, you know, that's from the people who accuse me of being a thief
And, and it's associated with not being able to copy and, yeah, basically not being able to rip something off
But there's a lot of major bonuses to having DRM, which is, for instance, getting a lot more information about your listeners
And being able to make your show a lot more interactive, understanding what people are and aren't tuning into
And I discussed this, well, we had a lot of, we've had a lot of ongoing conversations with the big digital rights management players
And, you know, so I've always been kind of searching for an open type solution where we can use all the benefits, but kind of, you know, can get away from the negativity of DRM
And, you know, that I had several conversations with Don Kats from audible
Man, this is so unfortunate because he took parts of the right idea, but then he put it all behind the corporate firewall
And, and he's charging people to use his infrastructure and his service
And that, that is not the way that I think I did a bad job probably explaining to him
What, what we wrote, the power really can be
And now, if you do the math on it, it seems like you're actually, you wind up paying quite a lot of money
To, to deliver your, you know, to really get this information where there's a lot of this information
Yeah, we could have done it differently, that's all I know, but anyway, so we'll have to see how that plays out
I'm not seeing a lot of, I'm seeing a lot of confusion about it from, you know, from podcasts, we're trying to understand
Well, what exactly does this mean and I think that what they're all seeing is, hey, this means money out of my pocket again
So, we're trying to reverse all that, you know, if you want, if you want, great statistical analysis
I mean, some really good, useful stats
Then you're going to be happy when we start coming out with the, with the PDN
Speaking of happy
Nothing like a little intweign on the Saturday morning
There's an edge of change that we can't look back and see
And just what went wrong
I want to know now when we are
Should I pretend in a little face, babe
Yeah, I know when or what you've done
Could you confess your face with me
There's an edge of change that you told me and won't think
Suddenly change your mind
Isn't it strange that you'd come here for me
Turn away and leave me behind
Now if he's like I'm drowning
If he's like I'm drowning away without you
I know the feeling
Cause I'll be a zombie for
I hope you don't feel just like me
I hope you don't like me
Isn't it strange that the world seems to turn away
When I try and explain
What's your strange that you can be as one
Yet another same
And if he's like I'm drowning
If he's like I'm drowning away without you
I know the feeling
Cause I'll be a zombie for
And if he's like I'm drowning
If he's like I'm drowning away without you
I hope you don't feel just like me
I hope you don't like me
Don't feel just like me
I hope you don't feel just like me
Would just lie me, I hope you'll I be
Love me, would just lie me
I hope you'll so feel just lie down
But I hope you'll feel much more
Baby, maybe not to I be
Not to I be
We'll go to my way
It'll Roger, an in time and happy on the daily source code
It is a
Let's see, it's a time for breakfast
What it is, one more comment I want to say about the podcast
Expo is that I think is really unfortunate
And somewhat strange that there is no channel out
This is not a blogging convention
So although there are lots of flicker photos
And there is a blogging going on, there's no audio
It's really strange
I would expect that it would have been made a lot more sense to stream
Some of the sessions or at least the key notes
That would have been great
Or create podcast
So I'm sure that they'll show up
Because people have obviously recorded these things
I just don't understand why
The brothers didn't think of making some of these things streaming
I think that's a great way to really hype up a conference
Anyway, it doesn't matter
Dude, we've done like a full show
Okay, I'm going to go have some breakfast
I might do a show tomorrow
Depending on what's happening and what time Doug K is flying back
I'm going to hit your right on the banana
So thanks for tuning in
DailySourceCode.com
As we can find the most recent podcast in the podcast feed
Or subscribe to the show
And iTunes
And we'll talk to each other very soon