Transmitters, we don't need no stinkin' transmitters.
Everybody?
It's Tuesday.
The power of New York.
The power ofNew York.
The power of New York!
The power of New York.
You know always for emergency work and one of those guys
like just leads it until the very end.
It's like it's okay that big crater in my jaw.
We'll deal with that another time.
So anyway, so now that we're kind of settled in
and Patricia found a good dentist, it was time
to start cleaning stuff.
So yesterday, we kind of decided on...
Patricia has a movie star smile, by the way.
If you've never seen her, Google Patricia Pi,
P-A-A-Y, and you'll see more than just a beautiful smile.
Actually, depending on the results,
you return from Google.
And it's all about symmetry and she's...
She really deals with technicians and stuff
when it comes to her mouth.
And so she's doing the same with me,
which is actually kind of cool because,
you know, I'll have one of those million dollar smiles.
I'm already, you know, like 250,000, I guess.
So I'm working my way up the chain.
So it's the daily source code for the next 40 minutes to give her take.
I will be talking about stuff going on in podcasting.
Of course, oh, by the way, I was going to say hit test.
I see that Michael Butler is online.
So why don't we see if we can get a hold of him,
because I still have hit test number 22,
which I decided I'd do with him together,
which was a hit test.
I've always had guitar solos.
Let's just see if I can reach him.
It says Skype says that he's online.
So let's see if we can get him on the wireless.
Let's see, it should be two...
Oh, man, it's really early in California.
It's like seven o'clock or something like that.
Well, maybe the computer is just on.
Okay.
Alright, well, he'll see that I call.
Hopefully he'll get to us if he is indeed awake.
Okay, stuff to talk about today.
Oh, this is something I've been holding on to for a couple of men.
It's might be even a couple of weeks.
By DJ Rico, R-I-K-O.
Something called Whistler's Delight.
22 tracks in this...
It's kind of a combination mash up mix.
It stands in a class by its own.
Seven minutes of Whistling mash up madness.
I'm going to give you some of the songs included in this.
And you'll catch on pretty quickly when you hear the song.
Peter Gabriel, Bangles, walk like an Egyptian.
Sweet George Brown, Centerfold.
You recognize some songs with Whistling in it.
Bobby McFarron, don't worry.
Be happy.
Actually, too bad.
I hate that song.
Otis Redding sitting on the dock of the bay.
Roger Miller.
It's all in this song.
It's seven minutes so you can skip through it.
But I guarantee you want to check it out.
Whistler's Delight.
The full version DJ Rico on the daily source code.
I like the voice of this.
Very huge riding there.
The whisklers . The light .
The full version DJ Rico .
The daily source code .
interest after hearing it for the second time, but it's certainly something different.
I discovered something really interesting while that was playing. I had this hum in my microphone,
and of course I have all those great stuff right, and I've got all the right cables and all
the right gear, and all of a sudden this hum appears, and I thought it was something in the
mic cable or something with an insert cable, but I've discovered at least how to produce it
and how to get rid of it and now I have to figure out what it is. The microphone is now
directed pointed directly towards my mouth, and it's completely level. Now if I tilt the microphone
up and I'll turn up the mic here for a second, so maybe you'll realize that files out there
can help me. Listen to the, as I tilt it more towards the ceiling, the microphone, you'll hear how
the hum appears. Listen, see now it's pointed up, you can hear the hum, and now
I turn it down and the hum disappears. So what the hell is that all about?
Can somebody please tell me? I was looking at the newspapers this morning. The UK is a real
big newspaper country. I really love all the, all the different newspapers you can pick up. It's
kind of like New York, you know, only instead of every corner where you combine newspapers,
you combine every shop, every gas station, everyone is selling papers, and there's all kinds
of different papers. And first of all, it's cool to see John Ren, a chairman of OmniCom
in the financial time, like almost the entire page. John is someone who made an investment through
OmniCom in our first company, which was Think New Ideas, and actually met him while I was
in New York, saw him again. What was in New York was the couple, wasn't that? Was it two weeks back,
three weeks back? And he totally, of course, understood podcasting was completely into it. And it was
very interesting article about how, you know, what the strategy is, and you know, basically OmniCom
has been secretly or secretly, quietly reorganizing, so they can really bring all of these combined
services under one roof to each client, you know, so that you have your television commercial
making, you have your planning, your media planning, where you're going to buy the commercials,
then you have your direct marketing, and what was the fourth one? Counting your money, I think,
was the fourth one. It was really interesting to see a big strategy change there for OmniCom.
And I think it's the right one because, you know, everyone knows that television advertising,
and certainly also radio advertising is not, you know, not as effective or cost effective as it
once was. So, big changes, and it's good to see the big big guns in there, working on it.
In the, in the times, so that's the London Times, there's this whole article, well, the headline
is Vatican plots against a Vinci code. And apparently, the Vatican is worried that people will start
to believe the blatant lies that are in the Vinci code. I got to tell you, I thought that
Vinci code was pretty damn convincing. In fact, I didn't read the book, I listened to it on
as an audio book, and it was really good. I recommend it. You can catch at audible.com. That's
where I buy my audio books. And I don't think I have it here. I would certainly let you hear a
piece of it, but they have, you know, good actors, good voices, good reading. But the Vatican is
really freaked out about this. And there's like, you know, there's 18 million copies in circulation,
44 languages, and just two years. And they're really going to do something about it. Not quite
sure what they're going to do. But already, books have come out like the Vinci Hokes and the truth
and fiction in the Vinci code. So interesting. I wonder if that stuff is in the US papers.
And I think it's already starting what I pretty much predicted would happen. We're going to see
the mainstream media now turning on the Michael Jackson's hand. And I've maintained that I cannot
believe that he's guilty of any of these charges. And I just don't see, I hear a lot of talk,
but I don't see a lot of evidence. I do see Michael Jackson getting slaughtered every single day
in the press, just everywhere. And it really is, even just the little things, you say, you know,
wacko jacko ha ha, boy, we didn't have a cute headline. I should hurt. So now it appears.
And this was, of course, page 33. It's not, it's no longer front page news. But of course,
it's the time. So I don't know if the time's actually writing anything front page about Michael Jackson.
But now it's turning out that none of these witnesses are credible. They're saying, oh yeah,
I lied at that point. No, I was lying there as well. You know, just completely no credibility.
Told us, Dean, Michael Jackson did not molest me. It's just, you know, the defensive, of course,
is tearing these kids to bits, which is also fucked up. You know, how can, how can all this happen?
It just seems so incredibly, you know, no matter what happens, Michael Jackson has damaged beyond
repair, as well, all the people involved in this, in this case. And God forbid, it turns out to be true.
Well, then, of course, I'll have to eat my words. But man, I got to tell you, I've met this guy
and I'll stand by my statement. I think he's asexual before he's anything else.
Yes, today, I talked about the mashups that I thought that they were kind of like, you know,
just stuff on the move and transition. And of course, Pimp Daddy said, got back to me on my comments.
I'm just trying to open it my outline here. Your comment about mashups of temporary is completely wrong,
Mr. Curry. It's the same with everything that's new and in reach for everybody. There's a lot of bullshit in the
beginning and really quality will survive. I'll never forget the feeling when I heard Beyonce versus Michael Jackson,
crazy in love and thriller, just you fork. If you don't know that one, here it is. So basically,
the Pimp Daddy is going to convince us that it is true that even if you go back to a mashup,
that, you know, you'll get the feeling just like you heard that song for the first time.
So let's all do the experiment together with thriller in love. Oh, man, that was like
not queued up. Very professional. Oh, yeah, I can see it. I'm really feeling good.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The fans became big enough, they like it's easy to see
Yes sir, I'm calm and you're the calm, my texture is the best bro
She's chillin' up, I've been chillin' up, I've been chillin' up, I've been chillin' up, I've got the name
Oh, I've been realin' to keep my words
Raise your eyes, I love you, raise your eyes
I love you, raise your eyes
You're on your left, you're on your right
You're on his right, and he's on his right
He's all dizzy, but I'm coming through the baby
I'm dizzy, or I'll go
Once he treat me,iegate, think it's your point
Young, then hurry
The darkness all across the land
A midnight hour is close ahead
Creatures crawling south of the land
The terrorize all in the world
And who's ever shall we find
Without the souls all getting down
My stand and face the harems of hell
And rock inside a corpse and shell
Yes, some place to lay down
I'll spread away
Shoot me out
Leave me alone
Young
The foundest guarantee in the air
The funker 40,000 years
And grills and grills for every team
A clown's in need to see your doom
And though you found to stay alive
Your body starts to shiver
For your own mortal can resist
The pain in your heart
And thus you're in love
What do you think of it?
Hello?
Oh, Patricia was standing right behind me
I had the speakers on for, she must have left
What do you think of that?
The mash-up
The what that I just played
I turned around and I said, what did you think of that and you were gone
Oh, I'm sorry
Did you hear it?
Okay, never mind
I'll play later for you
I was too sure
Okay, I'm sorry
Get off my show now
Yeah
Michael Jackson with
It's a crazy in love
What's my Beyonce?
Oh, great
How's it?
Thank you
I'll check your number in a second
Okay
Oh, man
Why don't we just try Michael Butler quickly
One more time
And then I'll move on with
Some updates
See, what is that?
I'm like, now the phone is going like goodness
It's just a busy fucking day today
Isn't it?
You can hear it vibrating
So we've got one incoming, one outbound
I don't think we're going to get a hold of Michael today
Okay
Anyway, got a lot of responses regarding podshow.com
A lot of people wondering
You know, what's going to happen
Anticipating
I'm hoping as I said to be able to make one or two announcements this week
But we're really going to be starting
First off with as I discussed in my previous podcast
With an investment in
In the content
In talent, really
And talent is not just people making podcasts
They're all the forms of talent who were out there in podcast
In the podcast community
We've also been talking to for a while
So that's where our first investment is going to go into
Because we have a lot of
Really interesting opportunities that
These first investments will be working with
You know, basically they can make money
Doing what they already do
So these are highly motivated people who
Already have built up an audience
And what's great about it is after our first phase
When we start working with
With our first talents
Oh, that sounds like the internet that I would say
Our first talents
That's my Dutch coming through
You know, then you'll be able to join if you're interested
And again, this is what we're doing is commercial podcasting
You know, there's clearly a market for this
And anyone who wants to participate wants to make money
Can make money
You know, that's the entire point
And you'll be able to participate with
Success of some of these podcasters that we're working with
In the first stages
To be able to be a part of their success and to contribute to it
And believe me, the way it's going to work
The more you contribute, the more you can make
So it's very simple
And again, there's nothing that has to be done with
Someone said, so what are you going to do about
Advertisements? Well, you know, you tell me what's going to work
That's really the big question
I believe what Howard Stern has done for years
Just think if you've ever heard Howard Stern is
Snapple commercials, I mean, that's an excellent way of
Advertising in a podcast
But you may opt for some other way to do it
It's I think that we're going to be okay with that
And, you know, Bill boarding this program brought to you by
Or this program was brought to you by that old works
You know, not everything has to change
Not all the models are completely wrong
But you know, if you want to transport them over to this new world
But a lot of it is going to work
And we've got it teed up ready to go
So, you know, that's the first phase of what you're going to see
And at the same time, we want to enable
Podcasting for much larger audience both on the creation side
But also on the listening side, that has to become easier
We want to introduce more audiences to podcasting
People who don't necessarily have an MP3 player
So there's all kinds of ways to do that
And that is the kind of stuff that you're going to be seeing
Coming out in the next couple of weeks
As we start to unravel and unveil some of some of the plans
I'm really, really, really, really excited about it
Almost excited, by the way, as this email that came in
Because, you know, I thought I had
Really come up with the perfect idea of using two dishwashers
Now, we already discussed that two dishwashers in your house
Is a great idea because you basically just take the clean ones
Out of one dishwasher when the dirty you put them back
Into the dirty dishwasher and run the cycle
And you always have, you know, clean place at your disposal
And you don't have to keep taking them, you know, putting them into the
Into the cupboards and taking them out is just one to the other
And then I thought that that was going to be it
Then John Hartnub sends me an email and says
The two dishwasher plan was not new to me
But as anyone described you, the logical extension of this plan
Simple, you buy two houses next to each other with identical furnishings
Live in one house until it's no longer habitable
Then simply move next door while you're living in house number two
Getting industrial cleaners to clean the dirty house
And have it ready for when you're ready to swap houses again
You know, when I'm rolling in all the hundreds of millions of
Dollars from podshow.com, that's for all guests
That's for all guests
Time for Adam Curry to take the Hiptus
With John Poelet
Hi Adam, this is another hit this
Just three simple in-throws and three answers
You know how it all works
I think we can handle this intro number one
One more time
Let's clean all things
And this is number two
One more time
I want to say
Sheera and the black devotion with Spacer
Can I have that for five out?
And this is number three
Oh no, it's not like that's the West Band or something
It sounds really cheese like a DX7
And these are the answer to answer number one
Okay
It's strong with y'all from try
Okay, scare me down with that
Where the hell you're going now
Come in
And answer number two
Sheera and the black devotion
The song is titled Spacer
He's a ladies man
Always with little kisses
Got that one right in that
And answer number three
It's the time excursion for
Oh, of course
This is rumours right
I'm sure
I'll do it because you started
Started by the jealous people
And they're in mess in something they had
Somebody else is holding me
Look at all these rumours
It's right on the every day
I just need some time
Some time to get away
From all these rumours
Yeah
And so number three
In today's hit test rumours
The time excelsion club
Well, that's it for today
All right, young girl
Feedback is welcome at hittestedgmail.com
And you can find information about this hittest
And a separate hittest podcast
As a young boy, let's dot to an L
That's J-A-N-E-O-L-E-T-D-T-N-L
Well, let them see you next time
For another edition of the hittest
Bye
Right on young, thank you very much
Excellent
And I'm still waiting for a Michael Butler to
Wake up
Oh, second, what is this?
I thought I heard a Skype call
Oh, it's not it's Ron Bloom
All right, let's talk to him
Hey, Ron, you're on the daily source code
Well, good morning at him
Good morning, daily source code
Listener
What are you? What time is it there in Miami?
Miami is a
Quarter past nine
We had a big emergency here in the city this morning
Oh, what happened?
Yeah, it was quite a big deal
A couple of us had to go outside
And determine whether it was necessary
To where longs leave shirts
Ha ha ha ha ha
Oh, man
You got the light
It's a beauty step in the temperature
Climate and we are indeed in
Short sleeve shirts
Oh, well hate you
We're in longs leave shirts here as well
All of those people who are listening from the
Colden societies of the world
Yeah
Back to visit
So what's up for today
Buddy, what are we going to be doing
Today we have a lot to do
We are kind of deluge with people
wondering about pod show
And how they can participate
and hopefully they can help make it better
So we're kind of getting into phase
of responding to the first group of people, you know, we have our little secret target group
that we're trying to kind of get involved first and then we have sort of our open target group.
You see audience how this ties in exactly with what I just said. Of course it does,
what the hell did you say? Something like that. It sounds really good only. Yeah,
keep going. I like it. You know, something else I was thinking about after listening to your
show yesterday was, you know, how important the directory, the personality of the
directory is, I've been looking around as everyone else has sort of these automated things
and just so excited to get ready to get to know our sort of our node managers and all these
people that are really, they're hidden superstars of content as the content makers and producers
start to proliferate the content editors, if you will, are really going to be the hidden superstars
of the genre and the secret producers who produce other talents. Right. Right.
Two groups very much like what happened that the good times in music and radio is when you
had great, you know, used to say in music business, what makes a great producer and they used
to say a great band. So by matching these great editors and producers to great talent,
I think we're going to see a whole new generation of fantastic podcasts. Poetry, man. That's just poetry.
Poetry and motion.
Slow motion. All right, I'm telling you. All right. I'm going to wind up the show. I'll
call you back later. All right. Thanks for putting me on. We're waiting for your first podcast,
you know. Well, I'm making a mission to update my weblog. So that that I did last night.
Really? Okay. What's the, what's the, what's the URL? Yeah, you're a genius. Oh, I'll
put a link to it. Okay. Mm-hmm. Okay. Mm-hmm. All right. All right. All right. I'll talk to you later.
Nice talk. All right. Take care. All right. And that's it for the daily source code, everybody.
Comments. Atomacteria.com will leave them on the weblog where you can find the show notes for today's
program. That's www.curry.com or we can go get the feed. It's daily source code.com.
It can also find the archive of the show. Tomorrow I'll be back. I'm finishing up.
Ron Skyping me. All right, everybody. Let's see, Friday going to London will definitely take
the eye river for that. Doing two interviews. One with a, a Dutch serious news program.
And the other one with BBC's Click Online. So I might as well do some sound seeing from the road.
Take everybody. Talk to you tomorrow. Bye. Bye.