Delta Sierra Charlie one nine or five.
This name is Edon Curry.
He's old way in a very moving wheel.
Right up, right through out the streets of Missouri.
His name is Edon Curry.
And though his vision's blurry.
He goes up dog that's very empty free.
Then say oh for his name is Edon Curry.
Edon Curry is named Edon Curry.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Hey everybody how you doing it is Thursday the 16th of June.
And you know what that means?
It's New Music Tuesday of course.
New Music can mash up and pot safe Tuesday on the Thursday.
Oh man I apologize for yesterday.
I was working on a humongous audio project.
I hadn't done one of these in all in years I think.
You know I had the big multi track recording software out.
It was pretty intense.
So I wasn't done with that until about a quarter to one AM of course.
By that I didn't feel like putting a source code together anymore.
And I started with relatively early.
So I apologize.
Of course I gave everybody a chance to catch up.
Most people are a couple days behind on the source code.
It's funny because I did the the Michael Jackson post Michael Jackson trial.
Post the verdict podcast.
And now you put a podcast like out there.
It just takes almost like 48 hours for people to hear it and start responding.
And the response once it started coming was.
Wow it was pretty much overwhelming.
Mainly in a positive sense but there are lots of good points there from other sides of the equation.
But I'm going to put that behind us now if you don't mind.
Let's move on to exciting things like pot safe music.
Got plenty of it lined up this hour.
Got some good promos.
Let's see.
I have a couple.
Actually two mashups.
One which will be a bit of a later on.
Also young pull-up checking in with a hit test.
It's going to be awesome.
And lots of stuff to talk about.
Patricia is off for a couple days.
She has left me alone in charge.
Oh wow.
So you know what that means.
Got my cell phone hand.
You got everything here to organize the entire operation here at the house.
Hopefully we'll remain undisturbed for the next 30 to 40 minutes as we bring you the daily source code.
The new music Tuesday on the Thursday.
Kick it off with a mashup.
The beat 52's versus Snoop Dogg.
The ace get a lot of airplay with that drop at like a time.
Rock it like it's lobster on the daily source code.
The beat 52's versus Snoop Dogg.
The beat 52.
The beat Blind Fort.
The beat 52's versus Snoop Dogg.
The beat 51's versus Snoop Dogg.
If that doesn't get you cranking on a day like this, then nothing else will.
I'm not ending rather abruptly.
By the way, I got a new version of MegaSeg that I'm trying out now.
It's a beta version which apparently is going to take care of all of the dropouts.
And the blitzlet we just see how to see what version it is.
I can tell you,
you, this is 3.1.3 beta1. Okay, thanks guys. Appreciate it. That is so cool. It's nice to know
that the so many folks will listen to this show and they're really trying to help out by sending
new software and this is definitely the place to try it out. I heard Madge Weinstein talking,
you should listen to the latest East Radio for the, I think it's for today for the 16th
Madge was talking about becoming quality control for Apple. I think that would be wonderful. I
can just see Madge at the very end of the assembly. Christ, my ass stinks. What is this damn
software? Okay, let's see. What do we have to talk about? First of all, yesterday,
not yesterday, I didn't do a show, but Tuesday night went to the Weezer concert at Brickston Academy
in London to Christina and her friend Ellie and this was all courtesy of Aaron from Parking
at Bitterman Square Circle from, well, his weblog and his podcast. I hadn't actually met
Aaron in person and man, he totally, totally hooked us up. We got there, we see around quarter past eight.
The band wasn't scheduled to go on until 915. So, went to Will call, they said, oh, no,
no, you have to go to the stage door. So, of course, immediately, I look like this mega
fricking hero to the girls. I go, yeah, we'll go to the backstage, come on, follow me, ladies.
You know, I got our VIP stickers and, you know, walked right in, no problem, right through the
side door into the, you know, right in front of the stage, literally. And it was great. The audience
was probably about the 30, 30-ish, of course, the band is now also a 30-ish. And it was good.
There was very mellow, very relaxed atmosphere and I hadn't been to a concert like this in a
long time where people were basically lighting up all over the place, which made me feel
right at home. And it was good. It was kind of a mix of just people who were out for an evening
to see some, you know, listen to some music, very low key, you know, a lot of pushing and
shoving up front. Although there was plenty of crowd surfing going on. And I think that Christina
and Ellie actually started a mini mosh pit right up near the stage. Man, that was rough, you know,
you know, here's your 14 almost 15-year-old daughter. And, you know, and she's there,
they're smaller than most of the people in the audience and the edging their way forward. And I'm
trying to keep my eye on them in a certain point. You just lose sight of them. And, uh, and just hope
for the best. And so everything worked out great and they had a fantastic time. Of course,
when they came back from the front of the stage, they had both lost their VIP special backstage
stickers, which, uh, is, that's a lesson they've got to learn. You know, you've got to hold onto
that stuff. So after the show, um, you went to the backstage area and I called Aaron on a cell phone,
explained the situation. He said, no problem. And within three minutes, he was right up front,
and he had new stickers, and he had more. He had a set list for each of the girls, which he took
right off the stage. He had drumsticks. He had guitar picks, even vintage guitar picks from the band's
2002 tour of, uh, Japan. I mean, it just, it was so great. It was cool to meet up with him and,
and chat with him about, you know, his view on music and podcasting. And what a great guy.
And I really appreciated Aaron. It was just fantastic with a great night out. And, uh, you know,
the, for me, the best part is, I don't know if you know how kids are, you know, kids, they take a lot
of things for granted. And, um, you know, kids are kids. But on the way back, uh, Christina said,
hey, Dad, I really had a great time. Thank you very much. And please thank your friend, Aaron.
And, and that did it for me. And I was like, whoa, okay. I've, uh, I've succeeded. So, um, and
also, let me just say about, um, about the band. Of course, I can't play a, uh, a wiser track because
that would be freaking a la, freaking a la. Um, very good. I really, uh, liked it. Sound was good.
It's a tough house. I think for, uh, for vocals, particularly, but the sound was very good.
And there were very much more technical than I expected him to be, uh, the, the guitar was just
unbelievably technically good and, and just rocking. And I recognized a hell of a lot more songs
than I thought I would. Great show. If you have a chance to see wiser, they're going to be on the
road road for quite a while. I think, uh, all over the globe, but I believe they're even going to go
back to Asia. So, definitely check them out if you have a chance. Good show. Good time, you know,
it's about our 15 minutes boom. It's, uh, it's just, uh, it's exactly what you, what you'd expect from a
a nice kind of pop rock, uh, show, but by mature musicians. Let's put it that way.
Great news. Um, about ipodder.org. We are in the midst of, um, talking to some
people. Actually, one person. It was very, dear to me. Um, ipodder.org is essentially the directory.
It's the directory that flows into, uh, pod catching software. It's the directory that's going to be
used for, um, you know, for a whole bunch of big pod casting initiatives. But the problem for me with
ipodder.org is I started this out and I started working with category managers who all, um,
some of them I, I worked with for a long time to help them figure out how to create an
opml file, how to, you know, get that into the directory and how to maintain it. And what you notice
with some, oh, boy. I'll be my wife checking in. I don't want a second. Hello.
Hey, babe. I'm, I'm in the middle of the show. How are you?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I, I'm strong. I'm not a show. I'm a bell's outrich. I'm a bell's outrich. Love you.
Mm-hmm. There we go. Uh, where was I? See, that's what happens, you know. They go away, but they
try and stay in touch the whole time to make sure you're doing everything right. Um, okay. So this was
really a community. Uh, and I was in touch with all these different people and as things start to get
busier with the show and with with pod show as well, I've been able to do less and less and basically
the automatic scripts are running and that's updating the home page and that's not always working
as well. So it really needs some care and some energy. And so we're looking at hiring someone to,
to really oversee that and really bring out all of the opportunities that are there for the category
manager for the node managers. Everybody who's works so hard on iPod or.org. So stay tuned for
some news about that. No damage announcements, though, for right now. We're just going to keep
it the way it is and I'll get back to you soon as I can. It is New Music Tuesday on a Thursday
pod safe. This is Chrissy and gonna be on a daddy's source code.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've never picked someone here. You've been in last place.
I can't wait to see this and look on your face. On the front page of your daily news,
it's the girl you always thought would lose. I love me, I'm gonna be all you think of
you
There's no question, you and I, I know that you don't matter, I'm tired
I'm a zombie, I don't wanna be, all you think is when I keep your eyes on me
I'm a country, not a way to see, yeah I'm a country, I'm a country
All you think is when I keep your eyes on me, I'm a country
All you think is when I keep your eyes on me, I'm a country, I'm a country
Yeah, I'm gonna feed no witness to you, I'm serious
Well, I'm gonna feed no witness to you
I'm gonna feed no witness to you
Ow
Do you wish me to spice up your sex friend?
I'm actually a non-alances, but I'm your hostess
Hi Adam, I'm Alexis
You're probably lucky enough to be among the 72% of couples that have a satisfying sex life
Oh yeah
But there's always room for improvement, right?
So listen to MXL, spice up your sex life show
A podcast dedicated to helping couples that have run out of desire, inspiration, complicity
Or that want just more great sex
Yeah, I want that
In the show, I review some interesting news bits and websites
I have advice, I tell stories, and more
Please your spouse or treat yourself
Visit www.MXL.ca
Or MXL podcast.blogspot.com
8.9th in my spicy sex to make you day
And remember, if you're going to love, love large
Bye
Please your spouse or yourself
Very interesting, worth subscribing to, I'd say
Hot show, content that will make you walk the dog
And kiss your mother
Hello Adam, we had live by thedrop.com
Thought that if we got a celebrity to endorse our podcast
We might get lucky and have our promo plate on your show
So here we go
Hi, this is my profession
I'd be from the show, on my family and my friends
That I'm so happy that you supported me
Just as prevailed today
I would say I'm not guilty on all counts
I told you everything
I'm so glad everybody believed me
I love children, and I would never do anything to hurt children
So thank you again for all your support
And I'm counting my shoulder show
Nice on thedrop.com
It's my shoulder podcast
Y'all tune in and check it out
And thank you again for all your support
Phew
Okay, I hope that did it
Be sure to check out our website at like by thedrop.com
Or subscribe to our podcast
You've seen your favorite podcasting software
Okay, we'll sound a little bit muffled there when Michael broke in
But I had me fooled almost for a moment
Okay, yeah, quick shout out
Let me see this is from Jeanette Beland
From Pasadena, California Adam
It's just introduced to the whole podcast world a few weeks ago
Found your podcast on iPod or it's a blast
Listen to your daily show on my laptop
That isn't till my own iPod is purchased
There's an entire community of fuller seminary students
And Pasadena that love the podcast
And check this out regularly, fill each other in
When we miss episodes
Just go to show their fans and all sorts of places
Looking forward to more good stuff from you
Thank you very much, appreciate that
Can you have printed them all out today
I'm so incredibly well prepared
See that was a double one
Okay, oh yeah, it's amazing who listens to this podcast
I think it was must have been about two weeks ago
Hold on a second, my phone is about I think
Can I already hear that it's about
Okay, now yeah, that my phone is going to ring
It was about two weeks ago
When I was talking about what I thought
It was an interview with audible CEO Don Katz
And so I talked about I didn't actually replay that
Because it was a very long interview
I thought it was on the media or future tensor or one of the NPR program
Which is I'm not sure now if that's what it was
But it came across to me and maybe that's just the way it was put together
Because of course, you know most interviews are cut up and spliced apart
And you know the host interrupts the flow
It came across to me that if you have a choice as a big company
I consider audible to be a big company
They've been at it for quite a while
I think oh man how long have they been in business like eight years and nine years
I heard I think was Don Katz talking and I said you know
It sounded like if you could choose between a extend or defend
Strategy as it comes to as it pertains to podcasting it felt a little bit
Like audible was taking a defense stance more than an extend stance
Well low and behold what shows up in my inbox today
Audio feedback from the CEO of audible
Hey Adam I was listening to the daily source code the other day
And was surprised to hear you talk about an interview with the CEO of audible
Well that's me I'm the CEO and I started the company
My name's Don Katz and we actually lived a few blocks away from each other in Mont Clare, New Jersey
I was a writer for Rolling Stone in the 70s and that was before
MTV came along and went way around Rolling Stone
And God knows we didn't defend let alone the extend as you often put it
As a new medium took over Rolling Stone
Anyway, I think you got me name wrong and the interview you were referring to was with Rob Greenley on the web talk
Radio on IT Conversations show
But as I listened to you I realized there are a few things I wanted to share with you
Based on your comments about the interview
I'd also love it if you ever wanted to come to audible and check out the technologies we're rolling out
So I want to extend an invitation
So the first thing I want to say concerns you take in my comments about the explosion of podcasting
And the correlation I made to the DVD market
I think you said that I played down the explosive potential of the audio download culture
When I said that iPods and other players are where DVDs were in the year 2000
In fact, the one of 10 people who owned a DVD back in 2000 exploded the 7 out of 10
And just a few years as the price of DVDs went from where iPods are now to under 40 bucks
I've always said that I believe this is where MP3 players and memory rich phones are going
The best is yet to come
I expected the explosion of digital media years ago
Way too early and I've got the scars to show for it
So a few people are happier and more euphoric about the growing awareness of digital audio downloads and I am
Now what I can be accurately accused of is believing that the podcasting environment
As opposed to the iPod culture is where DVDs were in early 1996
That brown the time I got going with audible, not like DVDs in 2000
We had to invent the first digital audio player between 95 and 97
And we brought out the first software system for secured downloads
And we put together an end-to-end system for delivering the content
And we built a business model too, all this way back when
And we've learned a lot about the things that simply have to happen to make the listening experience as powerful as the audio itself
We haven't talked much about how we're extending as opposed to defending since we don't like to make damn announcements
Until we're satisfied with the service we're going to have
But we'll be releasing podcasting features for audio producers in chunks of new functionality over the next few weeks
And months starting at NomeDex in Seattle on June 23
So if your game, I'd love to extend to you the same gentleman's agreement you had with Steve before the Apple podcasting announcement
And tell you about the new developments we have planned
In fact, if you're in London this coming Wednesday night, come to the launch party at Hush and we can talk
If you want to meet knock-around ideas we have podcasts, we could even do one together and that'd be great
So when we are in other, we're keeping an ear on pod show, so bye for now
Alright, thank you very much DonCats CEO of audible.com
And a couple of things that are very interesting about, first of all, it's unfortunate I didn't get this and the invitation until this morning
Which means I missed the launch party, which was happening in London last night
So I sent him an email and he got back to me immediately, he's still in London
So I'm hooking up with Don tomorrow morning before he heads back to the States
To my old stomping ground, the willabric mall and New Jersey was just so fantastic
That's where audible is headquartered
Something else I heard, which I really dig, is he said no damn announcements
I think we're changing the vernacular and vocabulary of Silicon Valley here
They used to be able to sign all these tough and non-disclosure agreements
Now it's just hey look, no goddamn announcements, that's an NGDA
No damn announcements, NDA
Gentlemen's agreement, I'm really liking that
So of course I'm going to hook up with him tomorrow
And I will come back to you my audience with as much as I can as I can
And if I were to put up a slide on a screen in front of an audience
And I said okay, who are the big players or who can be potentially big players in podcasting
I certainly would say Apple Microsoft and I definitely would have audible up there
So it's great that he's reaching out and look at the tools he's using
He's reaching out using our tools using the audio
So I'm very, very excited about that
Wow, okay, it is a new music Tuesday on the Thursday, the 16th of June on the daily source code
I have another pod save tune for you, this one was sent to me by Art Wixen
It's a mashup actually, Dave Matthews and something else
And it's a father's day mashup
I ain't got daughters on the daily source code
For all the daddies out there, that's you too
I know a girl she puts the color inside of my world
But she's just like a maze where all of the walls out
Continue to change
And I don't know like it
To stand on steps with my heart and my head
But now I started to see
Maybe it's got nothing to do with me
Some people live for a fortune
Some people live just on the face
Some people live for the mouth
Yeah, some people live just on the face
Some people pay and no business are paid
Be my name once we've been and I've been
And every phone and life's above all
All the support they show
It's so beautiful but I don't want to be now
And feel it you baby
I ain't got to go baby
Some people want nothing to be
Some guys want everything
But every lady's nothing
But you can go
Yeah, fathers bigger to your daughters
The daughters will love like it do
Girls become lovers
We'll turn into mothers
So mothers bigger to your daughters
Oh, you see that skin
It's the same she's been
Standing there
Since the day
She saw him walking
Now she's left
Clean it up the messy day
Some people say
Oh, I'll take
This is for the young
Some people think
We know they're around us
And it's known you're way to prove your love
And we know we're all
On the silver matter
And what's going on in me
We know when they share
But no one who is true
We can't
Call me
Some people want it all
But I don't want to be now
If it ain't you baby
If I ain't got to go baby
Some people want nothing
Some just want everything
But every lady's nothing
If I ain't got to go
Yeah, you, you, you, you
So fathers bigger to your daughters
Daughters will have like you too
Because we come to mothers
We turn it to mothers
So mothers bigger to your daughters too
Oh, as you can break
You find out how much they can take
Most will be strong
And more souls are out
But more is what's been gone
With I won't fall
A woman can
Can
How
On the half of every night
Look at us forever
You are the god of the way
That our power
So fathers bigger to your daughters
Daughters will have like you too
Because we come to mothers
So mothers bigger to you
So mothers bigger to your daughters too
If I ain't that you, don't find out
So mothers bigger to you
But every lady's nothing
We're going to forget
This is Kevin Crossman from the Frappac podcast, you know the Frappac, Ben Stiller, Vince
von, Will Ferrell, Owen Wilson and Luke Wilson, all those guys in those comedy movies,
while we cover it all on our podcast, news, reviews, and even a little Frappac music.
We've got this track from Piano Service Rex, Luke Wilson, Dan's Party.
So once you join us, hits the freppac.com, THE-fr-at-pack.com.
Did your life just bite? Have you had one of those days for the past several weeks?
Or perhaps you feel like the freight train to misery just loves to ride down your track?
If so, feel free to share your story among the rest of us miserable souls.
Send us your unfortunate event to email.mylifebitesbytes at gmail.com.
Perhaps by sharing our stories, we can find some silver lining to that thunderstorm we call life.
The My Life Bites podcast. The Send My Daily podcast of doom, gloom, misfortune, and things that just plain suck.
Visit us on the web at MyLifeBitesbyytys.com.
You know, if your life bites, you just might want to lay down some blues, perfect for a new music Tuesday on a Thursday.
I hate this business, Jimmy Grisswald, on the Daily Source Code.
Pay in front of Jim.
I'll never say the right things.
I hate this business.
I can't change with the times.
Don't claim the bitter best.
I won't sign on the dotted land.
I hate this business.
I hate these business.
It's just one reason why
I hate this business, I hate this business
It's nice to have three CDs to us
We've played a couple of us tracks on the Pod Cho
Good stuff dig it. I've really been getting into some mellower stuff lately and that really fits the bill for me
And it just did immediately get kind of cloudy and kind of dark and rainy and all by myself and feeling feeling just so lonely
But then again, there's always light at the end of the tunnel and it comes in the form of
Yon Polas
Hey Adam, this is not a hit test. It's 44 already. It's a special edition because you have to recognize
The music by the high tones the high heads and the little bells
Which could be difficult considering your age? Oh, you're career. I hear you go. This is number one
Um
Knock on wood Amy Stewart and this is number two. Oh
I know what that is you can hear by this listen listen to the listen to the hum of the bass
You know I know exactly
That I think is stings bass humming along on walking on the moon by the end of the final one is number three
Hey, I said oh
Considering my age. I think I'm gonna do okay mr. Paul that
That would be my favorite song to sing if I'm falling asleep while driving shout tears for fears
Okay, times up. This is answer number one. Okay. It's Amy. Yes
I got a word oh
Man, I love the 79
It's like thunder
Answer number one. Amy Stewart and knock on words and this
Answer number two
Yes, police walking on the moon also from 1979
Song
mistake
Make songs like that anymore
The police has answered number two and this is the third and final answer shout tears for fears
I'm talking to you
Answer shout tears for fears
Okay, that's it for today. I had just a little bit time left this week to create another one
Then I'll be on a short trip. So the next one will be next week
Oh, by the way. I hope you had them all three
I don't know
Despite my I just have to wait till you play this one on the daily source code. Well, okay
feedback is welcome and hit us at gmail.com and you can find the information about this hit test and of course
Disapport hit test podcast on yon pola dot com this j and p-o-l-e-t and dot com
Okay, thank you for listening. I have a nice week and see you next week. All right. Thank you very much
Yeah, that was interesting though. I like doing that trying to get the high hats, but I was not sure about Amy Stewart
That's Amy Stewart the original Amy Stewart AMI. I think it is Stewart knock on wood and really if you're if you're
I feel no long drive and you know you're kind of like feeling sleepy and but you know
You can't pull over. We don't want to pull over and you've already stuck your hand out the side of the window
Get some air flow in on your face. Then the best thing I find to do is just go shout shout that really that wakes me up
I hope it woke you up too
Seeing as it is new music Tuesday on this Thursday, June 16th
I think it's time to play a song by one of my favorite bands who I haven't played this song in a long time or any of their songs in a long time
Actually, it's just from their first album, which I think came out in 2002, 2003
I met them through podcasting and it turns out that they are now selling their music by the track or by the album on the iTunes music store
And I actually purchased the first album. I had had I had received it from the well
It's I'm talking about the lascivious bitties. I had received all of the traction their first CD
They just let me download them in MP3 format now. I have the really high quality. I guess it's was a aces
And I just played it over and over during the weekend and Patricia was listening to and it's just such good stuff
And I I felt like I really needed to play another track by the bitties from bitty locks
Here's headed south on the daily source code
Rose on the ground bitter taste in my mouth since my love
It ends up
Since my love
We first met at a side she looked at my head
Let I do keep one hand
Oh man, no that's that sucks
Now this thing was working perfectly for the entire show
The entire show mega sag is just cranking out the tunes doing great and then all of a sudden during the song that I want to vibe to the most it starts to crap out on me
Man, I'm wondering if it has something to do with with the AAC final hold on a second
Well, I'll do as I'll do this. I'm sorry about this. This is not what I intended
What I intended to happen. I can literally see that mega sag is frozen up. I'm pretty sure it has something to do with
With that file because when I was importing it, I saw that it got stuck there as well
No, if only I could get oh my god for like it. I tunes to work. Uh
Oh, what am I gonna do here?
Almost sick
With no cares in the world or one day
You're falling down
That you're
It ends up
It's up
That you love
Oh, the end you sound like an angel
Lasivia's bitties headed south and I'm sure that was some kind of digital rights management
And snafu that happened there, so I apologize for that go check him out on the items music store
The Lasivia's bitties at the end of the source code
Man, I'm sweating from that. You know, it's like sitting there and going like oh, what's happening?
Otherwise mega sag's been performing very well. I'm very happy with it
So we found another bug we can work on. Ah, thank goodness and that's it for the new music
Tuesday on this Thursday June 16th of the source code
Of course tomorrow morning I'll be meeting with Don Katz as I told you see you're a lot of ball in London
So to show maybe a little bit late as I probably won't be home until early afternoon
But I will have lots of fun stuff to talk about I hope
At least the stuff that
Doesn't fall under the no damn announcements rule, right?
Feedback Adam at curie.com your audio feedback is so welcome even if you're a CEO
Think publicly with some company
Show notes at dailysourcecode.com
We can find out about all the songs the mashups and the promo's played on today's podcast
If you want to send some men submit at potshow.com's the email address
If you've got a mashup, it's mashup with podshow.com and the pod save tunes pod safe it
podshow.com of course you can leave a comment on the weblog at www.curie.com
Okay
See what time is it? It's almost three o'clock or single-becoming home, which means I got to get dinner ready and oh
Mr. Mom again
I miss her already she'll be gone for a couple hours
All right, everybody. Thank you very much for checking it out. What's a show
Stay subscribed. I will talk to you tomorrow for the thank god it's Friday edition of the daily source code have a good one bye bye
Another podshow podcast stick it in your ear
You