Your daily source code from Monday may 16th 2005.
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear since radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's the start of a new week on the source code.
Adam Curry coming to you from Curry Cottage in lovely gilford.
A nice suburb of London in United Kingdom.
Look out at the window not too nice today.
The weekend was just stellar though.
Unbelievable.
They predicted wind and cloudy skies.
I guess it came one day late.
It doesn't happen often but it's good enough.
So I had the time to just break away from all things podcasting computer.
Anything going on in the office, basically.
Or the bedroom that we call an office.
Or that we sometimes call a studio.
Patricia came back Saturday.
Wind commander William picked her up in Rotterdam.
And flew her over in the Sessner 182.
Which is the plane I've been training on.
Which I will be acquiring once I have my license and I've been deemed safe enough to make the crossing.
Which could last half a year, nine months, ten months, man.
That's tough stuff.
It really has nothing at all to do with helicopter flying.
I'll tell you that it's just something completely different.
But I am getting a little bit more of the hang of it now.
At least I'm making work controlled landings.
And I'm understanding the navigation is so much better.
Because on helicopters, you know what I mean.
Look out the window.
Going slow enough to see where you're going.
If you want to turn left, right go up or down.
It's relatively simple.
You can slow down to a stop and mid-air.
Just not that way with airplanes.
So it's nice.
We flew around to different airfields here in the neighborhood.
I was starting, of course, from my home-based pharaohs.
And then Booget, I'll see you on Saturday after he brought Patricia in.
We went to...
What was it?
West London Aeroclob.
That's New Barcher.
And then Sunday we went to Goodwood, which is also just another flying club.
And it's unbelievable.
The culture of flying in this country is just so fantastic.
I mean, you land there on Saturday or Sunday.
And it's like you walk into a Biggles novel.
You know, if you know the Biggles novels, I'll put a link to something about Biggles in the show notes for today's podcast.
But wow.
And there's guys all decked out and there's businessmen who are clearly on their weekend off just flying around.
And everyone's having a good time.
And there's like 100 people in the bar cafe.
And just, you know, good time, food, coffee, drinks.
Really, really nice culture.
And normally, certainly in the Netherlands, if you come in, certainly if you come in from outside the country and say, hey, you know, it's Saturday or Sunday.
We'd like to do some training here on your airfield.
And of course, you have to pay for the touching goes and your overland approaches and all that.
But most of them will say, well, you know, sorry, this is for our club members.
And we just don't have time for you.
But everyone was really courteous and they let us do as many touches touching goes that we needed.
And it was just great.
It was really a fun feeling.
Great to be away from anything else that was going on.
You know, just, what when you're flying this, you can basically, at least I can only think about one thing.
That's flying because you get distracted for three seconds.
And, you know, that could be the difference of 300 feet or it could be the difference between on track or off track or forgetting something.
It's important that could be a real day record. So it was, it was nice.
I find that extremely relaxing, even though I, you know, it's hard work.
You get really tired after a couple of days of training.
Excuse me.
It was nice said that Patricia enjoyed her flight from Rotterdam to, to the airport here.
Because I was a little worried that she wouldn't like the, the small single-engine aircraft vibe.
This isn't really the smallest Cessna, by the way.
You know, you have the two-seater, the 152, then you have the four-seater, the 172.
And this is the 182 with retractable gear.
I know I've talked about it a million times, but I can't get enough of it.
It's my, my real hobby.
And it's bigger. It's like a cab.
It's like a taxi cab that flies.
But she had a great time. She loved it.
There was a lot of turbulence on Saturday.
I didn't mind that at all.
William took her up to 3,000 feet and brought her straight in for 3,000 feet all the way.
And it was good.
So that is a win in my book, which means that once I am actually approved to fly by myself,
and we can do some more that she'll go with me, and we'll have some fun together,
and we can go exploring some really, really looking forward to that.
If your name is Dave Weiner, you may want to pay attention to this podcast.
Some of it pertains to you.
But not this first song.
This is a mashup.
DJ Tripstrung this one together.
We will rock Beverly Hills.
Q-reaser.
More about it in a second.
Check it out.
But you don't want to make a big life.
Pain in the street.
Gonna be a big mashup.
You got mud on your face.
You big disgrace.
Gifting your trend all over the place.
If you feel we will rock you.
We will rock you.
More about it.
Or its world.
DJ Tripputed together. I'm just looking over to the other computer to the screen there. It was a
Weezer Beverly Hills Queens. We will rock you Joan Jet. I love rock and roll and Leonard Skinner's
Sweet Home Alabama and Link in the show notes is or Link to that is and all the information about
that mashup you can find in the show notes at dailysourceco.com or at curry.com. A lot of questions
always come in. Usually whenever there's a new article that appears about podcasting people
want to know what kind of equipment I use and what do I use for sound seeing tours. By the way,
I've noticed that I guess it's the way I pronounce sound seeing tours that it often comes across
as sound seen tours. So it took me about six or eight weeks before I figured out what are these
people talking about sound seen? What's the sound seen? It's like a sound scape or but it's just
misunderstanding the pronunciation sound seeing tour and it's actually a website which I have
to update or at RSS feed. A podcast feed for different sound seeing tours. It's sound seeing
tours.com. No wonder people haven't been able to find it. But many of the questions that come in
on email after an article about podcasting appears are similar to this one which came in an
audio which I like. So let's answer them right now. This is Tyler Collins from What's Really Going
On podcast. I have a question. Number one, what is the version of your eye river?
Okay. Oh yeah. Sorry that's the this is newfangled megaseg. The way it stops and starts.
It's the IFP 799. I believe in Europe it's actually the 899 and I don't know if that's
any difference in the models but the model number seems to be 899 in Europe 799 in the states.
What I like about the eye river is you know it's a device that you can create something on and you can
listen to something on it and it works on the same device and you can plug it on a microphone
or you can switch the in jack to a line in. So it really has all the capabilities you need built
into one little box and man the battery one double a alkaline battery lasts for fucking ever.
So I think just on battery charge alone it's a great little device. As a built in radio you're
couldn't record from the radio if you want although I'd never have I think I've only listened to the
radio once or twice on this thing but it's a great great little great little gadget let's see
what's next question is your talk what's going on. You use whenever you do a portable podcast
and number two what version of cast blaster or something comparable would you suggest for a Mac
user. I am currently using digital performer 4.5 I am a music producer and I make that work for me but
it doesn't work on a broadcast type level to where I can throw in sweepers and promos and so forth.
I was just wondering about that hope you're doing well. I enjoy your show and keep up the great
work man. All right Todd thank you very much. Well I use cast blaster a lot obviously but that's only
for the windows platform. One of my Mac and I am a Mac guy being my heart and my soul. I right
currently I'm using something called Megaseg and I'll put another link in the show notes to that
which may be a little bit of overkill for what most people are looking for if you're looking for
a podcast we can line stuff up and play list. Basically a playlist where you can stop the playlist
the midstream or stop automatically I guess the automatic part is what I use it for. You can insert
a break and say okay stop here and I'm going to talk here and then when you want to go you just hit
a button and it plays the next element. I started off using actually just quick time players just opening
up each element that I wanted to play in the podcast in a quick time player and then just basically
highlighting the player that was next and then hitting the space bar which will make it play.
That's a real easy way but of course for recording purposes it's a little bit tougher. I have
been using audio hijack pro their new version recently for recording because they now offer a
capability to record the entire sound as produced on your Mac which really makes your Mac one big
mixer and of course each individual application that you open so let's say it's a quick time or
maybe it's a real real player or it could be a media player it could be a whole bunch of different
things or Skype it doesn't matter what it is as long as you can hear it through the headphones
it'll record so that I really like and you can also mix in different applications if you just want
to hijack the microphone for instance so audio hijack pro is getting there but it certainly doesn't
the ease of use that I'd be looking for in an application that has the interface of something like
a cast blaster so nothing really for the Mac yet we're all kind of just string and stuff together
what I find doesn't work for me definitely doesn't work as garage band that doesn't work for me
what else about I think I've tried just about everything so yeah as I said currently I'm on mega
sagging that's that's working okay for me and all this computer talk makes me want to roll out some
pot-safe tunes from Ed Wright well it's bound to ruin my life
computer computer
well it's bound to ruin my life
well it hypnotizes my children and it's bound to steal my life
she spends more time in the chat room
she's meant more time in the chat room
that she ever do with me
I think I'm getting some electronic hell
and I don't really need
she got so many friends
I never seen me vote
I have never seen me vote
out of the morning late in the evening
sitting there that damn people
well I'm going to make me a website
one that looks real slick
I'm going to make me a website
it is website
one that looks real slick
well it's lost all to me
maybe is that well due to the trick
Oh no.
You got me out.
You got pictures.
You got pictures of your mail.
I'm gonna pack up all my files.
You're gonna move around down the night.
I'm gonna be a real fast model.
Take my data all the time.
Come here, come here.
Take it my wife.
Oh, maybe it's taking you away from your wife.
Ed Wright, computer computer.
Podsafe music on the daily source code.
If you don't know what Podsafe music is,
I'll reiterate the whole concept.
We can't play licensed music on podcasts,
whether that's just a legal issue that we have to get over,
or if it's a financial issue or whatever it is,
we just can't legally at this moment.
So what happened is we have lots of,
I mean, lots, tens, hundreds of thousands of people
creating songs on the computers,
on the computer computers,
and making it available for podcasters to play in their podcasters
as long as you point them back to the website.
So of course, the link to Ed Wright's computer computer
will be in the show notes at dailysourcecode.com.
Found on the great podcasters,
you know, in the broadcasting that we talk about formats
and formats are very different from,
well, then again, maybe not,
but in computing and computer engineering,
you always talk about formats.
For instance, let's see,
you have RSS is a format.
It's the way that information is formatted,
so that you can easily understand it.
A format and broadcasting,
the simplest way to explain it would be,
for instance, a top 40 radio station,
looks at a format over each hour,
and then day parts,
and then over 24 hour period,
to really put a sequence of songs
into an hour that will hold the audience the longest,
I guess, is the only reason,
and give you the most listening pleasure,
of course, formats have gotten really tight,
as we say in the business over the years
and have become a little bit boring.
But a typical top 44 mat may be
where the hour starts off with a big number one smash hit,
and then it's followed by what we call recurrent,
so that may be something from maybe 10 years ago,
followed by something that's up and coming,
followed by something that's in the bottom half of the top 40,
followed by a brand new song, so that's a format.
That's how you fill up an hour.
In podcasting, we're seeing formats emerge as well,
the hit test that young Paulette does,
and a young won't be able to do a hit test every single day,
if at all for the next coming weeks,
because he's in rehabilitation for
some medical stuff he's going through,
a young Paulette dot NL,
as we can find out all about that,
and listen to the hit test podcast.
But the format of the show
is of the little snippet that he sends into me,
is a good one,
it's three segments of songs that he thinks I'll know,
and of course he gives me little snippet of the song,
and then replays this snippet of the song,
and then gives me a couple seconds
of thinking time to come up with the answer,
and then at the end he gives me the answers and plays
on a longer pieces of the songs.
That format has now been copied,
which is not a bad thing,
is great, into a podcast called
voices from the vault.
Jerry Orkin does this,
and let's play along with
the show from the sixth of May.
I love it.
Good day everyone,
welcome to the second episode of Voices from the Vault.
I've checked the stats from our website,
and it looks like about 60 people
downloaded the first episode of the podcast,
so I'd like to thank everyone of you for adding me,
to your podcast downloader.
I've also had some very supportive feedback too,
so thank you for that.
I think I'll be incorporating some suggestions
that have been made into future episodes.
I'm going to try and do two voices
from the Vault podcast every week,
so stay tuned for some challenging listening
in the weeks and months to come.
Today I'll be playing other voices
of three famous screen actors,
your job is to guess who they are before I give you the answers.
Up in your ears, and we'll begin
with the first of today's voices from the Vault.
Try to do as your high-the-met...
if the... a message is a great thing.
It's a great thing you must never tell anybody
that there is a message at all.
Ever.
Did you get it?
Try to do as your high-the-met... if the... a message is a great thing.
It's a great thing you must never tell anybody that there is a message at all.
Ever.
I've already heard this show once,
so I'll just do the answers I had when I heard the first time.
The first one...
Okay, this one I heard was...
I didn't know.
This is from the Vault.
Sorry, dear.
If this is the day,
my emotional apparatus is...
I know.
I was plugged up with something.
I'm convention pushing and passion pumping.
It's not coming easy for me.
If this is the day, my emotional apparatus
is plugged up with something.
I'm convention pushing and passion pumping.
It's not coming easy for me.
So the first time I heard this,
I thought it was Marlon Brando,
but I knew it was the other guy who crashed in his Porsche.
I couldn't come with a name.
Pretty hard one.
This one should be a bit easier.
Here it comes.
Voice from the Vault.
Number three.
I still go back to my Prince now living Greenwich.
And I still go back there and take a walk in everything
still seems the same.
Which I think is the great beauty of this country
is that even though we're still culturally...
We've also managed to maintain a lot of our...
the things that make this country very special.
I still go back to my Prince now living Greenwich.
And I still go back there and take a walk in everything
still seems the same.
Which I think is the great beauty of this country
is that even though...
See, I thought this one was pretty easy when I heard it.
I've heard off the bat.
I heard the accent.
I know it was in the cold kidmas.
I didn't know the first two, but I certainly had this last.
Special.
The cold kidman.
Right now it's time for the answers.
The first of today's voices from the Vault.
Screenwriter, director, director, director.
Mel Brooks.
Ah, the thousand year old man.
A thousand year old man.
A message is a great thing.
It's a great thing.
You mustn't ever tell anybody that there is a message.
It'll ever.
The second voice from the Vault.
Taken from the interview on the set of the movie
Rebel without a cause.
James Steeze.
I was close.
This is the day.
My emotional apparatus is...
I was plugged up or something.
I'm convention pushing and passion pumping.
It's not coming easy for me.
And the final voice from the Vault.
That very modern movie star.
Nicole Kittman.
I still go back to my prince now live in Greenwich.
And I still go back there and take a walk in everything still seems the same.
Which I think is the great beauty of this country is that even though we're still culturally
right on top of it, we're also managed to maintain a lot of our things that make this country very special.
Send feedback to feedback at voices from the Vault.com.
Your suggestions are always welcome.
Until next time.
Goodbye from voices from the Vault.
Jerry Orkin with voices from the Vault.
Awesome.
Awesome podcast.
The highly interactive voice really works for me.
From the Vault.
Because the minute you're sitting there looking at your MP3 player and yelling at it, thinking
you have the answer, I call that the epitome of interactivity.
Absolutely fantastic.
Love that format.
The way it's started to morph into something new, fantastic.
Of course, a pointer to that podcast in the show notes as well for today.
So last Friday I was wrapping up the week.
It had been a real long week for me.
Patricia was out of town.
So I was doing double duty as Mr. Mom.
And then, do I miss all the stuff she does?
Taking care of Christina, of course.
And I was in the kitchen cooking.
I had the crap top with me.
That's my laptop.
The tablet.
The craplet.
There you go.
And I used that for Skype.
And I can connect the iTunes on that to the iTunes up stairs in the office.
So I can just listen to whatever's coming in.
So I basically have one place where my podcasts are updated through my iPodder.
And I can just stream that to any other computer I want to.
So I only have to have it in one spot.
Works really well.
And I'm subscribed to Dave Winner's Morning Coffee Notes.
And really religiously read scripting.com.
And you can imagine how really delighted I was when I heard the end of his Friday podcast
and he said the following.
My name is Dave Winner.
It's Friday the 13th.
One more thing to call out to Adam Curry who's got his pod show on serious is Dave viewing right now as we speak.
I wish I could listen to it.
I don't have a serious satellite radio, but I'm going to be listening to the, you know,
where everybody has to say about it.
Good luck to you Adam.
Knock him dead.
Break a leg.
You know, all of us that shit.
And I don't know.
Boy.
Okay, everybody.
See you all later.
Bye.
This is Dave.
So you can imagine I was like really elated.
I was so, I mean, that was such a nice thing for him to do.
Particularly because he's starting on Friday.
I knew that he was going to start the first podcast on KU radio in San Francisco on Monday.
And so I was like, oh man, that's really cool.
I got to make sure I say something back in my podcast.
And it really had been a tough week.
It worked very hard on putting the first four hours of serious together.
And I knew how to work over the weekend.
Do some more work for the coming week.
So it was nice.
It was just one of those things like, wow, man.
That's, that's an olive branch for sure.
And then over the weekend, a wired article came out written by Jenny Jardin from,
was just a lot of things.
Actually, it was a, a written interview from something we did on a,
her NPR piece.
She does a, I guess, a technology report on NPR.
So we had a couple of chats.
Very, very nice, by the way, I had never met her only,
I've been reading, boring, boring.
So it was kind of nice to get a voice to the, to the face.
And of course, I'm trying to get her to start a podcast.
I think she'd be perfect for one.
And the article, it was a very flattering article.
There was about me.
What did she call it?
She called it to communicate with the pod father or something like that.
And Dave just went off on this.
He went off on me in such an incredibly hurtful manner on scripting.com.
He wrote, he wrote about this, this article.
And then, you know, he calls me horrible things.
And I was like, whoa, this, it really, really blew me away.
And I'm not going to, you know, read what he wrote on scripting.com.
You can go and check that out for yourself.
And I'll put a link to it in the show notes.
But by coincidence, I did find a kind of a mashup montage sitting on
his server on this morning coffee note server that I, I don't know who made it.
But it is on his server.
So I'll, I'll share it with you.
It's, it's called the curry collage.
And I guess it'll give you the kind of an idea of what this article says.
It's Adam Curry.
You are a bitch.
Oh, yeah.
I apologize.
I'm a dick.
So dick some respect.
Wacky stuff.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I'm an idiot.
I'm an idiot.
It's dick.
You know, I'm an idiot.
You don't get so much fat.
I'm bad about what you're hearing that wild cherry sign.
I was like, what's that?
I can 70, you say 78.
Something like that.
Really think I give a shit.
Oh, what a hell of dick.
I'm a dick.
Touch anything sniff it all.
Touch it.
You're a bad man and you made me cry.
I hate you.
What?
You know, I'm an idiot.
He owed the key mode.
Have you been drinking?
Oh, yeah.
Snippin TV.
Let's be a dick.
Touch anything.
Oh, good good.
What a dick.
That dick.
What you just said is one of the most insanely idiotic things I have ever heard.
At no point will you even close to anything that could be considered irrational but
Everyone in this room is now dumber for having left into it.
So that kind of sums up what Dave wrote about me and
Wow, I was like how am I going to respond to this?
I think the best way for me to respond is to kind of let you know how I feel.
And then I want to talk about why I think this is happening.
And so the first, I'll play a song now.
The only really way I know how to express my feelings about what's going on
with how this craziness.
Isn't it strange?
The stars don't shine no more now since you'll go.
Isn't it strange that we can't look back and see
And just what went wrong?
I want to know now when we are.
Should I pretend in a little thing?
Yeah, I know when I want you to.
Could you confess your feelings with me?
Isn't it strange that you told me and won't think
Suddenly it changed your mind?
Isn't it strange that you'd come here for me
Turn away and leave me behind.
Now if he's like I'm drowning.
If he's like I'm drowning away without you.
Could I know the feeling?
Because I felt very sorry for.
I hope you don't feel just like me.
I hope you don't like me.
Isn't it strange that the world seems to know it
When I try and explain what's all strange
That you can be as one yet another same
And if he's like I'm drowning.
If he's like I'm drowning away without you.
I know the feeling.
Because I felt very sorry for.
And if he's like I'm drowning.
If he's like I'm drowning.
I hope you don't feel just like me.
I hope you don't like me.
I hope you're so free with just a lot of love
If I got home you'll feel much more together
Maybe not to love it
Not so happy, yeah
Not so happy, we'll go to my way
We'll go to my way
Roger from In Twine sums it up
Happy on the Daily Source Code
So I guess, and it's really, I don't feel happy
That Dave was resorted to name calling, which I think is so totally unfair
Because it's all about credit
Who created podcasting, who created this, who created that
What Dave accuses me of continuously is if not giving him proper credit
And what boggles my mind is that he would for one minute think
That when you have a publication that has editors and all kinds of people in the mix
And it's not a weblog that you would think that the only people
Who get written incorrectly about as you Dave
You know, Jenny Jardin actually was also blown away by what you wrote
And she said that today, Monday, she would be posting
The rest of the interview that was cut out by her editors
Where not only did I credit you but talk about all the work that you had done
But also Chris Lydon's work and many other people who contributed to podcasting as it is today
Including a Denny Gregoire who came up with the name
It's like, you know, I didn't write the interview
And this happens all the time
And this is what happened in January when we were in Miami
This roller coaster ride with Dave is like one day
It's great and then the next second it's all the way down
And it's very, very tiring
And the only thing I can really grom out of all this
And I've seen it happen a couple of times is that you just want to be famous
And you are, you know, and I think you don't have to go asking for credit all the time
By the way, if you go to a bank and ask for credit, you never get it
So you know, don't expect any other large institution to give you credit
Particularly not if you might have burned some bridges
Because, you know, sometimes you come across very crass
And people who hold the microphone or hold the camera
Remember that shit and they may not be holding it forever
But, you know, don't expect them to turn around and be giving you credit
Which is totally within the control of the person who has the credit to give
Which is not me, it's the publications who are publicizing this
I've written all the time about the work that you've done
And I'm not going to go back and call every single interview
Or tell them that they're an idiot or that they're a dickhead
The words you used, you know, on me
Because they wrote their story, it's the story they were interested in writing
So, it's very, very unfortunate
And I really can only chalk it up to the fact that you feel that you just not famous
Be careful what you wish for
I want to be famous, I want to wear minks and sattens and pearls
I want to be famous more than just any old girl
I want to have eyes as blue as the sea
I want all the people to look at me
I want my own show on TV, I want to be that girl
I want to be famous, eat out at sardies, have parties, that's fine
I want to be famous, go to Paris on private flights
I want to have lovers buy the score
Movie producers knocking down my door
This is the faith that is in store for me
Oh and I'm famous, I will wear a great trench coat and fake red hair
So they all will know that it is me
When they see me, how they'll smile
And me photographs to sign
I will say sorry babe
Talk to my assistant
I want to be famous, I want to have eyes as blue as the sea
Who's on the street?
Then when I'm old, I'll have a ball
There'll be shocked that I'm living at home
When I enter the gas will fall
To the knees
And then ask that the throats of my enemies
Man, all I don't want is cheese
When I'm famous, famous, famous
So exhausting
I want to be famous, I want to have eyes as blue as the sea
Who's on the street?
Then ask that the throats of my enemies
Man, I want to be famous, I want to have eyes as blue as the sea
Who's on the street?
Then ask that the throats of my enemies
I want to be famous, I want to have eyes as blue as the sea
Who's on the street?
Then ask that the throats of my enemies
Man, I want to be famous, I want to have eyes as blue as the sea
I want to be my famous better than all of my fellow much better than all of her
I want to be famous slowly and I'll know nothing
I'll hand up bitter and ugly and old, not just my body but also my soul
But a legend is my goal and a legend I'll be
When I'm famous, not I will give for the little people
I'll dance when I'm famous
Hey, my famous, my my
Philosophia's, famous on the source of code of apologies for the dropout
My Mac is not cooperating as it usually does
So I've been famous in one form another since I was 19 years old and believe me
There's not been a single single interview or publication anywhere that has gotten the story completely right
And it's just the way it goes and people take pot shots at you all the time and say the most mean and hurtful things
And often they think, hey, you know, you're a celebrity, you know, deal with it
Or that's what you could pay for when you're in the public, you know
That's why I've been such a supporter of Michael Jackson
Because I, you know, certainly knowing him having met him once or twice, you know, I, you know, this just certain things I don't
I don't buy into and I know how it can spin out a control and Dave is doing a real good job
But you're really making me look bad and it's just not fair because this is the way publications go
And I'd suggest you go out and, you know, do some interviews and put your story out there
And, you know, and get your voice heard or if you don't believe in the mainstream media
They don't read it, you know, that's just the way it goes
You should know much better than that and it's really disappointing to hear the way you think of me
So, I will leave all of us now with the very wise words of Connie Francis
And it's the last I'm going to say about her
It's hard on just how it's happening
Can't you see the damage you have done
You have driven him away forever
Yeah, it's hard, now I'm the only one
I'm the only thing he left on
And I know he loved me at the start
And I know he hates the sight of all my stand-ups
All the cars of you will just find
And I know he loved me at the start