It is source code episode 183. Guess what? We're still in Phoenix.
That's a very short night at the lovely airport building.
We came back for the 710AM flight to San Francisco.
Well, we hung around and waited for that to be delayed until 8.
And then they canceled basically every single flight they have.
So we once again have gone through the baggage resolution center to get our bags.
We actually have some meetings we really wanted to go to in San Francisco today.
So what we've opted for is to charter a plane, take us up the San Jose airport.
That's one of those executive decisions to make once in a while.
Now, my bag has been returned to me and I'm standing back to the old familiar carousel number one,
waiting for wrongs bag. We've been waiting another half hour for that.
And he wants to go.
And I say shoot, you know, as long as we're chartering a plane, you might as well wait the extra 5-4 minutes
to see if we can get his bag. So we made a gentleman's agreement.
When he gets back from the rest room, if the bag is not here, then we're just going to take off.
You'll see his bag eventually delivered hopefully.
So we're going to give you some sound seeing of that, I guess.
It's a 15 miles to Falcon Field, which is where the general aviation is located.
And we're going with the opportunity charter company.
Let me see if I can find, I think, wrongs and paperwork.
Nice guys though. Why the hook is up immediately?
I knew what to ask for, which kind of helps.
And thank you all by the way for your encouraging emails that you sent.
I got a whole bunch saying, oh well, you know, made that decision never to fly with
America West ever again.
And I would certainly advise the same.
And it's really not the people. It's a fucked up system.
And the employees seem to be just as frustrated.
I was in the restaurant myself just a moment ago.
Unfortunately, I wasn't recording. I should have heard the announcement.
Yeah, literally the America West announcers are saying, hey, we know this sucks we're sorry.
That's pretty fucking fun.
So we'll actually have a little bit of time to discuss the news that everyone's been talking about,
which is the presentation and Steve Jobs made yesterday in San Diego,
the conference after we met with him.
But it's all good. It's all good.
The reason Steve wanted to meet with us is he wanted to make sure that they were doing things the right way.
And I am very convinced they'd be able to call on a second kind of phone call here.
That's wrong, hold on a second.
Yo.
No, not yet.
Yeah, I'll call you if it comes off. Okay.
Okay, so that was Ron saying that he's going to give them an address to send the bag to.
All right.
Oh, man, this morning was so rough.
So I got up at five o'clock after, as I said about four and a half hours sleep.
I was so happy. I didn't wash my hair because the load dryer in the hotel was not working.
So I looked like shit to that.
But we're definitely going to make our meeting.
Yes, that's good.
Instead of two hours by commercial air, it'll be three hours and 17 minutes.
We're flying.
I think a set of four, 21, which is a turbo crop.
So it doesn't go as fast, obviously, as a turbo jet.
Although it does have turbine engines, it's just propellers instead of jet.
I would just say in a way.
So maximum cruising speed is probably about 359.
It's about 300 miles an hour.
And just open here for another second.
So we found out, by the way, why my bag came off and his didn't because they don't actually look for it by bag.
It's a tag number.
They look for it by name on the tag.
We're looking for a second bag that had my name on it instead of the name bloom.
So learn something there for future reference.
Make sure that they're looking for your name on the bag.
Because that's what they'll be looking for.
Not just the tag number, which is kind of similar.
Maybe they look at the name and then they provide a number.
Okay.
Not looking, not looking too promising.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to pause this throughout the trip.
Edit it back together before we upload it.
Later on tonight.
And stay tuned.
For more exciting tales from the road with Adam and Ron.
Later.
Okay, still here at the carousel.
Ron just walking back, so let's see what he has to say.
But I guess we're going where that is bag.
We out?
Yeah.
You sure?
Okay.
Okay, okay.
You know what?
All of the stuff we just wanted to get this flying.
We're waiting around for a little piece of luggage.
It's not just a piece of luggage.
It's your piece of luggage.
Okay.
Sorry.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
Off we go.
We need a safe.
You have a message waiting at the Beijing Assistant's location.
Boy.
It sounds familiar.
So what we're going to be are comes from NDR Station.
And from Conqueror, New York Magazine.
We're going to train it's angle.
Good.
That is Falcon Field.
Airport.
Falcon Field.
Oh.
Yes.
Yeah.
I got the address actually.
It's the line for young people.
5133 East Roadrunner.
So you got to go to Falcon Drive and then roadrunner all the way down.
Okay.
That's in Mesa.
Yeah.
It's Airport.
Small Airport.
Okay.
That sounded like a kind of thing.
Yes.
Mesa Arizona?
Mesa is a question.
Yes.
Famous for what?
Thousands.
Here.
Mesa is like a big deal with it.
Do you have a family used to, I'm recording this by the way, Ron.
I'm just saying.
I'm taking a grab.
Do you have a family used to own all the flag stuff?
A beer or the town?
That's the town.
And then, like some schmuck in my bathroom.
So did.
I got a hundred bucks.
That's right.
I have some beans.
And a brew.
All of flags that could have been ours.
You have a diplomacy in everyone.
I have to get there because he has a flymer at work.
How angry are you?
He's appointed in our system.
Yeah.
I think it should be a mandate.
So it's trying so desperately to save the airlines.
It's going to behave like that.
Shut up down.
Yeah.
And let the new airline start.
People can compete based on customers.
Yeah.
I don't know what the deal is.
America or elsewhere.
No leadership from the top.
No serious.
That's what it is.
Who runs the air?
Who runs it?
Yeah.
And these people love who it is.
They don't have a feeling of adjusting the other company now.
The field's like just the system is messed up.
They have a merger or they're afraid for their jobs.
They're taking quick and quick in.
Isn't it right?
They don't want out of every 50, you know?
Yeah.
Trying.
There's no.
What do you call it when you are?
When you help desk levels go up, escalation, process.
There's no escalation to seek you.
Yeah.
Okay.
We'll check in that.
Yeah.
Right.
Going to our meeting.
Nothing else stops from spawning.
Oh no.
Gas won't stop.
Yes.
All right.
Check in for you in a bit.
Okay.
You got that?
Yeah.
Here we are.
Mace the Arizona.
Yeah.
What does it ever really get hot?
That's the question.
It's not like 100 degrees.
Today's 110.
110?
Yeah.
So, around each area.
That's what it is.
90 to part.
That's nice.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Have a good one.
Thank you.
Come in.
You're open.
Come on, man.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Mr. Bloom.
Hi.
I'm just a flexible student.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
How do you know?
Okay.
Do you know what the likes do?
If Dave is here?
Dave would be in the office.
Oh, okay.
Dave?
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
On the rubble.
We're all set.
Good.
Just a quick rest room stop.
Good to go.
Great.
Okay.
You don't want to witness this.
I'll put you on hold.
Watch your head.
Oh, so this is a.
Yeah.
This is a little bit of a mine.
Next size up for mine, right?
It has the same basic kind of prophetic gear.
It kind of flaps in like that.
Very easy.
It's not easy.
Is that?
Yeah.
It's nice.
You got the external cooling unit coming away.
Yeah.
That's nice.
There.
I'm going to go.
Yeah.
You're going to go.
Go.
Don't.
Really.
Yeah.
I'm going to go.
Back there.
You can eat anything though.
Nope.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Yep.
Yeah.
Yeah?
That was pretty good, yep.
I'll give you another standard break-y.
The emergency satsets are this door here.
Yeah.
There's plastic cover over this window.
Hold this and push exit to the back.
See belts are normal buckle.
That's non-smoking flight.
And you have water and there's a newspaper right back there.
Six acts that you need them.
That's just not it.
Okay, okay.
This concludes your standard.
You know what we're talking about?
Barbie.
Well, I know what you're just going to fly around.
We talked about which airport?
Yeah.
San Jose.
And we talked about a car service and we got there again.
Yeah.
Hold that though.
That is guys a pros.
Why not just keep that big trap shed now.
No, that's good.
Yeah, we're going to the STC.
Beautiful.
That STC.
Oh, she's looking here.
You're making my partner so happy.
Yeah.
I'm happy we're going.
To be at that Fakaka airport for another three hours before we ever leave.
Where are we left?
Yeah.
No.
All right.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Now we need to take a picture.
I'll go perfectly with this mini-samsi one tour because you'll never believe the clay bar in.
This beautiful man.
This is what aviation is all about, dude.
I'm going to take a picture of me talking to you.
Can you see if that work?
I think it's not going to look at you, but it's back to the airport.
You can walk in a little bit.
It's 20% there.
I'm heading to get a mile on the other hand.
I don't know.
We've got our mini-samsi.
It's going to be pretty boring from here on in.
So we wrap up the rest of the day after our meeting.
It's going to be an interesting event that takes place during the flight for the next three hours.
Let's sit back and enjoy the ride.
Don't you later.