Daily source code for April 7th, 2005.
A top of the hour, I'm gonna go home, and then it's Adam Curry.
You're DJ, has only just begun.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped in my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hey everybody, welcome to the Daily Source Code.
Today's Thursday the 7th.
Oh my goodness, okay, a brand new form of Daily Source Code.
So today we've done this once before.
We've done it in Miami.
I'm testing out some data software.
Let me just call it the Cas Blaster for now.
This is going to be the easy-to-record podcast software.
Okay, oh my goodness.
It's been a while since I've been messing around with all the faders and all that stuff and all the software.
I've been working with a developer for the past couple of weeks on creating a piece of software that runs on a window.
It's a computer which will enable anyone to basically get a podcast recorded very, very simply.
And of course, there's lots of programs out there that record your microphone and there's lots of programs that can mix.
But to really make it easy, I guess that's all interface stuff, right?
So I figured today would be the day that I tried the second test of this series.
The second test of this, of using the Windows tablet.
I'm actually using the pen now to control the software, although it works perfectly well with the mouse.
But what the hair, right?
The sound, of course, will not be what you're used to hearing from the source code because I'm not running this through my sure SM7.
Not running it through any processing, no compressors, any of that.
This is purely a laptop and a headset.
And the headset is actually let me just see.
It's an all-tech lancing.
And it doesn't have the best of all sound quality because of course it's all about the sound card and the preamp and all that stuff.
But it does the job okay.
And the software is set up in a way that is just absolutely phenomenal.
It's really what I, as a radio guy, want to have because it has, and of course I'm providing a, like a semi screenshot along with the show notes.
You can take a look at this.
It has a row of what I'd call cart decks, which are basically jingles.
You can see it's one, two, three for so it's 10 slots for jingles.
And then it has four slots for songs.
Again, this is all beta software, so it could be crapping out, it could sound, it could basically sound shitty.
It has meters on it, so you can keep the levels kind of in check.
Basically, you want the two view meters to be in the yellow and they can hit the red.
In fact, on this meter, I'm seeing now you can hit the red almost all the way because when you, when you spike the meters to the right, then you're basically at zero db, which would be the maximum, it shouldn't be any more than that.
Also, no reverb or any effects like that, which apparently seems to be very tough to do in windows, at least while you're recording something on the fly.
But, you know, the whole setup is, it's, I gotta say, it's sweet, got three faders here, one for the headphones, which,
Oh man, okay, so I don't know how to integrate Skype yet, so I'm not gonna, oh, I actually should have answered that call, that was pretty stupid.
I bet you'll work too, what maybe it won't.
So that's something I gotta check out, that's for another beta test.
It has a mic fader, which you basically set once, so that you're not modulating in the red, then it has a little talk button, which you turn off, I just did that there.
And then it has an auto button, well, it actually has another fader for a player, which means anything you play from either the cart decks or from the song decks.
If you aren't comfortable with fading stuff up and down, so for instance, let me just give an example with the rock money-off opener there.
So now I'm basically sliding that fader down and then I slide it back up like that.
Right, so I'm doing that manually, it has an automatic feature, so if I hit that, it'll just bring down the level of whatever's playing to basically match your voice or your voice can talk over that.
And when you release it, it should automatically flow back up.
Okay, first bug determined, it doesn't fade back automatically.
Let me try that again, so I've got it up about the same, just grab the fader there.
This particular instance, the pen is not doing a good job, let me just grab the mouse, okay.
So now it's at equal level with a microphone and I hit the auto button and it just fades it down nice and smoothly so you can talk over it.
So that works well, only when I release that, it should go back to the same spot, and it's not doing that, okay, so that's something we got to work on.
Okay, so I can just stop that, that's pretty cool because everything immediately queues up, so it can be restarted, so you don't have to rewind any players or anything.
So I have a couple other jingles that I just and sweepers that I just loaded in here.
This is one that was sent to me the other day.
Hi, this is Rachel from audiocollective.net.
If you're listening to Adam Curry on the daily source code.
The only thing this beta software doesn't do is light my spliff, that's too bad.
It has a pause button, but I'm afraid to use it because I don't think that's implemented yet.
Okay, now to the player, the player windows, let me see, I just put a couple of things in here, just to give you some examples.
Let me kick this one in for you.
I think this is actually a mashup I might have played before, but we'll just roll this one out for you right now.
We roll rock and roll you on the on the on the on the on the on the daily source code.
We roll rock and roll you on the on the on the daily source code.
We roll rock and roll you on the on the daily source code.
We roll rock and roll you on the daily source code.
If you want to hear.
If I want to hear audience hear you hear me out.
And we'll be moving on and singing at some old song
And we'll be singing
We'll be singing
You need to keep stop
We will be singing
We'll be singing
We're singing
Okay
Hey, that's interesting
All right, learn something new here
By the way, you're just along for the ride beta testing with me, I guess
So under each of the song players
It has a little progress bar that shows you how far it's playing
Now I don't know if that MP3
Just had more like
Silence at the end of it
But let's see
Because I basically it didn't look like it was all the way at the end
So let me drag the
The progress bar to kind of
Where it's stopped there
Oh my second now, I'm just going on my pen
It's not wanting to react very well
So if I play it from here
Okay
Well that's another thing that has to be fixed
So you can't actually pause it
You can't actually queue it up to a spot where you want it to be
Okay, we've got to improve that
So I hope you're understanding
All the crap that I'm talking about here
Because basically the whole point of this is to
Is to have an application that
95% of the world can use
Which means it has to run on windows
And that is all encompassing
You put your jingles
Or your little bit you want to play
Stuff that you need to see the progress bar on to see how far it is
Of course why that didn't work out in that case
I'm not quite sure
You should be able to queue it up
When started from that spot that didn't work
So that's something we got to change
So actually I hope someone's writing this down
So we can make these improvements
What's really nice is there's
In the in the recorder portion of the of the interface
The record button shows you exactly how long
Been recording so that's 11 minutes right now
Okay, so that's kind of screw up the idea I had
Because I have a piece of the
Lissivia's Bitties the latest bitty cast that was from
Or was that yesterday's bitty cast the six
And they played a song
Just at the end of the show, which was written by
Bitty Amanda Monaco I believe
So now I'm going to have to fast forward to it
So let me see
So I can definitely drag
There's the girls
So let me drag the player over
That works fine actually
Okay, let me
Back to her house and she was so cute
So I'll go in the back to see
Okay, we're just a little bit more
I will be better soon
For girls
Okay, okay, here it is, let me just
Okay, so that's something we got to fix
Okay
Got to be able to cue stuff up in the middle of a song
I'm gonna play a song in Amanda wrote when she first met Andre
Okay, listen to this song. It's a beautiful song
Thank you
It's a sweetest thing ever
I've been wine, I've been dying
For so many a time
Left to wait for a date
And wait
Could be tall handsome stable
Or cultured yet torture
And yet they are one
And the same
Tall or shard
Oh, I don't care if he's got money
Lately they're one and the same
This one, that one
All a disappointment they should hang
Their heads down in shame
I'll hear him say
There is no one like you
The crises and old flames arrive
And make me blue but someday soon
I'll find myself a brighter flame
That won't be just one and the same
I'll hear him say
There is no one like you
No crisis, no all games
I know my lonely days all through
I'll have found myself a brighter flame
That isn't just one and the same
He won't be just one and the same
Oh man, the biddies, they sing so beautiful
Don't you agree
Just give me goosebumps
Okay, so that won't work perfectly
It ended the player progress bar
Showed the very ending
So I guess the wheel rocky thing was just a bogus MP3
It's amazing
Because I've been working with this developer as I said for a couple of weeks
And you think you've got everything right
And then you go and test it and it's all the stuff pops up
Oh man, no I need that
I guess it only really works when you're podcasting
I'm really trying to figure this stuff out
So let me just fire off another jingle there
Thanks to Tom Schooting
He's the guy that puts on my old radio shows online
The Korean vendingles shows that I used to do it radio Veronica
He does that from Australia
I sent him that whole box of cassettes when we moved
And he's just been putting stuff up online
Relentlessly, it's been great
He sent me all these jingles that I guess he found in some
On some cassettes somewhere
We talked a while ago about Big Bad Al
I think I was weeks ago
Kind of like the daddy over the radio
The guy who mentored me and a lot of other guys
That's what I actually played at the very beginning of the show
Let's listen to him again there
A top of the hour I'm gonna go home
And then it's Adam Curry
I use that one so often
Of course now it sounds kind of shitty because it's coming off of a cassette
16 minutes 23 seconds into this
This is so far going pretty well
What's nice about the program as I said it's supposed to be all encompassing
When you stop recording, it'll obviously stop recording
Then you hit save and then it pops up a window that asks you for some basic information
What does that information?
Well, of course, it's the ID3 tags, right?
And then you save it and it's done
It's already recorded MP3
It's compressed with a standard setting
We're using the same setting I always use on the daily source code
Which after months of fooling around with bit rates and sample rates
We kind of figured this is the one that works the best
So we simplified all that
These of course I guess could eventually all be advanced options
If you really want to set that
But after that
There will of course be an upload piece
And I've been thinking about all these tools that are coming online
And I mean it's like there are so many different recorder packages out there
There's a big benefit to having an interface like the one that I'm using right now
Because it's really set for podcast
And at least for a particular type of podcast
There's more I'd love to have Skype integrated into this
So if you want to just call someone on Skype it just records that
Or maybe you could even set a level on that
Something we got to think about as well
But then the upload to the server where you're hosting it
I think that should just be using the meta weblog API
Which I believe does in closures
Not 100% sure but I think it does
Because then basically it'll create a blog post
And you could use that with any weblogging software
You could use it with any podcast hosting service
And even though I definitely want to
Rule the world global world domination
Anything we can do with podcasting
It seems like that's the smartest way to go
Because there's going to be lots of different programs
To record and to upload
And it just takes away all the hassle of trying to figure out
How do I get it up there?
How do I FTP then create the RSS feed?
I think it's some programs that I've seen out there
Create an RSS feed for you
And then it'll upload that as well
But I think that it seems if we just follow the path
The blogging software has gone
There's lots of different applications
That are basically just using the meta weblog API
To talk to in this case I use a
Manila server for my weblog
And I've used radio user land
Through the meta weblog API
And currently I use Mars Edit
Which is made by
I think Brent does that
Or does net news wire of course I do that on the Mac
And then it makes a lot of sense
Because then instead of trying to compete on all these weird levels
You just compete on the interface
Whatever interface works best for you
And you could switch back and forth between
Different programs
Perhaps depending on what type of podcast you're doing
So it's kind of a bummer that as I said
I can't queue up some of these songs
Believe me by the next beta
I'm sure I will be able to
I found this show which is
It might be an existing radio program
But probably only on AM
But it's a financial podcast
The following is a presentation of the Tiger Financial News Network
I guess
I guess it is from a network
The Tom O'Brien show
He'll just scan forward
What you hear?
He'll show
Pieces of eight
What you talk about is principles
And whether you agree
That's using the auto ducking feature there
Automatically lowering that anyway
Okay, so that's the Tom O'Brien show
Podcasts I'm now subscribed to
It does sound like it's coming from a
From a regular radio program
Okay
Well, I guess we've pretty much done everything we can
For this particular test
There's one very important thing
I still have to wait
Hold on a second before I get to that
Let me just unplug the power cord
Let me go mobile here for a sec
We walk over to the Mac
Where I have my other show notes
Usually
Let me just check and make sure I'm not missing anything
Using the headset is kind of cool though
I hope it sounds reasonably okay
No, the only thing I had in there
Was the Bitties thing
Okay, so we've pretty much
Everything I want to do for this beta test
A little bit shorter source code
The normal but
I hit all the things I wanted to hit
Except for
The fact that I would like to wish
My beautiful wife
My bride of almost 18 years
The happiest birthday
You could ever imagine
Because it's her birthday today
Happy birthday baby
I love you
Alrighty
So
Thank you very much for
Bearing with me on this test
As I said, I'll be providing
At least a partial screenshot
Of the software in the show notes
So you can see
Kind of get a visual representation
Of what I was talking about
We walked through the interface
And you'll be able to comment on that
Email at amercurry.com
Or of course on the weblog www.curry.com
The latest show
The podcast feed and the archives
All on dailysourcecode.com
Tomorrow I'll be back
And we'll see if we can improve on this
Or maybe even get some effects going
I don't know
It's kind of a work and progress
And I'm really enjoying it
A better way to bait a test podcast
Offer with on a podcast
Take care everybody
I'll see you tomorrow
Bye bye