Get us here, Charlie, two five three.
Please save me from people who've been told what to like and then like it.
In my opinion, if you're over six years of age and you're still getting your music from the radio,
something is desperately wrong with you.
I can only hope that somehow MP3 players and file sharing will destroy FM radio the way they're destroying record companies.
Then, even though the air will probably never be safe to breathe again,
maybe it will be safer to listen to.
There are no secrets.
Only information you don't even have.
Adam Curry.
With sixty million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then, the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky and crispy.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
It is October 4th in the year of our Lord, 2005.
Hello, everybody. It is Tuesday.
It's the 4th that is 11.15 a.m. here at Curry Cottage.
The affluent Surries Subber.
It's a beautiful day.
A little bit chilly, but it's that perfect sunshine kind of nippy English weather.
You know what I mean?
It's a bit nippy outside.
Hey, I'm caught up. I'm caught up with my sleep.
I woke up this morning, quarter or seven, ready to go.
After having caught up with my East Enders episodes last night.
Oh yeah.
No matter what happens in this country, no matter what technological innovation or governmental change will take place,
we will always have East Enders.
I've got to show that it's damn full today.
I actually overloaded the playlist.
It's so many promos that since I put out the call,
and that's those lazy ass podcast.
Just to set me some promos, they're not so lazy.
Ask anymore.
But it's fantastic.
I can really feel everything just growing,
growing around us.
Podcasting.
Going place is big.
Oh man.
So, pod safe music.
I'll be talking about the pod safe music network.
Of course, some feedback on the biodiesel
the shit just does not stop people peep talking about it.
Hit to ask from young palette to number six to three already.
And, uh, so we gotta have some other cool stuff.
We'll, uh, get through it.
Just hang with me.
You'll be fine.
I'll take you on your way to work.
On your way home.
And if you're listening to us on channel 103 on serious satellite radio in the morning,
6 a.m. Good morning.
What are you doing up?
Hey, um, art for mashup town sent me a brand new mashup.
Actually, this was supposed to run yesterday.
It's Kaiser Zook.
I think that's the way you pronounce it.
K-H-Y-Z-E-R.
Zook, C-U-K-A.
First brought to you by mashuptown.com.
It will get you moving though.
I guarantee you that.
Pretend we're bringing the mashup on the daily source code.
Don't get violent.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, no, so now었able you yer I go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go,
But it's not fair, it's fair
But it's not fair, it's not fair
It's fair, it's fair
Only, only when you're home
You ain't got a ride, only when you're home
You ain't Got a ride, only when you're home
It's the one time supposed to be your born baby
You got freedom by but come acting crazy
Feminists want out a good time baby
Why you try to pull like I'm the acting chain
One time supposed to be your born baby
Get freedom by but come acting crazy
Try to pull like I'm giving a good love in it
Are you trying to pull like I'm the acting chain
Hey you love me, say you love me
But you never step over me, yeah
Yeah
Woo woo woo
can be promise only.
There we need some time long
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, க 알ade
You hear that little skip again?
Damn, and I'm telling you, man.
I heard actually a pretty good rumor
that Apple, the supply lines for Apple are very, very low
that never been this low, which often signals
a new product line coming out.
So the rumor that I read was that in two weeks,
it's gonna be a new line of Max,
possibly like a professional line of Macintosh's.
Oh, man, what I love to buy a new power book.
You know, I just can't do it, you know,
I can't, I can't, you know,
there's either two ways to go.
I reinstall all the OS and clean up the hard,
and it probably the hard drive is probably
it'll crunchy at this point.
And I probably could have,
can I actually tell how much memory is in this machine?
You know what, that's a bad idea.
It's a bad idea, open the system profile
while you're trying to record something, won't do it.
But that's the rumor, so hopefully that's true,
because then I will definitely go for a new machine.
Getting back, getting into the swing of things here,
a small pile of bills, that's not too bad.
You know, that's kind of one of the things
I dread about coming back is, you know,
you're gone for a couple of weeks and you come back.
It's build time again, invariably.
It's always build time, but some other cool things
I got re-invited to the invite actually
came a couple of months ago, Rob over at Eagle 94
in Gilford, it's a great station.
Because, you know, we've discussed this radio really works well
when it's local and they're talking about the local community.
And Eagle 94, the PG and something show at the morning,
our very local, I like that.
And that is actually Christina,
we'll sometimes switch to that in the car.
Of course, I'm listening to Radio 4, which is the elite talk station.
So she's not very interested in listening to that.
So Friday, I'm gonna go over and visit with the guys at the Eagle.
I'll be kind of fun.
Lots of email coming in,
regarding the podcast Patricia and I did on Sunday
where she is a musician as a peer, commented on,
most of the songs that I played from the Podsafe
and Music Network in the past week or two.
And it's great because even the songs that she had
suggestions about, I think that just about every single artist
has email and it said, wow, you know,
she really has a great ear.
That was actually a demo that I made and I agree.
I really want to have a better production.
And she's gotten some offers to produce some records.
I love it, love it, love it, love it, love it.
And there's something else really cool happening
with the Podsafe music network.
Now, Podsho is nothing to do with this next to promo
or with the show, as far as I know.
But I thoroughly supported it.
And I think that we should do some more with this
because this came, I heard this and I was like, oh my God, you know,
we've already reached, we've already reached this point.
What point?
This point.
Hey, this is Brother Love from New York City.
And just like you, I'm listening to the PMC Top 10 countdown.
The place to hear Top Podsafe tunes being spun by
Podcasters across the world.
Thank you, Podsafe Music Network, love you.
It's time.
Time for another PMC Top 10 countdown.
With your host, the Seedalk, Chris Daily.
Counted down the Top 10 Podsafe tunes being spun by Podcasters.
And now your host, the Seedalk, Chris Daily.
Hey, this is Chris Daily.
Do you love good music?
Are you tired of the garbage that's being spun
on terrestrial radio?
We'll check out the PMC Top 10 countdown.
Join me as we count down the Top Podsafe tunes each week,
but don't just take my word for it.
Here's what some of my friends have to say.
This is a dream of Thorpe.
Keep listening to the PMC Top 10.
Hey, everybody.
This is Rob Kosslo and your listening to the PMC Top 10 countdown.
Hello, everybody.
This is Joe from The Bomb Huppies.
You are listening to PMC Top 10.
Podsafe Music Rocks.
Podsho, content that will make you squeeze the dog
and burp your mother.
Hi, this is Craig from The Bits of Silicon Hell podcast.
This is Dude Matt coming at your respect.
I'm not scared to tell all the people
that come and download our show from iTunes, the website,
bits of Silicon Hell.com, and everything.
What can we expect to hear when we download it?
You never really know.
You might hear anything.
For Tevo to Unix to pretty much anything.
Pretty much anything to do with technology.
And it can go over the directions as well.
And it really just a bunch of friends who work or have worked
in the technology and support field.
And we like to sit around and talk about the stuff we're working on,
what's cool, what's coming up.
And sometimes we have stories from the past, things that we've had to do.
So check us out, go to www.bits of Silicon Hell.com.
Or do a search for bits of Silicon Hell
in iTunes, New York store, under podcasts.
Just subscribe, and we'll be here until you do.
Adam Curry.
Hi, I'm PW Frantan, creator of the Ponsho Knitworks Digital Flatsom.
And before I listen to the Dawn and Drew Show,
I had never heard of a corn hole.
Listen to Dawn and Drew every day,
either on their podcast at dawnandrew.com
or their show every evening on Syria satellite 103.
Like me, you might learn something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
PW, you kissed your wife, Ross, with that mouth, man.
Yeah.
That's right.
If you're listening to us on Syria,
it's everything that we now podcast on the
podshow podcast network is a simulcast.
Well, not everything, but a lot of it.
We're getting started.
I got to get a whole damn channel from those guys.
We know, so we got to prove ourselves first.
We'll do it.
So the first start is there.
We normally are on 6 p.m. Eastern time, 3 p.m. Pacific.
That's when we start with our four hour block of time.
Got madged and her friends, Dawn and Drew and their friends.
Steve Gilmore and his friends.
C.C. Chapman and his friends, P. Dubb and his friends.
So it's pretty horizontally programmed.
But what they do now is they repeat it in the morning,
starting at 6 in the morning.
So that's the first start, right?
Why don't they just give me four more hours?
No problem.
We can fill it.
It really works.
What was I going to say?
Oh, yeah, so that promo by P. Dubb.
He actually sent in a request, you know,
who's been getting requests for cutting liners and promos
and sweepers and jingles and stuff like that,
is Christina ever since we used Ron the podfinder podcast
as the kind of like the imaging voice.
People are really, really into her, into her stuff.
And it was great because, you know,
I told you, she did that audition yesterday.
She was a disning auditioning for the part
of Lizzie Borden in a play about Lizzie Borden at school.
And there were two other candidates.
And she had to be there early at 8 o'clock to do the audition.
And she didn't get the part.
She got the part of like narrator, which, of course,
makes sense because she does have a great speaking voice.
So she was pretty bummed out.
But then when I was able to say last night,
hey, you know what, there's like two or three requests
for people want you to do some stuff.
And they'll actually pay you for it.
And she really was riding high.
And it's so typical, it's so typical that you can have success
doing something that in school, they'll say,
you're no good at, because doing this stuff really is,
it's also acting, it's performing, it's performing.
She likes doing that, so I'm very, very proud of her.
Oh, man, let's move on.
I've moved some stuff around, because I felt maybe today,
we'd break the show kind of in half and bring you young polette's stuff.
Oh, I'm proud of you, casting with Adam Curry.
I suppose you think you know me.
I do know my music.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, just, okay.
Young polette with young polette.
Hey, Adam, this is Huttest number 63.
Rocking, man.
And again, I have selected three songs from the 80s.
Okay.
And hopefully your recording problems are gone and over.
So nothing will be skipped from this hit test.
Young really fucking hates it when the stuff skips during the hit test.
So let's all be real careful and hope that nothing skips.
So three intros and three answers, and this is number one.
Oh, wait, you're solving my test.
Well, that would be a J-Giles band that's centerfold.
Come on.
Number two.
Oh, she's too...
Ready for the world, Oshila?
Do, do, do, do.
Is it Oshila?
You're allowed for me?
No, no, no.
Oh, thanks.
You.
Baby, I owe you.
I don't know who sings it.
Is it yours, maybe?
Something like that.
I think I got a ball.
And this is Huttest number one and hit test number 63.
Did J-Giles band has number one?
This is centerfold.
The song from 1982 to J-Giles band.
And this is Huttest number two.
Full force, full force.
I want you just for me.
Shit, okay.
Dallas, Shila.
Whatever the beyond just name was.
Full force get ready one time.
And when you're all alone, I'll send you the moment you're about the world.
Can't you see?
I want you just for me.
Damn, one hit wonders, but pretty good.
Can't you see?
I want you just for me.
Full force, sorry.
From 1986, full force.
And this is Huttest number three.
Freeze, and I owe you.
Yeah, yeah, it's freeze.
I guess I kind of sucked it there.
I'm from 1983.
Freeze and I owe you as answer number three in today's hit test.
Well, that's it.
I hope you did well, Adam.
I hope you enjoyed this one again.
Of course.
I really love the music from the 80s.
So hopefully, there's enough to feel a lot of hit tests to come.
Okay, as always, feedback is welcome at hittest.gmail.com.
And you can check out the site on yonpolet.com.
J-A-N-B-O-L-E-T.com for the blog.
For info about the hittest and the hittest podcast,
and also the iTunes link to all the tricks in the hittest.
So if you're going to buy some, please do it using my link.
Well, thank you for listening.
See you next time for 64.
So until then, bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
Yonpolet.
All right, I didn't do that good actually.
I recognize them all at least.
And please do yon's links if you want to purchase something.
One of the tracks that you heard from the iTunes music store.
The show notes for the daily source code, which you can find through daily source code.com,
or from www.curry.com.
Working great these wiki notes.
And I saw, and also received an email when I was actually
read it on the plane, on my way back, that the guy who said this wiki
up, and there were a couple of wiki's that were set up at the same time.
This guy Michael, it's a really horrible story.
He lost his job.
And I guess around the same time, I don't know if it was before,
he started doing the wiki show notes or during or whatever.
And so we actually put up a tip jar.
So I guess I'm going to hire him.
I'm going to have him do these show notes.
Because I'm not quite sure how it works.
I guess I have to look at the history of the wiki, but something's working.
Because he basically, I guess he starts out and he puts the run down in.
And then people just start adding stuff.
And I really, really appreciate it.
It's really made these show notes a lot richer than they were.
And although I do miss having them along in the RSS feed, it's, man, it really does.
This works.
It really does work.
Here's a thought.
Well, I got to think.
I got to think about when it comes to these wiki show notes.
I really see the benefit.
I see some of the drawbacks, but we're getting close to something good.
So Michael, I'm going to send you an email.
I'm going to take care of you.
And everyone thanks who put up wiki's and got stuff going.
And even though we had one wiki that was up, it looked really good.
And then it fell down and it fell down for a long time.
Then people kind of migrated over to the alternative link.
And Michael's just doing a great job.
And everyone who's adding stuff into the wiki show notes is doing a great job.
Really, really appreciated.
I guess we're now into the vehicular part of the part of the show.
Hannah, I'm just a Mark Pika from the Travel Commons podcast.
I was catching up on some of your daily source codes last week.
Last week, I'm Friday.
And her dimension, your observation that the American card design is getting better.
And Friday I was in Detroit, actually in Warren, Michigan, driving down Van Dyke road,
right by the GM Tech Center where a lot of that design happens.
And then anything about driving around in those areas of Detroit is that you see all the brain
new cars, either the one either they've just been released or they haven't even been released
there's sort of pre-production cars.
So I must have seen at least three or four the new Pontiac solstices, guys running around
in that two-seater, two-seat roaster with the top down because it was a nice day for adding Detroit.
And that's a sharp-looking car, saw a bunch of the new Chevy HHRs, which is sort of,
it looks a little bit like a PT cruiser, but it's really the design cues or a take-off of the
1940s suburban, but a lot smaller.
And that's a neat, you know, neat looking car.
And saw a sub-brain new mercury kind of their mid-size one hadn't seen one of those out around.
And then you always see a couple of the cars that are actually truly pre-production still haven't
been announced, so they've got the big black bras on the front and the back, so they're driving
them around, but you can't tell what they look like because the front and the back are hidden.
So that's always been a neat thing about living in the Detroit area.
And if you think about it, you don't get that out on the west coast out in Torrance,
California, where the big three Japanese are located because they really don't have design
capabilities out in California, all the Japanese cars are creating cars or designed over
and Asia, but in Detroit you get to see where they've got the engineering and design,
you get to see the brand new stuff before comes out.
And that's, I don't know, it's a neat thing.
And I would agree with you that that American cars have come a long way,
and there's some really neat styling, you look at the Chrysler 300C, I don't think anything
touches it. And I think this next way of stuff coming out of coming out of GM, especially the
Solstice in the Saturn Sky, which, you know, it's interesting. I was watching top gear the other day,
which is the big British once a week, BBC Auto Show, which is very well produced and hosted
and the whole format of the show is just really, really interesting, even Patricia will watch that show.
And they slammed the 300C, I think it was a best of actually, but they completely slammed it.
And I was actually pretty interested in it. Does it come in diesel version?
I, which is going to be Saturn's, his buddy of mine tells me much,
edgeier cut at the solstice, some neat stuff. So, I just some thoughts on that take care,
and talk to you soon by now.
Well, okay, well, that's funny. There was still said there was like two minutes left on that.
Okay. Good. Go on. No problem. Let me just forward that.
Yeah, that's cool, man. Thank you very much for the report. We need pictures to go with that, actually.
That would be cool. If you see something like that, take some pictures. Those pictures actually.
I think they sell. Don't automaggings buy those. All the time. There comes iTunes again.
You can quit iTunes in million times and it keeps coming back, like,
fucking bad Mexican lunch, man.
And I've turned off all of my widgets and my dashboard and it's still coming back.
Some more thoughts on biodiesel now from one of our listeners.
Hey Adam, this is Mike in Kansas City.
Been listening to the daily source code of late and I've had a couple of points on biodiesel.
This is something I've been looking into for a while myself and I've read a few reports,
and I could probably do the research and look at all of them.
Although I'm sure many people have already emailed you about it before,
but something that doesn't make sense about biodiesel at this point in time
is that it's a negative energy source. In other words, it takes more energy to produce it
and grow it than you actually get from burning it.
So unless there are some scientific breakthroughs in the near future with the production and use of biodiesel,
it actually does not make any sense at all as far as a replacement for petrodiesel.
And secondly, on the topic of taxing biodiesel, the reason for this is that at least here in the United
States, fuel taxes go to the construction and maintenance of roads.
So this is why folks who make their own fuel need to pay this tax because they use the public roads
and this is funded out of the fuel tax, which makes sense because most people in order to use the
roads have to buy fuel. This is why also farmers are able to buy diesel, at least in this
party of the United States. They're able to buy diesel with almost next to no fuel tax at all,
and it's also why if they're caught using farm diesel on public roads, it gets some pretty stiff
fines because this fuel is meant to be used out in the fields where they're not putting anywhere
and tear on the roads. That's all I've got to add for now. Thanks for the music and the entertainment
and the thought provoking topics raised on the Delta CR Charlie. Keep it the great work.
Yeah, dude, thank you very much. Yeah, I agree with that. I think, of course, you got to pay
tax for keeping the roads running. That's no problem. So I just don't know what the mechanism is for
that. And regarding more energy, more energy to create biodiesel fuel than it, than it
results in, I don't know, man. You're the first one actually that has said that. So I'm sure that
you're that you've done the research, but I just don't see it. Can't you just use corn oil to make
more corn oil? I mean, I know, why do you need heat? Do you need heat to make corn oil? Do you
need heat to make hemp oil? I'd love to know more about that for sure. I don't know why don't
rush a hit. I heard you talking about running your car on vegetables. Just as you know,
the small vegetables that I want to be able to use up before the go up. There's a bin back sitting
outside my house. I just want to come and take them up to make some moonshine petrol with
worth advice. I'm on a special date at the moment, and I personally have been running on
vegetables for the last four weeks. A little on vegetables, but tend to, because rather
a bad smell, I've been shouldn't have paid off the walls for the last couple of weeks. It's been
pretty bad. So if you plan on running the car, then I've been prepared for a little bit of the
exhaust to smell a little bit. You don't want to be known as that low to try to surround
guilt, but in a line show that smells about five. And you certainly don't want to say it to
be associated with those old fasts and tools, especially at your time in life. Anyway,
let me know if you want to take care of that bag of cabbages up to that south side. And
keep that for good work with America and podcasting. Yeah. Thank you very much, Rodger. I'll be
sure to pick up that cabbages and stick it in my tank. Meanwhile, you might want to stick this
one in your ear. It's amazing what you'll find if you just drop in with a pot-safe music network.
Went in and checked out the recent plays, recent spins, and I eventually got through to,
found that CC Chapman had played this on a show just last night, even though I hadn't
heard the show, it was very apparent through the network. And it freaked me out when I saw the
name. It's PW Fenton and the second ward. That's right, I've very own PW. On guitar and lead vocals
with silence, treatment. Whatever I've done this time, I know it must have been back here.
Whatever I've done this time, I know it must have been back.
When you can see that silent treatment, I know you're really mad.
I've given that silent treatment, and I don't know what I've done wrong.
I'm giving that silent treatment, and I don't know what I've done wrong.
When you can see that cold show, maybe. I cannot check for what I've been here long.
I'm giving that silent treatment, and I don't know what I've done wrong, and I don't know what I've done wrong.
What I've done wrong, and I don't know what I've done wrong, and I don't know what I've done wrong.
Stop giving me that silent treatment, and it's what I've done wrong, and I don't know what I've done wrong.
So frustrating, I'm gonna cry.
Poo, Pidoob.
And the second award.
With that silent treatment, Pidoob, man, all right,
I dig that.
And that's from his now defunct band, I guess.
That was from 1997.
And only now listed on the podcast music,
now we're gonna tell you this guy's slow.
Awesome, man.
Okay, Pidoob, get your band back together
and do a, do like a song for the show.
Do a song for the, oops.
Oh, my, CD drive, just open.
Do a song for the daily source code.
That would, that would love that.
I would be eternally grateful for that.
Very, very cool.
He's uploaded like four songs,
so the four, five songs to the podcast music network.
Check it out, music.podshow.com.
So home now for two weeks time,
going back around the 16th or 17th.
I think that what we're gonna do is,
I'm gonna go back the 16th,
stay for like an eight or nine days,
then fly back.
Then we're gonna go for a quick vacation
because Christina has half-term.
So she has like a full school week.
So what is that?
Nine days of vacation.
So I think the what we'll do is we'll go visit some friends
and Portugal for a couple of days.
And then we'll come back and then I'll go back.
That's San Francisco.
Because this is really a crucial time.
We are, you know, we've really been doing a lot of work
on two areas.
One is for listeners.
How do we make sure that we get our 100 million listener
March completed?
We're already moving.
I think we're probably, in listenership,
based upon studies and intuition and our own numbers.
I think we're probably around about 10 million people
listening to podcasts now globally.
That's probably about right.
We've at least listened to a podcast
and are subscribed to a podcast.
Or worse, who have clicked on a link
and listened to a podcast,
but you know, don't have the whole automatic part down yet
that there's not using it.
So we're, that's gonna be pretty cool.
When we launch that, that'll basically be podshow.com.
So what you see now, of course,
is intentionally left lame to throw you off the track.
But what we'll come out with first
and this is really pertinent right now.
Yahoo, I guess, is a starting to point to podcasts,
which is great.
Oh, man, do I love that?
More distribution, more exposure, more listeners, fantastic.
The downside and this is now just kind of rippling
through podcaster land.
The downside is that if you get a link,
we don't really know what it means yet.
If you get a link from Yahoo, what happens?
How much bandwidth is that gonna cost you?
Does it mean that a million people show up at your door?
We just don't know yet.
We're following this closely, of course.
Now, this is something,
although it won't have the same impact as iTunes.
It's definitely gonna have some impact.
So we are now, what is the word?
Accelerating our development of the podshow PDF,
which is the podcast delivery network.
And the idea here is that anyone can host their show
for free on the PDF.
And we've discussed this before.
So you get unlimited bandwidth.
And when I say unlimited,
I mean really unlimited, unlimited bandwidth.
So, you know, and we hope you become enormously successful
because, of course, you'll have different ways
to work with the system.
You can pay for features.
You can exchange those for an ad that will be attached
to your podcast.
You could not have that and just pay for it if you want to.
But you get it for free.
And look, if you get a whole bunch of listeners
and you're interested, we'll help you monetize it.
So, this is not really announcement,
but it's coming very, very soon.
So, those of you who are worried about bandwidth
that we are coming with some solutions,
that I think will really, really blow you away
if you've been thinking about podcasting,
or if you're, I'd say pretty much if you're doing one already.
That's the one thing that we've got great interfaces.
We've got all kinds of tools to use,
but we really just, you know, it costs money.
That's at the end of the day,
if you wanna go and buy bandwidth and sure,
you can get a really good deal on 15 gigs a month,
or maybe 30 gigs a month of transfer,
but if you need to go buy it, you're gonna pay anywhere
from, I'd say, 70 cents to a buck 25 per gigabyte transferred.
And that's real dough.
So, you gotta be able, if you have that,
that's fine.
If you don't, then there's, you gotta figure something out.
So, we're gonna come up with that very, very soon.
What else do we talk about recently?
About the Arbitron ratings,
the radio measurements got some feedback about that
from Brian Kiran's, Kiran's, Kiran's.
Hi, I'm Brian Kiran's from Kiran's.
I was undirect podcast, I was singing to you.
Daily source code for Monday,
and I was just wanna give you some feedback
on the radio rating systems.
I did a similar ratings review,
or Nielsen's type thing for the Canadian radio system,
and the television system at different points.
And it was basically the same, you get a little flip book,
and you write down the times that you listen
to a particular station, so say I started at 815
on Monday morning, I'd write down this station,
and then I'd remark a little arrow down
to then when I finished listening to it.
So 815-845, it would be the time I'd listen to it,
and then I'd do that for each day,
or every time I listened to the radio,
we didn't have anything else for any other kind of media,
because in the late 90s, there wasn't any TV on the internet,
or radio on the internet, like we have podcasting now.
So I just wanted to give you that little tidbit of information,
it seemed to be the same for a U.S. or Canada,
anywhere else where they do rating systems.
So take care of them, keep going with the daily source code, I love it.
Right, very scientific, there you go,
that's how they measure it, very scientific,
please write it down, please take notes
and write it down and hand it into us.
Yeah, that used to work in school too.
Haven't talked about sound seeing in a while,
sound seeing tours.com, sound seeing tours.com,
where there's a great collection of sound seeing tours, obviously,
and the audio collective is done with as well
from an elephant.
Hey, I'm this is Dave from the audio collective,
and I'm coming to you with 800 pounds of elephant,
strapped to my butt.
That's right, it's Dave from audio collective.net,
and we do sound seeing tours and a whole bunch of different kinds
of podcasts and, you know, just cool stuff like that.
And we're big fans of the daily source code
and you show on serious, keep up the sweet stuff.
And if you want to check out our show,
that'd be cool too, audio collective.net.
We do a podcast about once a week,
and it's me, my wife Rachel and our friend Corey,
and he Corey is kind of out there sometimes,
but hey, I guess I'm right in an elephant right now,
so what can I say?
So come in to you live in the top of an elephant,
when I live a podcast and straight from off
to the elephant right here, talk to you later.
I'll show a dot com, recommend listening with
at least one foot firmly planted in reality.
Hey, Adam, this is Ray Anthony, former corporate radio guy,
and hey, Ray Anthony, yeah, what are you doing?
Well, Gary Coleman, I'm striking out on my own this time
with a new podcast at radioguide.com.
It's kind of like a radio show with entertainment news
and current events, but this time I don't have to worry
about my boss yelling at me calling on my hotline,
so I can say what I want.
What you talking about, Ray Anthony?
Well, that means that we dive a little bit in the politics
and some taboo subjects like touchy conspiracy theory.
Who's today?
You leave her out at the radioguide.com.
Yeah, radioguide.
That's really true.
That's really the big difference.
And we welcome anybody who's from traditional radio
and wants to get podcasting a shot.
It's so liberating.
Because what really is, when you're on a live broadcast,
whether it's on radio or television,
it's really easy if you're not on a live broadcast
because you can always, what we call burn tape,
although it's not really tape anymore.
And they'll just roll it back and hit play and record
at the same time over again.
At least that's what we did at MTV.
But I think the burn tape concept,
everyone in television is familiar with it and radio.
So I mean, you burn the tape.
And but when you're on live, television or radio,
you're constantly everything you say,
go through this little filter in the back of your mind.
And this little filter looks for little nuggets
in your stream of consciousness.
Before it hits your, the part that forms the words
in your brain and then spits it out through your mouth.
It's looking for bad words.
Words we can't say or, and this is,
and that's one thing.
Because you know, you can basically pre-program yourself.
You know, that's done since childhood.
You're not supposed to say a number of words.
And so that's pretty much, that's where your filters
originate.
Everyone has the filters.
But then you have to add to that corporate policy,
political stuff on MTV.
That was even though we were, oh man,
we have so many outtakes that were so funny.
But you could never talk bad about the artist
or anything even close to that.
So it becomes very tiresome
because you're always running your entire stream,
thoughts stream, you're running it through this filter.
And that filter is almost entirely removed.
Oh, actually completely removed when you're doing podcasting.
Or when you're doing, when you're podcasting.
And it's, you'll like it.
You'll really, I'll check it out radioguide.com.
We'll make sure I check it out.
Let's do one more from the Pod Safe Music Network.
If you don't mind, this is song that'll actually
couple of people pointed me to this.
Uh, actually, this guy's guys going to own record company
going and kind of an 80's revival type sound.
Skycar, this is Alicia.
You're one of a kind of perfect fit to my body and mind.
Just like a dream come true and dance through my life.
Just like you do, I wish every night, you're here to hold me tight.
You are what I seek, my little angel with a deadly strength.
Oh, Alicia, I won't turn around and walk away.
Oh, Alicia, I will stay forever and a day.
Oh, Alicia, would you feel safe and sound?
Oh, Alicia, liberators love I ever found.
Oh, now I won't put it down.
I won't let it down.
Pain of future, right in the time, be at a side.
Oh, you are one of a kind to every kiss.
Just close my mind.
You make me feel that it is upcoming baby.
These repeats, you're touching so profound.
Never lose.
My name is Alicia.
I will stay forever and a day.
You are what I seek, my little angel with a deadly strength.
And you are what I seek, my little angel with a deadly strength.
But you're so profound, never lost, suddenly found
Come on baby, look my way, move on close here and stay
Oh, I need shot, I won't turn around, I walk away
Oh, I need shot, I won't stay forever and if they
Oh, I need shot, would you be what I feel, say the sound
Oh, I need shot, look right at the slow, I have a phone
Oh, I won't put it down, I won't let it down
Pain of future, right at the time
Be at a side, I won't put it down, I won't let it down
Pain of future, right at the time, be at a side
Oh, I need shot, I won't turn around, I walk away
Oh, I need shot, I won't stay forever and if they
Oh, I need shot, would you be what I feel, say the sound
Oh, I need shot, look right at the slow, I have a phone
Oh, I won't put it down, I won't let it down
Pain of future, right at the time, be at a side
Pain of future, right at the time
It could all run through kind of like one clearing house because one thing I know for sure
the the amount of work you have to do to log and track and
Oh man to make sure you know just we should have some kind of blanket license that we can that we can use now
Of course we still have to do better on reporting back
But so far I think we're like 90% or 95% of
Podcasts who are using these from the podcast music network. I'm reporting it back into the network and
So that's you know we're doing it now just for
Just for the love and for giving back to the artists, but
When we and I'm presuming that we will cut some kind of deal when we cut a deal
You know these other artists within the pod safe music network can also take advantage
I would at least be the way I want to
Stuggling with the bar still here. That's the way I want to put the deal together is
That they would automatically become a member of either a scap or be a mile
I wonder if you can be a member of both if that makes any sense probably not
So I think we can come up with a real win win situation here. You know come up with
Something that really cost the podcaster nothing unless money's being made on the show
Right and
We'd act as the clearinghouse and then as a bonus benefit
We'd sign up
You know we'd have some kind of I'd love it to be an almost an automatic type of
Pod safe
We call it pod safe membership to the to these collection it because that's what we agree right there collection agencies
So that way
Even if your song is played as a pod safe music tune
You'll also get compensated if money was made through the use of that
I think we should still keep the the fair use out front and center because that's really really important
That if you just want to put a show together that it you know you can just use some pod safe music and
That it won't cost anything
So
That's that that is happening this week and uh and also very just just a little side note
That you know remember when they added a Alaska and Hawaii to the United States
I don't remember personally, but
It wasn't all that long ago
Something similar is happening over in Europe. They're adding Turkey
I guess now that the talks can be officially on and Turkey can officially
Applied to come into the European unions can be there and just to see what happens there
All right, everybody that's it for me
DailySourceco.com is where you can find all the info about the show. I'll be back tomorrow for the hump day edition take care