Delta Sierra Charlie two eight eight and hello everybody
Welcome to the daily source code today is Tuesday and we're gonna do something different today. Oh, Yousa
It's been quite a quite a crazy morning actually first
So much to tell but the bottom line is I'm in the curry cruiser and today will be a cruise cast as we check out the brand new
The brand new car that we got this is the Jaguar known as the pronunciation the Jaguar
XJ Super V8 which means it's the the big sedan or saloon or whatever they call it here and
It has a supercharged V8 engine so I'm in the driver side right now as you can tell
Engines off although you shouldn't well you should be able to tell I guess I can already hear my
Phone interfering
Okay, let me just oops
Let me just put that over there. I don't want to turn it off in case someone needs to get a hold of me
Okay, so the first thing we're gonna do is we're gonna start this puppy up
All right, instantly the V8 came to life
I did some
Oops, oh no, it's non-bod save not good
I did some preparations for today show and I
Burned a CD and I'll gladly talk to you about all of that experience so let me pop that in right now
So we can do something kind of you know halfway official
Hi, this is PW Finton creator of digital platinum and producer of Adam Curry's Pacho on serious satellite radio
And I'm mad as hell and I want to quit my day job
Shit, this is my day job never mind
All right, PW yeah, you know the sad thing is he still wants to quit his day job
Okay, hold on a second. I'm just getting something out of my coat which I put on the back seat here
Man, what do I do with my
Okay, we can't
Leave
Unless we have a lighter
Oh
My sitting on it. I know I took one with me. Where the hell did it go?
Ah
Being out got it. Okay, so what I'll do is
After I'm done recording the show I'll evaluate it and see if
See if I need to mix the the actual tracks in probably just to give you a good sound you know good effect and
More over to make it stereo, but I want to demonstrate some of the cool features of this car
So let's get the show crank and shall we
$16 million worth of airplane straps my ass
Then the next generation radio content in my years
All right now we're really started with your daily source code for Tuesday
A rolled on the window see if I can let you hear the engine at all
We won't go to do that. I forgot this is a CD so I put the CD in and you know you'd hope that the CD player would recognize the the track names
I thought that that was burned right in when you burned something off of iTunes. No, I just get track three track four
Let's listen to the engine for a second
400 brake horsepower supercharged and this thing is full of amazing fucking gadgets
So one that we back it up here. That's the door's locking my left hand mirror
Pointing downwards of course. It's got all the amenities of a Ford we've talked about that and actually I have to say
You know, this is as we say here in the UK a proper motocar
It's built in Britain even though it is owned by Ford which is not a bad thing in fact
The only two things I can really
Identify that are you know that feel kind of out of place home. I want to bump into my neighbors car here
Which kind of feel out of place for for British built car and
Which are clearly Ford influences
um
Is this little
Green LCD display home on the microphone swaying back and forth this little green LCD display which sits right in my
Spadometer which is the middle dial in front of me
It's the ugliest fucking thing you've ever seen and so it shows me how many miles driven that's basically your trip computer
But it's also with feedback for the for the navigation this is gonna be I might have to
I might have to mount this mic differently and I know if this is gonna work for us here
Because with the swaying I can already hear my voice coming back it for
Okay, so now we're a driving away from the cottage something
Wow, what was that? I would drive or intervene. Oh, I got to tell you about all this stuff
um
So we've had the the studio A8 mobile here. Hold on trying to adjust this microphone so doesn't sway too much
We've had the studio A8 and of course we've done a couple of shows from from the A8 which is now gone
And we pretty much in the in the year that we've been here
We've gotten used to driving on the left-hand side of the road
But that was in a left-hand drive car and
This is the very first right-hand drive car we've ever had and let me tell you it is some you know
I'm it's something different all together. I don't know if this
Swing microphone is gonna work for us. It's kind of a weird sensation
Because I'm constantly drifting over too far to the left of course
All on we have a yellow yellow green here
And it's it's scary because you really have this sway microphone is not gonna work out a lot
Let me let me do this differently here. I'll just I guess I'll just clip it to my uh
I'll just clip it to me. Okay. All right
Man that doesn't sound as good and I does it. Well, I'll just crank that up and we'll see kind of crank it up here
Oh crank it up here. Hold on
Okay, already doing things I shouldn't be doing in a brand new car with a right-hand drive. There we go. That's a little bit better
Okay, so I'm constantly drifting over to the left
I'm a danger on the road. I'm a menace to society at this point actually
Wow this car is telling me all kinds of things
So it has a a center console
First of all there's some I mean there's some basic cool shit in this car
I see warmers very important for me. I love having a heated ass and heated backside and
The minute you turn that on the cherry wood steering wheel immediately starts to warm up
Which is just the most luxurious feeling for all I gotta tell you
You basically manage everything through a center touch screen console
Which has
Advantage and disadvantages but there's some other really cool shit that they've put on board this machine
Let me give you an example
Climate temperature 21 degrees
Right so it just set it to 21 degrees to make it nice and toasty warm in the in the studio
I mean while I'm just driving off towards what I know is a very windy country road
Because it's nothing better than driving a new car on a nice sunny day, which it is today. It's beautiful in Surrey
And having some great driving around music, you know, just to kick back and hit the accelerator and
And enjoy the tunes
So while I get out to a piece of open road where I can demonstrate some of the cool things this car has let's
roll out some
tunes
This is uh, well of course you've probably heard this several times on the daily source code
By now you should know Matthew evil, right?
Now there's control so sharp it'll make you bleed
We don't talk with just punts of clock can't find each other in the same old grid that maybe a little escape what we need
We love and you work like a dog every morning
The city's paying like the loud taste stain on your dress
Get in the bay and before you break down
And don't cost the down to leave this town
You're on the road because we got to get out of this mess
So let's drive away
Let the sunlight chase us all day
Not gonna stay in the way
Let's drive away
It's a good way.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Those were the song and that took it for granted.
But bumping the road, not really in part of the track.
Come on, come on, it's alright.
You made me believe tonight.
Love and makes you so damn good to be left.
Oh, so let's drive away.
Let the sunlight chase us all day.
Nothing goes in in our way.
Let's drive away.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, but I see fast, but I gotta be going.
Oh, yeah.
We've gotta be more than the coffee shops in the bar.
Baby, baby, it's still late.
Baby, baby, it's just late.
We need you take my hand and we'll get in the car.
Oh, so let's drive away.
Let the sunlight chase us all day.
Baby, that's all I got to say.
Let's drive away.
We'll drive away.
Baby, baby, it's still late.
I've said it before.
I'll say it again.
Top down, driving around music from Matthew evil.
Drive away on your daily source code for this Tuesday.
Hold on, I'm just going to queue up the next track.
Make sure that we have that ready.
Okay, perfect.
So here's the thing I want to share with you about this car.
It has, well, they call it adaptive cruise control.
I call it a fucking auto pilot.
By the way, I really hope you're listening to this podcast in the car.
Because there's, I love listening to podcasts while driving or while in.
And I think not just on the move, but while in a car.
Listening to someone doing a podcast in the car.
I can't explain why, but there's something about it.
I just, I don't know if there's some kind of connection there.
So that's how actually, one of the reasons I like Pacific Coast,
Hellway so much.
So they call this thing adaptive cruise control.
So you know what a cruise control is.
It's, oh, actually it's kicking in now, man.
Okay.
A cruise control is probably going to beep at me in a second.
It is essentially when you're driving along,
preferably on the highway.
And you know, you want to keep a constant speed.
Either the speed limit or whatever the flow of traffic is.
And you set the cruise control.
And it will maintain the speed you set it at.
And you can, I'm sure most of you know this.
You know, you can nudge it up or down a mile or two with the usually hand-based controls.
And if you hit the certainly the break and in most cases the accelerator.
And basically anything you do, even a sudden move on most cars,
these days will disengage the cruise control.
So the adaptive cruise control utilizes the same,
I presume the same technology as the sensors that assist you with parking.
And what it does, it sends out, I don't know if it's infrared or what kind of beam it is.
But it sends out a beam to the car ahead of you.
And then you have a setting which allows you to determine the gap you want between the car ahead of you and yourself.
So right now I'm on a one of those perfect country two lane country roads driving through.
Hold on a second.
Let me take a look at the navigator.
We are on Epsom Road, hold on a second.
Navigation zoom out 10.
Oops, that was a little too much.
Navigation zoom in 5.
Navigation.
Love it when that shit works.
We're driving towards the leather head.
Obviously the car has voice response.
You figured that one out right.
So I have the cruise set to 65 miles an hour which would be way too fast for this road.
But it was portions of it.
You can certainly drive 65.
And what's happening now, you can hear the car slowing down.
It's doing that all by itself.
Because the car in front of me was slowing down to make a left hand turn.
So not only does it do the accelerator work for you.
Whoa.
Okay, you don't want to set it when someone's just turned around a corner because it couldn't see a car ahead of me.
I hope you can hear the engine.
Okay, so now I'm going to hit resume.
So it knows it wants to go 65 but it can't because there's this white station wagon in front of me.
So now we're doing 30.
It's even slowing down the car ahead of me slowed down a bit.
And if I put my foot just touching the side of the brake,
I can actually feel the brake being depressed like an invisible foot.
And let me tell you last night when I tried this feature out.
I was on the same road but it was pitch black.
There's no street lamps here.
And it was just amazing.
It's exactly what you want for these dark windy country roads where you have no idea what's
around the next corner.
You know, and you could even be blinded by lights of an oncoming car.
And now you can kind of just follow the guy in front of you at a safe distance.
You can set the gap that you want.
And it's like, all you got to do is steer and just, I can stay awake.
I love this.
I'm sure on the highway would be, you know, we should actually take this puppy out.
Well, how much time do I have?
Okay, we should take this puppy out on the highway.
I think that I'd love to see if we can share some of the experience
of accelerating with this supercharged engine.
So I've got to find a place to turn around.
But right now, I'm cruising on a country road.
I don't have to worry about monitoring my speed.
I'm safely behind the guy in front of me.
It's, uh, I love it, man.
This is awesome.
So while all that's happening, why don't we go over to some feedback?
Adam, Adam, Adam, Adam, it's empty be again.
Maybe we can get back to some feedback from today's show.
Wow.
I can hardly believe my ears.
Right after Patricia claims you have the perfect cock.
She brought to me something more than sex.
And she turned her down.
Turn for having her come in your pod, shut it shut.
That's right, man.
I care about the show.
Come on.
What is that?
What has happened to our girl pod father here?
I mean, it's great.
You're dedicated, but honey.
I think that's a little too dedicated.
I can't take time to enjoy the wine.
Hey, don't worry, baby.
I tapped that ass later on, all right?
Anyway, it brought to mind that one of your listeners emailed me the other day to say that
he was ordering a copy of our new album because it was so romantic.
He thought it would put him in the mood with his lady friend.
So I was thinking maybe I should send Adam a copy of three and he's easy to help
put him in the mood of Patricia.
So, uh, you know, give me the address and I'll hook it up for you, baby.
You know what?
This sounds like an emergency.
What did I just send you on right now?
It's a jazzy one.
So I think Patricia and even Christina will I get it.
It's called a bide.
It's by low spirals from free and easy.
And if you did get, I could be persuaded to add it to the podcast of music network.
Just for you.
This is lovely, Angie.
Thank you so much.
Wish your ass was here.
Get in the warm one.
See you next to me, honey.
I'm going to call you.
What's going on here?
Something to me though, when in your sleep, and love my time,
to rise again someday, as feels we hold,
and as we can't stand it.
Let's watch our shoes,
leave our golden face,
hey, hey, got to pass away,
I say let it pass away,
let it pass away, let it pass away,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Let it pass away,
I pray that it pass away,
And if nothing could be my love
I'm not a passing way
I'm a passing way
And if there's no way
I'm not a passing way
And if there's no passing way
Love spirals and G.B., thank you so much, Ronnie.
I hope you do add that to the pod save music now,
work that'll be fantastic if other people could play it out.
So I've turned around now and I'm heading back,
as I said, cool feature of this car is that it has a center console
with a touch screen, which you basically manage everything through.
For pilots, by the way, this is a very strange concept
because one thing you don't do in an aircraft
is touch the screens of your instruments.
Because you always have some kind of oily residue
that will transfer onto the screen and then at night
it becomes kind of hard to read, you get smudges and glare.
And it's hard to see what's on the screen
when you're flying that can be pretty critical.
In this case, it's basically radio station presets
and a couple other things and the map really doesn't really
affect it all that much, but it is kind of weird to touch the screen
because that's not, you know, my instinct says no, don't do that.
The voice response system has blown me away.
I mean, I've had voice response systems
and all kinds of gadgets and gear and phones and you name it.
And you know, you go through hours of training
and I got in this car and immediately it worked.
Now, it has a menu-based system
and I'll just run through the top level menu for you.
It'll do that, it'll do that for you.
So you can hear all the things you can control
with just by pressing a button on the steering column.
Help.
Voice commands are generally given
in the following format, device, function, setting.
For example, radio tune, 99.7 FM.
Or we use a name.
Yeah, the play track three.
To give a command, press the voice button.
After the tone is completed, speak naturally.
In general, to cancel a command, push the voice button again
while the system is listening.
To hear a list of items for which you can then ask for specific commands,
say voice help.
OK, let's try this.
Just skip the verbal feedback for a command, press the voice button.
OK.
Voice help.
Voice help to get help on a specific system,
say one of the following commands.
Radio help.
Radio memory help.
CD help.
Change a help.
Phone help.
Phone memory help.
Climate control help.
Display help.
Navigation help.
Navigation memory help.
Navigation root help.
Voice memory help.
Help completed.
Wow.
OK, let's try this.
CD help.
CD help for any of the common CD functions,
the following commands are available.
CD play, OK.
CD play track one.
Valetrack numbers range from one to 99.
OK, let's try that.
CD play track five.
Cool.
Hit me.
It's going to work.
Well, that didn't work very well.
Let's try it again.
CD play track five.
Thank you, Runder a lot of pressure.
Watch nine competitors battle it out
to become president of their own record label
on the biz.
It's a new kind of reality show.
I'm demanding only online at awellmusic.com.
Oh, that was it.
OK, cool.
All right.
So that's the voice response system.
That's fucking crazy.
Let me see what should we do next?
I'm thinking, let me give you a little hold on.
Let me see where we are.
If I can, I'd love to give a little tap on the accelerator
to give you an idea of what this puppy can do.
We got some time.
So let me think.
I don't have anything pretty sad.
I think I can just drive off to the motorway, which is highway.
Actually, right now I'm on a parkway, if you believe it.
I didn't know that they had parkways here.
So here's everything that happened this morning
as I had this idea last night, of course.
And I had most of my prepared what I wanted to do,
and I'd kind of thought out the route and everything.
So first thing that happens is, well, first of all, yesterday,
Patricia came home.
She had a doctor's visit, and they put her on a 24-hour blood
pressure monitoring system, which is funny,
because she had to wear this device to bed, which
looked like a fling stone's version of an iPod.
But hung on her belt, this big ass thing,
where the battery and a little display,
and then a tube, the ran around her shoulder,
or across her back to her left arm,
where the wrap goes on that inflates,
and it inflates periodically.
And she had to wear that for literally 24 hours.
So last night in bed, she had to write it.
I was joking the whole time, I was in hunting,
what's planned on the iPod.
And what happens like every 20 minutes,
or it doesn't seem like it's a set time,
but it felt like almost every 20 minutes.
You hear her, and then a little buzz,
and then the pump would be activated.
So we had that going all night.
And at one point Patricia got up to go to the bathroom.
And she, of course, she forgot that she was wearing this thing.
She pulls like the old bed, and I'm going with it.
Anyway, so she got up at seven this morning
to get Christina up and ready.
Usually she comes and gets me about seven, 15,
or something, and she was like, drive Christina to school.
And Christina was not feeling it all well.
I think she's now as this three day or four day cold.
So she was going to stay home.
So of course, that put me behind no matter what,
because I didn't get out of my,
get my ass out of bed until 830.
And then the usual morning ritual,
and then I got my gear, and I could not find
a simple connecting cable, a three and a half inch plug,
another three and a half inch plug
for my wireless microphone,
to plug it into the I River.
And I'm tearing apart everything.
I must have left it at the condo and San Francisco.
I don't know.
I had two of them.
I think it's probably still hooked up
to the M and 50 for some reason.
It's gonna connect into the I Mac there.
So for some reason, I left it.
Okay, no problem.
So I went off to go to the stores called Commit.
They usually have just about everything you need.
I also need to get some CDs.
You know, I need to get new batteries.
And I got a new wire, and I was ready to go.
I'm in the parking lot.
I'm okay.
I'm gonna start recording right here
in the parking lot in front of this Commit Store.
Forget about it.
The three and a half inch, a three and a half inch cable,
which is a beautiful one I bought, by the way.
You know, the gold standard, whatever,
with titanium wiring.
It was in one of those packages
that you can't open without a fucking jackhammer.
What is up with that?
I mean, I understand trying to protect stuff from theft,
but I had to drive home to get pairs, scissors to open it up.
And now here we are.
Finally, everything's all together.
So I'm driving back into almost our hood now.
Driving past our gas station,
which I will be visiting regularly
in this automobile.
I'm sure, although we really don't drive all that much
at all.
Steering wheel, cherry wood, nice and warm in the hands.
My back is heated up.
It's perfect.
Perfect for another promo.
The Potsay Music Daily podcast, Your Daily Domes,
of 100% Potsay Music,
every Monday through Thursday,
I choose a theme for each day,
and you get to hear great songs of life.
You're taking the easy way.
Give me a found, not all the joy.
Some things will never change.
I'm still that jealous for it.
I want you to know me.
I'll leave it now now.
Yeah, you push me to the limit.
You're watching never get it right.
See what side doors on mine.
It fits that fun share.
Bring me my gift out brother.
I'm home.
The listeners get to vote for your favorite songs.
Every day.
Then for Friday's show,
I take all the most food it looks throughout a week.
And play your top 10 favorites.
So, if you want to discover something music,
or just want your day to go by,
just that much faster.
Check out the Potsay Music Daily podcast.
Potsay Music Daily.
Potomatic.com.
So, that is the first show I've heard that's on Potomatic.
That's pretty cool.
And I really am digging all these pod tape music shows
that are cropping up.
We've got a couple of top 10 countdowns.
We've got the spotlight.
The young palette is doing.
I played a piece of that yesterday.
So, look for that coming up soon.
I didn't get the Christmas song stuff up yesterday.
I'll have that up sometime today,
and start posting the first songs to thexmus.podshow.com feed.
So, that you can subscribe to that,
and fill up your iPod for the Christmas season.
Let me see.
So, now I am getting close to,
actually, I'm in Burfum,
which is spelled Bravo Uniform Papa Hotel Alpha Mike.
So, I used to say Burfum,
but that's before I was a part of the side here.
Okay, going through a roundabout,
so trippy man driving on the left and sitting on the right,
but it's kind of, oh, shoot, fuck.
Damn, that's not what I wanted to do.
I'm driving the wrong way now,
and hold on a second.
Let me turn around.
So, one other thing that I found at the comet store
is, yeah yeah yeah yeah,
please go away from here.
And it was at the cash register.
This thing called Kid's okay.
And it just caught my eye briefly
as I was paying for, you know,
CDs and the cable and the batteries and everything.
One of my hearing here.
Is that okay?
That's a little, oh, a little splatter through from the radio.
This thing called kids okay.
And I think what caught my eye, you know,
you, of course, you see much more than,
than you recognize, I guess.
I, you know, you're the neurons on your eyes
or picking up all the light and, you know,
so you're seeing things,
but only certain things register.
And the word ping was there.
In fact, I think it was more than just the word ping.
I think it was the sentence.
Don't ring your kids, ping them.
I'm like, yeah, I'd love to be able to ping my child.
What the hell does that mean?
It sounds like a perfect, it's the service,
which I signed up for immediately.
I haven't configured it, but I'll be doing that later on today.
So I'll let you know how it goes.
It's a service.
Oh, I suck, I got it.
I'm on it.
I'm going to parking a lot here trying to figure out
a parking place to turn left and what the hell is this?
This is where it gets confusing parking lots,
because sometimes the inner parking lot,
they want you to stay to the right.
It's, it's indicated with arrows,
but it doesn't help the damn foreigners, you know?
Okay, let me see if I can get out now.
So this is the way out.
Yes.
So it's a service that you set up on,
you can do it online, you can guess you can call an operator.
And it works through text messaging, SNS.
And you can set up three different phones.
And then what you do is you send a text message
to a service number, I think it's like 76, 6, 3, 0,
or whatever, they have one of those text numbers.
And within 60 seconds, oh yeah, so you send the message
to the service number, and then you ping,
and then you're, you can set up a name.
So let's say I would do ping Christina.
And then within 60 seconds, it sends you back a map
with the location of that cell phone,
which of course presumably has your child attached to it.
I was like, oh my God, this is so cool.
Is that over-modulating that it is shit?
OK, so incredibly cool.
Now of course, it's not as accurate as, say, a GPS would be
by no means because, and they actually
had this whole disclaimer thing in the very fine print.
They say in general, you're going to find that the distance
will be within 500 meters of the location of the cell phone,
the loss of your child.
But it could be up to two kilometers.
In fact, it could even be as much as seven kilometers
if you're out in open field.
And that, of course, all has to do with the density
of cell phone transmitters and towers.
But forget that, I love this.
I love it.
Now, of course, you can't just set it up for any phone.
You have to have consent, and that's kind of interesting.
You have to have consent of the other phone,
not of the user, but of the other phone,
because, essentially, they have to authorize
this ping service on their mobile by replying
to an incoming text message.
And then, from that point on, if you ping the person who's
cell phone you're pinging won't even know,
as long as they have the phone on, it's pingable.
And what I'm wondering, though, is this math that you get
but I guess you have to have an MMS capable phone,
off to look into that.
I don't know if it probably won't work on the blackberry,
but I still have the MDA, of course.
And I'm wondering if this is something
that will only work in Europe, or if I don't even know
if it'll work outside of the United Kingdom.
And there was also another disclaimer in there saying,
hey, all this information that we get about the locations
of the towers, et cetera, that location-based information,
it's only as good as the cell phone providers
that, as good as the data the cell phone providers
are giving to us.
So there's a lot of disclaimers in there,
but I think the whole concept is just fascinating.
I haven't told Christina about it yet,
but I certainly will.
I wonder what her response is going to be.
So we'll see what her response is.
I mean, I, you know, that I trust her.
And it's just, I was just blown away.
I mean, how comforting is that for a parent?
You know, okay, she's in town, you know.
She hasn't gotten on the train somewhere,
and she hasn't jet it off with some boy in a sports car.
Okay, we are now getting on to the A3.
I think this is the A3, isn't it?
This is still the slip road.
It's actually telling me that, okay,
well, let me emerge into traffic here.
We're doing 60, 65 miles an hour.
Okay, now I'm going to hit the cruise.
The adaptive cruise is on,
and I've actually set the speed limit to 77.
It's not doing 77.
I'm doing about 64, because it is now keeping me
nicely behind this red car ahead of me.
I mean, the left hand lane, which is the slow lane here,
okay, so I'm going to move over it.
Let's see what happens.
It immediately starts to pick up some speed some steam
because there's no car in front of me.
Well, a car just moved in front and slows down a bit,
and it's completely maintaining the speed
that I set it to, this is beautiful.
So now I'm doing about 75, and I'm behind a car
who's actually going a little bit faster.
So I just set up.
I'm probably at my 77 miles an hour right now.
But I don't have to worry about what's happening
if the guy up front decides
to all of a sudden hit the brakes.
So let me get to a straight piece here,
and then we'll see what this puppy can do.
So this is, yes, about, okay, so now it's on the adaptive
cruise control, slow down just a little bit
to take the other car ahead of me into consideration.
And I want to, yeah, let me give you,
obviously, this is, okay, so now we're doing 70,
and after this next corner, I'm going to floor it
and see if we can, I don't know what you'll hear.
I have no idea how I've done this year.
It's okay, this is nice, here we go, floor it.
90, 100, 110, it's just, oh my god, 130.
Oh, okay, I'm going to slow down now.
Shit, that was cool.
Whew.
The spite, what you might think, I'm not a big,
speed-free, okay, let's just chill out for a second,
after that one, okay.
Woo, woo, listen to this.
You cannot be driving on a highway, freeway, motorway,
or any kind of way without some driving music from the road.
Here she goes, brother, love other than your source car.
Hey, Larry.
Some shot, and it's so good to you.
Whatever happens, don't leave it so soon.
It's so right when it's okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeahi!
I still be back again, this goes, this goes
What's it goes again?
She died and tell the story
Oh, she like the tale of a glorious story
It's tales
It's easy to keep it by, and I'm gonna love you forever
That's the first thing
No, I want to be a little married
But I don't want to be a brand new toy
Just that, yeah, yeah
We'll go outside
I know where we can do it
Yeah, I know, I've been told
It's like a world
So there it is
It's a treasure
I want to be the guy
That goes home, we're new to the house
Oh, you're crazy to write
Like a little kid, I get it, yeah
Spare all your time
But I'm not up for that
But it's no real man
This goes, this goes, this goes, this goes
Yeah, yeah
We'll go, we'll go, we'll go
No, I'm not way she's better
And that's the first thing
No, I don't want to be a brand new toy
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
It's like a world
So there it is
I know you need a lot of friends
Oh, you're my mother, my decision just
Please, don't you think of your mind
Where you go is
Yeah, I was going, come on and love me
It's like a world
No, not up, give it
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, well we all had a good practice together just for free, yeah, yeah good, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah My Oletjust arms All Land, takes a ton of Andy Know' bro,
from the album of the year it is our very own brother love and there she goes almost at
the end of this daily source code one more thing that we have to do navigation
destination curry cottage navigation select curry cottage you please say yes or
no yes select you reach oh man it's now calculating the route even though it's
not telling me that I'm seeing it on the on the display and now here's the
interesting thing we go from the guy
see now also not got a woman so I've got like a like a couple living in my car
my goodness okay oh by the way thank you all so much those of you that sent in all
I think with the way from this guy thank you all so much those of you who said that my sound
was completely opposed the past two days actually I think it's probably since I did that
slow thing with Patricia I figured out what it was we remember the power went off and then it
came back on well what happened is my somehow the the faders on the mixing board weren't responding
so basically I was happening I was sending audio into the compressor for those of you
give a shit sending audio into the compressor limiter at the same time also sending audio out
through the regular outputs of the fader so it was kind of like combining the signals and that gave
that that whole like weird phasing effects so it you know it was hard to hear it on the headphones
but once once I had it then I knew what to fix so I appreciate everyone who does have their
ears on unlike me for helping me out on that one okay so tomorrow we'll be back with the
Wednesday edition of the Daily Source Code Friday is a flying day the wing commander if all goes
well is going to pick me up in the morning I'm going to fly Friday we're going to fly Saturday
so it's a double training and then either a fly back Saturday the end of the day or maybe even
Sunday morning so I might be staying in Amsterdam one of my final visits I think now that I'm just
about done with everything cleared up with everything that that I had to shut down there
yeah about right took about a year to close down life my god that's a long time
if you are subscribed to the Daily Source Code I really do appreciate it stay subscribed people listening
if not it's real easy to subscribe go to dailysourcecode.com it's where you can find the
the podcast the feed is the little orange on white XML button and you want to copy that link
and paste it into your iPod or lemon or perhaps you can use iTunes if you want you can also
find a link to subscribe with one click directly through iTunes on the show notes page
to dailysourcecode.com or www.curry.com very nice having you along for the ride today keep the
feed back coming I really appreciate it and you be looking looking forward to more from you
it's uh adamatcurry.com if at all possible please please don't
don't put the MP3s into the mail mess of themselves and of course promos promos dot pod show dot
com or as uh mark yusher motor kimono you my nip cough would say my pus that's right my promo update
system come on over everybody um right so I should be back in what no it doesn't even tell
me how many minutes it'll be until I'm back man that must be the Ford part of the car hey see you
buddy bye bye