Delta Sierra Charley 2...6...5...
There are no secrets!
Only information you don't get higher!
Adam Curry!
A $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
And it is Monday, October 24th in the year of our Lord 2005.
Good morning everybody from Curry.
It is, once again, right in early, only a quarter to nine, 846 AM.
And to start of a new week.
And of course, it's one of those foggy, dreary, damp kind of cock-eyed days,
which will burn off around.
Great weekend. Lots of stuff to share with you.
Now, if you subscribe to the podcast feed, then you probably already saw a little bit of what I was going to share with you on the Delta Sierra Charley Victor.
It's the first video podcast.
We'll talk about that.
Got some nice pod save tunes lined up with, actually one that's, I think, pretty funny.
And some excellent feedback on topics that we talked about last week.
Oh, yes. Are you ready for this week? I don't think I am.
Just kidding trying to accommodate myself here to get up and rolling because it's got a real busy day at the office.
I want to be there as early as possible.
I think I told you this before that when I'm over in the UK at the cottage,
then I try to do all my meetings between 8 and 11 AM at Pacific Coast because that of course is,
for like 7 PM in the UK.
But when I'm here though, I've got to switch it around and I've got to delay everything until past 11.
Good old ADL from mashup town has been sending me cool mashups to listen to for,
I usually sounds when every single day, even throughout the weekend.
So I have a lot of choice, actually a big selection to choose from.
But this one really got me when I heard it for the first time.
Because it's song that is geared to my heart, at least one of the two,
well, actually both of the songs just mash up or geared to my heart.
The first one, which you could tell is blondies rap, sure, was a huge hit at the time.
I've gotten to a higher radio in Amsterdam and then of course,
while you're here mixed in with it, which I'll leave a surprise.
It's a song that I grew up with.
The dating source code is Monday to 24th.
Good morning, everybody.
Right here on the stove, right here on the stove, right here on the stove,
get into this as a bar, and to this grill we're throwing.
Like a dog without a bone and a actor out of bone, right here on the stove.
There's a camera on the road.
It's great to square my life as no one.
It gave a lot of money to me.
Let your children play.
If you get to find a way to keep found a way.
You're on the road.
So we're running your hands out like you're a man
Gotta love your man
Yes
I see what you want to be
Just have your body on
To eat doesn't matter
I'm all fooled
Your balls will be too big on
Now it's all back to space
Where you and I have a heart
With a huge face
Saying you're hot
You're hot
And you're gonna stop
Just pass on
Chuchai
Cook man for more
Start deep in body
And now you're only eating dogs
Now it's sitting in the way
And you're gonna be eating
But a rock and roll country
You're gonna stop
We're gonna stop
When I first started at Radio
Dessable in Amsterdam
In the Netherlands when I was
I'm gonna say I was 16 years old
That was the first pirate station
I ever worked at
This was a huge hit at the time
It was just so...
It was big
It was underground still
But it was just big
And of course we were spinning
And off of vinyl back in the day
And this was funny
To actually meet Fab Five
Fredie years later
At MTV
When we see years 667
Eight years later
Even later than that
See
See, who, maybe even eight, yeah, nine years later,
I met him, Fab-Fab-Fab, Freddie,
when he started off at YoMTV Rapps.
And of course, the doors writers on the store
mashed up there.
Wow, I had a weekend full of porn.
Yes, right.
A big guy, porn.
Ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, I'll let you participate.
Now, can you hear a smell this?
Yeah, I'm gonna open it up.
Can you guess what this is yet?
Doesn't sound too good.
Doesn't, okay.
Oh, man, it's like, I'm opening up a brand new,
or actually the contents of already been removed,
but opening up a power book box.
This is, oh, just smell that.
It's a combination of styrofoam and a card board
and plastic wrapping.
Oh, I had not won, not two.
Ha ha.
But three containers that I opened up this weekend.
That's right, Saturday, God up at a nice, leisurely noon.
I think I was a little tight.
You know, this jet lag,
even though you jump right into everything,
it does kind of catch up with you.
So, we can do nice to catch up on a couple hours of sleep
and so God up around noon.
Now, just easily got myself caffeinated,
then Patricia called,
those things that you call the phone,
or did she call on Skype?
I can't remember, but we chatted for a while.
Or she's on the phone, actually, for a while,
probably about hour and a half.
If there's one thing I really, really, really miss
about not being with my girls is the talk.
You know, yeah, I think I've gone through this before
that I wind up catching myself talking to myself
and Patricia misses it too, you know,
when Christine is off to school,
then there's basically no one home
and she starts talking to herself.
So maybe we should record those two conversations
and create a mashup of that.
Anyway, so after I was done off to the city,
I found, oh, I found all kinds of great things.
I was, of course, in a headed in a relative B-line
for the Apple store,
but I had a couple of other things I want to do first.
I found out that only about four blocks from here.
Finally, I found the whole food supermarket
that I was looking for.
Everyone told me was in the neighborhood somewhere.
So I found that and it turns out
that actually market street in Union Square,
it's not all that far from the condo.
If you, you know, as long as it's not raining,
it's definitely a very doable walk
without groceries and stuff.
So I got, oh, man, I've been keeping a list.
You know, you really don't realize
how many things, what kind of stuff you've gotten
in your house that you use all the time
until you reach for it and you're like,
oh, I don't have that.
Like, I still don't have glasses,
but I do have light bulbs everywhere now
of the appropriate wattage, which is nice and low.
Anyway, between 25 and 40 watts,
preferably a pink or rose,
it works so well on the interior shots.
And then I had, you know, I did get a,
oh, yes, I had to get a track suit.
I'll tell you why in a second,
I'm swimming trunks.
And then it was off to the Apple store.
So I done all the stuff that I really needed to get
and then I was ready to do some shopping.
And boy, did I?
In my possession now, I have a brand new G5 iMac.
That's the 17 incher.
The 20 incher was not in stock.
It is a 1.9 gigahertz machine.
It was crazy because I ordered, you know,
I wanted to get all the extra memory in there.
I want to put another gig and a half of memory in,
but they didn't have the extra memory,
it lay in around, which just kind of sucks.
I mean, so I said, you know, if I want,
I have to go back and have it put in there,
but I have the pro car or whatever I paid extra for.
So you don't have to wait when you hit
the genius bar.
Anyway, I got that.
And then I, Connor helped me out at the Apple store here
in San Francisco.
And we talked a lot about what kind of power book I should get.
And I decided on the 15 inch,
one point, it's like 1.67 gigahertz.
It has one gigabyte of RAM installed.
Again, there, I wanted to have an extra gig installed
again, same story, no RAM available for upgrades
on Saturday.
So I got that.
And of course, I mean, when you're off buying stuff,
you might as well get a new video iPod.
Seeing as it is, the format everyone's talking about.
So I got a black iPod, one of the new ones that plays video.
And, well, you can imagine what I spent the rest of my week
and do, that's right.
Enjoying all of my porn.
Mm-hmm.
It's a good line.
If we just don't weekend, I picked up a ticket.
I was mild to freeway every week.
And you're not shown who we are.
Would be rock stars now.
And yes, we like to roll up in those big ones.
This is Lori.
And this is Joe.
Together, we are a guy.
A girl and a bottle.
We have been listening to the daily source code
and have been worried about your cholesterol levels.
We also think that perhaps you haven't been as faithful
about listening to our podcast, Tis Tisk.
If you had listened to episode 8 of Guy Girl and a bottle,
we visited the Thomas Fogardy winery.
You would have learned as we did that Dr. Fogardy
is a world renowned vascular surgeon
who still practices medicine at Stanford Hospital
right here in Silicon Valley.
According to Dr. Fogardy, there is now evidence
that wine consumption has health accruing benefits.
The evidence has been validated and redocumented
in multiple additional studies.
We've also learned that the nitric oxide extracted
from the skins of grapes proves to be the active ingredient
that decreases the level of cholesterol
and bad lipids and increases the level of good lipids.
Elements from grape-scrinac extract also relax the blood vessels,
decrease the tendency for blood to clot
and create a blood pressure lowering effect.
Quoting the good doctor, wine by all scientific research
criteria should not be viewed so much as an alcoholic beverage
but more as a health food.
We couldn't agree more.
Follow us as we discover other interesting winearies, wines,
and health food in the in-around Silicon Valley.
You can find us at www.gngb.com or in iTunes.
By the way, there are some stellar woneries located
less than 15 minutes from your sugar daddies on sandhill road.
Why don't you bring the pod squad out and meet us
and we can visit a couple of our favorite woneries?
Oh yeah, I'm free.
Okay.
A bottle, the pod show crew,
after the sugar daddies and sandhill roadsie.
And this is Joe, she's a girl and we've got a bottle.
And you guys are nuts.
Thanks.
Hi, this is Ed from the Ed's Mixed Bad Podcast
and you're listening to The Daily Source Code
with the pod father Adam Curry.
Welcome to trackingtechnology.com.
I remember not that many years ago.
The only technology that drivers really used
was the telephone.
Using a laptop and GPS is kind of impractical.
The employee that you never asked for a year.
That's the perfect fit.
Yeah, that might be good.
This is a podcast where we talk to drivers, owner operators,
industry leaders, and company owners
about what drives their system.
The most important thing is that we have an always
platform.
If you go optimization, it is for every company
from one truck on up, either from a website
or integrated into a dispatched system,
or virtually everything that's in every store
is how at least once on a traffic system
is one that runs every day.
You don't think about it.
You don't have to worry whether or not
it's going to run today or tomorrow.
So subscribe today through iTunes or trackingtechnology.com
and learn what technology drives the trucking world.
There's just no excuse for not taking advantage of it.
Oh, that's right.
And there is a lot of technology out there.
And a lot of it now in the Curri condo.
So as you notice, I've been getting a lot of feedback
about my cholesterol levels.
Very indigreesive of feedback.
But pretty much everyone says the same.
More exercise, less fatty foods, and stop the smoking.
Well, we got two out of three.
So I got my track suit, got my dearest track suit
and because Patricia had forgotten to pack it for me.
And I'm not complaining because I do have the world's only
self packing and unpacking suit case.
At least on one segment of the trip, it packs and unpacks itself.
And she'd also neglected to put my swimming trunks in.
And we have a wonderful spa.
A spa here in the building, a hot tub spa.
Me and all my Asian women sitting in the spa.
Me sniffing them.
They smell so wonderful and fresh.
So I went to, so yesterday, after I spent,
I don't know, I was up really late,
playing around and setting up and configuring.
It was beautiful, by the way.
Remember, I had my entire life on this one firewire drive.
So I just cloned it on both the new eye Mac
and on the power book.
And then slowly started to add the things that I needed.
And I'm very, very pleased.
And the speed is unbelievable.
The difference between my old power book G4, which
ran at one gigahertz, and the new one, which also, of course,
has a gigabyte of RAM, which is probably double what
I had in the G4, in hindsight, that's probably
one of the reasons why I was running rather slowly.
Oh, man, this thing just zips along.
I freaking love it.
So I stayed up nice and late.
And of course, I got the Wi-Fi in the condo.
So the power book went to bed with me.
And it just couldn't stop playing.
And then Sunday got up.
And then I had a, it was great because Patricia actually
video chatted me on the on eye chat.
I had just kind of like woken up.
Same time, you know, midday, oh, God, do I love sleeping
late?
And we talked for about two hours on the eye chat.
And it was great.
And I was able to show her to walk around and show her
everything.
And because she's, you know, she's only seen the condo kind of
pre, well, after she left after the vacation when both
the girls were out with me.
And yeah, it was good.
It's too bad about the Christina having a vacation.
She has a vacation all this week.
So she's off because that meant that, you know,
Christina's like me, she goes to bed really late.
And she loves to hack around on the computer
in the middle of the night.
And so she was still up otherwise.
I'm sure we could have worked out some cyber sex.
We always flash each other briefly, which is exciting.
Oh boy.
So you know, hit test today.
Yann has been sending almost one every single day.
But it's crazy how it works out because if I don't receive
a hit test in my Gmail, then loan behold,
there's always a backtracks podcast.
Backtracks podcast.
So you think you know your hits backwards and forwards?
Yes.
Do.
Yeah, right.
It's the ready.
You're listening to the backtracks podcast exclusively
on the daily source code with Adam Curry.
Hey, buddy, bring it on.
Yeah, Adam.
You know, bring it on, man.
Let's get right into this week's quiz.
I'm ready.
All right.
Here we go.
Let's do it.
Number one.
Hey.
So, I got it.
I got it.
You've been hit.
The tone you can hear.
It's a quiet ride.
Come on, feel the noise.
Or it could be slate.
I think it's quiet ride.
Time's up.
Number two.
I don't know.
I give up.
Number three.
I know this one.
I think that's it.
Sound a lot like it.
Time's up.
Okay, here the answer.
All right.
Number one.
I'm here.
Number two.
I wonder what this one is.
I'm here's number two.
I'm walking in the rain.
Walking in the rain.
That's good.
Number three.
Oh, you can hear it already.
Uh-huh.
86.
Sevent five.
Five.
Yeah.
So, how did you do, Adam?
Two out of three.
Not bad today.
Thanks for joining us on this week's BackTract's podcast quiz.
You can visit backtract's podcast on the web at backtractspotcast.com.
Come on, catch your next time.
Back, back, trucks, podcasts.
Spin it back.
Thank you so much.
Oh, God.
You know, and I just sit here, stand, and swing, and and sing.
And I love it.
It really gets me going on a Monday morning, especially.
Thank you very much, back, trucks, podcasts.
So I had all my stuff together.
I had everything installed, and I figured, well,
let's see, I had some things I had to do.
New pod finder coming out tomorrow.
So I had to record the pod finder, send it off to my buddy Dave Fox.
Actually, I saw it came back already this morning.
He's on East Coast time.
So he gets, he gets to work around six.
He's very, very, very busy little beaver.
And so I was thinking, what kind of, oh, I, of course,
promised that if I had time, I'd put together a video
podcast.
And I really put a lot of thought into what I was going to do.
And it just doesn't make any sense to put a camera
on, you know, on me while I'm doing the source code.
In fact, I think it would be, I'm still,
you know, I want to keep those things kind of within the theater
of the mind, you know, I don't want you to see what I look
like when I'm doing this.
You've got your own image that you've conjured up in your mind.
So I, I figured what would be kind of cool
as to put, you know, it's this video stuff.
This is what I was working on in 2000.
I think it was 2000, started 2000.
I had a company called Jamby in the Netherlands.
And I think I told you this on Friday,
we were creating a kind of a, well, something very similar
to podcasting actually, where we had an application
which was built in Java.
And that was probably the downfall of the, of the whole.
Well, it wasn't the reason why it fell apart,
but it certainly didn't make things easier
because at the time, Macintosh was just migrating from OS9 to OSX.
I was a Mac user, you know,
so that made things very, very complicated, the Java stuff.
It worked, but then the swing set, as they called it,
didn't work too well in the beginning.
Huge memory and resource hog.
But the idea was, you had this, what we called it,
the JOP, right, the jerkoff platform.
And you would be able to share little video clips.
And at the time, we had, you know, broadband was just kind
of coming into play.
We had the always on connections.
And people were sharing, you know, wacky video clips
like crazy.
And, you know, we still do that today.
There's still all kinds of cool things going around.
And what we did is, very similar to what we're doing
now with podcasting is we said,
okay, we'll create the platforms
of people can share this stuff, but also show them how to make it
and we'll create content to port into the system.
And we were using a combination of Nutella,
or I think it was probably open nap at the time.
Napster, to be able to share because, of course,
bandwidth was still a huge concern, particularly upload speeds.
So we were looking at Napster, to the Napster technology,
to share the videos and to transfer them complete peer to peer.
And RSS, to subscribe to different channels,
which, you know, was like here, what do we call them?
We didn't call them buddies.
We called them the Freedom Rangers.
And, in fact, the application was called the Freedom Controller.
It was, I'm telling you, it was great.
And it was so, absolutely the right idea,
but we just, we were way too fast.
We went to video before, we could even really do audio.
And, of course, at that point, the only portable player
was really the Rio.
And there was no content for it, except for the, well, actually,
I'm sorry, there was a lot of content for it,
but this was right around the time where Napster was getting
in the trouble and stuff was starting to blow up,
and which I think also really affected the Rio.
So it felt very natural to me to walk around my power book
and my eyesight recording the video that I use
for the Delta Shara Charlie Victor.
Number one, I hope you saw it.
If not, you can probably download it from dailysourcecode.com.
I think you, you'll probably have to right-click
or left-click whatever and download to disk before you play it
because I don't think the web server has been configured
to play the M4V files or M4A, M4V file, whatever it is
that the iPod uses.
But I found that it'd be very, very simple, you know.
Had three clips put them together, got some appropriate music
which was of course, well, go look at the video
and you'll see it.
And I put the whole thing together in about an hour
and hour and a half, something like that.
And then, you know, uploaded it, put in the podcast feed.
And I got a lot of great responses to it.
The most interesting thing, let me see if I can actually
bring up one of these Gmail feedbacks that I've gotten.
Here we go.
This is from Brian Know, who does the Frank Truth,
one of my guilty pleasures of listening to non-pod-safe music,
all about the life and times of Francis Albert to Nutripe.
Adam, just watched the video from Craig Condo,
a very cool and evocative.
Nice way to promote the music network, too, of course.
I actually had the place pretty much pictured as it is,
except not quite as warm in terms of furnishings for some reason.
And then Brian says, didn't greet the prospect
of video podcasts with much enthusiasm,
bandwidth production time, expense, as an old radio guy.
I just love audio, theater of the mind, as you put it.
But he did think it was cool.
And he also saw, oh, man, I got to point you towards this
Bush-madge mashup that Katya put on her feed.
It's very, very funny.
And also, Tiki Bar, as Brian says, is extremely cool.
So I guess I succeeded, I succeeded in bringing it
across the vibe that I want the condo to portray.
Now mind you, if I had done that video differently,
it might not have fit within your image there, Brian.
So video is man, we're just learning what all the different nuances
are in audio.
So the analogy goes to publishing with Microsoft Word,
you have paragraphs, you have fonts, you can make something
bold, you can italicize it, you can use paragraph, page breaks,
all kinds of ways to really try to express yourself
through text.
And in audio, we have compression, we've got the way you mix stuff,
we've got background music, we have the sound of the microphone,
all different ways to really accentuate what you're trying to,
or accentuate what you're trying to convey,
or whatever you're trying to create.
It's as a lot to it, there really is an in video.
Man, you just get a, well, you get one, not just one dimension,
but a whole shit load of dimensions along with it.
So I'm a firm believer though.
I think that there will be, there's going to be some very
interesting things happening with video podcasting.
I haven't quite seen the content yet that has blown me away,
but I'm pretty sure it's going to be short form.
And of course, definitely user-generated.
Hey Adam, this is a PD over at Lovehouse Radio.
I just wanted to thank you because now every time that I burp,
I think of Sincel and every time I see a tree in my front yard,
I think Sincel, so I'm thinking about coffee,
every time I move the grass, but I just wanted to let you know
there was kind of a reversed all this.
On Wednesday, I had the third of four dentist appointments
for a Rooknowing Crown.
And as usual, I took in my iPod and was catching up
on some of my podcast, and I was listening to your show
from, I guess, on Tuesday.
And you played a song on there from Carmen Tyler.
And right about the time the song started was the same time
they were putting together the cement for the temporary filling,
which happens to be the most got-offel smell ever.
So unfortunately, I don't think I'll ever be able to enjoy
a Carmen Tyler song or at least the song drifting
that you played without having that smell
somehow permeated into my nose.
So I just wanted to let you know there was a little danger
with the whole marketing thing, but for the most part, yeah,
I think Sincel, every time I belch.
So I just wanted to pass that along to you
and also to let you know that during my dentist appointments,
I have now turned my dentist on to podcasting.
So he kept asking what I was listening to when I let him know
and mentioned your show and CC's accident hash.
And he's now become hooked.
So taking easy, keep it rocking, keep it real,
and spread the love, love house radio, talk to you later.
All right, thank you very much, PD, PD love
from lovehouseradio.com.
You know, you're right, it's time to do some reprogramming.
For those of you who have only recently started
to listening to the daily source code,
hopefully you're subscribed if not, go to dailysourcecode.com.
Pick up the podcast feed or do that in iTunes.
You can search on daily source code or Adam Curry.
We've been doing this sound-vertising experiment.
And they seem to be working very well, though, of course,
they work and reverse as well.
Here's kind of how it works.
I'm going to help you out.
Let's see what we should do.
OK, you're on the road.
This will only work for people who are actually outside
and I guess on the road during our commute.
Now, I want you to look out for a motorcycle, OK?
Look for a motorcycle.
There's bound to be one somewhere near you.
OK, you got it.
So we're going to call that the motor mouse, right?
M-M-50.
See the motorcycle?
You can't help but think motor mouse.
M-M motor mouse with the motorcycle M-M-50.
That's right.
What am I talking about?
The M-M-50.
When you see that motorcycle, now you won't be able to stop it.
What's probably going to happen is, even when you think of a motorcycle,
you're going to think M-M-50.
And what's real simple is you're going to think of those two wheels,
the motorcycle has you're going to think, two round speakers.
Is it working for you yet?
I'm not going to get through to you on this one.
All right.
So this is the first official sound-vertising test
of a real sponsor, the Logitech M-M-50.
How would you like that segue?
This is the device that I've been
raving about ever since I've actually been talking about
on the shows before the whole sponsorship deal started.
This is a portable, I call it like a breadboard.
It's about the length of a loaf of bread,
only what is it, maybe an inch and a half thick.
It comes in its own nice little portable carrying case.
And what it is is it's a portable amplifier, speaker set,
actually sound processor for your iPod.
And it has a slot in the middle between two speakers.
You've seen similar devices, I'm sure, although I've never
heard sound like this one.
You slide your iPod in and immediately connects
and it has a little remote, which is kind of like,
it's about the same size as the remote on the I-M-G-5,
which I'll gladly tell you about.
And with that, you can do the volume, you can advance,
you can pause, you can turn it on and off,
you can fast forward rewind, you can turn on the,
what is it, the surround sound system,
which is kind of cool, actually this surround sound
I've been digging that, it sounds pretty good.
And it also has an additional jack at the back
if you just want to connect up your computer.
Now that's what I've been doing.
I have it connected to the output of my Yamaha.
So the thing I play off of the G-Mac,
just off of the G-5, I-Mac, runs right through
the M-M-50 as unbelievable.
The sound fills up the condo, it's got a nice crisp,
kind of like, whoa, you can feel,
you can just feel almost the compression of the air.
It's really unbelievable how good this thing sounds.
And if you want to know more about it,
go to dailysourcecode.com and click on the picture
in the show notes of the M-M-50.
And I guarantee you, from now on, whenever you hear
the sound of a motorcycle, whenever you see those two wheels
spinning by, you won't help, but be able to think M-M-50.
And if it doesn't work, let me know, too,
because then I have to change my tactic.
So I'm from the pod safe music network right now,
as I scoured through it over the weekend.
This is a Elizabeth Longer quartet from New York.
I liked it because it was in French.
What do I do with you, what do I do...
I'll tell you with you, but I don't want to go for you.
I'll give you a thought with you, but you don't want to go for you.
I'll show you, from now on, but I don't want to go for you.
I'll tell you, with you, but I don't want to go for you.
What do I do...
So I'll do this and receive it,
I love you, I love you
I'll give you a break, but you don't want me, why?
I'll give you a break, but you don't want me, I'll give you a break
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ka-ka-pa-pa, yeah yeah, yeah, ahh duh-hh,ega yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah.
at the Elizabeth Lonning Jure quartet, I think that's the way it pronounced it.
No ID3 tags, so I had to kind of switch back and forth, just says track 01, that's very helpful.
But can you tell that I'm kind of in my jazz mode recently?
I don't know, I'm just, I've learned a country to jazz, all kinds of stuff.
Speaking of the, of the Podsive Music, now we're got another great podsive tune coming up
for it after the next promo.
Let me see, I was talking about Christmas music.
And man, all I had to do was mention that we needed some podsive Christmas music,
since there's a whole bunch of stuff that you basically can't touch when it comes to the traditional
Christmas carols.
Well, the carols actually you can't touch, but you'd have to be able to cover something.
The Podsive Music network just filled up with all kinds of Christmas songs that people have put in together.
So I am still looking for the absolute Podsive Christmas hit, and I guarantee you're going to find it.
And when we do, oh man, we're going to play the crap out of it.
The page ingrtion from mommycast.com.
And we love Adam Curry, the daily source code.
Ah!
And check this one out.
The song for free by Todd Lerner.
The beat is free.
You can talk free.
I will sing.
Take this song for free.
I will work for you.
Pause it, works for download this song for free.
One price with which you cannot do a fine publicity.
To share the song.
But don't steal that.
Take this song for free.
I'll give away some intellectual property of some harmony.
How about a counter melody?
Take it all in free.
Take this song for free.
Take this song, it's free.
Here's the bridge I wrote for free.
To plug into the song.
The fruit is from me.
The memory.
The bridge hasn't all the melody.
That gets the song to where it's got the bridge.
Take this song for free.
I'll work for you.
Pause it, works for download this song for free.
That song for free.
Todd, you can't forget to take this song for free.
I'll play this song, it's free.
Again, the bridge I wrote for free.
To plug into the song for you.
The memory.
The bridge hasn't all the melody.
That gets the song to where it's got the bridge.
Take the whole song for free.
Free from me.
Take this song for free.
I'm Todd.
I don't know if you've had a love for it.
Like a song for free.
Someone just buys a seat.
Take this song for free.
Oh man, when I first heard that, it cracked me up.
I'm like, yeah, that's exactly the spirit.
Todd Learner.
Song for free.
I don't know if songs for free.com exists.
But music.podshow.com certainly does.
And that's where you can find all kinds of great pod,
say music to play in your podcast.
And of course, it is for free.
And the song that I had to do is report back that you actually did it.
One other toy that I played with over the weekend.
What's that only 43 minutes down?
Time is moving fast.
One other thing that I played with over the weekend was my
brand new television.
I've been working, you know, playing with the,
with the Comcast cable box, which has,
I didn't know I had DVR in there.
It's got digital video recorder and Comcast is pretty cool.
They're getting close to some really good stuff, man.
We can go to the on demand.
And if you missed a particular series
from any of the premium channels and one of the networks,
they've already recorded it for you.
So I was able to watch Bill Mar.
I was able to watch the West Wing.
Now I could set a timer so I can, you know,
anyway, so that's pretty cool.
But what I saw real in live in real time.
I don't know if it was a, if it was a repeat or not,
it was the actor studio.
Neither watch that on Bravo.
And Angelina Jolie was on, oh my God.
She's on the list, right?
We discussed that.
And she is definitely definitely on that list for me.
You know, the list that my wife and I have,
she has a list I have a list.
If you bump into this person, then that's okay.
Oh my God.
She's very intriguing.
And a wicked past, really, really interesting.
She's twisted in a very, very sexual way.
But if you ever chance to catch that,
definitely do because she answers a lot of questions
that you may have had about Angelina.
And she's also just a sweet girl with a lot of tattoos.
See, Alaska Pod Show.
Yeah, it's real.
We're no Adam Curry and we're no Don and Drew Show.
And we certainly didn't win any podcasting awards.
Because we're too new for that.
We're just podcasters.
Pod casting from Anchorage, Alaska.
That's right.
I said Anchorage, Alaska.
We're the biggest state, you know.
We're bigger than Texas.
Who claim, if Alaska melted, we would be the biggest state.
What a bunch of crap that is.
Anyway, if you got a pod show, you got a gig.
You got a promo.
Kick it to us and we'll plug in.
And if you're a subscriber,
you can go over to our website at www.lascapodshow.com
and read the show notes.
Because you would really have nothing else to do.
Pod Show.
Content that will make you squeeze the dog
and burp your mother.
Pod.
Pod.com
Don't get mad.
Get media.
Manpaw.
I this is Jay Donley from ad pod.com
and we are thrilled that we are on Adam Curry's daily source code.
And he is the pod father of pod casting.
That's like being on Leno for television.
But he really liked our very metal interview.
But it sounds interesting.
I definitely want to hear the Barryman.
I like Barryman a lot of stuff.
He really likes Barryman.
And I float it down, made it into a ballad.
And that's what he was hearing.
So does that mean that Adam Curry listens to mad pod?
But it sounds interesting.
I definitely want to hear the Barryman.
I like Barryman a lot.
Pod.com
I this is Shadow Steel.
And you're listening to your global audio connection.
Madpod.com
This is Jay Donley.
So check out Madpod.com.
We have interviews from the past and present.
So remember, don't get mad.
Get media.
Madpod.
Shadow Steel or whatever mother.
That's a district truck named.
I think there are 25 Shadow Steel's running on the country right.
Madpod.com
So Adam, what about me, man?
What about me, Jay Donley?
I'm the one who made the promo.
I'm the one who sent you the promo.
Hey, don't leave Madpod.com
Not Shadow Steel.
My shadow's my partner.
It's all about getting exposure for more shows, right?
Madpod.com
Jay Donley, everybody along with Shadow Steel on a madpod.
You see, actually after I said that,
that probably wasn't the original Shadow Steel.
I got an email that says, what are you going to talk about?
I am the only Shadow Steel.
I think it was probably Shadow Stevens.
I was shinkin' of.
Okay, let's do one more time.
Jay Donley, Shadow Steel or the madpod.
Okay.
So here's what's on the agenda for me today.
Today, actually, pretty late.
My buddy Julia's coming up from Los Angeles.
Going to meet her around 11 at the office.
Julia used to work with me at our previous company.
Think new ideas.
She ran all corporate technology.
She ran a lot of technology for us.
And she lives in Los Angeles.
Can't convince her to move to California.
She's in California.
She moved to San Francisco to come and work with us.
So I figured, well, I'll bring her up a wine and diner.
And then she'll probably have a whole bunch of other cool people.
She'll turn her son to ours.
She found our temporary space.
She's been really, really good to us.
So I'm going to go hang out with with jewels.
And tomorrow there's this big Google thing called the zeitgeist.
It's like a Google media conference.
So I'm definitely going to check that out.
I've been thinking about clandestine recording
because everyone who's anybody in the valley will be there.
So if I don't, well, you know what Steve Gilmore will be there.
He'll be recording everything.
So let him do that.
I should hope at least Steve.
Okay, data source code.com is where you can find the latest episode for the daily source code.
It's updated just about every weekday Monday through Friday.
And you can find the podcast feed there.
Just go to iTunes and the search for daily source code.
And you can subscribe to it right there.
Free download for Mac and for Windows.
Adam at curie.com for your feedback.
I had a couple ones that I'll have to move over to tomorrow.
If you send me something, please don't attach it to the email.
Please put it up on a server and put in the ID through tags and send me the link.
All right, everybody.
Have a great week.
Have a great Monday.
And I'll see you last tomorrow.
Bye bye.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.