Delta Shia Charley 2-2-4 and good morning once again from Berkeley, California.
We are in the Megaspiti Ford Taurus once again.
Let me just check and see that it looks like everything's recording.
A little low on battery on the, let me see.
Oh my microphone, so this may be the last,
instantly the Taurus roared to life.
This may be the last shot I have it recording on this, on this set of batteries.
Still at the, oh, that's how it's turned.
Still at the Claremont Resort.
And still pretending to be on vacation, which of course isn't really true.
The girls are still kind of on vacation, although yesterday, oops,
on the, my bag on the floor here, and so it doesn't.
Why?
Crash off.
Hold on.
Going to the gate to the hotel.
Good morning.
Thank you, God.
No, not yet.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Well, we got two more days before we're checking out.
So, yesterday Patricia Ankristina and Marta Ron's wife went shopping
for some stuff for the apartment here in San Francisco.
Now, of course, I'm going to be using the apartment myself
namely by myself.
Of course, Patricia and hopefully Christina will come along once in a while.
See Claremont.
That's where I want to go left.
Yeah.
So, they were really thinking about ease of use and just my personality
when looking for furniture and they bought some kind of,
I haven't seen a picture of it.
It's been described to me.
But I think it's one of these big monster mega couches
that may even have the cup holders don't write in.
Not quite sure if they got me that version or not.
But I know it has a reclining section.
So, I'm completely jazzed about that.
Like my Albundi couch.
So, that's going to be, that's going to be very cool.
But they really spent a whole day.
Man, they should have done a sound scene tour
because first of all, we had the cars.
Since I had part in my car at the apartment
and we took Ron's car to our board meeting,
we had a boat hold on this is yellow and we stopped.
Which was on Sandhill Road.
The famous for its venture capital firms and that's where
both the Clienter Perkins and Sequoia capital are located.
So, we had to drive down there, not down.
So, then they had to find a car to rent.
And I think they had the car.
They drove two blocks and they went in somewhere
and immediately the car got towed.
And then they had to go get the car back
and it sounded like they had quite an adventure.
So, we really didn't see them again until like 9.30.
Because they were just all over town getting stuff.
So, that was cool.
So, for them, that wasn't really much of a...
Well, this was planned.
This was definitely planned.
That we're going to be working on the apartment.
Now, I also ordered a whole bunch, or Patricia,
I both ordered a whole bunch of stuff from J.C. Penny.
You know, like sheets and pillows.
And yeah, I can't get an answer out of them as to when they're going to deliver it.
So, I don't think that's going to happen before we go.
We're scheduled to go back on Friday.
And I'm sure I'll be back in maybe only two weeks time.
So, hopefully we'll have a lot of the stuff set up.
And you're just building up a household real quick
because a lot goes into that.
You know, you need stuff like trash cans and bleach and iron.
So, I'm sure there's plenty of stuff that we haven't thought of
that they'll have to pick up next time I'm out here.
But it's going to be very livable.
That's for sure.
So, yesterday we had our...
It wasn't really...
Well, I guess it was a board meeting.
Probably board update is more like it because we just received our financing.
So, you know, there's a lot of stuff that you know,
just that you normally talk about in a board meeting
that we couldn't do in this particular case.
But, you know what?
I gotta tell you, we had our plan and we came out here
and we started talking to venture capital firms and we targeted the ones
that we wanted to work with.
And, you know, we got what we wanted.
I am very impressed with, you know,
with the people that we're working with.
Particularly Randy Kamazar, Ray Lane,
Ramshiram,
Chandor, Marquami.
I mean, these are people of access to just unbelievable
networks of people and companies.
And, you know, phone calls are made and stuff gets done.
And, that's... that is really impressive,
but also very exciting.
Because there's, you know,
we just ask for stuff, you know, you ask for something
and it gets worked on, it gets done.
And that's, I love that.
And we've been doing a lot of stuff.
And a lot of stuff that we've been talking about
over the past year, really,
but certainly over the past half year,
about things that need to happen.
I think that we're going to have some good news about
bandwidth, delivery, and hosting for all podcasters,
I think we're going to be able to do some really cool stuff there.
I was just skimming through the ping page yesterday,
the latest podcasters listening to what people were saying,
and more and more I'm hearing anyone who has,
like anywhere between two and 500 listeners
to their show subscribers or downloaders.
Yeah, that starts to run into real cost on the bandwidth,
on the downloading side.
So I think we're going to have some great news
about that in the very near future.
Also, as promised, putting our money
and our resources where our mouth is on indiepotter.org,
that is the directory for me known as iPod.org.
You may have already seen that the performance
of the servers doing better,
but all the stuff that we really talked about,
more tools for node managers,
more ways to feature their node, their category,
the better access to the homepage of indiepotter.org,
which right now is really just a set of scripts
that I put in place that is kind of working.
Easier ways to delegate sub nodes, all of that stuff.
We're working on it, and there's three people
not really starting to plan out and map out
what we're going to do with that.
It doesn't happen overnight.
It's not like a big bundle of cash
and smart people show up at your doorstep,
and then everything's fixed.
There's actual work that has to be done.
But we've got the resources,
and I'm extremely excited about the work
that's going on.
The office is great.
It's small, and this is our temporary office
until we get an offer accepted
on one of the three places that we're looking for.
It's all south of markets,
so it's in this nice area of San Francisco
that's kind of young and upcoming.
A lot of residential,
like on the right way.
A lot of residential neighborhoods are being built,
which is where the new baseball stadium is.
It's just, I don't know, I like it down there.
It's a good vibe.
By the way, thank you for everyone who consulted
either Wikipedia or the CIA World Factbook for me.
It seems that there's about the lower 700,000 people
that live in San Francisco.
It's funny, because for East Coast,
there's like myself and Ron and Brian,
and some of the other guys.
That's like New York on a Sunday morning at 6am.
This is totally luxury.
There's no traffic out here.
There's nothing.
Although I do recall 10 years ago
when we had think new ideas,
our professional services company,
and we were doing a lot of work for.
See, we had work out here.
We came at a Silicon Graphics building,
some kind, I don't remember what it was.
A web presence, I'm sure,
I'm reaching back to grab my,
perhaps some money for the toll.
And they've got so many toll booths,
and no traffic.
Love that.
It's foggy again today.
Can barely see the Bay Bridge,
or the tops of the Bay Bridge through the fog.
Yesterday, it turned out to be beautiful,
just nice and sunny,
and it's never really cold.
At night, it does get chilly,
but I haven't worn a jacket or a coat.
I probably should start thinking about that.
I don't know if it's the weather changes significantly,
at all.
I've been led to believe that there's not a lot of change.
Good morning.
Thank you.
I'm led to believe that there's not a lot
of real seasonal change in the weather.
I wonder if there's more sunny periods.
Well, it's either way.
Well, a second, I'm getting squeezed here.
All right, I'm ready.
So it is 10, 15 right now,
and I'm obviously I'm driving in.
The girls are taking it easy.
We weren't back at the hotel until about midnight.
I've had a great dinner, though,
at 21st Amendment,
which is on,
what is that on?
Is that on?
Brian?
Or Folsom?
I think Brian?
There's a lot of good food in San Francisco.
They were immediately saying,
the food out here, the restaurants are just great,
which is true.
A lot of good influences from different countries,
just good cooking in general.
So they're going to come in later.
Christina was such a trooper.
So here's almost 15-year-olds.
We're birthdays on the 27th,
so just was it nine days from now, ten days from now.
That's kind of boring for 15-year-old
to have to go furniture shopping,
but I think she's really held up
and helped Patricia and Marta out
with jumping on mattresses,
whatever trouble they could get into.
But as a reward today,
I think they're going to go to Union Square
and go do some serious chick shopping.
I'm sure they'll enjoy that,
and Christina always loves a little shopping trip.
And so we'll meet up at the office later.
I think we're going to have a little hangout
at the end of the day.
Michael Butler should be coming over.
He hasn't seen the office yet, and of course,
he's a part of the company, Steve Gilmore.
I'm feeling one or two other folks may pop up
to get on our radar screen out here.
And I'm going to have to be in by 1030,
which I think I'll make no problem.
It really is only a 15-minute ride from the cross to the bay.
For a time magazine interview that Ron and I are doing together,
and I think there's some interview after that,
because obviously the news of the funding,
caught attention of the press,
and podcasts and continues to grow.
It continues to be a lot of excitement,
new listeners coming in every single day,
enjoying just all this new stuff.
And it really is.
As I said, I was just skimming through the ping page yesterday,
just listening to new stuff that's popped up,
and it's so amazing.
There is so much great content, different content,
you know, funny stuff, serious stuff.
You know, I think we're going to need more,
something we're talking about yesterday.
If I could really have my brothers,
if I could push all the buttons,
and I'm hoping I could do some of that,
we need more atom curries,
and I'm not saying,
cloning me,
I'm saying,
we need more people who can guide new listeners through the landscape.
So, you know,
I have my own taste,
both in pot-safe music,
and podcasts that I like,
and I like to turn people onto that.
So, you know, when you listen to the daily source code,
normally when we're doing a normal source code,
which we'll commence again on Monday,
and we're back at the cottage,
and got everything up and rolling.
And I'm back in front of my compressor limiter,
and I have time.
Yeah, I like to roll out promos from shows that interest me.
We need different guides for different types of stuff,
and I've actually been thinking about
maybe we can position some of the pod squad.
You know,
I think we should do that for new listeners that come in.
Michael Butler,
he represents a whole different set of podcasts
that was really involved in rock pod-safe music.
But not just that, you know,
he's had some fabulous guests on recently,
and he also points to a lot of great podcasts.
You know, I'd like to see Steve Gilmore,
guide people towards
technology and business podcasts that are great
to listen to and subscribe to.
And, you know,
Madge Weinstein is already doing this with Q-Potter.
So, I think that there's, you know,
there's something there that
that we should work on,
because, again,
we're all about bringing the listeners in,
getting listeners interested
and helping them find their way.
So, I do that's just something that I've
been thinking about.
Trying to figure out how we could
make it even easier for
more listeners who come in
to get what they want,
enjoy what they want.
And, obviously,
if they're not hearing what they like
and they want to do with themselves,
have an easy path for that as well.
So, we're,
I'm off the Bay Bridge now.
I'm amazed at how I've been doing
without the GPS.
I really am.
Let's see.
So, now I want to get off
the fifth street exit,
which I think this is it.
So, I'm driving right by
the apartment,
which overlooks this off-ramp of the Bay Bridge.
I think what I'm supposed to do here
is hang a sharp left
on the fifth street.
Yeah, this is it.
Ah, still lots and lots and lots
of homeless.
There was something on the news
that I was,
yeah, and that's up on Brian.
Perfect. There's something on the news.
There's a guy who started a company out here
and it made me chuckle.
And he basically is paying homeless people
who normally hold up signs saying,
you know, help me,
or need money,
or whatever.
He's paying them to hold up advertising signs.
And I thought that was such a brilliant idea.
You know, everybody wins.
The advertiser wins.
He wins is the intermediary
and the homeless person has a job.
I thought that was such a brilliant idea.
I don't know what the legality is of it,
but I thought it was,
yeah, just that, brilliant.
Something to be said for that.
And that's going to kind of wrap it up for today.
As I am now,
just about to pull up to the temp office.
Here I'm Brian.
You've successfully driven in with me
and you've guided me into work.
So I appreciate you hanging out with me
as I'm just about the past third street.
So, you know, you've heard of court TVs
gavled the gavled coverage.
This was daily source codes
ignition to shut down coverage.
Okay, let me just roll it right up here.
Parking fun of
a typical San Francisco hippie VW bus.
And that's it.
I will undoubtedly,
if I have batteries, etc,
talk to you tomorrow.
Thanks again.
And,
17, not almost 18 minutes.
All right, take care. Bye-bye.