Thank you.
You got me?
Is it working?
Everybody hear me okay?
Yeah.
Wow.
What an interesting couple of days it's been.
It's been just phenomenal.
I was thinking, well, what can I do?
You know, keynote usually.
I thought keynote's were supposed to be at the beginning of something, but now in
hindsight I'm like, wow, this is pretty interesting to have this tremendous opportunity
to speak with you at the end of a conference.
And I was in my hotel room yesterday or the actually the evening before recording a daily source
code.
And I realized that it was episode 199.
And I thought to myself, wouldn't it be a cool idea to do a source code with you
at being essentially, oh man, I should talk to Steve Jobs about that.
It's actually number 200.
I have multiple computers set up, set up.
If anyone was ever listened to the daily source code, this is the crapplet, so let's hope
that it stays intact for today.
So if you don't mind, I'd like to do a source code with you.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
Delta share a charlie, two zero zero, something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who managed what you can hear since
radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
60 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
And the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm shining into the future.
I guess it is.
I'm curious.
Well, hey everybody, welcome to the daily source code for June 25, 2005.
I got to tell you, I really have a lot of thought going to the source code for today.
And the first thing that freaked me out was, Chris saying that you have an hour and a half to talk.
I was like an hour and a half.
I can't do more than 40 minutes.
That's the set amount of time that I have in me.
Obviously, that's very relevant to this particular spot where we are, this area of Seattle.
Because 40 minutes marker actually came to life.
And I noticed that day liner would not hear certain things in the daily source code.
He'd say, well, I didn't hear that bit.
I'm like, well, why didn't you hear that?
Well, my walk was over.
He would walk around this area right there.
And this walk was 40 minutes.
So I said, well, shoot.
I'll keep it to 40 minutes so you can hear everything I said.
How are you?
My goodness.
We have learned so many exciting things here.
We've seen so many interesting damn announcements.
The web feed, the streaming feed, has been just amazing.
We've been able to sit in your hotel room and listen to the part of it.
Be a part of the conference.
And it still had very much an uncomfortable feel to it.
Which, of course, is a term that was coined for BlahverCon.
And the feeling and the vibe has been good.
What I like about the unconference is kind of the tradition of starting off with a song we all sing together
and Dave, of course, let us with a yellow submarine at the beginning of the conference.
And I felt that maybe we should start a new tradition and we'll do a mashup at the end of the conference.
So this is the four minutes for you to do an aggregator stand.
If you want to check your mail for a second.
And if you want a band, that's okay too.
All right.
Sergeant peppers paradise.
Jimmy James.
On the source code.
Ryan, sin, sin grab the handcha.
He'll be called you a moment in charge of the song.
Trust me.
Sergeant peppers paradise.
Drunk.
man.
He gave up her door.
If you guys believe only our names.
You can newborn to the home.
Call me a moment in charge on your shirt.
It's such an endless life in my soul now
This is how you know they gotta go, they gotta go, they gotta go, they gotta go, they gotta go, they gotta go, they gotta go
Woo!
It's one thing to do today
It's such an endless life in my life
It's again
Clearly also nice photo opportunity to come here
It's such an endless life in my life
It's such a wonderful feeling, it's a wonderful feeling
If I live in the evening, I'll only return to you
I'm a boy and I'll make it round
Let's see if I can sing a song
Let me put you on the scene round
I live in the evening, I'll only return to you
Don't do anything, don't do anything, don't do anything
Alright, well, I prepared it, I forgot
I could go on for a day and listen with stuff like that
It's just fantastic match
Jimmy James, Sergeant Pepper's paradise, the extended edition
It's here for a scobel, for getting everything going there
We'll go on that, we'll go on that, we'll go on that, we'll go on that
Fantastic
In 1969, some of the brightest and most creative musicians got together for their own benefit.
And in the process, it actually changed the world. Some of you in this room were there.
Who else was at Woodstock? Come on. You know, still, see, go more as there.
Dave won't you there? Yeah. In fact, I think I wrote a post that Dave wrote a couple of weeks ago.
They said it felt like this was going to be like Woodstock.
And here we are, 20 years ago today.
Excuse me, it is like Woodstock. It is like Woodstock.
Almost 25 years later.
That is a question.
Yes, I think it is the brown Wi-Fi that you got to be careful of.
So really, we have several hundred of the most talented creative brilliant minds here,
jamming together with new instruments.
And this time, the world is listening instead of a couple million. That is a really big deal.
And if you have had a chance to look at the output of this conference, it is just astounding.
You know, there is thousands of blog posts that are showing up on techno-radi.
Flickr is just overflowing with pictures. Look at yourselves, Christfake.
Look at it. Look at what we have got. Still cameras, video cameras, microphones.
This is just phenomenal. We are the media. It is astounding to me.
The real question is, what message should we be sending to the world from nomads?
I think that message is we want to take back our media.
Not to put it into our hands to hold it, but to put it back into our hearts.
Here is what I have learned so far in the past couple days.
The internet is obviously very powerful.
Powerful as a communications medium, also as a marketing medium.
And we have heard a lot of different opinions and viewpoints on that in the past couple days.
And no matter how hard we try, it is never going to be one or the other.
It is always going to be both.
So, I suggest we just admit that and start embracing it.
It is kind of our version of free love.
Because free love is communications.
It is free speech.
Free love is for users.
It is for developers.
It is for lawyers, politicians, big companies, small companies.
Free love is for the people.
And we need to be continuously enabling that.
And we need to bring in our audience.
That is what I mean when I am talking about the 100 million listener mark.
We have to let people know that it is happening.
And we are getting very close.
People are starting to catch on to it.
So, what is it we have been called here, not the early adopters, but what was the term?
Exactly.
But in order to make this happen, we do need some fuel.
Microsoft, we need some fuel from you.
Apple, we need fuel.
Real, we need fuel, audible, we need fuel.
And we are going to help you sell iPods and music and operating systems.
But please keep listening because we are telling you what we want.
And we need to get some stuff done.
How are we going to get this done?
How are we going to get big companies to work with us?
How are we really going to get this flowing?
Yesterday on the Gilmour Gang, which I thought was a great episode, by the way.
I really enjoyed doing that.
I drew the analogy between the meeting that day one and I had in 2000,
that spurred days creation of the enclosure tag in RSS 2.0.
So I compared that to the, I think it was a television commercial,
or one person is walking on the street with a candy bar.
The other is walking on the street with a jar of peanut butter.
God knows why, look right in the commercial.
They bump into each other and they both have a taste and it's like,
oh, this is a really nice combination.
And of course, that is what became RSS peanut butter cups.
I don't even know that's a real story, but I loved it as an ad.
So the result of that was four years of Dave and I,
basically, sending back huge media files, posting about it,
talking about it, he'd created the first aggregator that understood
and closures.
So we had a great experience amongst the two of us,
but I think after about four years, the peanut butter and
chocolate got a little old, and nothing really happened.
So perhaps a better analogy is what happened in 2004,
I don't take the analogy to the movie big with Tom Hanks.
I wouldn't see that movie.
Dave can be Tom Hanks for this particular example.
The magic really happened when we switched places.
When I, as a user, became a developer,
and Dave was a developer became a user.
And how did that happen?
I don't exactly remember the month, but it wasn't 2004,
and I was receiving new content from Dave.
It wasn't the greatful dead and P3.
It wasn't the quick time movie trailer.
It was something new.
It was interviews.
The Christopher Liden was doing.
And how this is like, wow, here's a guy who knows how to interview
people.
And this is something that's being distributed through this new distribution
mechanism and it's showing up automatically.
And I was delighted.
What was even better I'd have to say is when Dave became so frustrated
that happens once in a while.
It became so frustrated with, well, I can't speak on his behalf,
but I think with just radio and traditional media
that he wanted to make it himself.
And I know that he...
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Well, I wanted to get to a different point about that.
No, no, no, it's going.
No, no.
If you're going to get it, but you've got it.
Make sure Steve was told that he was.
Steve Gilmore was an inspiration to you doing that, Ben.
Correct.
The result was very interesting to me.
The result was, and I'm a professional broadcaster,
the result was these programs or shows or audio blog posts,
whatever the hell you want to call them, these files that would come down
to my desktop automatically that had Dave recording.
And it was fantastic.
It was completely everything was breaking microphones falling.
The recording was on when it should be off.
It was off when it should have been on.
And I loved it.
I was like, my God, this is fantastic stuff.
This is so fucked up.
It's great.
I love it.
I need more of this.
I was totally totally enjoying it.
Yeah.
But I had my own frustrations, because at the time I had about a 45 to an hour
long commute in the morning.
And so the radio user land aggregated would bring down the MP3 files
and put them on my desktop.
And every morning I'd have to go into the folder, find the file,
drag it over iTunes, iTunes, and had to synchronize with my iPod.
And I became tedious.
It doesn't seem like a big deal.
But there were days where I said, I don't have any time.
I mean, I don't have time to go through that sequence.
But yeah, it just takes time.
And I was frustrated.
And I think it was blocked the first second blogger kind of thing.
And we were in Boston.
And I'd asked developers, just I'm sure, as Dave, and I know he did, had asked
other people, how do I record?
What kind of microphone should I use?
And he probably didn't even get any good input or feedback from me on that,
or anyone really.
So he took a whole bunch of time to figure out how to do it.
And by trial and error found a recording program that would work for him,
and a microphone that would work for him.
And so I started to do the same, because I couldn't get anyone to create that
little, really that little piece in the middle.
I said, it seems to me, like, and this is me talking to developers.
It seems to me like we should be able to create something that
looks at an RSS 2.0 feed with enclosures.
Identifies as a new enclosure.
Downloads it and puts it on my iPod.
And every single developer I talk to said, yeah, absolutely real easy.
I'll do it for you tomorrow.
Well, that's the same thing as me saying, yeah, Dave, I'll hook it with the mic tomorrow,
because of course it never happened.
So out of my own frustration, I built that piece that made life easier for me.
And that is, of course, users and developers partying together.
That's really what happened in my mind to make this podcasting to take off.
So we finally reached a point where we were able to swap roles.
And really, we stepped into a different dimension.
It was really unbelievable.
We swap roles.
We can do that now.
We're able to communicate our experiences very quickly and efficiently with each other,
which gives us incredible power.
And I'm sure that I'm not the only person in this room experiencing this.
I'm sure that there are developers here who are having user experiences,
and learning a lot more about that, and users who are having developer experiences.
And technology is really enabling that quite a bit.
So here's what I learned as a developer.
This shit is hard work.
God damn.
It's unbelievable.
And it's writing a language, except you can't flub it.
And you can't say, oh, well, I'll drop a comma here or a colon there because with code writing,
no way, the interpreter says, not going to work.
If you're writing for humans, it's a little more easier.
Humans are, you know, we'll let that kind of pass through.
And wow.
It's an art form.
It is 100% art.
There's so many decisions to be made.
So many different ways to approach a problem.
So many different ways to do something.
I was blown away.
Really, learned so much.
And I hope that there are developers who have learned a lot about users.
I also learned that the really easy shit gets done last.
And I think that's pretty critical.
So for me, it was very easy to say, please take that download
an MP3 file and put it on the iPod.
And because it was easy, I believe it was overlooked and it wasn't done.
And we talk about users and developers.
They work at big companies, too.
Some of you work for big companies are in this room.
And people, big companies, make up the DNA of these big companies.
They're just people.
They're users.
They're developers.
Just people.
And big companies can be really helpful if guided correctly because they have the resources
to create any infrastructure needs that we have.
And because of web logs and podcasts and people and users and developers
who are already together, we're actually getting some stuff that we want.
Look at what happened here at this conference.
RSS going to be built right into Windows.
I mean, even they didn't think that would ever happen.
I think Tuesday or Wednesday, not even a year after the term podcasting was coined by Danny Grigwar,
podcasting support built right into iTunes.
To me, that's just phenomenal.
But we really have to make sure we get even better signal to noise ratio in our conversations,
and then we're really unstoppable.
And we need to do this in order to enable the full power of subscription.
Because that's really what I see going on here.
This power of subscription.
That's really changing everything.
The whole models are turned around.
By the way, it's the dream of mainstream media.
They've always wanted something by appointment.
Radio by appointment.
That's why you hear on the radio today.
Hey, tune in tomorrow.
Don't go anywhere.
I'll be right back.
Because we've got to bring them back in.
Make sure that they tune in.
Now all we have to say is, hey, stay subscribed.
Very, very powerful stuff.
So before we can really show the world where the parties act,
we need to, I think, fix a few things.
I think these are relatively simple.
Let's get one click subscriptions working now.
And just like the internet is going to be for marketing and communications,
there's going to be some formats that are crossover.
So there's RSS, there's Adam.
There's MP3, there's WMA, there's AAC.
I think we kind of all see the formats.
I was very happy to hear the aggregators speak.
I'm not quite sure who said it, but someone said,
we're Switzerland.
Switzerland is neutral.
Very expensive place to live, by the way, Switzerland is.
But if that's the commitment, the aggregator developers are making,
then Shapo Baha hats off to you because I think that you really hold the key to a lot of this stuff.
So you eat Adam feeds, you aren't eat RSS feeds.
Can you eat the feed, colon slash, slash one subscription,
can you eat the Adam element subscription?
I think so.
I think we just need to say, okay, we have a couple multiple, several multiple formats.
Let's just implement it all and move on.
So we can just go because the users out there are audience,
people who want to listen, who want to watch, who want to read,
and who also want to write and want to create audio and video.
They're ready for us, but we just have to fix a few of those things to help them along.
Metadata, got some good work going on, some great namespaces for RSS,
media RSS is one, Microsoft lists, Apple is doing a namespace for podcasting for their iTunes.
We really need to get working on attention.xml.
If you don't know what that is, check the show notes, they'll be a link to Steve Wilmore,
who will be very happy to explain that.
It's critical we get some of this stuff going.
And also let's address the bandwidth issue now before it becomes a real problem.
I had some time to think about what we discussed yesterday.
And I think it is time to make a corner turn on PTP, particularly for podcasting.
So until something else comes along that we all agree makes sense,
I fully intend to implement Bitcoin and support it, and I hope you all do too.
And I have some ideas and I look forward to working with the aggregator developers and the podcast developers on making that work.
Because I think we can do it, and if we all bond together, then we can really make some cool stuff happening.
It's going to be critical, because the experiences are going to start to be great, very, very quickly,
as listeners come in and we just don't have the bandwidth to serve them.
Just pass the pay for the bandwidth to serve them, it's probably even worse.
So these things I think are really simple with the group of people that I've seen here that I've met here,
I've spoken to many of you, what I find fascinating is that I know everyone of you.
We either corresponded through audio feedback or a project podcast or a regular weblog.
And you know a lot about me too, it's kind of interesting.
I asked him, you know, how's Patricia? How's your mom? How's the dog? How's the cat? How's the beautiful man? It's absolutely beautiful.
I think we'll see some amazing changes happen in the next six months.
I'm comfortable with even predicting something like that.
The music industry is I think part of the media that we're about ready to take back into our hearts very quickly.
And here's why. First of all, the tools for the so-called professionals absolutely know different from the tools they so-called amateur's use.
You're using pro tools, you're using audition, you're using garage branch, and the jagger uses garage man.
So there can be no difference with the output.
If you're talented, you're going to have the same quality as someone who, like a big jagger.
Only you don't have the same type of push out into the world.
It's not the distribution, by the way, because we've had distribution for a long time.
People are creating their music, their artwork, and they're putting up on MP3s, putting up on sites like garageband.com or MP3tunes.com.
We also have the sales mechanism already in place. My God, we've got another piece that's already there.
CD Baby, iTunes, I think, has like 11,000 pod save music tracks.
They don't call it pod safe, but we do.
So that's there. What are we missing?
What is the key link in the chain that we've been missing?
Well, if you look at the music industry as the way it is today, there's the awesome power of promotion through radio.
Although that is also kind of diminished a little bit.
Radio is really sunk into packaging and marketing and playlists.
You know, because they have very defined set of time in traditional broadcast media.
But when is the last time you heard a disjockey?
Excuse me, Sensei O.
When is the last time you heard a disjockey go, I love this band.
I'm going to play this fucking record every single day until you love them too and go to other concerts and buy their t-shirts.
You don't hear that anymore.
You hear?
Five, thirty-five, everybody how you're doing is zero and all the other.
So an amazing thing happened last year when I stumbled across some music from a band from New York,
four girls who've studied a Juleard and they're called the Lissivia's Bitties.
And I love their music.
Certainly not something mainstream that would make it onto Jack FM or whatever the formats are.
And it was nice about it.
I just sent him an email.
I said, hey, can I play one of your songs on my podcast?
Well, sure.
We own the rights to that.
It's ours.
You know, we've created it.
Go ahead.
We'd love for you to play something.
An amazing thing happened.
After I played it, I got an email from Leon Westover, the singer for the band.
She says, Adam, we sold like 200 CDs in one day.
And when you're selling CDs at 10 bucks a pop,
you're putting 90% of the profit into your pocket,
that becomes rent money.
That becomes pretty significant.
Now they're on a 10 day tour.
You know, they're selling out 5,600 room, a seat rooms.
It's fantastic.
Just,
I think it was last week.
I stumbled across another song,
a guy named Rob Costlow.
He's in Los Angeles.
And when it comes to picking hits,
this is something really big in the radio industry.
You know, you had these music directors and, you know,
they award winning, billboard award winning,
music director because they know how to pick the hits.
When really, it's just repetition.
You know, if you have a song that has what they call a hook,
a catchy hook,
if you repeat it over and over and over again,
you're eventually going to learn that hook.
You're going to learn that song.
You're going to sing it.
You're going to recognize it.
You might even start to like it.
In fact, I think you probably will start to like it.
That's why your commercial jingles work well.
If they're repeated continuously.
So, Rice, Rooney,
the San Francisco treat,
we all know that one.
And I'd like to teach the world to sing,
who knows that.
That's Coca-Cola song.
So, you go to your iPod and say,
can't wait to put the Rice Rooney song on my iPod?
No, you know.
But you know it because of the repetition.
I think that's a waste of time, really,
to get someone to know something.
What's much more effective,
but what's happening now, is podcasts.
There's our listening to each other.
So, when I played, actually, I'll play a little bit of it,
because it's a really beautiful song.
When I played this particular track,
I got emails from all over the world from people saying,
I want to play that song on my podcast.
I loved it.
Rob Costa sent me an email yesterday.
He's been booked now in thousands-seat room gigs.
He's been asked to do movie scores.
It's just phenomenal what is happening.
And why?
Just because we're passing off this information,
we're passionate about what it is,
and we're sending people straight over to the creator of the music,
and he's able to sell it and promote his music online.
This is for a couple of seconds.
Here's really beautiful.
Thank you.
Isn't that pretty?
Yes, absolutely beautiful.
So, here's just a guy with a keyboard,
recording on whatever tools that came pre-packaged with his PC.
I knew you know if he used a Mac or PC,
and we're able to share that.
We're able to actually generate
revenue for him.
Attention for him.
He's able to go out of the world and continue with his art.
I think that's extremely powerful.
Sorry, Rob.
I'm going to stop there.
So, I think our message to the world,
what I would hope,
is that we are taking back our media,
taking it back to its roots,
where it belongs,
in the hearts and the minds of the people,
and we're doing that to the power of subscription.
So, I'm going to let you off really early,
because my podcast is only supposed to be 40 minutes.
We're just about there.
I do want to thank some people personally
for making not only this conference possible,
but for what is happening,
we are truly, truly seeing something very special
that's happening,
and make sure you get your message out.
Everyone's got their tools with them,
to make sure you prepare the people that listen
or read or watch whatever you're doing,
that it's coming,
and that they can participate,
and they are absolutely welcome.
So, first of all,
I'd like to thank all the developers
for all the work that they've been doing.
I'd like you to give me a big hand.
I'd like to thank Dave Winner for his work on RSS,
OPML, weblogs, podcasting.
We don't always agree on everything,
but I respect you,
and I do love you.
They've won it.
Thank you.
Robert Scoville,
we're all your Robert.
Stand up for a second.
Not only should you be running Microsoft,
you actually already do.
And then finally, before I get out of here,
Chris and Ponzi, ladies and gentlemen,
what a fantastic job they've done.
Come on out.
All right, that's the Daily Source Code for today,
June 25th, 2005.
We'll see you all on Next Source Code,
and at the next NomeDex.
Thank you very much.
We'll see you all on Next Source Code,
and we'll see you all on Next Source Code,
and you all on Next Source Code,
Okay we've done a lot of things for this week.
Bro what are you doing with this world?
I'm just thinking,
Right on.
So anyway, again, we're actually wonderful.
I have a glad and keep experience that ever 200.
Number 200.
Yeah.
Twenty-two hundred, whichever one is split over.
Anyway, anything else?
That's it.
Okay.
We're going to talk a lot under the name.
I just said, just wrap up again.
We're going to come up here and one of my long-side games, just tell me we're going
to have to relax for a little while and talk about what we're going to be.
I'm going to say that.
You