Source Code, February 28th, 2005.
Autistic, it's Adam Curry.
Yes indeed, it is the last day of February.
The power of the door.
Everybody, how you doing? It's been a while, but I'm back.
Back at the cottage. This is your deadly source code.
Today is Monday, it's the 20th, February 2005.
I'm Adam Curry, bringing you the best when it comes to mash-ups,
pod save music and all kinds of crap about podcasting.
Oh, then again, is it really crap?
Hey, you know, we got some shit going on.
Boy, it's going to be back right now.
I'm actually, I'm all alone in the cottage.
Patricia's off for a two-day piz trip, yep.
You know, I'm home and she leaves.
She'll be back Wednesday, so I'm holding down the fort here,
keeping the home fires burning.
Christina's off at school.
It is 10 minutes to 12, and I am so ready to bring you another source code.
It's great to be back in the big green chair.
Got my smoke here, and a little bit of tea.
That's right. Nothing usual, sir.
I kind of sensed out, I have to be quite honest.
Maybe it's time to change the,
the bylink on curry.com.
Maybe it should start selling something else.
By the way, I have sold double digits in the sensio machine arena.
That means I've sold my latest check.
My latest check is 23 sensio coffee machines,
countless coffee pods.
Somehow the stuff seems to be working, you know?
It really does.
You talk about something on your podcast.
You make sure that you have a way to sell something on the website.
People actually do come back and buy it.
It's great. It's what we call a business model.
And boy, there's a lot of them floating around these days, unbelievable.
It seems like everyone's announcing a network or a hosting solution
or something of that matter, it is really,
it's just catch and fire ever since the New York Times started talking about it.
We're all talking about how to make money with podcasting.
And we've actually talked about that before.
We've talked about commercialization.
I think that was three or four podcasts to go when I was in San Francisco.
Today, actually, I want to talk a little bit more about what producers are looking for,
what we need, because I think that before we get to commercialization
and selling advertising or sponsorships or underwriting or subscription,
something else I've been hearing a lot about.
People looking for avenues to make their podcasts for pay only.
For instance, rumor is that audible.com is going to be doing something which would make total sense
because at least on the Macintosh, I'm pretty sure it must work on Windows as well,
otherwise it would be pretty silly, but audible allows you to subscribe to programs
to X amount per month and they, well, they don't automatically show up on your iPod.
You have to go into audible.com and download them, but they do have a billing mechanism,
so that makes sense.
So I'm sure that lots of people will be interested in providing their content that way.
Campy too long before Apple opens up iTunes for exactly the same reason.
So I think there's going to be some interesting stuff coming up in the next couple of,
well, couple of months, maybe even couple of weeks.
In fact, I was going to play this a little bit later on on the show, but mine is
well hit it now.
Welcome to the Bitter's Bill.
Hi, Sam class.
My daddy.
This is 2005, the year of the podcast.
I can't be the first person to say it, but you know what's true.
This podcast thing is going to be gigantic.
Oh yeah.
You know, there's one thing that people consistently say to me when they know that I'm,
that I'm the guy who does the daily source code.
And by the way, it was pretty cool to be in the United States where I hadn't really been for a long time,
and so many people know about podcasting, know about the source code,
know about what's going on.
It's just, it's really been pretty much endearing,
but consistently, no matter where I go.
Someone will always say, dude, where do you get those mashups?
And my answer usually is, I get them from Pimp Daddy'sit.
And email showed up this morning.
Yo Curry, here's another track to kick start this new week.
I heard on the daily source code that people ask you where you get your mashups.
As a collector, I can show you in your listeners some cool sites that you can link to on your weblog,
so people could explore the wonderful world of mashups themselves.
No worries.
The special ones are really hard to find, so there's always enough of this source code.
This track, the one I know about the playboy, was made by Fuego.
One of the best in this kind, also one of Sid's personal favorites.
This is a mashup between Janet Jackson and Therapy.
Many masses of, I want you back.
This is one of the best ones he's ever heard of,
and you can find that at Fuego.nl, of course.
This is listed in the show notes, but I'll spell it for you.
Curry style, Papa Hotel, Echo Uniform, Golf, Oscar, Oscar, dot, and L.
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar,
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar,