Delta Sierra Charlie 1-9-4.
The Bayer Court of the State of California for the County of Santa Barbara Santa Maria division.
The people of the State of California planted it versus Michael Joe Jackson defendant.
Case number 1-1-3-3-6-0-3. Count 1 verdict.
We're the jury in the above entitled case by the defendant not guilty of conspiracy as charged in count one of the indictment.
And we're not in the program because there's no reason to reach out and you should see.
Give me a lot of love and feel the hope that we've been waiting for
We love you, we love you, we love you, we love you
We love you, we love you, we love you, we love you, we love you
And you don't see it all
And we go
Oh
And we're doing great
We'll stand and shine and jump over us
We're running like that
Into the morning there's too much to go
Oh wow
It's like a different way
Brothers, oh, you've never heard of me
I'm great on the way
And you're losing it so jobably
Tell me the heart
You're the real son, Javier
And you're the hero of your day
Everybody be glad
Because the sun is shining, Javier
And everybody wake up
Into the morning and into a happy day
Hello, hello
It's like a different way
I'm in this night
In your world
We don't sweat, we be free somehow
We're in love with you
Make sure the heart that we've done and see
We're talking to you
Brothers, oh, you've never heard of me
You're the real one
And you're the real one
You're the real son
And you're the real hero of your day
And you're the real one
Dad gets a shameful life
At a curry
He came with him
And I'm Carrie
He's old way
Into the heart
Movyingève
From when I'm Carrie
Through past them, three tombs started.
His name is Anon Kari.
And bow him, vision's blind.
The old tombs died.
And the three tombs died.
His name is Anon Kari.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Hey, everybody. It's Tuesday. It is June 14, 2005.
Yes indeed, not guilty on all counts.
You think I want to talk about that today?
Yeah, I think so.
Oh man, first of all, I get to say I told you so.
We'll just get that out of the way right now.
We'll be talking about Michael Jackson, the verdict, and what it means to America and the world in general,
because it does have significance.
It is about one thirty-five in the afternoon on Tuesday here in Kari Cottage,
bringing you the data source code.
Oh man, it was busy this morning.
We've got up and actually Christina was not feeling well.
You're going to love this.
She yesterday she had to take a cake to school as a part of a food technology.
Yes, it's a technology now, cooking.
But it's a very creative school.
So she made her ask-out cake.
I have to post a picture in the show now.
She'll love what this thing looked like.
But she got some red food coloring die on her skin.
And she immediately broke out in an allergic reaction.
Which was, it's kind of scary in a way.
You know, it's just a red die on her hand.
And then of course she rubbed her face.
And she got, you know, a face star to swell up a little bit.
And she's never had anything like that before.
She didn't feel too well last night.
So we kept her home this morning from school because she just wasn't feeling good.
Although a mac and miraculous recovery.
Because tonight, of course, is the wiser concert at Brickson Academy in London.
And I've got tickets thanks to Aaron from Bitterman Circle.
So I'm going to have to go to the gym and on a feeling sweaty and mucky and pumped up.
But ready to bring you an awesome daily store's code with some pod safe music on the way.
Of course, I'm talking about Michael Jackson.
And did I mention it?
This is the show where we just love to bring you mashups?
Well, check this one out.
Boulevard of Broken Dreams.
Green Day versus Oasis versus Travis versus M&M.
And I hope you had sent it in on the daily source code.
Brick us, but it's only me and I walk along.
Two days going to be the day that they've got to throw it back to you.
I want this empty sheet on the boulevard of Broken Dreams.
Where the city sleeps in the middle of the night walk along.
But by now you should have somehow realized what you got to do.
I walk along, leaving everybody feels a way to go.
I'll show you how to make shadows all in one of what's beside me.
Make shadows all the way to the only thing that's needed.
Sometimes I'll tell you where someone will find me.
Two days will not walk along.
If you don't come back someday.
I walk along, leaving everybody feels a way to go.
I'll show you how to make shadows all the way to the only thing that's needed.
Back then the weather's on the street that the fire ringing out is out.
We'll have our broken songs, Green Day vs. Oasis vs. Travis vs. M&M. Ed Hagopian sent a whole mess of mash-ups to
mash-up at podshow.com. Thank you very much Ed. Very much appreciated. Love here. I love that Oasis
tracking. The lyric that gets me is a backbeat word is on the street that the firing your heart
is out. Man, that's awesome. Everybody, here we go. Let's break down for a second here. Lots to talk
about today. Of course, I have plenty to say about the Michael Jackson verdict that coming up in
just a little bit on the source code. Thank you very much for subscribing and checking us out. Let's see a
couple of... First of all, did I mention how much I enjoy doing this show every single day? I really
love it. What makes it so cool is the feedback that I get. It comes in through email, through MP3s,
people on the street. It's really nice. Thank you. We talked about blindcasters yesterday,
about accessibility on the Mac, accessibility on Windows, and we played a little bit
from Shelley Brisbane yesterday, and I got to several comments about that. Here's one. I just
been listening this from Wayne Taylor, by the way. Shelley Brisbane has said that Windows doesn't
include a screen reader, as far as I'm aware, the Microsoft narrator has been included with Windows
since Windows 2000. Not knowing much about screen reader applications. I can't say if the screen
readers any good or not, however, there is one out that just thought I'd like to get this point out
there on the show. Okay, so apparently, and I got a couple of emails about that. Now, I don't know
if this Microsoft narrator is worth its salt, so I'd love to hear about that. Let's see. Jerry
Hallithen says Apple is once again made a cutting edge move by including a built-in screen
reader or screen reader in OS X Tiger. Windows users have to buy an additional screen reader.
Well, apparently, that may or may not be true. A problem is, while Apple encourages developers
to follow their guidelines for making apps accessible, Apple themselves have it followed their
own guidelines. As a member of the blind community using Apple's voiceover, that's standard in OS X
Tiger. Now, not having access to iTunes is so incredibly disappointing. I love Apple,
I've always used their products, but in this case, they're falling short of their own goals.
Hey, next time you have Steve's ear, how about mentioning the fact that iTunes is still
inaccessible? I'm sure he hasn't a clue. Well, I'm sure he's listening, so he heard that.
Let's see what else do we have here? Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. If you've never heard the
skinny on sports, the fastest 10 minutes on your iPod, it's brought to you my Matt and Andy
Skin, who were up in up in Canada, and Andy Skin sent an email to me and to Ron and to Brian,
our operations officer at Pod Show, just some stuff. But at the end, he just kind of put a little
PS there, which I thought was interesting. He said, I officially passed my PhD in medicine,
medicinal, and medical science today. So I guess that makes me doctor skin now, which indeed
does sound a bit like a porn star. Congratulations, dude. I'd rather wanted to listen to someone
you don't know, talk about things you don't care about in a way that hangers,
offense, and probably upsets you. Oh, my, yes. Well, you're in luck. You can listen to the
starcast, a podcast about politics, entertainment, technology, humor, stupid bits, and lots and lots
of swearing. It's like the entire internet in one easily downloaded file for your listening
convenience. You're listening to a starcast. I'm pulling yours for that,
I'll see you all for this a bit more interesting. Check out the latest wildly acclaimed episode
of the starcast on the web at starcast.com. What's the, uh, I love your website, your starcast,
are all new to your podcast, um, all the podcast, uh, what's your internet, how I care.
Yeah, woohoo! The starcast for slightly the reason why you shouldn't let just anyone produce a show.
Holy crap!
Ah, Joe, content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
This is Rob from podcast 4011, and this is the strangest of the strange podcast review.
In today's review, we'll be looking at the daily download by Chris Rockwell. The concept
behind this podcast is rather simple. Chris records his podcast each day, while he's going to the
bathroom, hence the name, the daily download. This is truly toilet humor. But Chris doesn't
in a very, I hate to use the word tasteful manner. He mixes in good comedy and original ideas
including poop experiments, where you the listener get to send in ideas for Chris to do
different experiments. The sound quality on this podcast is excellent. Sometimes,
too excellent if you've listened to the podcast you know what I mean. This podcast is definitely
not for everyone. It's not for those that get grossed out by bodily functions. But if you're looking
for humor, this is an excellent podcast. You can find this podcast at apeboymonkeygirl.com.
That's apeboymonkeygirl.com. Now, it's not the number one downloaded podcast on the internet,
but Chris is definitely making a push towards number two. Until the next time, this is Rob at podcast
4011 reminding you to listen different. Here's some rather appropriate music to leave you
with.
Got to love that smell.
4011 review, strangest of the strange review of the daily download. Good feature, actually.
I guess it would make sense for anyone who appeared on the podcast 4011.com podcast to get a review
and that to be distributed and people can play that in the show. It was digging that very much.
Excuse me, if you have a promo by the way, just fire it off to submit at podshow.com.
Happy to play it. Just send it off to us. That's really all you got to do.
Some podsafe tunes right now. I'm going to slow the mood zone just a little bit.
This is something different for the source code.
It's a new age style solo piano piece. Rob Costlow and I do.
I really like that. I almost want to put words to it. Then again, I think I'll be great for a movie.
Of course, it's easier to write words to make a movie.
I like to do something where it's really, really nice. Sorry about the drop out there.
Just another little glitch. Not doing it on the on the crapplet today on the on the cast blaster.
I figured I'd just use this set up. I didn't have a lot of time to reroute all the wiring,
so I'm just leaving it the way it is. Okay, time to talk about Michael Jackson. All right.
So as listeners to this podcast, I have been saying that Michael Jackson is innocent. I've been saying
that from day one, I've been very outspoken about it. And there you go. He got not guilty verdict on every single
count that was brought against it. Now, why do I? Why was I so sure of this? First of all, I've met him.
And if anything, the guy is asexual. I know that is very hard to understand, but some people just are.
Some people just aren't thinking about that. Some people just doing other things with their life.
And just choose to be that way. And I think Michael Jackson is one of those people. You can kind of feel it.
You know, if you're in a room with people, you can feel what they're, you can kind of feel their aura.
And even though when I met him, there were tons of kids around. I think I told the story before.
I was in the studio. He was there. How we Mendel was there with just tons of kids. And of course,
how he was doing all those voices and the kids were loving it. And it really was just a fun atmosphere with
kids running a boys and girls, by the way. All kinds of kids running around. You can just kind of feel it.
You know, it's just a good, relaxed vibe, a good atmosphere, but nothing at all sexual. And that just did not
emanate from the man. Secondly, I know what it is to be be raided and raked over the calls by the press,
not to that level, not at all. I've never been accused of anything like that. But I've had accusations.
And once they show up in the press, um, everyone copies it. In fact, let me make a note. I should
make a note to my copy paste culture essay that I wrote a couple of years ago on a copy paste culture.
I'll put that in the show and know it's on the daily source code.com and www.curry.com.
So you can read that again because it really is that way. And it's not just in mainstream
media. It's everybody. It's how we learn, it's how we grow. We copy things. We paste them.
We emulate our heroes. And when it comes to mainstream media, if it's written up somewhere,
and if it's okay for a major publication to call someone wacko, jacko, or the gloved one,
or any other derogatory comment, then, you know, it kind of gets copy pasted. Everyone says,
oh, okay, I can kind of do that. And it becomes a meme and it becomes fun to do.
Um, but it's, um, it's not right. And it's very, very hurtful and very,
it potentially very, very damaging. Now, is Michael Jackson, um, is he, is he off-scot free?
Did it? Is everything okay? No, he'll be fucked up for the rest of his life because of this.
You can't trust anyone. Once you've been in a courtroom and you see your former employees,
talking shit and you see people lying. And now, now, look at television for a moment. And this
is really important. We talk about this. So after the not guilty verdict came in and actually,
I was upstairs in the studio last night and Patricia said, oh, they're about to hand down a verdict.
And I said, really? And yeah, so I checked Google and Google said, yeah, 145 p.m.
You know, they're going to come with a verdict. So, of course, it was 215 p.m. p.s. t. when the verdict
finally came. And, um, it was funny because I could see I was skipping through the channels.
Now, every channel had, uh, was bringing the audio live. Everyone had their spin micers talking
about it. And it was all about, you know, so what happens? What do you go to jail?
Will you immediately be, you know, will you be able to go home first? Can you get his toothbrush?
You know, and all that stuff. And once the not guilty verdict was in the first thing that
almost everybody said on American television, I can receive plenty of that over here, was, oh,
not guilty doesn't mean innocent. And that is the most disgusting thing I have ever heard.
Because you're supposed to be innocent until proven guilty. So to say, well, he wasn't proven
guilty, which me doesn't mean he's not innocent is fucked up. And you really go against everything
that the United States stands for guilty until, uh, not guilty. Fuck, I can't even say it now.
Innocent until proven guilty. So that means not guilty is innocent. That is the equation.
There's nothing more nothing less. But he has been raked over the calls. And, you know,
we really, as Americans, I'll count myself as an American. We really should be extremely ashamed
of what happened here. Um, the, we all ran with it. I didn't personally, um, but it was tempting.
It's tempting to make jokes. It's tempting to go along with the flow. But we've really, really
hurt someone. And there's no way you can make up for it. Of course, now, uh, I, in, in the gym, I saw
that MTV and VH1 and everyone's now playing Michael Jackson videos. And it's the evolution of
Michael Jackson. It's like you're, you're, you're hypocrites. All of you hypocrites. Just nasty.
There's only a couple people who said Michael Jackson is innocent. Um, that I know of. And
Harold Orovera, okay, put me in, uh, in a box with him. That's fine. But, um, this, this was, this
really bothered me. I'm so happy, um, that, uh, that Michael was, uh, acquitted, essentially, of every single
of these accusations. And it's, uh, interesting because Christina said, uh, my 14 year old daughter
said last night, she said, you know, it's really the same everywhere you go. So this goes outside
of the U.S. She said, if you're different, then people don't understand you and they tend to
put you in a corner and make fun of you. And it's about, you know, being different. And then I thought
myself, wow, that's, um, first of all, you know, she feels that she's different in a way. And of
course she is, she doesn't have, I'd say, quote, the traditional parents or quote, the traditional
lifestyle or quote, the traditional or normal upbringing. But what is normal? What, when you say someone's
different, different from what am I the same as my neighbor? Are you the same as your neighbor? Are you,
is your family the same way? Do you have the same issues? Probably not. So what is normal? And then
it hit me. Of course, it's whatever television says is normal. And I'm not talking just about
sitcoms. I'm talking about whatever is portrayed on television. And that comes from news outlets,
it comes from predominantly from commercials. That's really where it comes from. And just spinning
a little bit further on that. Of course, it's smoked a joint by then. So I was really into it.
And I was talking to Patricia and Christina, you know, so we're, we're, we're philosophizing a
philosophizing. Yes, we're philosophizing about this. And I was saying, you know, as as a helicopter
pilot, I can really imagine a mini helicopter view going up maybe not too high, 200, 250 feet
and flying over all the houses. And just remove the roofs for a second in your imagination here.
Because I know you can see it right. You're 250 feet above a city or a town. You're on city. Just
imagine that and you're flying over your house on a couple of their homes. Now the roofs are off.
And what will you see every single night? You'll see all of these families doing the one thing
that is considered normal, namely watching television. You're sitting there and you're being programmed.
You're being programmed by anyone who has the frequency, anyone who has the channel. They are
telling you what is normal. Are they doing this on purpose? No, it's a game. What they do is they
tell you, this is the way you should be. And this is the product you have to buy to be normal.
And by the way, look at the commercials. Look at what you're brain. This is really red pill blue pill
stuff. Look at what your brain is taking in. Look at that information for a second. It's unbelievable.
And by the way, everything is sexually related in commercials and advertising. All of it's about,
you know, you won't get laid. That's basically, you won't get laid if you don't buy this product.
We're being programmed. That's why podcasting is so wonderful. That's why web logs are so
wonderful. That's why we're trying to pull this into the mainstream. Get some of, let's change advertising.
You know, let's bring some of that advertising into our space and we can change it. I really
truly believe that. And there will be enough diversity that no single person or no organization
can hold the key to programming your brain. And this is the time when I do it once every half
year where I say, please take the XN TV experiment. The XN TV experiment, I don't want to, of
course, put a link to it in the show notes is a wonderful written experiment that you can take
at home that will help you understand what television is doing to you and doing to your brain.
And you're not relaxing when you're sitting in front of the TV. Your brain is an overdrive.
It's filling in blanks. It's making assumptions. It is taking assumptions and putting those
in the places where it's potentially even dangerous. So, you know what I should do? I should
do an audio version of the XN TV experiment. That's something I'm going to work on for this week.
And all in all, if you really want to understand Michael Jackson, there's one very simple way.
It's just go listen to his art.
Looking around in the lost and found at my heart, no one understands.
Such an imagery means. So, you've learned my fate to compensate for the child.
I've never known.
You've seen my child in my heart. I'm searching for that wonder in my ears that hurts
and that picture's dreams. I'm requesting and being on the ground before you touch me.
Try hard to love me. Look with me, your heart, the internet.
You've seen my child in my heart.
So
You won't change dreams that bring
Because I love such unTMITRIED things.
It's been life made to compensate for the child.
I've never known.
Have you seen my childhood?
I was searching for that one therein, my youth,
like a fantastic one.
Stories to share, dreams I would dare.
Why do you love me?
Why do you change me?
Why do you want to love me?
The pain for you.
I pay.
Have you seen my childhood?
Before you judge me, try hard to love me.
Okay.
Michael Jackson, that's the theme from Free Willy.
Thank you very much, Mike from Cas Blaster for sending that into me.
All right, everybody.
Let me just backslash on the Michael Jackson stuff.
Hey, I'm Bolette.
It's time for the hit.
With Yarn Poles.
Hey, everybody.
This is hit test number 43.
Again, recorded with a bed of 14 of Cas Blaster.
Right on.
Let's start right away.
Three intros and three answers.
This is intro.
Number one.
Oh, yeah, like that one.
That would be one of these nights by the Eagles.
One of my favorites.
And this is number two.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I love these.
That's, um, yellow.
Don't bring me down.
Two for two, I think.
And the final one is always number three.
Yes, that would.
Yeah.
Of course.
How appropriate is that?
The girl is mine, Michael Jackson, and Paul McCartney.
I think I got them all three this time, y'all.
Okay, times up.
They're all pretty easy, I guess.
So I guess you'll have three out of three.
And this is answer number one.
The Eagles.
One of these nights.
And check.
One for the Gipper.
One of these.
And these nights.
Oops.
Should've been using cast glass.
One of these crazy old nights.
We're gonna find one.
One with red screen.
One is mine.
Love it.
Yeah.
The Eagles.
Answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
The Eagles.
Don't bring me down.
You got them running all my life.
Everybody!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Who the weekman!
I tell you what's wrong, big boy,
and get up and go!
Don't repeat it!
I answer number two, the electric lights,
Auguster!
And this is the final answer.
Michael Jackson and Paul McCarty, the girl is mine.
Every night you watch when I'm in the dreams.
Save that she's yours, not mine.
On the Friday evening only one.
Really just a waste of time.
The girl is mine.
Answer number three.
Well, that's it for this very quick hit test.
Check out the hit test podcast at
gmail.com.
And feedback is welcome at hittest at gmail.com.
Well, I don't know how you did well.
See you next time.
I guess next week for number 44.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
Young Bullet bringing you the hit test.
Very regularly on this podcast.
The daily source code.
I love it.
I just hear no songs.
Really gets me in a great mood.
Let's see what we can do.
About 40 minutes per week.
Oh my God.
So tonight we're off.
Around 17 we'll be leaving the cottage.
Christina and her friend Ellie.
We're going to go off to see Weezer at Bricks and Academy.
I decided that I'm just going to drive myself.
It's only 47 clicks to get there.
Although you drive half of it through the best parts of London.
So I'll take along the I River just in case we decide to do some
signs.
Sound seeing on the way there after the show.
Just the show will be good.
Just to get some feedback.
So let the girls jam her on about how much they love you.
As always, your submissions to the show are welcome.
And this also goes for the pod show on serious.
Send it off to submit at podshow.com.
That's for your promo.
Don't forget podcast and for your pod save music.
It's podsafe podshow.com.
And for your mashups.
Mashup at podshow.com.
And of course there's daily source code.com.
We can find the podcast feed.
Also on daily source code.com is archives and the most recent show.
Of course, www.curry.com for comments.
All you can find show notes there as well obviously.
Oh man, I'm feeling good.
What a little gym workout can do for you.
And in one week from now, I'll be off to the states again.
Got some more beers happening there.
So that's very exciting.
Your feedback direct to me out on thecurry.com.
You can also sing your MP3.
That would be much appreciated.
Okay, everybody.
I'll be back tomorrow for the Wednesday edition of the daily source code,
which as you know is new music Tuesday, we do it on Wednesdays here.
Take care, everybody.
I'll see you tomorrow. Bye-bye.
Another podshow podcast.
Stick it in your ear.