Delta Sierra Charley 2-6-0
You're dating?
Yeah!
Friday Friday!
One, two, three!
Good morning!
There are no secrets!
Only information you don't get out of here!
Adam Curry!
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hey everybody!
It's Thursday, October 14, 2005.
And hello!
I'm doing it for Mother!
I come to you from Curry Cottage, direct from the UK from the affluent suburb of Gilford and Surrey.
It is the daily source code.
Everything seems a little bit soft today.
So just a minute, let me see.
I'll forget my own soft.
I'm just looking at the audio.
Let's try it this way.
Awesome!
Come back!
And it's busy!
My sisters here, although I have to admit, I don't think I'm going to go around the show today.
She just left with...
Oh, I know what the problem is.
This is interesting.
Let me add some volume in.
Watch your ears, okay?
There we go.
That's better.
A little adjustment on the mega set.
It's so hard rebuilding three computers at once.
It's biggest challenge at my professional career.
It is indeed Friday.
And what a couple of days I had.
Hopefully you heard yesterday's source code recorded in the middle of the night.
Wednesday night in Amsterdam.
Everything went very well, though the business crap that I was dealing with.
Thank you for acquiring.
In fact, it went exceptionally well.
Exactly the way I planned it, although it took much longer than expected.
So, yes, there's flight back.
I actually had an easy jet book and had a couple of different options.
It lasted so long that I had to call the Wing Commander.
Which meant I had the most awesome flight back in the most implement weather you can imagine.
I am actually...
I am sea conditions, tens and London radar guiding me the entire way.
I felt like...
I felt like Jodie on almost.
I was flying with the big boys, you know, separated by only a couple thousand feet from...
from 747s and stuff like that.
Love that fly.
All right.
To kick it off.
You're Friday.
You want to crank this one up.
It's Bono versus Bono.
I hope you know who Bono is.
You two and let's Zep.
On the source code.
You need...
Ooh!
Baby, I love you.
Not too stressed.
Back to school now.
Wait there, instead.
I'll hold it in your meals.
I don't want to give you my love.
One whole hour ago.
Two whole hour ago.
In the high and winter crossing and rain
See each other natives and the souls on to your bed
From the fire down the land, the rain on the sky
See a face of fear rushing down the land
From the fire down the land
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let
go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
let's go, let's go, let's go, we are all prepared, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, right, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Bono versus Bono. Let's up on YouTube. I don't know. It's down a little. I guess let's
up on always sound a little messy almost, but yet it isn't. It's a good one, good
mash up digging it. I might even have time for another mash up today if we if we
really want to get the weekend into full swing. It's crappy weather today. It was, well,
as I said yesterday, it was just horrible. We had about 800 feet cloud ceiling at
Fair Oaks, which is my local airport. I just got to tell you, this was the first full
trip where really from the moment we took off to the literally the moment we landed. I
was under radar control and flying on instruments. And now I'm really starting to
understand the the difficulty of instrument flying. You have to imagine or you
have to know that when you fly into clouds or inclement weather and you can't see
anything it's just basically white or gray and it's all it's surrounded you. You'll
probably think within a few seconds, I feel like the plane is drifting towards the
left. You know, I've got a compensate. We're actually maybe rolling over right and
banking it already 30 degrees and you won't even know it. This is of course what
happened to Kennedy Jr. Because he didn't have enough experience. I guess it's a
vertigo thing. And you get into clouds and if you don't have any experience with
this, if you haven't practiced this over and over again within 35 seconds, I guarantee
you'll be wondering what that boat is doing in the clouds because you'll be upside down
flying straight into the drink. Of course, I was crossing the English channel, but it was
a lot of fun. And I got the hang of it. I can do it. But it's very, very, very intense.
But it's cool, you know, and you're being led and they tell you, okay, turn left
240 and you know, so you turn left and keep your altitude if you may taint the
altitude at all times, of course. And then, you know, they'll send you down and then
you break through the clouds and there it is. There's the airport right in front of you.
It's just the, ah, it's a great, a great ride. Definitely an A ticket.
Ah, okay. So several things to talk about today. I want to continue the discussion
about the new video iPod. A lot of excitement about that, particularly from people
who are already doing video blogging, man, that I receive a whole bunch of emails.
So I'm also seeing more people now doing video versions of their podcast. So they'll,
they'll do the regular podcasts, but they'll have a camera on them. And it's, it's, it
is kind of interesting. I haven't actually seen a very long one other than the Mary
and Carla, is it Mary and Carla show? Actually, I'm going to play one for you later on.
And there's something very exciting coming out of the brain of Mad Dwindstein. And you
know there's a lot of crap going on in there. So we'll get to that just a quick, remember
I was talking about that Danny came movie earlier this week. And I couldn't come up with
the title of it. Thank you all very much. Of course, I could have gone to IMDB and, and figured
it out, but forgot to do that. Song is born as the title of the movie where, where music
is changing right all around these professors, including Danny Kay while they're writing
the big book of music. And then they emerge and it turns out that jazz has already been
born. And, and of course, they, they freak out completely. They've been writing the book that
is outdated. It's a great movie. I wonder if you can still get it on. I wonder if it's been
published on DVD or if there's a way to get it. So looking forward to a short weekend, Saturday
of course, my sister is here with her girlfriend. And so they all went off shopping and
go for thank goodness. But I'll see if I can get the tip on for a short
day. You got to talk. You've got to listen to my sister. She really is hilarious. It's
very, very funny. So I'll maybe we'll do that Saturday. Sunday morning early, though, I leave
for San Francisco for a pop at least 10 or 12 days. We got a lot of stuff to do. And I'm
excited about seeing the team again, although it seems like the stay at home has been way too
short. Ah, yes, the things we do for love. Hey Adam, this is Andrew Darlow. I'm a photographer
and editor director of magazine published out of Long Island, New York. I've been totally
hooked on podcasting for quite a while. Thanks in great part to you. Thank you. And I've listened
to just about every Delhi source code since May. And I also listened regularly to about
60 other great podcasts. I also keep writing about podcasting and how benefits,
graphic arts, professionals in my editor's letters. Since there are so many great podcasts
about Photoshop and imaging related things and technology. And I also hope to have my own podcast
sometimes soon. Your recent bedcast with your lovely wife Patricia was was really great and I'd love
to hear more of those. Also the two songs that you played with Patricia singing when you were in
San Francisco. I thought we're fantastic. So feel free to bring more of those to us.
I'm also leaving this message because I just listened to one of the podcasts that I
subscribed to called Killer Innovations by Film McKinney. Film was recently in New Orleans for a week
helping out in the really effort in a number of ways. And his words are what really makes
podcasts in such a powerful medium. He speaks at length about the situation there as of about
10 days ago. Straight from the heart and directly from his personal experience. And in a way it was
sort of like when you were in San Francisco doing your sound seeing tour at two or three AM you just
got a really good sense of what life is really like and what people are faced with. Straight up
without the dramatic music and without the 30 seconds sound bites. The podcast can be found at
KillerInnovations.com and the show is from October 3rd. The show is also available in iTunes.
I highly recommend listening and as Phil says if people do have the means to continue supporting
their really effort they do really need it. Keep up the great work and I hope that we're able to meet
at the big podcast Expo in California next month if you're planning to attend. Bye bye.
Pod Show content that will make you squeeze the dog and burp your mother.
This week on the travel comments podcast we talk about air world our own little ecosystem. All
the food stalls were connected. Same kitchen, same employees, same company. I don't think that's
sort of you know that's sort of concentration is is doing great things for my taste buds.
Breaking through a business travel gets you past the veneer of your travel destination.
Now tell you warn is not a place most people go when they visit Detroit you know heck it's not
even a place a lot of people go when they live in Detroit. However driving down Van Dyke Avenue
between the Chrysler plant up in Sterling Heights and the GM tech center you're sort of
weight in the middle of the Detroit auto culture and what Daddy does on travel. You record podcast
you go to meetings and you eat and you drive nice cars if you get your hands on them. All this
and listen your comments on the travel comments podcast. My name is Mark Peacock and I hope you'll
join me. www.travelcomers.travlco.com. Trying to think it's effort. The guy who also podcast from
different bathrooms while traveling it's that's not Chris Rockwell but I think there's somewhere
there's a podcast that does that that is travel related. Podcast Expo let's talk about that for a
second. It's coming up November I think until November 11th and 12th and this isn't too far
from Los Angeles is what I understand. Now first of all I've worked out the schedule I'm definitely
going to be there and just looks like the entire podcast universe is going to descend upon
the portable media expo and I think I think we have a really good time actually. I think it's
going to be where no index was you know maybe the woodstock of podcasting where see what we do
did Delta Sierra Charlie 200 from there was 200 yeah 200 and that was a great gathering with
the Microsoft announcing their support for RSS and just you know all kinds of good stuff going on.
This may be kind of like a Monterey festival. I'm not sure there may not even be an analogy but it's
going to be cool and a lot of the Pod Show programs are going to be there podcasts, podcasters
I think a lot of it's actually a Pod Show family members who work in the office or are going to
make the trek. I think Dawn and Drew are going to have their own sweet. I'm thinking like you know
maybe I should make a big entrance. Maybe maybe I should maybe there's a source code listener
in the neighborhood who's got a helicopter and then we loaded up with some beaches.
Yeah let's let's do a pimped out chopper ride and arrive at the expo.
Okay maybe not but that again we're going to get a huge penis limo with magic and Dawn and Drew
of be kind of cool if we had all of us degenerates in one limo that would be fun. Anyway I think
it's going to be a good time. I don't even know that much about the expo itself. I'm sure there's
all kinds of people displaying wares and I guess there's going to be plenty of hardware vendors and
software vendors but I'm really looking forward to meeting all of the podcasters. That was the
same thing at Nomdex because you meet someone you hear the name and like yeah I know you you know
it's almost like when you read someone's weblog and you know them so intimately but with podcasting
it's even something different because you you you can recognize the voice and and it's fun.
So I say that somewhere around the first or second week of November we'll see height and
activity in the podshvier. Podsaic music network did my regular check this morning. Actually
it across check as I received an email about a band they said they were listed on the podsaic
music network. Check it out indeed they were but I actually sampled the music first
from their website and then from PMN as we call it. It's three girls who really I should say
not girls. I just say women. Now I should say it's planet on women. Check this out.
Oh this makes me feel good. Nothing like streaming guitars. We're looking at women.
Waking up the neighborhood. Planet of women.
And you said that I know for. Planet of drinking. Leave me to your door.
But we haven't even left before. Power's drink has got it to my head.
It needs a one-one. Take care. Take care.
Can't smell it or catch on. I'm on the wall of my head.
I want to make a shout at all. You got me feeling good.
Waking up the neighborhood. Planet of women.
And you said that I know for. You got me feeling good. Stay in my way.
Waking up the neighborhood.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
With a yêurate sheet?
Rotten- let this end. Leave my heart again. I'm just real component.
🤶🌶 💜🌶🈜
When you touch me, catch it all this time.
Keep blooming when you hate your death in mind.
I tell you I I will never feel good.
Won't you kiss me a little passion?
I don't know what I'm making
I don't know why I'm making
Cause I don't know how I'm gonna feel in good
Why you get out of the neighborhood
Why not get out of the neighborhood
You've got me feeling good
Stay in our place
Why you get out of the neighborhood
Why not get out of the neighborhood
I don't know why I'm gonna feel in good
Why you get out of the neighborhood
You've got me feeling good
Stay in our place
I don't know why I'm gonna feel in good
Why not get out of the neighborhood
Stay in our place
Why you get out of the neighborhood
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Ah Ha Ha Ha, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's it.
I was sorry about that, that was me enjoying the tunes, waking up the neighborhood from
the Podsake Music Network.
You'll find a link from the show notes on dailysourcecode.com, I got to talk to Michael
Demett.
He's the guy who's maintaining the wiki show notes, oh man, it's just been crazy.
Time's on.
That just sucks.
I hate it.
I don't mind if someone's a thousand miles away and he's so used to someone being
six, seven, eight thousand miles away and in your ears when you're talking to him on Skype
but then you have to take all that time zone into account, which we could change that.
That sucks.
I'll just wake up at the same time.
I'll go to bed at the same time.
More about the video iPod, I've received a couple of interesting comments that, of course,
it plays video, we've all seen that, but they've also changed the internal specs for the sound
recording.
It'll now do what we'd call in podcasting a high quality recording and 44.1 kilohertz sample
rate.
Is that the sample rate?
Now, the 44.1 kilohertz encoding rate, bit rate, if something like that.
Anyway, it's good enough.
It'll be great for sound seeing.
I think they're coming up with what I haven't seen yet is what kind of microphone attachments
there will be.
It'd be awesome if you could plug in just any, any old microphone or, you know, we'll see
if you need a mic preamp, but the iPod economy will present whatever it can once the
specs kind of get out and people start developing stuff.
That's good news.
And I've been thinking about, you know, what kind of content works for a video iPod?
And it's not like all of a sudden, I've been thinking this because I know lots of people
have an RCO or other type of portable video device best, Sony PSP, of course.
And by the way, iTunes 6 apparently plays the Sony format, so that's kind of interesting
there.
To it, yeah.
I think that, you know, first of all, I'm a strong believer that, then when it comes
to video, personal porn casting is going to be a big deal, but I also thought about,
and here's a million dollar idea for you because, of course, an idea is worth a million,
but a brand is worth a billion.
The million dollar idea is dating service.
Think about that.
You subscribe to a site and you say, okay, here's the profile of the person I'm looking
for.
And then whenever there's a profile that matches, you'll get the little video on your
iPod.
That, I think, would be pretty cool.
Because it's much more personal that way.
If you have to look at something on your computer, this way, and that does work for me.
If you have some time and I think it all has to be relatively short.
So far, I'm seeing pretty much just short video things come across the wire, but I doubt
there's going to be a lot of interest for, well, you have to think about the size of the
screen, you know.
We talked about that the other day.
When you have a music video, when you see, if it's like a boy band and you have a total
shot of the boy band, you're not going to get any kind of detail.
So that's kind of a waste.
So we'll have to start thinking differently about, particularly if you have television
background, you want to get into distributing these files through iTunes, iPod and R.C.
and all other means.
And of course, the infrastructure is there, which is great, you know, I think I've
said before, Madge Weinstein has been putting videos in her podcast feed for quite a while
now.
It's some of it's funny, some of it's rather disturbing, but it's always worth watching
because it's short.
So I'm just waiting to see what kind of creativity pops up.
And then, of course, it's going to be interesting to see if there's a high demand for it.
I don't know how board people are with television.
I know that they're board with television, but how many people know they're board
with television.
Is it time again to point to the XNTV experiment?
I think it is.
And let me do that.
I'll make sure that that shows up in the wiki show notes for today's source code.
The XNTV experiment, please take this experiment, do it.
It'll cost you maybe, well, you can read through it and get the gist, but it really works
if you do it.
How, no matter how mundane some of the test seems, do it, you know, it'll really enlighten
you about what's happening when you're watching television.
It really will, it actually almost got me to stop watching television.
So then, depending on how many people we can save, that will determine the market for
video podcasting.
So Mad sent me a little note that I wanted to share with you because, well, once again,
she's on the cusp of technology and is starting a really something interesting.
Of course, we already have Q-Podder.org, which now has over 100 queer podcasters, queer
casters, Q-Podders, whatever you want to call it.
And now there's some packaging going on in Q-Podder.org world.
Hello, Adam.
As Mad's wine steam from East Radio, I have some wonderful news for you.
Related to this business about video podcasting, as you know, and mentioned, I've been
doing this sort of thing for very long time, longer than I've been podcasting, in fact.
And I do have a website that's been around for five years, called InsaneFilms.com.
But that's not what I'm calling you about or leaving you this for cock to message.
I'm leaving this because I have wonderful news.
I've been working round the clock with some wonderful people over Q-Podder.com, particularly
the Sky Panther and John Eng.
And we have, in the past 24, I was created a brand new website and feed called FagRigator.com.
That's right.
FagRigator, a lagRigator, what it is, is, the way it is twice.
It's all of the queer and queer friendly video podcasts all in one feed.
So when you get to your video, I potto if you just want to watch it at home on your
video and you don't want to pay for shit.
We will offer you this.
We've been holding on a second, Madge episodes of Lost are not shit.
The only downside is that they only allowed if you're a member of the US store.
I just watched another episode of Lost Last Night and we're a season behind here and
so I'm pining for that and it's time to open up a US account on the Apple iTunes store.
So don't knock that, that part I think is really good, that's not shit, it's a damn
good show.
Already been, the Q-Pod of Folks have already been creating video podcasts for some
time.
We've all been doing it for months and you can already subscribe to FagRigator and see
all of our wonderful videos and these same missexuals are very creative items carry.
You should let us give you a blowjob sometime, not me, but this person named Young Blood
is something anyway.
That's another story.
I don't do that sort of thing in the world.
You should send me that story, man.
That's been, I don't know what I'm talking about, forget that.
But anyway, FagRigator.com, you can subscribe to it at feeds.feedbunner.com slash
aggregator.
FagRigator.
And it should be an iTunes soon, I just submitted it.
It's all happening so fast, so fast, this is so exciting, I am very, very excited about
this video podcasting and my black video iPod is on its way.
And by the way, Adam, I really, you can cut this off anytime I don't need to talk
for the whole time.
But I really, really hold on, I wouldn't be a good podcaster if I tried to hide something.
The fun is all on the stuff that you don't want to put on the air.
Really need a car, I am tired of driving around my fat ass on the bicycle.
Can you please get somebody to sponsor me and my fucking show, give me a car and that's
all I'll fucking talk about.
You don't even have to, like, I don't even have to tell them I'm sponsored and I'll
just talk about it all the time with something.
Anyway, that's probably something you won't want to play on the show, but I don't care
if you do it.
It's up to you, it's just show and talking to God too much.
Anyway, thanks Adam.
Talk to you soon.
Hey, baby.
Thank you, honey.
But yeah, imagine, Skype me when I was an Amsterdam and I actually said, oh, I'll be right
with you two days later, I've gotten back to her, I miss she's not angry.
You know how lesbians can get well, so of course I subscribe to the Fagrogator and it
works.
There's just a whole bunch of videos sitting there and my items, I don't have a video
iPod.
Well, I'll look at one when I'm out in San Francisco, I'll go to the Apple store, maybe
you'll look at it.
But now I'm confused because I thought I really wanted the Nano and I was convinced
that there would not be a video iPod yet.
I was so convinced, man, was I wrong.
And I don't know, I don't know, sorry, my brain fried.
I owe an apology to Sarah at the Wall Street Journal as a few listeners pointed out because
she was so sure that there was going to be a video iPod announcement.
It's funny because she was so sure that I said to her, look, you know, I could be wrong.
But unless Walt Mossberg knows something that you can't tell me without killing me later,
then I think it's new power books.
And I guess that's it.
I guess that the Wall Street Journal knew well ahead of time what was what was going to happen.
But I own a apology to her because I was convinced it was going to be the new power
book.
So now the story is starting to kind of unfold.
And apparently there was some issues with the new power that last line of power PC,
the power books Apple is going to bring out.
They couldn't get the 1.7 gigahertz processor to work properly.
Some buggy's going on.
And that's mainly because an Apple, you'd be surprised how small the development teams are.
But all the resources, of course, are working on the Intel version of the new power books
and max.
So that's a reason why they couldn't stop on the bugs quick enough apparently.
This is what I read in the papers this morning here.
What was it?
Did I think it was financial times?
I think so.
So that's why those have been delayed.
But they'll probably be coming out next Wednesday.
I already heard rumors that there's going to be an announcement and that'll be those final
power books.
So I guess I'm going to pick up one of those because I'm sure it'll be at least, I don't
think they'll get the Intel power books out by Christmas.
Oh, would not be awesome.
They might, they might.
So I'll just have to purchase a new power book.
But I was bummed out because here I am, you know, we've gone through this.
I've been an unofficial beta tester for Apple since, well, actually my dad did have an
Apple 2, but I never really got into it much.
But, you know, the Mac Plus and the ED in the 512k and whatever and the 2 effects and
the black and white power books and the logbill, I mean, I've owned them all.
I mean, just none of them, maybe I've spent, you know, $50 to $100,000 an Apple product.
It could be totally possible if you're talking about, you know, not just the computers
but whatever other paraphernalia that goes along with it.
And so that was a new G5 power, I'm Mac and I just bought an I'm Mac and the sales
guy didn't know.
He didn't know to tell me to wait for like two days, I was really pissed off.
Well, it happens to me all the time, but I was glad that I, you know, that I waited with
the power book because we are going to get the new power books and I guess at the end
of the day, it's cool because there is a new iPod that's also a cool church key to have.
So after I subscribe to the Faggregator, I ran across this video cast, which actually,
I think Meguseg is going to play the video for me, but you will definitely get the audio.
Let's see if this works.
Five months ago, I bought my new I'm Mac G5 for 1799.
I'm about a month later, I got the new I site camera so I could do video conferencing.
The one this is up on top of the monitor.
I'm about a month and a half later, I got the new I'm 90 miles for 50 bucks.
If you add those all together, you're looking at about $2,000.
Now I steam job, I now it's a good even a faster I Mac with the built-in I site and I'm
mighty mouse included for 1699 for the 20 inch.
Thanks, I held a lot Steve, I won't my $300 difference back.
And now all you people that are buying the new I pod video, you can watch me ran and
rape about it on your new I pod.
So all of you that are getting that great deal for 1699, you can go after yourself.
See you later.
Alright, so I don't know about the doing that on an I site that doesn't really work for audio.
Hey guys, if you're going to do video casting, excellent, awesome, I love it, but please
make sure you mic yourself up, you know, get a get a love mic or something because
it's really blows.
Anyway, I totally agree on this stuff too, I mean, it's not about the $300 difference
whatever, but you know, shoot man, and we even discussed about all the inventory had dried
up so you almost could have known, but I didn't expect that.
Anyway, let me see here I have a couple more email messages from the Gmail about that.
Let me see Joel, the cloth one says, yeah, Apple did release new I Mac, it's a GFI with
an I site camera built in new video card and remote control as well.
And he says take your GFI back and get the new one.
I don't wonder if you can do that, can you go back and say, hey, I feel bone, I wonder.
It seems like a, seems like I'm not really going to want to do it.
And this is Liam, Liam Gladi, we actually sent me a link to the Apple Insider who are
pretty bold about their statements and they have a whole article, a whole blog post and
you just bring it up here about the new power books and oh, this is where I read it.
Okay, so I thought it was the newspaper, but Apple Insider actually, almost second, I just
got a pop-up window for Apple Insider, great guys, thanks.
Right, here we go.
Let's just see if there's anything that missed, 17 inch models will support a native resolution
of near 1920 by 1200 pixels.
That's nice.
They'll have a faster hard drives, larger hard drives, it's a, it's a good article actually.
Oh, and so apparently before that happens, we're going to get a new software upgrade and
OSX 10.4.3 update.
I remember all those years of being a Mac enthusiast and no one really gave a shit.
They didn't care, like you and your damn Mac, don't care at all.
Alrighty, so I got one more promo here, actually a couple more, and a few more things
I'm going to talk about, and more podcasts music on the way.
Hi, I'm Adam, I did my first podcast in the Canadian Arctic, in the middle of nowhere.
It's an excellent podcast, it's called Windy and my little friend.
I'm a bit dedicated to it, I'm not coaching much.
I'm going to be very explicit, I'm going to see how I'm doing all the things I've been doing
in my first episode.
I love playing promos, in languages I can't or primarily understand it.
I heard explicit, I think, explicit.
I heard, hmm, heard that in there.
I think I played what a Finnish man, I knew it was dragon them.
I heard that and there, I think I played what a finished promo the other day, and I got
a couple emails from Finn and saying, you know, dude, that wasn't like an entirely family
safe promo, I don't know what the guy was talking about, but it's cool to see podcasts
from all over the world.
And it's interesting to see that France is up and coming, and actually it may not even be
that crazy, you know that, was this from Canada, but in France, they really have
a tight control on their media.
And we used to talk about this, the French actually, so if you look at the three television
systems that still exists today, of course, everything's going digital now, high definition.
You have the NTSC standard in the United States, and of course, the States is so big,
that, you know, that's not really seen as a protectionist move, and of course, well, you know,
who kind of developed television, but the better standard with high resolution is pal, that's
what the most of the rest of the world uses, and then you have C-Cam, and C-Cam is what France
has used, and I believe they still use it, and you just, you know, you can't receive a French
program, and back in the day, a French video cassette would not work, unless you had a multi-standard
VCR and television, but really, you know, it's because they have, I don't know what the
percentage is, but it's a high percentage of French content only, so they really want to protect
their culture, which is now, there's a lot to be said for that, and Canada has some similar rules,
I believe, but Patricia and Ivan or Sister were there for three days when they went to the
Chanel show, and they said it was, it was just unwatchable, it was just cry, it was really,
really horrible, and you only have like, you know, three or four channels, and I think the radio is
probably in the similar state, although you do have energy and RJ, which is a pretty hot station
in France, but maybe just maybe the word of podcasting is started to infiltrate, so I'm looking
forward, let's see if we can press that through and see what comes out of France, they got a lot of
culture there, that's for sure, a lot of stuff that we just haven't been exposed to, and I missed
the French, Chanel, Chanel, once in a while, and I wanted to point you to an article written about
MTV that Nicky Fink, and I KKI, F-I-N-K-E, she writes for the LA Weekly Magazine, it's also available
online, and she interviewed me for this piece, but it's about how music has left MTV, and I
got really excited when she was asking me all these questions for this interview, because
I think, wow, here's a journalist who understands it, she has 10 million readers, I mean,
it's a huge publication, and she's syndicated in multiple publications, and you know, so of course
we started talking about podcasting, and that article's not about podcasting, but she will be doing
one, I think, and she also wants to do her own podcast, and she's done radio, and I'm really
excited about bringing her into our community, because here's someone who just rags and rants
and raves about mainstream media all the time, and she's spot on, she pointed me to another article,
she wrote about the media coverage of Katrina, check her out, definitely, Nicky Fink, and look for
her at a podcast, you know, you very soon.
It's an ever-ending highway, life, dust and diesel, but there's a rest stop on the side of the road,
a sanctuary of songs for the spirit of your mind, hit the brakes, and take a seat at the U-turn
cafe, the U-turn cafe, with your host, CC Chapman, find it at U-turncathay.com
this is Dr. Larry Payne of another night shift, the emergency medicine podcast,
you can find my website at www.anothernightshift.com, or you can subscribe through iTunes.
Before we go any further, let's just get this over with right now. Yes, my name really is Dr. Payne.
Yes, I hear about it from my patients about 20 times a day, but you know, I went to medical school
with a guy named Tom Hurt, a guy named Joe Die, and I think I got off fairly easily.
I've practiced emergency medicine for over 22 years, my podcasts include content for emergency
physicians as well as anyone that's trying to hack through the jungle of modern medicine,
and I'm also eager to respond to listener comments and questions. I think personally that podcasting
is a perfect way to reach patients in other physicians. What I can't do though is diagnose,
treat, or prescribe in my podcasts. I'm not going to prescribe anything like those ads you might see
in your inbox every day, Adam, like for Viagro, Cialis, not that you'd ever need any of that stuff anyway.
Adam, you are over 40 now, you just had another birthday, and you never know when you're going to
start to need to think about these things. Maybe we should just talk some time. But anyway, I love talking
about emergency medicine, and I hope everybody will subscribe, listen, and learn along with me.
Once again, my name is Dr. Larry Payne. I've been called a pain in the neck, a pain in the well,
use your imagination. Once again, this is the another night shift emergency medicine podcast.
My website is www.anothernightshift.com, and you can subscribe there or just click on the icon
and items. I look forward to speaking to you again soon, and thanks for having me on the daily
source code. And we are just getting started with all the possibilities that podcast and
can bring us. That is clear. Thank you, Dr. Payne. Uh-huh. I have unfortunate name for the
profession, indeed. That's great, though. And do you notice how lots of doctors are really
media ready? I mean, is that just me? Or, I mean, you see, of course, all these make-over shows,
and ugly duckling shows, and stuff like that, and all these doctors really know how to sell it.
I think that it's because they, they really know how to talk to people. So, yeah, that's a podcast
I'll subscribe to. I don't know if it'll bring me down. I hate hearing about sickness and illness.
That's not good. But that's what we're going to see. I think it's so clear. Even I am still operating
under kind of a hybrid of the old model of broadcasting, and we're seeing things, and
we're literally seeing giants shift overnight. There's just so much incredibly exciting stuff happening.
What's going on with Yama? What's the vibe on that? I like what they're doing with tagging. That's
kind of cool. That's, that's rather interesting. Has anyone swapped it out and is anyone using it
as, as a directory, or are people still, it doesn't quite work well on search yet. I think that they
have an index everything yet, because if you, if you do a search on a topic, although I think they
are indexing show notes, but if you do a search on a topic, or just a name of a show, you get maybe
an episode from July or from June. For instance, if you do Adam Currier daily source code,
of course, the feed pops up, and the show we can subscribe, but the episode, it picks a
couple of miles. I'm not quite sure how that works yet, but I'd like to hear some feedback. Let me know
what your experiences are with Yahoo. Okay. Earlier in the week, I played a tune. I was really
excited about this artist that entered the Podsake Music Network. Excuse me. With this Friday
vibe, it's a little bit dreary outside, a little bit rainy. I figured I'd listen to a couple more
of her tracks. Actually, I have now downloaded every single one of the tracks that you put up
on the Podsake Music Network, and I think what I should just do is just go buy and buy the album,
because this is good stuff. Of course, I'm a sucker for a bit of jazz. Robin Stein, a shy boy.
Will be my boy. You irresistible kiss of you. It's time to stop this flirtation
in the conversation. You don't need to be shy with me shy boy. Now you're my boy.
And you're not so shy anymore.
Yeah, time to stop this flirtation in the conversation. You don't need to be shy with me shy boy.
Now you're my boy. And you're not so shy anymore. No, you're not so shy anymore.
You know what I mean, you're not so shy anymore. For the Podsake Music Network,
at music.podshow.com, Robin Stein. You're not such a shy boy anymore. Cool. I love it.
Do the genre sort when you're on the Podsake Music Network. Just look at all the different songs.
There are all the different genres. It's not just angry indie rock. When it comes to Podsake Music,
it's really something there for everybody. Okay, thank you very much for checking the show
out. Once again, atomacurry.com for feedback. And if you want to send me off a promo,
fantastic. I love to play it. Stick it up on a web server somewhere. Don't forget your ID3 tag
so that I can identify what the hell it is. And in the software that I'm using. And of course,
for if you're not already subscribed to this podcast, you can go to dailysourcecode.com.
You find the podcast feed there. You can also search it in in iTunes, of course. And who knows?
Where in the future, you'll be able to search for podcasts and be driven towards fun things to
listen to. We will assimilate you and control you. Everybody, if I don't talk to you over the weekend,
Monday, definitely, as I said, find a San Francisco actually going up to Redmond for a meeting
early in the week. And I'll be telling you all about that. So take care. Have a great.
Ffff! Reek it. Another podshow podcast. Stick it in your ear.