Delta Sierra Charlie 2-3-8
The $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
It's a battle carry.
And it is your daily source code for Friday's September 9, 2005.
It's just an hour.
Hey!
You can do it!
It's the end of the week and it's been quite a long one.
For me at least, you know, back and forth to New York.
Yeah, just to get a door knob in New York, darling.
And it's going to be an interesting show today.
Got some really cool and fun and great news to talk about and some stuff that really sells.
So a bit bittersweet today's show is for me, certainly right now,
because I just saw my two girls off.
They're off for the weekend.
I'm going to visit Patricia's sister Iván and Rotterdam.
I wanted to get her on the show because people keep saying,
Hey, bring Patricia on.
She's a lot of the show's better when she's off.
I hear you.
I'm trying to.
Trying.
Christina's going with it.
They're going to a fashion show on Sunday.
And I couldn't fly myself, unfortunately.
But I got a great deal on KLM this time around.
Now I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
Because KLM happens to have a couple of flights,
where they call their city hop or they go straight to Rotterdam,
which is very convenient much better than easy jet to Amsterdam,
and then an hour in the car, and they'll be basically right there,
and the family can pick them up.
And it's a nice little convenient,
a fucker 100 dual turbo prop.
It's a nice play.
And the ticket price unbelievable,
round trip for the two of the $198.
It's almost nothing.
So I've got all my instructions.
You know, everything I have to do around the house.
Which includes, well, you know, feeding the dogs.
I've got to feed myself.
I've got to keep everything clean.
I've got to, I'm so pussy with.
And I've got a whole list of stuff that I kind of do.
We got some interesting pod take music that was submitted on the show today.
And of course, you're going to kick it off with a mashup.
This came from mashuptown.com.
Base 211.
So I'm kind of conscious going over there.
It's oblatif.
10.
It's a lot of bitches up here at the night, boy.
I'm about to get drunk.
It's whole damn.
What a barat.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
No more fuckers.
I've always got a career.
And I like you busy.
And this party in here.
And I'm ready to talk.
And I'm ready to go see her.
She arrived again inside.
So I ain't gonna be able to pull it to the side.
And invited the chairs.
Pull up the chair.
And I can swear.
No drama.
Put care for a player.
Workin' with a mind stuff.
I ain't got time to waste.
Let's vacate the place.
That blind's a trace.
Trying to deface in the ground.
We stay cast to trade.
You'll find it.
You're bound to kick.
What we found is fate.
We can watch to incredible mace.
Master beat.
Why settle away?
Let's sescalate.
To the never super alien.
Seek your rivers on the rivers.
And let's get rid of movie shakes.
Come on.
And this is my favorite song.
Listen along.
And the DJ throws it on.
And if I leave you tonight.
And I fall asleep.
And wake up.
Hopefully she got some tea.
And this is my favorite song.
Listen along.
And the DJ throws it on.
And if I leave you tonight.
And I fall asleep.
And wake up.
Hopefully she got some tea.
Hey.
Holy Holy Mary.
Yeah.
Wake around the club.
Who do you everywhere?
She caught me standing in my homies.
Damn it.
Me do approach.
Can't make she smile on what's here.
But she got a vanilla.
But your turns are baby fathers.
Baby bottles in cereal.
She out like us.
I got a lot of the nerdy.
Oh, the DJ's pan.
Oh, be so on the steady.
Oh, and she's in pain.
That she wants to be here.
No.
With the real thing.
Not the deal though client.
And I know I don't want to be here.
And home with some double deals.
Full of silicone.
Tinned red chicks around me outside.
Found me outside.
Clown me outside.
Tell I pop the truck.
And they found me outside.
Busting at the bitches screaming.
Oh, today right.
And this is my favorite song.
Listen along.
And the DJ throws it on.
And if I leave you tonight.
And I fall asleep.
And wake up.
Hopefully she got some tea.
And this is my favorite song.
Listen along.
And the DJ throws it on.
And if I leave you tonight.
And I fall asleep.
And wake up.
Hopefully she got some tea.
Roll up all these everywhere.
Gotta find a certain chick's atmosphere.
Oh, be so these blaring.
And then she got me fair.
And then she don't come over here.
And then try to eat me.
Let it run.
Leave.
Like a box of cherry.
Yo's carry cupcakes.
And chocolate.
Titsy rolls.
How am I to order?
Cause I got a big girl.
This order.
So the cover up.
They're blah blah.
Oh, I split.
And I got time to play.
Less investigate.
Another place today.
Ladies, less in weight.
Dresses, petite.
No window drapes.
Words about them.
They got them.
All grand beings.
Got your open jeans.
Seems to be a little link was seen.
Wouldn't hurt much.
No touchy.
And this is my favorite song.
Listen along.
And the DJ throws it on.
And if I leave you tonight.
And I fall asleep.
And wake up.
Hopefully she got some tea.
And this is my favorite song.
Listen along.
And the DJ throws it on.
And if I leave you tonight.
And I fall asleep.
And wake up.
Hopefully she got some tea.
Oh.
Yeah.
You gotta have tea, baby.
It's just what looked right.
But me, be honest.
You know tea.
And we're working, all of a sudden.
Yeah.
I'm feeling good.
Shaded back this day.
Oh, be Christ.
Come on.
I think those Beatles guys should do something together.
I turn out to be some from mashuptown.com.
I think there's some kind of this is a contest submission or a contest winner.
It seems like the given away iTunes stuff over there.
iTunes music store downloads and as you go check it out, mashuptown.com.
Tell Art, I sent you.
Okay.
One of the reasons that the source code is late today,
or later the normal is now, what is it?
720, almost 730.
Oh man, East Enders is coming on.
It's because I had a two and a half hour chat with Cast Blaster Mike,
who was a developing Cast Blaster.
And we had some really creative discussion.
We always spar with each other.
Because I'm horrible at getting back to people.
And he hates that.
But then the creative juice is really started to flow.
And we were able to teach each other a couple of things.
And he's now working on something that I'm so excited about.
Which I'm just going to tell you because I mean,
he's totally got all the pieces in place.
It just has to learn a bit about the one reason why,
or the number one reason I should say, why I'm not using Cast Blaster
to record the daily source code.
Now there's a number of reasons.
And we've talked about a pro version.
And what should be in the basic version.
And well, one of the things,
see, when I do a podcast,
I've been doing radio since I was 14.
And we really pioneered a lot of different ways
to kind of adapt and hack if you will.
Traditional audio recording and studio equipment
into systems that would work for the type of art that we do.
And this pertains completely to podcasts as well.
For instance, back in the day when we played vinyl,
remember those days.
And we, of course, could not afford, or we called a quick start turn table.
I think techniques was really the SL was at 2000.
I can't remember the SL 100, maybe.
That was the first turn table that could really start up a record.
You could cue it.
So basically, you put the needle drop the needle down.
For those of you who've never seen a record player,
you drop the needle on the, drop the needle on the record.
And the drums just go like this.
Sorry about that.
And then the minute the song starts,
you'd stop it with your finger.
And the reason you could do that is because we put a slip mat.
First, we'd put an old 12 inch LP.
We put that on the turn table.
And then we'd put a, we call a slip mat,
which is like a velvet anti-static mat,
but an oversized one.
So we'd cut it out of velvet ourselves.
And it would be anti-static as well.
So that if you grab that mat,
then basically the record that would sit on top of that,
would not play.
But underneath the turn table was still turning.
Now granted a little bit slower than, you know,
the desired revolutions per minute.
But that was the beauty of it.
As when you let go of the felt mat,
then within a quarter revolution,
it would be up to speed.
And you could start the song with start playing.
In fact, sometimes, and that's called queuing.
Sometimes we'd queue up the records too tight.
And then it would kind of like,
whew, kind of like, you know,
horrible in there while I was getting up the speed.
And you know, that used to be a part of the art is
how tight can you queue the record.
And the way you started it and get this is
we break open telco relays.
Relay for those you've never seen one is essentially
an electro magnet that when activated,
when current flows through the electro magnet,
it then pulls down the metallic hinge.
And it goes click.
And that can, of course, in turn create a circuit.
But we weren't using that for the circuit part of the
relay opening or closing.
We were using that.
We'd break off the plastic housing.
And then we'd have the slip mat run in between
the electro magnet and the lid.
So when you activate it,
click it, it would basically grab the mat.
So then we put micro switches.
I hope you don't mind me getting into this.
It's just, you know, it is kind of important to know
where I'm coming from with this stuff.
We put micro switches in the faders.
So basically the volume sliders on the mixing board.
We opened it up and put the micro switches in there.
So that when you had the fader closed,
then current would flow through the magnet
and it would keep the record in place.
Then we had an override switch right in front of each
turn table.
We had two.
You clicked that.
The relay would open and then it would start playing.
So you could queue it up.
Click the override off.
And then when you open up the fader, boom.
I just opened up a secondary mic fader here.
But literally, you know, sometimes you hit it so hard that the
button would go flying off.
You know, this is the old school old school days of
how you used to do it.
And, you know, I remember when we had our first CD play,
when we played our first CD, it blew out the transmitter
because the frequency range was so broad.
Anyway, so I'm very, very used to,
basically flying blind.
I don't have to look at the mixer to know what I'm doing.
And I'm already adapting quite a bit with the set up.
Now, because, you know, everything's coming out of
megasegue.
So basically, if I want to start something,
and it's all queued up, then I, then I just hit the
bit of button on my Mac and then it plays.
And then I, you know, I'm also doing a final mix
basically of the show.
And I'm riding the faders a little bit and, you know,
when stuff is a little bit too loud or if I want to
sound more in the background.
So you're doing a lot of things.
And you can't do that if you have to do it with a mouse
on a screen.
So we talked about the idea of hooking up a MIDI controller,
which we'll have a number of faders and buttons to start
stuff and connecting that to cast blaster.
And I'm excited about this because it'll have,
it'll be such a tremendous benefit.
Now, this Yamaha-per-first professional audio
workstation AW16G because the R is left on the
tarmac.
It's a heavy thing, you know, but it's basically a big
cast blaster like piece of software on a hard drive
with a computer.
Only it's not built with the functionality of cast
blaster, which, of course, is why it doesn't
really suffice.
But it does have a number of things that work well.
And one of them is that I can basically mix
stuff.
And there's some other ancillary things like processing
etc.
But, you know, there are ways to solve that.
So anyway, this is something that I think would be a
great addition to cast blaster to have that capability
built right in.
So that you can use that on the screen if you want,
but if you want to plug in your MIDI controller,
so you have faders and buttons to start stuff with,
wow, how freaking cool will that be.
So I just wanted to say that that was very, very exciting.
Yeah.
734, everybody.
AAC writes Jeff from podcast shuffle show.
So rather than stir up controversy and talking behind you back,
talk podcast alley and other forms about the acquisition.
I just asked directly.
Oh, I see.
It says, rather than stir up controversy and talking behind you,
back, back, talk podcast.
Oh, I don't know what that behind you back.
Talk podcast alley.
I don't know what you're saying.
I know what you're saying, but it's a weird sentence.
I'll just ask directly.
A lot of folks, not me, says Jeff,
were surprised about the acquisition.
Maybe you can say a few words on a daily source code
now that the deal is done.
That's a good point.
And I'll tell you why I haven't mentioned it
is because we've been working with Chris McIntyre
who created podcast alley and is the,
the heart of that community.
You know, we've been working with him for months.
You know, and we had meetings in New York.
And we certainly, I certainly have talked about him a lot
and have been promoting podcast alley.
We've just been working with him for so long
that it felt, you know, so natural.
He's just, he's there.
I mean, he's moved out to San Francisco.
He's, he's relocated.
And he's also splitting his time with his lovely wife
and Nashville.
I mean, he's, he's really very committed.
Just another one of the, and I think it's now 25 people.
Podcastors, producers, engineers, developers,
business people, designers, project managers
that, you know, that believed in this crazy ass vision
that we have and have, you know, have followed Ron and I
and, you know, and that was not necessarily a free ride.
You know, the people who really had to work
and really had to help us out and step up
and we have an incredible, incredible team.
And what's cool now is I have,
I've, I'm starting to relive eye chat
for the video capabilities.
And I said, I was missing stuff at the office.
I just didn't feel a part of it when I'm not there.
And so, well, why don't we set up a power book and
KJ, Chris Jacob has had an old power book, I guess,
that the hinges had fallen off or something.
And they've set it up, it's that's kind of like my office space
and through eye chat, we can just have a full-time video
connection.
And we have, it's a very open office in general.
So it wouldn't be out of the ordinary for me to be talking
here and other people being able to overhear it
and vice versa.
So that's pretty natural.
And I found this great apple script,
I hunted around for it, but found it on Google.
I chat TV script, which is,
was built for a different reason.
It was created so that you could watch whatever
your television is running or your TV was running at home.
And I hacked it up a little bit.
And so now I basically have a remote control
so that if I set my status to a certain message,
and, of course, that message is coming from my unique identifier.
So go ahead, set the message.
You're not going to be able to get in.
Then the other machine, in this case, the one in San Francisco,
will automatically request a video chat with me.
So, you know, I could turn it on and off.
And that's very cool.
And I've set it up here at the cottage,
so I can do that from remote and do the same thing
from my laptop.
So, and it really does make a difference.
You know, we have lots of Skype calls and conferences,
but being able to see everybody and just kind of
shout back and forth.
And of course, I've rigged up the output of my studio
into eye chat so that I can play stuff.
And, unfortunately, I can't, they can't watch and listen
along as I'm doing the daily source code,
because it's too much stress on the machine to do video
and to be recording straight to MP3,
because that is my recording machine.
So, until I get a dedicated machine for some of the video
stuff, I will peel to do that.
But, and I don't know if I'll feel comfortable
with it quite honestly.
That's kind of weird.
Okay.
Are we ready for some bummer shit?
This is really fucked up.
So, one of our community has fallen ill
and it's very chilling to me.
I've been a big fan and subscribed to the Skype
to Calleady podcast.
And I was turned on to Skype to Calleady by PW,
who, of course, puts the serious pod shows together.
And we featured promo and episodes of Skype to Calleady.
And it's, you know, it's good stuff.
It's well produced, it's well put together.
And PW has been actually,
he's been on my case saying,
you should really talk to Derek
because, you know, he would be a great guy
to do some work with on the audio side for pod show.
And my travels just hadn't really allowed me to do that.
And PW even sent me a tickler on that last night.
Tell him I was a dickhead that hadn't called yet.
I hadn't gotten in touch.
And today, for multiple sources,
I got some really quite shocking,
just terrible news about Derek,
as he is now in hospital with a form of aneurysm.
And this news has spread very quickly through
the podcast community because it is a,
it is a very popular podcast.
And swoopy actually put out a podcast today on the feed
that I wanted to share with you,
just to make sure that you heard it.
And this is one of those things that
I really didn't want to do,
but I unfortunately have to,
just to let people know that
skepticalities aren't really going anywhere,
but we are going to be on a little bit of a hiatus for a little while.
Derek, unfortunately,
he is in the hospital at this time.
He complained of a headache during dinner
and then got physically sick and very quickly deteriorated,
but thankfully by that time he was nearly to the hospital
where he was diagnosed with a VMA,
which loosely translated although not correct,
is somewhat like a brain aneurysm,
where he was bleeding into his brain.
He is in a coma right now,
but it is drug induced as he is sedated,
and he is on a ventilator,
and he is intensive care.
His wife Susan and myself
are surrounded by friends
and Derek's family is coming from New Jersey,
so this is the fastest way
that I could let people know what was going on
and today was actually a really great day to start with
because we found out that
skepticality was one of the top nine podcasts
that Steve Jobs mentioned,
and he showed our picture
at his Apple keynote address introducing iTunes 5
and we were excited,
and that was about an hour before
the world changed a lot for everyone.
So it is very too soon to know
his prognosis at this time
is that he will be in intensive care
in the hospital for at least several weeks.
I have faith in his doctors
and I have faith in all of you.
Please don't send anything.
I mean, you can send email
and things like that, but it is too soon.
It is too soon to know
and for what could have happened today
it worked out really well
because if he would have been home
and he had a headache
and he wouldn't lay down
he may very well have died in his sleep
and this way at least we caught it as fast as possible.
He was to the doctor as fast as possible.
They believe the pressure in his head
and beginning training that blood out is fast as possible.
And he's a strong guy, he's a young guy.
He's in pretty good shape.
So this is one of those things
that nobody could have forcing.
And I like Derek, we trust science
and hopefully science will help us out this time.
And we're going to get through this
but for now, just
you know that I'll be around
and we have some great shows
that we haven't been able to share with you yet.
So that may be coming, but in the meantime,
that's pretty much all there is.
So thanks.
That's like the fourth time I've heard that
and it gets me every single time.
And I guess the only thing that we can do
is to have that Derek and Suppy and Susan
and all people who are close to them
in our thoughts and in our prayers.
Thank you.
You know, one of the, uh,
one of the things you do
and professional broadcasting
is transition really quickly from
from mood to mood, you know.
Hey, my name's Simon Gege.
I'm from pale spring.
Oh, that's an example.
Fuck.
Um.
So look at the news.
And it'll go from, you know,
a really sad human interest story
segment.
It's all human interest, basically.
To, uh,
and now meanwhile on Wall Street.
Uh, but I really have a heart.
I'm doing that.
I feel like I'm just a little bit bombed.
There's still, uh, hurricane Katrina,
and he had those birds.
I was never beautiful in the background.
Well, let me open up the secondary mic.
Uh, let me just position it.
Hold on a second, sure.
It's kind of a shitty sounding mic,
I want, but I've got some kind of gate on it.
Okay, so now, won't pick anything up.
All right, how's it, fun experiment?
Uh, let's see, oh,
do I have a really, I told you about that.
interesting potsafe piece of music coming up. We'll just check the old on the
outliner here. No, it is now time for the promo that interrupts us so
rudely prior to this message.
The webpage especially dedicated to this brand new podcast is at HTTP. I miss
blighty.logspot.com. I'll give you that again in just a moment. The podcast is
every two weeks and we feature news from the UK. Not the kind of news you'll
find on the TV or radio but more the kind of news you'll find down the pub.
Which is just how we like it. Plus every time we have a recipe for you cook up a
bit of Britain wherever you are in the world and of course we want to hear your
comments, stories, suggestions and we got some good tunes too. So remember that
name. I miss blighty. Our web address where you can sign up to the RSS
feed is as follows. HTTP. I miss blighty.logspot.com.
HTTP. I miss blighty.logspot.com. We're looking forward to seeing you there.
We're looking forward to you subscribing. And hey Adam, if the room is a true, maybe
you'll be subscribing yourself soon. Take care. Thanks for your time.
Hi Jill. Content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
Hello Adam. This is Mark Phillips from the FBS Multimedia podcast. I'm here in London
at the launch of the new iPod Nano because I know they've the source code listeners
tend to get everywhere and of course we're here as well and also the iTunes phone and iTunes
version 5 as well. And I must say I'm one of the first people to actually get my hands
on one of these iPod Nano's and man they are sleek and sexy and tiny and I think Apple
have another winner. Anyway, I've been looking for an excuse to send you a trail or a promo
for the show for some time. So here it is. It's called BFBS Multimedia. You can find
this at www.bfbs.bravo.com slash Multimedia and it's presented by Dave Raven and
myself Mark Phillips and it's the friendly podcast about computers, the internet and technology.
As I say, we've been running now for quite some time and we have a lot of fun. We actually
make the show on a house boat on the Thames but that's a whole other story which may
be all I'll tell you another time. Anyway, do have a listen to the show. It's at bfbs.com
slash Multimedia and keep up the good work with the Doni source code.
You know what's even better than a house boat on the Thames? A podcasting buddy with a
house boat on the Thames. Oh yeah, I've got some podcasts. I'm subscribed to Boyd and
Multimedia. I did the jobcast. I played the jobcast Sunday to Monday. Of course, we talked
about the idea of getting CV cast back and we received them. We've actually received
MP3s and someone even dropped an eye river in envelope. Please don't do that. There's
no need to do it. Just email us an MP3 or a link to an MP3 file. But it's fantastic. I was
like itching to play a couple of these for you. But you know, obviously there's a whole bunch
of reasons why I can't. The no one has it has expressly said go ahead and play it. But if you're
going to do a CV cast, you don't mind me playing a bit on the edges so we can kind of close
that loop from the jobcast. And we're going to do another jobcast because we just went through
some requirements about some more resources we need. And I think this is a very cool way to
you know, to get the right type of people in because, well, if you listen to podcasts, then
you know, that's already one big checkbox A. Some more feedback here. Rod Templeton. Victor
Echo 7 Romeo, Julia Tango from Vancouver, British Columbia. Just to note that, say, thanks
for acknowledging the work that the ham operators have been doing since the storm hit New Orleans
last week. There've been a number of stories in the media about how they're helping to keep
communication lines open during this devastating period of time while there are a number of
HF communication nets running constantly. There are also a couple of services that use voice
over IP as their primary method of communication. And there's a couple of links there to the
voice over IP weather net. Both of them. And then the IRIP, IRLP dot net, both of these sites offer
streaming audio of the communications when the nets are active as they probably will be next week.
When the next storm started making their way west. Okay. So in just in this aside,
a lot of people emailed me this. More code is no longer required for access to some parts
of the ham spectrum in the US and is not required at all appear in Canada. Okay. Maybe I should
get a ham license. I wonder what the requirements are here in the UK. Now be kind of cool. That's
really what we need. Isn't it a ham radio here? And we need to assume some slow scan television
and uh, yeah. But it's cool though to see the ham operators that are really helping out with the
hurricane Katrina. Incoming subs-based signal signal signal signal signal signal signal signal signal.
This is revtym from revtym.com. Member of the godcast network. Many people are making requests
to those with any means possible to contribute to Hurricane Katrina's victims.
Truly, this is a tremendous catastrophe, the likes of which we will be learning for months to come.
In Matthew 936, it says when he saw the crowds, he had compassion on them because they were
harassed and helpless like sheep without a shepherd. We all know that there will be time for anger
and analysis, but now is the time for help and for our prayers. Later on, there will be time
for addressing the leadership issues and procedures. What the overwhelmed people need at this moment
is hope, not division. They need comfort, not more distress. So please, focus on being united
in helping the families left so devastated by this tragedy that frankly most of us escaped.
We are asking for you to pray for your prayers. We are asking for compassion and for thoughtful
understanding to all of the hurting during this time of great pain. And most of all, let us bring
hope to the hopeless and to provide strength in the time of enormous hardship. This is Rev Tim
on behalf of the God Cass Network and if you would like to find easy links to the Red Cross,
Convoy of Hope, or Samaritan's Purse, go to RevTim.com and click on the show notes page.
Thank you and may God bless you.
I love Rev Tim. He really, I listen to all his podcasts or as many as possible.
He's always got inspiring. He really is.
So is Warren Atkinson who said, Adam, just listen to your hotel podcast. This is earlier
in the week from New York. Hadn't heard you before. You got potential. But do yourself a favor.
Get yourself a producer. Bit too much dribble, dribble, dribble. Having said that, let me say this.
Keep going. Thanks Warren. I'll try and do something with this.
Merrill. Oh, this is nice. Yeah. This is a Merrill sent in a pod save tune for me to play for it,
which I'm going to play. Said for the last week, I vacation in the Colorado Rocky Mountains.
We opted to drive there rather than fly. And the trek was around 1100 miles from Austin, Texas to
Estus Park, Colorado. Estus, I guess, or Eastus, Estus? No matter how you cut it, I loaded up.
No matter how you cut it. I loaded up a couple of weeks worth of the daily source code into my
iPod with FMI trip. So you could presumably hear it on the the car radio. And you kept me
company on my journey driving into the night. I must say that I've never been so entertained
for such a long period of time. Oh, Merrill, I love spending that in those nights with you.
It's amazing how intimate of an experience it is hearing your voice rambling to me. While driving
on a dark highway at 70 miles per hour around 3am, when my kids in wife with my kids and wife
sleeping in the seats next to me, I couldn't have done the trip without you and your daily source.
So thank you for the podcast, but okay, anyway. So then out of the blue, Merrill
provides a pod save tune, which I did check it out. It is actually pod save. I don't think it's
listed on the pod save music network yet. And it kind of sounded like this was a vinyl recording,
but I think it's intended to sound that way. But it's just a kind of tune that I definitely like.
It's a Dick and Jane. You know, I'm trying to like Dick and Jane. It's got to be good, right?
So for some reason and rightly so, Merrill thought that I would like this tune,
and I do. It's not really bad. It's titled Not the Way You Need.
I burn bridges just to see if they've got a few to burn. I can't get my head to learn.
Yeah.
What the hell is wrong with me? Oh, your shackles just to see if they've got a whole different
way. Can't get my head to learn.
What the hell is wrong with you? You find a little turning around.
Yeah. You claw your way back to me. Can't you get your eyes to see?
What the hell is wrong with you? You tried my every move.
Keep in watch over me.
Can't you get your eyes to see?
I don't love you. I don't love you.
I mean, I can't love you. I can't love you.
I'm the way you need.
I gotta follow my own. Learn to do it alone.
There's no one leaning on me. I gotta set you free.
What the hell is wrong with me? I let you take the lead.
You got my head to learn. Can't get my head to learn.
What the hell is wrong with you? You tried my every move.
I love them to prove to just let me go.
Can't you get your pretty eyes to see? I don't love you.
What I mean is I can't love you.
I can't love you. I'm the way you need.
I'm sorry for this. I ain't kind of like a
a downer laid back maybe a little bit mellow podcast but that's it.
Have yourself a really great weekend everybody. Thanks for listening. Thanks for
subscribing. I'm tired of the rock money and off at the end of the show. I say the
same thing every single time anyway.
Another pod show podcast. Stick it in your ear.