throughout the course of this morning.
In connection with this tool.
I don't have any information at this time.
Hey, everybody.
How are you doing?
This is the Daily Source Code.
Well, a second.
We turn that down for a second.
Daily Source Code episode 2-0-4.
Today is July 7th, 2005,
and the this morning around 9.30 between 9.30 and 10 o'clock.
Everything that was a receiver in our home,
here in the UK in Kilford,
turned into kind of the crisis information flow.
As we now know, and it is 3 or 330, almost 3.40.
Is that 33 people have been killed in the London bombings,
hundreds wounded, some severely,
all kinds of horrible things.
These were obviously terraced attacks,
and although Al Qaeda has claimed responsibility,
we don't really have any details yet.
So it didn't feel like this would be the day to do a normal up in
how happy are we source code?
Let me just listen in for a second,
because they're just doing a press conference,
and they're talking about,
well, each department is talking about the days events,
and it's only turning it on for a second.
It's most personal for a man, as well as the rest of the
multiple police service,
and at the time he's much more banningly,
he's been investigating these incidents,
we're not prepared to discuss how many...
Okay, it sounds like...
Sounds like they're just trying to get everyone out of the city,
they've asked everyone to leave in an orderly fashion,
so it's not to create a tremendous,
you know, blockage of all roads out of London,
but they are asking everyone to go home.
Everything's been canceled.
The city is effectively shut down.
There's no subway services,
buses are being checked continuously,
and there's not a lot of detail information.
Thank all of you for sending me email and text messages,
asking if everything's okay, all three of us are fine,
and we were at home in Guilford,
which is 25 minutes outside of London,
but already tonight at the church here,
there will be a vigil, I guess.
And as more news comes through,
I'll be sure to related either on my weblog at www.curry.com,
or if it makes any sense, then I'll do that on a podcast.
So I want to leave you with some wise words from Stevie Wonder.
Hello!
Good morning, friend!
Here's your friend,
neonounter.
I have serious news to pass on to you.
Who will be my name?
Well, I'm about to say
Couldn't mean the world disaster
Could change your joy and laughter
To tears and may
Is that thought
And he
Come love today
Don't delay
Seniors in my doorway
Hey
For now
We can live long
Stop
Beat me
Before it's gone too long
Oh
The force of evil plan
To make you inspire the nation
And it will if we let it destroy
Yeah
Every time
We all stay
Proposal never imagine
If love and peace you
Treacher
Then you'll hear me
When I say
Whoa
That love
And he
Oh
Don't delay
Seniors in my doorway
Hey
For now
We can live long
Stop
Beat me
Before it's gone too long
Oh
The force of evil plan
And it will if we let it destroy
Don't delay
Seniors in my doorway
You know that hey
It's gone too long
Break any many calls
No
I can see
Oh
God
Something across love
In me
The love of me
Don't delay
Seniors in my doorway
You know that hey
It's gone too long
Break it
It's right to break my thoughts
No
You got a strategy
Before
Seniors in my doorway
You know that hey
It's gone too long
Break any many calls
No
I can see
Oh
God
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, so good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good,, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, bad, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, very good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh