Delta Sierra Charlie 2-7-1
Pacific Coast Hellwaves, World of Tomorrow's Celebrates
Adam Curry's New Direction in Entertainment
Adam Curry was once a videojockey whose talents were relegated to the broadcast airways of cable television
Today he has a new direction
As the pioneer of podcasting, Adam Curry creates downloadable shows each day from the comfort of his own home
This newfangled form of radio highlights Adam's very prominent new direction
The general consensus is that Entertainment as we have known it has grown limp and lifeless claims Adam
And I'm just the man to give the world the new direction they've been searching for
Adam Curry's new direction crosses borders of geography
That new direction extends to an audience of all ages, greens and colors
Given the highly touted demographic Adam Curry reaches, it is apparent every day Adam gives a taste of his new direction
Two males between the ages of 18 and 34
This medium has the ability to reach everyone Adam says proudly
I want my new direction to be the new direction everyone is talking about
My new direction will bring the world to its knees
Adam Curry's goal is to expose his new direction to men, women and children and possibly livestock
Did I say he wants to expose his new direction to men?
Yes, yes I did
Pacifico's hellways world of tomorrow salute you Adam Curry and your new direction
Now matter how small and insignificant that new direction may seem today
We are certain that we have not seen the last of your new direction
Hey Bobby
There are no secrets
Holy information you don't be a liar
Adam Curry
16 hours worth of silk boxer shorts wedged in my ass
And so much then say what's coming up my ears
We don't mean us taking care of him
I like to think I'm flying into the toilet
I guess he's fat on curry
Almost live from the carnage of the 5-7 music Tuesday
Day and over morning after
Leaning back from a chair and a greasy spoon cafeteria
Last night was some beer larynest on our way
But again we're back in a lot of day
Chanting shit sitting at the wall table
Telling jokes playing with the salt
Looking out the window
Girl points two plates of full English circle
We're plenty of scrambled eggs and plenty of fried tomato
Get my phone out
I'm sorry
You fuck up
No no no
I'm fucking I'm no way really
I'm fucking take it a leave it
Believe and then cow wins right
You need to hold it down, Jack, put your phone back
Quit staring, space in the inside, that's that
You want you much more for not hanging on
Stop me if I'm wrong, stop me if I'm wrong
Why should I see better one through the sides
We're richer, for I know I know I'm alright
Now the girl's rude, I know she's rude
But she's rude, right through you, you've got your need soon
I'll hit her voice, yeah it's getting burned
I know you have stuck, thinking I'm burned
My goal, means you can fight with this girl
Just like I said, that's all I know
I'm alright, honestly, it's not like that
Yeah till I've come pranks and like a sack
Jumping when she claps and that
Wait, do you really think I act like I'm telling you
I'm serving the aces and it's game set a match
Perfectly in control of this goal
I'm gonna leave her all, I'll be foldin' I'm holding you tall
Girls' old, high-speed girls
Game over, game over, two Cole
Holding her voice, yeah it's getting burned
I know you have stuck, thinking I'm burned
I know, being she can fight with this girl
Just like I said, that's all I know
I know you have stuck, thinking I'm hurt
I know, being she can fight with this girl
Just like I said, that's all I know
I'm alright, honestly, it's not like that
I know you have stuck, thinking I'm burned
My goal, is getting burned
I know you can't beat some female birth
Don't satisfy yourself, it's a mash-up and something new for something new for the mash-up
archive from James Burling, he actually sent this to me the other day, so just note
you'll take a look at the show, have a bit of a stick for six months or so, keep on rockin'
the free-ruled, anyways, heard the hay mug mash-up on Thursday's show, and suitably inspired
decide to have a crack myself, the result is don't satisfy yourself, mash up the rolling
stones and the streets, and you can check that out at flamemusic.com, very cool, I like it,
it's ended so incredibly British, you know, it's Tuesday, it's November 1, 2005, at least
that's what it is where I am right now, it may, you know, your results may vary due to time
and other weather conditions, it's all pod save music Tuesday, I was listening through a
whole bunch of tracks on the PMN Pod Save Music Network, listening to a couple CDs that
came in and Patricia, you know, she kept walking and saying, oh that's good, what's that, and
oh, that's brother love, right, and just kept going in and out and I said, you know what, why
don't I just play a whole bunch of pod save music tracks, did you hear that? I almost sound
like Susie Chapman, Susie Chapman, what is that worrying here? One of the machines is probably
the crap, but the crap was hasn't been very, hasn't been very good since I got back,
it seems a little sickly, after that Windows update from yesterday just hasn't been the same.
Okay, so we will be talking about a couple other things as well, interesting interview from the
the CEO of SBC, you know, I'm gonna grab, let me do that for you right now, this was something
that was a business week article that was, I don't know if it was pointed out to me if I stumbled
across it. I just want to read you a quote from the CEO Edward Whitaker of SBC Telecommunication,
these guys are huge, right, so they own lots and lots of pipe, lots and lots of telco services,
and here it is, let me just get down to this one piece. Okay, now this is really, really interesting,
because, you know, back in the day, the cable systems totally believed that they ruled the world
and they should be paid, in fact, in many, many countries in the world. Broadcasters actually pay
cable systems to be carried throughout whatever their territory is. Now with the internet, of course,
that works a little bit differently because customers basically pay for access to the net. So the
question here in business week is, how concerned are you about internet upstarts like Google,
MSN, Vonage, and others? And here's the answer, how do you think they're going to get to customers
through a broadband pipe? Cable companies have them. We have them. Now what they would like to
do is use my peat my pipes for free, but I ain't going to let them do that because we've spent
capital, and we have to have a return for it. So there's going to have to be some mechanism for
these people who use these pipes to pay for the court portion they're using. Why should they be
allowed to use my pipes? The internet can't be free in that sense, because we in the cable companies
have made an investment and for Google, or Yahoo, or Vonage, or anybody to expect to use these
pipes for free is nuts exclamation point. Well, ain't that interesting? What the hell does that mean?
You want to get paid both ways? I mean, we're already paying for the access. Now you want to charge
Google and Yahoo to deliver data? I don't know, man. That sounds freaking scary to me, because what's next?
Podcasts, of course, because we're shipping a shitload of data across the pipes, and now we're
going to start charging for it. We got to keep our eye on this dude, man. He's dangerous.
Something deeper, because I need to know there's someone to come hold you and laugh with and
think about when I make up my mind to hold you to know you. I'm a lucky man. Well, yeah,
I'll see the chicks that smoke and drink. I'll be right home when you eat in the glass.
The lips, I'm a massive alien. I know you'll follow me. He's out of your arms. I'll know you'll drown
over me. I don't need to scare you. I'm just telling you how I feel. Just look into my eyes.
Never do you ever try to trust me. It's risky. I'm not trying to catch a hole. I've been through
well. It's for ringing. I'm a thrive of me alone. Yeah, I'm sick of chicks that smoke and drink.
I'm alive and I won't wait for life. The lips, I'm a massive alien. I know you'll follow me. He's out
of your arms. I'll know you'll drown over me. He's out of your arms. I'll know you'll drown over me.
I don't need to scare you. You'll drown over me. He's out of your arms. I'll be right home when you're
I'm sick and sick and sick, that's all
In dream, lie, how we ain't in for life
You live, tell the best you can
The things that are real, I know you
Follow me down from your heart
Don't mess around, no mess around
That's for me, because I know why you're me
Because I know why you're me
Don't mess around, no mess around
From the album of the year
As it's titled, Brother Love, the second chicks
Podsafe, on your daily source code
This is Tuesday, Podsafe, music Tuesday
Just rollin' out a whole bunch of excellent songs
Brother Love was sweet enough to send over a copy of the album
He had sent it while I was in San Francisco
And so of course he sent it to the UK address
Which I gave him earlier
He was here waiting for him with a couple of brother Love T-shirts
One for me, one for Patricia, one for Christina
And he is still without a doubt the undisputed king of the Podsafe music network
Top and pod play
Go check it out at music.podshow.com
I'm amazed, every day there's like
I knew up to 50 to 100 tracks coming in
It's crazy
Yesterday I played
A mini-mini sound seeing tour from Graham Shaw about his Senseo machine
And I was amazed about these different speeds that I heard
I'm like, oh my god, I actually played it for you
Listen to this
Because my Senseo basically makes this noise
But then I was stuck in his cover
I was stuck in his cover when I went into overdrive
Listen to this
Oh man, that's three gears on this thing
Do I have the wrong model?
So I received an email
Adam, the change in tone was me
Clumsily speeding up the dead air to bring my audio feedback down
From a minute 59 to a minute 39
I thought this Senseo noises added something to it
But I didn't meant to think of anything interesting to say
I was my first attempt at anything audio though
And it was done at a single take
When I recorded the first bit I really had my Senseo still on Amazon packaging
Which is sitting next to me, absolutely Graham
It's just freaked me out
So you may want to get audacity
Or some other freeware open source program
And edit that next time
Instead of foolishly
Speeding it up
It really had me freaked out
And I actually I went
I went downstairs
And I made a couple of Senseo
And I tried the dual button
See if it was a dual button thing that you had
For two cups of coffee
But now I know the answer
But of course it is
It is just a thought for the designers
That find machine
No one was received for this discussion about Senseo
Tap up the cards
That card
Hi, I'm Mr John Rob here from topofthepods.com
Last week we heard a message on the daily source code
About a podcast
Having a dilemma about displaying the show notes
That might spoil the content of the show
As you might know
We recorded a daily podcast
Where each show we talk about a topic in the form of top 10 list
Now we had a similar problem with our show notes
Just playing each top 10
And that was spoiling it for the listeners
The solution we came up with
This UCSS
That's cascading style sheets
To hide the spoilers by default
Then use a small piece of JavaScript code
To display them
It saves you having to create two different versions of the show notes
And most importantly
Doesn't spoil any surprises for listeners
Whilst remaining totally search engine friendly
If you'd like to see this in action
And help yourself to the code we wrote
Then head over to topofthepods.com
And we there feel free to check out our show as well
We also noticed that the idols going down
A storm at the pod show headquarters
Now we love this gadget so much
We've teamed up with Firebox to offer podcast listeners
Money off this fantastic gizmo
Just head over to fibox.com
Ford slash top of the pod
To claim your money off found you
So what are you waiting for?
Treeself for Christmas
Thanks Adam
Thanks very much
Bye
Now thank you
Thank you for helping me with
Another eye dog mention
I have to do one once a week in the show
Christine I immediately took it from me by the way
I'm trying to get her to do an endorsement for the for the eye dog
She's already run out of pair of batteries
You have the thing on for like
20 hours straight
Just popping along
It's like you know
The batteries will eventually wear out
But it's interesting to see how they've I'd like to know a little bit more about the programming of the eye dog
How they you know what what
What decisions they made in writing in writing the code because it seems that
It has a certain patterns that the lights move in the ears move when there are strings
And it doesn't really seem to go to a to a beat necessarily
But still it's synchronized
I don't know it sounds like maybe there's some sophisticated
Digital sound processing in there. I have no idea
Let's see
Oh, yes, this is an important thing I have to say
I've received many many emails about this
There is no such thing as a dual CPU iMac stop it you're driving me nuts
Multiple people wrote in about that
Okay, I'm sorry. I thought there was I thought there was going to be a dual processor G5 iMac
I was wrong apparently that's only the desktop
So about I'm real happy with the ones that I have the one here in the cottage and the one at the condo
And people also correctly told me that the 10-foot screen interface that I'm that what I call the 10-foot screen interface is called front row
Right, I'm wondering if there's a way to get front row on different computers if you can
If you can install the software and maybe use a universal remote or buy remote separately
And of course you have to hook up some kind of infrared receiving device because I really do enjoy it
And of course, I still have the the older G5 iMac. I'm too fucking lazy
I'm just too lazy to call up return it everything's working it's installed
It's fine. I don't need the camera and the CPU powers okay for what I'm using it for so I'm not going to take it back
And what's cool though is I do have the other G5 iMac and the condo I have it set up and the middle of the floor with one of the
One of the shades raised just you have to keep the shades kind of closed because
Especially when you're not there and during the day it'll bleach your furniture or the sunlight that comes in through all those
You know wonderful wonderful panoramic view windows
So I've raised it up just a little bit and I can dial into it using iChat and I can see what the weather is in terms of scope
Yeah, yeah, I'm geeky. I know hey, I also received the brand new
Hold on let me just grab it
The brand new mojoan CD these are the guys from Holland that I played before and I think I had somewhat of a
A planetary intergalactic premiere with what I think will be the single like the or the whatever
They're going to be pushing to radio. I think that's what is it my world?
Well, the title of the album is my world and if it's always the same it was I think was always the same is what they're pushing
But I listened to it this morning and there's a lot of great tracks on this you can find that at mojoans.nl
Mojoan ES dot nl
These guys are independent. They've really been working very very hard of known for a number of years
And I just and totally once again in love with their work
Check this out. This is a very very typical low-jones track
Can't get enough on the daily source code
Can't get enough can't get enough
I can't get enough can't get enough
Can't get enough of you
You're gonna be stuck
Trust me
You're gonna drive this car
You're so I'm gonna be played on radio
Trust me
It's terrible in advance
I trust you
You're gonna travel the road
Anywhere the wind blows
This town's much too small
You gonna get them all
The world's a little tiny bowl
Trust me
Can't get enough can't get enough
I can't get enough can't get enough
Can't get enough of you
I smile and be eating
And what you do is made
You gotta move your hips
Fill up your lips
Take silicone tips
And you're gonna make it
Trust me
You gotta go and stop
Follow my advice
One day you realize
I am always right trust me
You'll be fine
Trust me
Can't get enough can't get enough
I can't get enough can't get enough
Can't get enough of you
Can't get enough can't get enough
I can't get enough can't get enough
Can't get enough of you
And if you can't recall what I just said
You got a different story I had in your eye
Playin' another game stuff
Sayin' your match, I found someone new
I had enough of you
I had enough, I had enough of you
I've had enough, I've had enough, I've had enough, I've had enough.
You're absolutely cool.
I've had enough.
When you unwrap a new CD and slide it into your drive slot.
And then iTunes opens up, ready to import it,
and then you get the message saying,
the CDD, date, C-D-D, C-D-B, database,
does not recognize this disk.
You're like, oh, yeah, I'm the first one.
I can enter all the information correctly.
That is, that's like CD porn, right there, man?
Mm-hmm, love that.
By the way, you know, I almost bought the CD-D-B database.
It was in, oh, man, it was, it must have been 1996.
1996 or 1996, maybe even, you know, seven, I think.
And I called the guys up, I said, this is phenomenal.
I want to buy this, you know, this is great.
And they just sold it a week earlier.
And of course, now it's licensed to every single player in the world,
oh, well, what have been good?
Hey Adam says that Tim Smith, I know you get tons of mail,
so I'll keep this one short on your daily source code,
270, you mentioned you were using Windows.
Now, forgive me if I'm mistaken,
but I thought you were an Apple guy.
Why are you, or were you using Windows?
Well, that's it, I guess.
Thanks for finding time to read this.
Maybe you can enlighten us on the next show.
Well, 270, this is 271, real simple Tim.
I have a mix of all kinds of stuff here.
Of course, I'm an Apple guy.
I love Apple computers.
I just, you know, I am totally smoking the crack pipe there.
But you got to have Windows, and I bought a craplet,
which is kind of cool because I have it on top of the podcast complex.
And I use it basically.
I use it as a screen for show notes and emails that want to read.
In fact, I'm reading your Gmail email right now off of the craplet screen.
It's kind of cool because the screen will twist and tilt and turn,
because you're able to turn it all the way back and fold it over
to make it into a tablet.
So I can twist it just perfectly so I can see it.
It's at eye height now.
So that's really, but I use a mix of all kinds
of different operating systems and computers.
In fact, when you have a Mac these days,
you basically also have a Unix machine.
And I find myself increasingly using Unix commands,
just because it's so much faster than starting up a GUI,
of some program, or finding something and dragging and dropping.
And once you know how to tab auto complete paths and file names
in a command line, you're really off to the races.
And you can pipe stuff.
And yeah, if you can do a little bit of shell scripting
kind of on the command line, if you ever learn to do that,
is really going to help you with a lot of shit.
And also when files get locked up and stuff,
it's easy to go in and just sort of rebooting
or whatever other fix there may be if a file doesn't want to delete,
you just go into command line and get rid of it.
By the way, I've also made some horrible mistakes
from doing that.
Well, like RMSH, that was one of my favorites.
We interrupt this podcast to this question.
Who is Matthew Evil?
Official sources give conflicting reports.
Some claim he's an independent musician.
Others say he's an intergalactic superhero.
One report even goes so far as to say he's a ninja barista
with a bad attitude.
So just who is Matthew Evil?
If you think you know, you could win a copy of his new album,
beer and coffee, send your completely fabricated
and absolute baloney biography to who is at Matthew Evil.com.
If your bio gets used on the website, you'll earn a free CD
from Matthew Evil to read the gods on his truth
and a whole lot of fabricated crap.
Visit www.methu Evil.com today.
So what do you think of the new format with the pod save music now?
I don't know if it's sustainable at all if I can find four or five songs
that I really like that I want to play every day.
Having a good one on this Tuesday, Fraut Safe Tuesday.
There was a time when nothing stood in between us.
Now there's a curve in the world so sharp it'll make you bleed.
We don't talk with just puts the clock,
can't find each other in the same old grid that may be a little escape.
What we need.
We love and you work like a dog every morning.
The city's a pain like the loud taste stain on your dress.
Hit in the bay and before you break down,
it don't cause the damn to leave this town.
We don't know the road because we got to get out of this mess.
So let's drive away.
Let the sunlight chase us all day.
Now nothing gonna stay in a way.
Let's drive away.
We're in the song and that took it for granted.
We're bumping the road not really in part of the drive.
Come on, come on to eat self-right.
You made me bleed tonight.
The pain's here so damn good to be alive.
So let's drive away.
Let the sunlight chase us all day.
Now nothing gonna stay in a way.
Let's drive away.
Let the sunlight chase us all day.
Sorry, but I seem fast, but I gotta go in.
It's gotta be more than the coffee shops in the bar.
Lady, maybe it's too late.
Lady, maybe it's just late.
We need to take my hand and get in the car.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
So let's drive away.
Let the sunlight chase us all day.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Call me an 80s-oriented, figure-her'd flag, give you my spend.
Someone else's gotta like the sugar.
Oh yeah.
Matthew Ebo from the bot save music network, check it out at music.botshow.com.
Definitely that top-down driving around sound.
It doesn't quite fit with the weather today in the United Kingdom.
Also, don't have a convertible.
I want to help.
Thanks by the way to the Pacific Coast Hellplayers for the opening of today's Daily Source Code.
Marking my command and nip cough.
It was nice enough to send me that.
Ah yes, my new direction.
It's what everyone's talking about.
Hello Adam.
This is Dave Owen.
It's time.
She will always help me.
Hello Adam.
This is Dave Owen.
A.K.A. On the week.
Formally of Olympia Washington.
Now, living up here in North Vancouver, BC.
Hey, I thought I'd give you a holiday because I was catching up on some shows.
And expresses the empathy for you about your turmoil.
Putting together some of that IKEA furniture.
But I tell you, you're not alone.
You see, just moving up here to Vancouver, I had to get some IKEA gear.
And being a little older and wiser, I got it delivered.
Yet the guys came with the truck on a Sunday to deliver it and looked up at the steps to get
into my house.
Yeah, and they weren't going to do it without the extra fee.
So I had to bribe them with super tasty nugs and a little hash sprinkled on top.
And sure enough, I got the couch flat into the house.
Then it was up to me to figure out how to assemble the thing.
I was so confused.
I figured I might as well record it and I make a podcast out of it.
Now, don't be alarmed.
All my podcasts aren't about assembly and furniture.
And well, I make several of them.
Now, I don't know if you remember a few months back at Nomdex in Seattle hanging out on the balcony
overlooking the cruise ships and joined a dude with my colleague, Cosmo and I.
But since Nomdex, we started busing out a bunch of different podcasts including the club site
Breakfast time podcast.
I can't remember.
Additionally, I make a couple others.
The one that I talk about the IKEA furniture is chug lawn with Uncle Wee.
That's me mostly schlepping my laptop around Vancouver, taking transit, scoring herb, talking
about architecture, economics, transportation, and...
Well, weed.
Notice the scoring weed comes before he talks about architecture.
Additionally, I make a show called Postcards from Gravity Beach.
There's 16 of these up already.
And it's me reading from my literary heroes,
Carawak, Tolstoy, Broad again, James Joyce, etc.
As well as reading some of my own work.
Yeah, I have some audacity to try and follow those guys.
But I'm having a good time with it.
I put some smoking jazz tracks in the background,
or sometimes even play along with some live music.
Finally, for hockey fans, I make one called The Conucks Outsideer for the local hockey team here.
You know, I don't have any inside contacts, so I'm like, I'm just the Conucks Outsideer.
And I'm having a good time with that one too.
Now, that's a lot of podcasts to remember if you want to check them all out.
But you can, they're all listed in iTunes.
Grab postcards from Gravity Beach, club site breakfast time podcast,
Chugle on with Uncle Ween, and Conucks Outsideer.
Now, the easy way to do that is just go to UncleWeed.net
and pick up all the feeds there.
And don't worry, all these podcasts have lots of shows already,
so they're not disappearing.
Uh-huh, Adam, I guess it's just one more thing than closing.
Spark one for you.
You know, we've been talking a lot about podcasting and education
about using RSS feeds and enclosures and podcast pod catchers for lectures.
And there's been some debate about that, but, you know,
luckily, the debate seems to be kind of raging on outside of the educational system
because colleges and schools are catching on.
Hey, Adam, we're back in Dota Sierra, Charlie 267.
You were talking about universities and podcasts.
And you said, of course, it's great to be able to have an RSS feed
from either a certain course, a certain class, a certain professor, a certain lecturer.
I think it should be turned around.
You damn right, it should be turned around.
Who wants to hear from me, a lowly lecturer, when you can hear from our far more exciting
and engaging students, no one.
That's why here at the I-Generation Honours course in Communication Studies
at the University of Western Australia, the students are doing podcasts
as their major assignments.
We've got everything from an alternative commentary to the Simpsons
to a parotic pod play, satirizing the bold and the beautiful.
If you're all your listeners want to know more, you can visit us at
iphonegeneration.blogspot.com on the web, all search for
I-Generation in the Archions Music Store.
For a quick test, here's something every good play needs.
An Intimition from Queen of Petey.
No, no, no, so I cut the intermission out.
I didn't have enough time.
I just saw the funniest thing happen.
I'm looking at my window.
And we have, of course, more painters and guys here today.
So there's a car parked in front of our house.
Did you ring the bell?
In the cul-de-sac, and I saw the neighbor back as car.
Oh, man.
He backed his, his beamer.
Three something.
Three series.
He backed it out.
And backed it right into the, into the painter's car.
And.
Yeah, I bet she rang the doorbell.
Well, I can't stop the show for that.
I'm sorry.
I used to sneak around in order to see you on Saturday nights.
I was 15 and you used too much aquanette.
I was supposed to be asleep, but I just couldn't resist the lure of
headbangers ball.
Hey, I hear you're really into that show lost.
My husband and I might have something right up your alley.
Hello, Adam.
This is Ryan Jen somewhat jealous husband.
And yeah, we're so much into lost.
That's filmed right here on this island on Luhavey.
That we started a podcast devoted entirely to the show.
It's called The Transmission.
Now that Apple and ABC have partnered together to sell episodes of this great show
on the iTunes music store.
Think of our show as a free perfect companion.
On every show, we do a recap of the last episode.
We analyze it to death.
And then we take listener comments.
We listen to some theories, which is the best part.
We talk about some production news, spoilers, rumors, all kinds of stuff.
So Adam and anybody who is a fan of what Stephen King calls the best show on television
come check out The Transmission.
We even do a special enhanced version with chapters and graphics for those of you
cool enough to be using iPods.
You can find us on the iTunes music store.
You can just look for us under a lost or you can come straight to our website at
HavaEup.com slash lost and listen to it straight from the site.
And thanks for your great show, Adam.
I still love you.
Hey.
Yeah, I love you too, baby.
Oh, they got insurance forms out now.
I'm in front of that.
Hey, and never ending quest to find a new Christmas hit.
Check out Natalie Brown.
Oh, they got insurance forms out now.
Oh, they got insurance version out now.
Okay.
But as you go away, what's funny is to ride?
Dashing through the snow, in one horse open sea,
Or the fields we go, laughing all the way,
There's on both tailoring, making spirits bright
What fun it is to ride and sing a sing song tonight
Chicken chicken one day, all the fun it is to ride in one horse open sea,
Chicken five, chicken five, chicken one way, what fun it is to ride?
Or the fields we dash, dancing through the snow,
Chicken five, chicken one day, all the way, chicken one day, all the fun it is to ride in one horse open sea,
Chicken five, chicken one day, all the fun it is to ride in one horse open sea,
Chicken five, chicken one night, all the fun it is to ride,
I think we discussed this before, you know, shades of Mariah Carey only, goodbye Mariah.
We've got our own Podsafe Mariah and Lovener.
Now what's this? Ah yes, of course, the music tells me I'm ready.
Hi Adam Steve Webb here, thanks for listening to the invitation I appreciate it.
The anniversary, the one-year anniversary for life's spring is coming up.
It's going to be actually right after the podcast Expo.
You remember this?
When I go out girl?
Okay, hold on, I'll tell you what, why don't you listen to this promo, I'm going to let the dog
out of my office here.
It's almost like the old days, isn't it?
Hitting you right between the years with the message of hope, love and good news.
This is life's spring, and I'm Steve Webb, your host.
Hey Adam, thanks for this brand new avenue with communication we all call podcasting.
And thanks everybody for listening.
I'm out of here.
Thanks everybody.
The Lord says everybody, give me a bow.
Oh man, perfect. I'm telling you, I love religious podcasts.
There's broadcasters of all sorts.
I get to kick it.
Yeah, I sent that promo into your way back in December.
And then I was just really tickled when you played it for me on the daily source code.
But I've got an invitation for you.
This I think would be totally unexpected by the rest of the community.
And that would be how about Adam Curry being interviewed by one of the godcasters.
And I'm trying to put together really special show.
And I thought it would be really great if we could do a little
little conversation you and me.
I think it'd be fun.
I hope you're enjoying your time at home with the girls.
I know it's been a long time for you.
And so I'm sure it's good to see Christina and Patricia.
Please tell the two of them that I said hi as well.
And I also wanted to say thanks again in person here as a work for playing Jimmy Bradshaw's music.
If you go or to the PMN listing for Jimmy, you'll see that several podcasts have played his music.
And I think that's great.
He's enjoying it.
And I think that we're helping to get the word out as well.
So Adam, enjoy your weekend and enjoy your time back home before you come back to California here.
I do hope to see you in Ontario.
But if not, I'd sure like to talk to you for the life spring podcast.
Thanks again Adam and blessings on you.
Oh, thank you.
It's so sweet.
So Patricia came back.
She stood with the guys outside for a while trying to figure out what it happened.
I wonder she's going to come up and tell me what's so amazing.
It was like a slapstick.
It must have been the sun or something that was in his eyes.
Hey, it's Pod said music Tuesday on the Daily Source Code.
We have one more pod save tune than roll out for you after one more piece of feedback.
With $600 worth of rest.
Strap to my bonus.
I'm Stalin, man.
Hi Adam.
This is Graham coming to you from beneath the huge beautiful skies of North
England with little feedback on the DSC.
First heard about it when I steep mentioned it in his keynote a few months back when they
launched.
First mentioned the iTunes were going to be supporting pod cast.
I got to say that initially I thought you were just some big headfag with a fucking ego
problem.
Jesus, man, you got stuff to say.
I've just got so excited about all this stuff.
You've got going down at podshow.com and hearing about all the new great stuff with pod casting
and it's really, really blowing my skirt up right now.
I'll tell you.
The pod save music network.
I've been kind of trolling around that just recently and it's just fucking phenomenal, man.
I tell you, I discovered this artist called Alison Crowe who you've just got to get some
of her stuff and put it on your pod show.
Outstanding stuff.
I also thought it would be really useful to have an extra genre for sort of jingles and intros and
outro and all that for us kind of newbie pod casters who don't know how to put all that stuff
together to be able to download stuff and use it on their shows which would be kind of
cool too.
That's pretty much what I've got to say.
Just want to keep up the good work, Adam.
We love what you're doing.
Really excited about it.
I don't know how many people out there.
Share your excitement or whatever.
This must be how Henry Ford must have laid a wake at night thinking how the fuck am I going to take all of this
great technology and put it in a hands of just everybody.
There's some good stuff going down and it's interesting to be the part of the next real big thing.
Talk to you soon.
Keep it real.
Take care.
You know, I'm thinking that Henry Ford was probably laying a week at the laying a wake
at night going.
How do I get a hammer in the back seat?
Or pod safety is the wind up the show for today.
Bob Gentry and upside down.
I've been talking in my last sleep when I'm waking up.
Well, my tongue is tight.
I've been thinking I should leave.
Instead of waiting for her when the time is right.
I've backed the bags under my eyes.
Well, I've seen enough to know what it's like.
Just turning me upside down.
Tell me what I've done wrong now.
All I can do is try it.
When everything's breaking me down.
Looking at me down side out.
Well, those rules got changed somehow.
Maybe it's suicide.
To stay here and just stick around.
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now.
Till now.
I've been walking in my last sleep when I'm waking up.
Well, my legs are tight.
I've been thinking I should leave.
I've been walking in my last sleep when I'm waking up.
When everything's breaking me down.
Looking at me down side out.
Well, those rules got changed somehow.
Maybe it's suicide.
To stay here and just stick around.
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now.
Till now.
I've been afraid to just walk out.
Ain't no way to stop me now.
I've been walking in my last sleep when I'm waking up.
Looking at me down side out.
Well, those rules got changed somehow.
Maybe it's suicide.
To stay here and just stick around.
I was able to hide every bruise on my body till now.
Oh, till now.
I've been walking in my last sleep when I'm waking up.
Until now.
Oh, man.
I could just play all those songs over again tomorrow.
The same type of show.
Just loving it.
Of course, I'm that giddy at this configured the valve process.
So you heard me kind of switch it on there in the last moments of the show?
Oh, yeah.
That was great, Curry.
Idiot.
And just in on the Gmail.
Hmm.
Hi Adam.
I work for Channel 4 News.
That's over here in the UK.
We're making a feature for more for news to broadcast this Friday on the phenomenon of porn
casting.
I think it would be awful to consider running such a piece without your input.
So if you have the time, I'd like to come to see you at some point this week to conduct an interview on the subject.
The interview would be short and sweet or as we say.
New style.
Hopefully I could be out of your hair and have another hair joke, man.
Hopefully I could be out of your hair and a half hour or so.
If you're too busy, maybe we could set up an eye chat or something similar.
That would be kind of cool.
Talk about porn casting on the eye chat.
Hmm.
Not to think about that if I have time or not.
All right.
DailySourceco.com is where you can find the latest show and where you can find the RSS feed to
use to subscribe.
I'm also putting the iTunes link these days in the direct show notes.
Not in the extended show notes, but in the direct show notes.
And if you're got anything to say about the songs, check it out there or send me email
Adam at curry.com.
And I'm back tomorrow for the hump day edition.
I'm the source code.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.