Daily source code, May 12th, 2005.
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear
since radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
It was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Everybody straight from Curry Cottaging Guild for this is your Daily Source code.
Oh, right-hand another bright sun shiny day in the UK.
You know, I don't know where that bad rap comes from that it's always bad weather
and Britain is just not true.
It may be a little bit cold, but the sun really makes up for it.
And I am a little lagging today.
I had some visitors last night.
I'll tell you all about that.
Power, power, power, power, and power.
And coming up of course today, the promos got a lot of those.
Got some pod safe music that I want to play for you as usual.
Also, young Polettes hit test.
Number 38 already.
I've been sitting on that for a couple of days.
I just haven't had time to work it into the show.
And some email.
Got emails to talk about that came in through at amercurry.com.
Unfortunately, I noticed too late that I only have two sheets of paper left.
Actually, three sheets of paper left in the printer.
So, I kind of like switch between applications between recording and readings.
So, bear with me today.
Power, power, power, power, power, power, power, power.
So, a couple of days ago, I think it was Monday.
I received an email from corona one.
That is the handle of one of the chopper pilots that we flew with when I was in Iraq last
year.
That was February, 2004.
When the Dutch Marines were over there and we did a live radio broadcast for our entire
week.
And I've kept in touch with most of the guys, you know, some of them are off to Afghanistan now,
actually.
And it turns out that, oh, bon, go ahead, sir.
It turns out that the Dutch pilots, and I'm talking about Shenukh, primarily Shenukh
helicopters.
If you don't know what a Shenukh is, that's Helicopter with two, two rotor heads.
So, not two rotor blades, but two rotor heads.
So, you got the rotors on the front and rotors on the back.
It's, you know, the big one that can transport, like I don't know, was at 25 or 30
people and all kinds of different configurations.
That's where we actually flew in Iraq.
They also fly cougars and think they used to do links or something like that.
But these guys apparently are so good that they train pilots all over the world, particularly
in the simulators.
It also turns out, you know, this, that there's a Dutch company in, in, uh,
hoofed daughter, if I believe it is, who really farms out most of the flight simulators
all over Europe.
And, uh, I guess since there's a Dutch connection there, the, the Dutch pilots are the
ones that train everybody.
So, don't doubt that Han, that's his, has his name, that's Han, uh, that's hotel alpha
November, not Oscar November.
Although he's quite a Han, uh, it turns out that he, um, uh, is about, uh, located
about 35, 40 minutes away from Guilford, uh, where the cottage is.
And, uh, you know, he sent me an email, he said he'd seen some of the, the rag mags
in Holland.
He said, you know, fuck them, don't, you know, don't get brought down by whatever
the media saying.
Which was nice of him to say, but, you know, not that I really let that happen anyway.
And, uh, he said he was here for a couple of weeks.
And, uh, so I sent him a mail back and gave him my current phone number because he only
had my, uh, my Dutch cell phone.
He called me.
He said, well, you know, you know, we're, we're here with a couple of guys.
And, uh, we'd love this type of ice cooker for some coffee.
I said, yeah, anytime you want.
Just how about tonight?
So, last night around 8 o'clock, uh, four, uh, four of these guys showed up on my door
steps.
Two bad Patricia wasn't here.
She totally would have, almost, and just my microphone here.
She totally would have enjoyed it.
They showed up with flowers, a typical Dutch tradition, you know, whenever you go to visit
someone, even if it's just for coffee, you bring a little bouquet of flowers.
And so they, they brought, uh, their obligatory, obligatory bouquet, which was very nice.
And we had a great time.
And we, of course, we had a lot of aviation talk and, uh, talk a lot about Afghanistan.
Um, NATO is now, um, has about 9,000 troops in, uh, Afghanistan.
I'm not quite sure what the mission is other than peacekeeping because it seems that, uh,
it's still kind of messy over there, uh, Karzai, you know, that's the, I think that Karzai
is the dude who, um, who has the cape and the funky hat, which, as a total shill, you
know, he, I think he used to be on the board of directors of some oil company or something.
Um, so he's now the president officially elected and he said, oh, we need some help, you
know, and then, uh, there you go, uh, Yaptop Schreffer, um, that's the official pronunciation
as Dutch guy.
Uh, you might know him as Jep De Hoopsheffer, uh, he's the head of, uh, NATO right now.
He said, yeah, no problem with send everybody over.
So I think, uh, a couple of shinooks are over there and, uh, lots of the, uh, the crews
that were that, uh, I met in Iraq or now, also over there.
And of course, they're saying, hey, come on over, you know, and I can do some podcasting
from there.
So, uh, I, uh, I'm, I've been, I've been contemplating it.
I wouldn't mind going, actually.
I have no idea what, uh, what the situation is or what's going on, but it might be fun to do
that.
So we'll see if we can, uh, move the, uh, uh, uh, I guess it's the Air Force, enough of the
Air Force of the Marine.
I guess it's just the Air Force right now that's there.
See if we can get him to, uh, to, uh, to give me a ride over and, uh, we could hang
up for a little bit.
That might be an interesting podcast.
If I can get some connectivity to upload, uh, speaking of, um, aviation, uh, I, uh, I've
seen this before, but I figured I just, I read a couple of them off, um, Peter George sent
me the aviation gripe sheet.
And I have to know that, uh, particularly in commercial aviation ventures, there's always
a little bit of, I'd say, healthy tension between, uh, engineers who maintain, um, uh, uh,
the machines and pilots.
And this is, uh, some actual maintenance complaints submitted by, uh, quantas.
That's Australian, uh, the Australian Airlines.
The quantas crews, the pilots, and the solutions recorded by the maintenance engineers.
Uh, by the way, I want to point out quantas is the only major
airline that has never, ever had an accident, but you probably knew that if you ever saw, uh,
rain man.
So, uh, I just run out a couple of these stuff.
They're pretty funny.
So, pilot says, um, left inside main tire almost needs replacement.
And the ground crew says, almost replaced left inside main tire, pilot says, test flight
okay, except auto land very rough, engineers, auto land not installed on this aircraft.
Pilots says something loose in cockpit solution, something tightened in cockpit.
Pilots says dead bugs on windshield and the engineer say, life bugs on back order.
Pilots say auto pilot in altitude, hold mode produces a 200 feet per minute descent.
So, and the engineer say, cannot reproduce problem on the ground.
And it just goes on and on and on and on and it's a fucking hilarious.
And of course, all, uh, I'll post a copy of that on, uh, on the show notes for today's
a daily source code.
So, uh, after that visit last night, even though we didn't do any beer drinking,
which is very typical of, of, of people in aviation, I'm just tired.
And it's also of course, because Patricia's still on her, on her personal slash business trip.
And, um, so I'm, uh, I'm being Mr. Mom.
Oh, by the way, um, the dinner that I had at TGI Friday is where Christina had invited her
current boyfriend, um, Benji, he couldn't make it because he, uh, I guess he, uh,
goes to the gym on, uh, on Monday night, so it was a Monday, Tuesday night.
So I have nothing to report on fortunately, but she did bring her girlfriend, uh, Ellie.
And they're both in the same class, same grades, uh, many of the same classes that they take
together. Uh, so I did get a lot of information and intel.
Actually, much more than I really wanted to know.
Yeah, thanks for everything you're dealing with podcasting and hate all you daily source code listeners.
And Adam, are you, or any of the daily source code listeners like?
Because it plays the same songs over and over again.
Well, then why don't you check out the defy radio podcast at defyradio.blogspot.com.
We've got some great music. You would not hear otherwise, uh, bands like architect.
If you're sick of all the same radio stuff over and over again, defyradio and turn on defyradio.
Defyradio.blogspot.com. Well, isn't that a coincidence? Just having to look in the
pod save music bins and submit your pod save music to podsafe at podshow.com.
It is a great tune. So check out the defy radio podcast and architect now on the source code with most of us.
We've got it all figured out. We've got nothing left to lose. We've got it all figured out.
We've got it all figured out. If we're gonna make a movement then I hope we make it soon.
And if we're gonna make a movement we need you, uh,
most of us screaming at the radio.
Now we'll always be on our feet so we'll always be on our feet.
We've got it all so figured out. We've got one thing left to do. We've got it all so figured out.
We'll make our movement and if we're gonna make our way out then I thought we'd make it soon.
If we're gonna make our way out we need you now, most of us screaming at the radio.
Now we'll always be on our feet so we'll always be on our feet so we'll always be on our feet.
We'll always be on our feet so we'll always be on our feet so we'll always be on our feet.
Oh, stars screaming at the radio. We'll change, most of us screaming at the radio.
We'll change, most of us.
Sir, do you know what a podcast is? The podcast is something that you hold your little eye
pod and I believe it might be a cradle where you put it inside the cradle if I'm not mistaken that
things that I'd nature. So you have no idea what a podcast is. I don't have no idea what a podcast is.
I think it's a blog of some sort. Do you know what a podcast is? It's supposed to be a program
that can be captured to go into an iPod. I don't think that's really the way people think about it.
I know what it is I've heard of it but I don't really understand the concept.
Now, ma'am, do you know what a podcast is?
Well, no, yes, I don't know.
So it does have something to do with vegetables.
For the morning, for the night, no.
And it banana is when you say what you're saying when you're saying what you're saying.
So all in all, in your words, a podcast is...
I like it a lot. Excellent, thank you very much.
Thanks to Jeremy Coleman, the guys over serious. We're putting that together for me.
Yeah, we still got a long way to go on podcast. You know, yesterday, oh, we moved my mic here.
I was going, you know, we have everything now on the pod show servers, all the podcasts,
the pod squad and daily source code. And so I have a better access. We actually have finally
have real access to my stats. And I found out something very interesting. First of all, each
individual daily source code, and it does vary, is downloaded, because I can, of course,
you know, tell if someone has actually been listening to it. That would require DRM digital
rights management, which is such a horrible word for actually something pretty cool,
you know, because you're your player, you know, MP3 player, actually can tell if you press
stop or, you know, pause or what you skipped. And it can actually send that information somewhere.
And there would be some great reasons to be able to send that back. You know, how about podcast
Ali, a bit Chris McIntyre would love having some of that info to publish it. But of course,
so we immediately associate DRM with not being able to copy files, which of course is also a part of it.
But so I certainly talk of downloads. Each individual show of the daily source code receives
anywhere from 75,000 to 100,000 downloads, individual unique downloads, a couple of interesting things.
Of that number, and this is what really blew me away, about 20 to 25,000 actually are downloaded
by iPodders. So that means that really only, well, let's say I'm just going to be conservative,
20% receive it through an iPodder, through a subscription, and the rest all
downloaded by clicking on the link on daily source code.com or on curry.com.
So that really tells me a hell of a lot. First of all, there's a big relationship between
podcasters and the audience. It's actually the audience with the content, which is extremely nice.
The second thing it tells me is, damn, we got a lot of work to do. At least if we're talking
about iPodders and really building up the Tvo experience and having things just show up,
could also mean, of course, that bandwidth has gotten so good that people don't mind waiting for
things. But I think we really have a lot of evangelizing to do. And also what's interesting
is that each individual show, it's not like everyone listens to it on Thursday or on Friday,
when it when it shows released. In fact, quite the opposite. It takes up to, well, sometimes up to
four weeks for really the downloads to slow down to a couple of days. It's even after two weeks
you're seeing thousands being downloaded every single day. So I guess the whole concept of time
shifting really goes much further than when I publish it. And when you theoretically have it
automatically downloaded, the actual consumption of it really differs. And I think about it,
it makes sense. Because people, maybe you catch up on a couple of shows over the weekend or you
save stuff, you know, you just, I don't come in a download five or ten podcasts because it
is a goma trip or I'm taking a plane ride or something like that. So I always thought there was
the other way around. I always thought that that in essence, we probably had 80% of people were
subscribed through iPodders and 20% were downloading it at random, but it turns out to be
exactly the opposite. And another statistic, which blew me away, which was in the Wall Street
journal yesterday. Here's a riddle for you. What percentage? Now, you know that the people are
using iTunes, music store and Rhapsody or whatever, all these different music services to buy
music legally online. Apple is doing what it's like 1.2 million songs a day that they're
that people are downloading and buying. So what percentage do you think that is of the entire music
business? I got to tell you that I really thought it was much, much larger. It's only 2%.
Can you believe that? It's only 2% of the entire revenue of the music industry. So, you know,
that's a lot to think about. And then something showed up in email,
hold on after I said, I don't have my printer as on a paper or so. I finally received the open letter
to the podcasting community from the, um, what is it? The pod spec working group. And it sounds
like a pretty good idea. Let me see if they have a, let's say you were out. What is the URL of this?
Of course, I'll put that in the show notes as usual. Um, the URL is pod spec WG. And I'm sorry,
PSWG dot blogspot.com. And I like the idea what they're saying here because, um, so the basically
it's an open letter to podcast software developers, directory managers, content produces content creators
and listeners. Hey, I fit in every single one of those categories. Um, we form the podcast specification
working group because we believe further collaboration can eliminate barriers to the growth of the
listening audience. We propose further to further refining existing standards. I don't know what the
standards are, um, or what you want to refine and create new ones with, uh, with the necessary. I
guess that should be one necessary. Um, the groups current aims are to enable one click subscription.
Yeah, that would be nice. We haven't even figured that out in the weblog world yet. So I don't know
how that's going to go. Um, standardization of metadata, describing podcast, so directory services
and users can more easily find content. I'm all for that. Of course, that's, you know, part of that
is how we fill out our ID3 tag information. And I like this idea very much, but I was severely disappointed
when I went to the website. And it doesn't seem like it's a very independent group because there's
basically three iPodder applications are listed there on their links page, uh, to Jay Potter
and, um, two other ones I can't remember offhand. I like, you know, that kind of sucks. You know,
so, you know, that's not an open working group in my mind. Either you put everyone's iPodder on
there and solicit everyone to, you know, to list their application on your page or you do nothing.
So that was a bit of a disappointment. So I'm not going to join up yet until I, you know, find
out if there is some kind of ulterior motive behind behind that. Which I'm not against by the way,
but, you know, this comes across as like a real open thing. And, you know, if they're promoting
only specific applications that that doesn't seem entirely fair. I just wanted to mention about
architect, the song that I played there before the promo, uh, which actually had bits of that song,
used to be in Pensacola, Florida. And a month ago, they moved to Nashville, Tennessee,
uh, obviously amazing rock and roll. Uh, I'd like that very much, Brian Witt sent that into me,
so appreciate that Brian. Okay, you listening to the daily source code. My name's Adam Curry,
and he is another interesting podcast you might want to check out.
I'd now a public service announcement for listeners of the Daily Source Code.
Hi. My name is Chris. And like a lot of Americans, I have an elderly parent to take care of.
Morning, son! Oh, hi, Dad. Where are you off to this morning? I'm going to do some yard work.
I got my plaid shorts, my black socks, and my white shoes on. I'm a sleeveless shirt.
I'm going to get the Rototiller and Rototill the garden. Uh, Dad, we have a rooftop garden.
This is an apartment building. Oh, do we? Well, in that case, I'm off the Rototill the garden and put it
in a new skylight. See ya! As you can imagine, my father has some pretty strict and expensive
medication requirements. So expensive, in fact, that even with my health care coverage,
I just can't afford to keep up with his medication and we've had to cut back on his dosages.
And frankly, I don't think that's fair to someone who's contributed so much to our society.
It's senior citizens, like my father.
Hey, son, guess what? There already was a skylight up there. Yeah, I know, Dad.
Well, you got two now. I think I'll go put a third one in. Maybe over the baby's room.
By the way, how old is the baby now? He's 25, Dad. Yeah, they're so cute when they're that age.
So make sure to call your congressman and senator and tell them to vote for initiatives
that keep medication costs low and to protect our senior citizens. Thank you.
T-E-K-N-I-K-A-L-D-I-F-I-K-U-L-T-I-E-S. You are experiencing technical difficulties. Please stand by.
Makeins of each track or pot life, of course, talk about it and if you like and be promoted.
If not, you may attain a dignified science. So take a listen to next big thing, Radio at next big thing,
www.lipsen.com. Or visit the website at www.nixbigthing.ca.ca.
On is everyone in service, on our Canadian Bible opinion. I'm there as well through my questions. We're at them.
Yeah, right on. Okay, uh, I was, I was going to say, I was going to say something very prolific.
I'm sure a whole lot of seconds. Let me look at my notes again.
Oh, dude. Okay. I've told me to mess this up now.
Really, really done a bad job. I have some email that I wanted to read.
Hold on. Just bear with me, please. Again, my, my printers out.
And, oh man, I closed up the entire file of notes that I had.
Hold on. Oh, man. Maybe I should just leave it for what it is.
What I put that in. Where did I put it? Oh, here we go. Okay.
It's opening up kind of slowly. I have, I've really done a lot of rewiring in the studio. Okay. So now, of course,
the thing is like, frozen up. Ah, there we go. Don't you just hate it when you hear people messing
with their computer? It doesn't not just totally freaking suck. Okay, here we go.
There we go. Email from Joe Schmidt. This is interesting because this is going to put me on a
sound seeing tour. I love doing the sound seeing tour. Adam, first one, uh, you know, a source
co-blow, a boin, boin, boin, boin, boin. I don't drink coffee, but if I did, I would definitely buy a
senseo from you. I wanted to ask you, uh, if you had any information on the Millennium Vault 2000,
which is located in Guilford Castle. I recently had a post to my blog about the world's largest
time capsule. According to Google is located in a sewer in Nebraska and Joe lives in Omaha.
But I found that Guilford is home to the Millennium Vault 2000. It appears to be much bigger than
the one in Nebraska. A problem is it isn't very well documented on the net and I couldn't find
any pictures of it. So I thought I would ask you a Guilford local. If you had any, uh, to add any info
to add or pictures that I could see of the structure. So, uh, I'll put a link to your post, uh,
in the show notes, Joe, and I will definitely have a look. I had not, not been to the Guilford
castle yet. Um, so, uh, I say that's perfect for a sounding tour. Be on a look out for that sometime next.
Hey, Adam, this is another hit test and this one is created in the home studio with all the
equipment, uh, and it's probably the last time I'll be open. You got extra equipment at your house,
able to do that because this week is the first week of my rehabilitation program and I'll
only be taking my notebook and cast Blaster as you know. Um, because I don't know if I'll be having
internet access this first week. This hit test has been made in advance. Oh, by the way, thanks
Kevin for creating the, um, hit test announced the guy edition. It was fun creating it and it really
sounded great. I love the tour. And suddenly, everyone wants to do a hit test for me right now.
Don't let him do it, but certainly he's not going to happen. Oh, Russ, there is some special occasion
and, by the way, in the future, it's certainly possible that you'll be hearing a lot more from us
and that's Kevin and me then. Uh, okay, something going on there. As always, three intros and three
answers. All right, and this is number one. It sounds a little bit like rockwell, somebody's
watching me, but I couldn't really tell. And this is number two. Uh, okay, I give, give me a little more
than that. Yeah, and that's always impossible. And the final one, number three.
Stand by me. I think it's stand by me. And times up and this is answer number one.
Yeah, it's rockwell. Got it.
And somewhere you can hear Michael Jackson's in the background, that's right. And they're
a good paranoid. Somebody's watching me. Like the paparazzi.
Somebody's watching me.
All right, well, and somebody's watching me. And so number one in today's hit test,
and answer number two is probably a bit difficult because the clip was very reassured.
It's the distinctive sound of the bass or the beginning of this track.
You gotta stand out.
may be together, we can get somewhere. And ever places better.
Fatherly, we together you a neat find, we're the kind of dicen going on. We'll take a faster
record, and keep on grinding.
Several members would work out, down in your car to the back of the Mickeyç‹.
See the lights stay out with both of them
You're on the next map round my children
Oh my god
And I'm feeling that I'm alone
And I'm feeling I could be someone
Be someone
It's Rishi Chapman
And her song, Fast Car
And so number two in today's hit test
And this is answer number three
The zombie
The time of the season
Let it try
With pleasure
It's the time
Of the season for love
Answer number three in today's hit test
The zombies and the time of the season
And by the way all the intro and the clips
Were partly edited by Richard
Thank you
And he'll be probably helping me out
So with the editing stuff in the coming months
Because it seems like I won't be having all the time I need
To create everything I need for the hit test
Well, that's it then for today
As always, feedback is welcome at hittest.gmail.com
And you can find the hittest and the hittest podcast
And the information about it
And the hittest podcast has been there for
I guess more than a month now
And I promise that
When I got the time
When I'm in Apple Doran
I'll be creating one as soon as possible
Okay, that's it then
Thank you for listening
And keep in mind that it's could be a week or so before
The next one will be a week or so
I hope I'll be able to create one sooner
But it all depends on the internet access
And when the line will be connected
So thank you for listening
See you next time
Bye bye
Thank you very much
Young pull out everybody
Young pull out.nl
Young pull out.com
And you definitely besides just the regular hit test
That I play on the source code here
Have a listen to one of his hit test podcasts
The really good is very personal stuff in there
And that's definitely something I want to
Also play on on the serious pod show
And good luck young with the rehabilitation
And let me know if you run into problems with the
With the internet connection
Maybe I can put in a couple of calls for you
Hey, if you want to submit a mashup
To the daily source code pod show
It's a mashup
Let me make sure it's right out
Yeah mashup
At podshow.com
If you have pod safe music
You'd like to have played on any of the shows
It's a pod safe at podshow.com
And of course anything else
Promotes you name it
Just in it off to
Submit at podshow.com
Watch social club house band auditions
Day one
Next
You're all
Thank you very much next
Oh
No next
Dog watch social club
Brought to you
WWW dot dog watch social club dot com
I am curry
You big pod daddy
Nihao
Sa jaha
Hello everyone I'm podcast random
Make a China
Specifically in Taiwan
Yes, that's right
The first podcast coming to you
And both English and sometimes in Mandarin Chinese
And maybe even Taiwanese
Who knows
In any case that I'm just gonna let you know about our new show
Getting a leg up on music
Culture
Information
The whole point is to share
Music from Taiwan
Both from local Taiwanese people
Foreigners living in Taiwan
Or joint league
And also to share with Taiwanese and Chinese friends
From a great music
From
Erica
So
We did well let you know to tune in
And keep informed
This is some great sounds
Get some old Chinese culture in your ear
Yeah
This is the greatest since take up
And I'm telling you
Anyhow
Be sure to look for us at getting a leg up
And of course
The girl is
Leg up dot
L-I-B-S-Y-N dot com
Leg up L-E-G-U-P dot
Come on and get a leg up and tune in
Later on at a curry
She's very good
Yeah, all right
You know that is the market to be in these days
Man, China is just rocking
I really like the visit there too
Any more podcasts ors out east
Let me know
Let me know you're out there
So
Thank you all very much for listening
Stay subscribed to the Daily Source Code
You can find the podcast feed at dailysourcecode.com
Comments
Of course can be left there
Or on www.curry.com
Show notes is
Where you can find that on both of those sites
Obviously
Pretty soon
My new dailysourcecode.com
Site will be up
Working hard on that behind the scenes
Which means
I'm done crap
It's up there
It's got to get some design going
If you've got a design
Please
I'd love some help on that
Feedback to me personally
Adam and Curry dot com
If you want to submit something
Those three addresses
Once again
You can find them in the show notes
And for one more time
For promos and podcasts
It's a bit at podshow.com
Free of pod save music pod save at podshow.com
And for mashups
A little low on the mashups these days
But thanks to the serious show
I can play a lot of them
So
Bring them on at say mashup at podshow.com
Alright
Tomorrow
Thank God it will be Friday
Patricia's coming home this weekend
Can't be soon enough
As far as I'm concerned
Good man
Doing overtime
I'd really do miss her
Thanks for listening everybody
Stay subscribed
I'll talk you tomorrow
Bye bye