POT show.
We bring good podcasts to life.
Delta share a Charlie.
3-0-1.
Come to daddy.
You're my think.
But we're not ready yet.
But we should get a pet.
You're my think.
But don't think.
Let's have a baby.
I'm my think.
My hair's a little grey.
I'll beat you all to play.
You're a pink.
You're my think.
Let's have a baby.
Oh baby.
The city closed at me on max.
A million.
Children in a baby's sack.
The city closed at me on max.
A million.
Children in a baby.
Oh baby.
My say.
We just don't have the space they might say.
The city closed at me on max.
A million.
Children in a baby's sack.
The city closed at me on max.
A million.
Children in a baby's sack.
The city closed at me on max.
A million.
Children in a baby.
Children in a baby's sack.
So, candy butchers, let's have a baby!
Found that on the podcast, I'm using Network brand new, of course we know from what to do with
Michael Cooltune, from the Hang-On Mike CD.
Hey everybody, how you doing?
It's Monday and we're getting closer to Christmas and I'm back in the cottage.
Good to be back home, let me tell you, the flight wasn't all that great.
Of course it was once again my favorite airline virgin, upper class, get my little
bed, sweeten everything but, man, it was, we sat on the tarmac for about an hour and a half,
it was completely reigned and fogged in and everything was slow so it took a while to get
off the ground and then it was just like, I don't know man, I don't know what they fed
everybody in the lounge but it's stank, people just smelling up the whole cabin and it's so
hard to sleep if it seems like someone in 49F, if they fart, it wops all the way up to
8k but of course it could also have been the person in 7k.
It doesn't matter, it's just, oh man, laying down there trying to get the some sleep and
then, just, oh, this is whafting, now damn, so, not a lot of sleep, add to that, just
before I left Patricia and I had spoken on the phone and she told me what she was going
to do to me when I got home so that of course made me rather restless, thinking about it.
Don't worry, I totally collected.
So anyway, Patricia and Christina have decorated the cottage, look great when I got home
yesterday and all the, we got a tree in the back which I'd gotten just before we left and
that's got all the lights and there's lighting inside the house and there's reaths and
there's everything, it's just a complete perfect Christmas atmosphere, just I'm so ready
for it.
And of course the weather cooperated completely, really clear day, blue skies about one degree
below freezing so just, you know, perfect and I haven't been to the high street yet,
which is where, you know, it's the shopping high street, every town in the UK has a
high street and that's where all the shop starts what they call it, and our high street
is very, very picturesque, you know, with carolers and it's a traditional English
Christmas.
So maybe I should do a sound sing to it and maybe, maybe tomorrow or Thursday, Patricia
now do a quick sound sing, not a full show, which is a quick sound sing tour of the
high street in Gilford.
So let me see, I think I've finally have to give up completely on the Yamaha 16A W
workstation, 16, was an AW 16G.
I don't know what the hell is wrong with it, but even if the face is off or it's just,
you have to configure everything internally with the onboard, you know, this little display,
which is, looks like it's made by Ford actually, you know, crappy little green yellow
display and it's hard, you know, it's, it's hard to troubleshoot it because one parameter
can be off and it's not as easy as just looking at cables and following them along.
So I put the sound craft back in and although I don't have the, the pre-processor on, on the
microphone, I'm just running everything through the stereo valve, here my voice is starting
to go, running everything through the stereo valve processor.
So maybe later on, I'll figure out if I can put the other preamp in and I just, I think
I'm getting up on the on the 16A W. It's time for just a good old fashioned analog board.
I don't know about these digital ones, man, that just don't do it for me. I like to follow
the wires so I can think about how stuff's being inserted and where it's going to, and
actually I think it kind of sounds better, although I don't have the reverb on now, so you'll
have to kind of pretend that it's in there. Oh, what else? So Christina has two more days of
school, took her to school early this morning, no traffic, beautiful, great to be back in the
jag, I have to say, as much as I love Trinity, the jag definitely has some benefits to it,
seat warmers, perfect, 400 brake horsepower under my right foot. Yeah, it makes me feel manly.
So today, I think we go through a couple of a couple of G-mails, of course we have our
biodesal segment, which now I've completely produced, well, I'm not going to tell you all about it.
It's coming up. Let me see, we were talking first about Gmail, Gabrielle, I was talking about
wanting Gmail on my blackberry, and so I got a whole bunch of similar emails as Gabrielle sent me.
A green that the labels are crucial to the Gmail experience, so there's this, you know,
there's this Gmail client that you can use on your blackberry, but it's still, it's basically,
here's the thing, all these Gmail clients, it doesn't matter what it is, it's the push email
that makes the blackberry so interesting. The meaning you have to, you know, wait for more than a second
for something to be retrieved from the network, it's just too slow, it takes too long, and it's
not that the network is slow, it's just the machine has to build up a screen again, so maybe the
new blackberries will be faster. But, you know, the idea of push email where, you know, you just
click on the email tab, and there's the email already sitting there, you know, I didn't have to
ask for it, and have to retrieve it, that is such a benefit. I just like it, you know, the blackberry
can synchronize, I think, what does it do in exchange server? So when it makes sense, can't we,
maybe that's an open protocol, or there must be some kind of protocol that we can, look,
blackberry isn't a Microsoft product, so clearly they know how to communicate with the exchange
protocol. If we can then have your blackberry communicate with Gmail the same way it does with your
exchange server, oh, man, then you have an unbeatable combination, unbeatable. Imagine setting up filters
in your Gmail, you know, send this off to my blackberry, don't send this off, and then the reconciliation,
when you delete something, or label something on the blackberry, then it would be labeled in Gmail.
That's what I was looking for. There's all kinds of workarounds and hacks, but I'm looking
for like a full-blown solution, and it seems to me that all that's needed really is, you know,
hey, what's that? Yeah, we're going to fly tomorrow, someone going by, want to see my mom
in Holland, so we're flying early, or not tomorrow. I'm sorry, Wednesday, we're flying early
from Echo Golf, Tango Fox Trot, to Echo Hotel, Romeo Delta, throughout her day. They were
going to get in the cab, drive off to my mom's place, we'll hang out for a while. We'll probably
have to leave around three o'clock, I want to make it back, while they're still light.
You know, that was funny last night. I must have been a re, I don't know if it was a repeat or not,
but top gear, which is by far. Actually, it won't in the ward, what do we, in any ward, I think.
Top gear is the best automobile program, best written automobile program. I don't think a single
part of it is written, but they do these great, beautiful montages and little, you know,
little mini documentaries that they're testing cars out. They really do a great job. It looks
like it's shot on film. It's just beautiful, lots of in-car camera stuff, lots of
drive-by shots. It's just, it's very well done. You can Google top gear on Google video and
there's some of it in there. So, yesterday they raised a front, was it from Northern Italy to London.
They raised a Bugatti. And this is the Bugatti that has 1,000 brake horsepower and has like
eight cylinders and some crap like that. So, the race that against, here it is, a Sessna 182,
not an RG mind you. And so they raised the airplane against the Bugatti and it was, it was
absolutely a fantastic, just a great montage. And I liked the in-plane shots as much as I did the in-car shots.
Oh, this is kind of interesting news. Apparently, comic book podcasting is the next big thing.
Adam and the rest of the daily source code listeners, my name's Neil Gorman and I wanted to take
a minute of your time to kind of make you guys aware of something which I think is some pretty
big news for the world of podcasting and the world of comic books. That news is that Marvel
comic books, which is a really well-known, very reputable company that has a lot of money and an
enormous fanbase, has started to podcast. And I think that this is just really, really wonderful news
for the world of podcasting because it shows that companies like Marvel that already do have a
big fanbase and already do have a lot of money, are really realizing that podcasting is a
viable way to disseminate information to their enormous fanbase. And actually, you know what
here, I'm just going to play a little clip from the first Marvel podcast so that you guys can kind of
hear this. And after we're going to come back and explain some of the things that are talked about
in this little clip for maybe some of the non comic book reading people out there. So the
sit tight if you don't understand everything that's being said right off the back because I'll
try to explain it in just a moment. Hey, that's your Lieber's Heart. It's Joke Sada,
Editor-in-Chief of Marvel Comics. And I want to welcome you all to our very very first Marvel
podcast. That's right, Marvel podcast. You heard it here for us. You will be here yet here first.
And who better to have us our guest for our first Marvel podcast, but Damon Lindelock.
You know, I can write a lot of little demons credits for you, but unless you've been in jail or
hiding under a rock, Damon is the co-creator and one of the major writers on the number one TV show
lost. And who is in a fan of lost? But then again, who is in a fan of Hulk and who is in a fan
of Wolverine and even Barrier, who is in a fan of Marvel's Ultimate Universe. So Damon,
along with superstar artists, L'Neal Francis, you, will be bringing you the first ever meeting
within the context of the Ultimate Universe of Wolverine versus Hulk at an ain pretty folks.
Okay. Now, like I said, I'm going to try to clear up something which is going on here.
Damon Lindelock is a writer. He writes for the TV show lost. He is a co-creator on the TV show
lost. And now he is writing a comic book for Marvel Comics. That comic book is called Hulk
versus Wolverine. It's not out yet, but it's going to be hitting the new stance pretty soon. Adam,
you might be pretty interested in this. I know that you're a big fan of the TV show lost. And
I don't know if you read comic books, but you know, if you do, pretty sure this is a comic book
you're going to want to pick up. And if you don't, well, then maybe this is an excellent comic
book to start with. You know what I'm saying? Thank you Neil. Neil went on for a couple more minutes
there, but did think it was pretty interesting that Marvel Comics is doing their own podcast
from Marvel Comics herself. So that is, and there's lots of comic podcasts. I think I actually
have one coming up in the in the promo in a couple of minutes. Regarding that podcast, lots of echo.
Needed a little bit more cowbell. That's all. You know, every single time I mentioned cowbell,
you know, the people that immediately send me email and say, hey, man, what about the cowbell?
And how about the drum cadences? I don't have any drum cadences. Send me a new one. If you got one.
Send me a really good drum cadence. I love them. But I used to get them in the email all the time.
I'm talking about a year ago. We're doing drum cadence of the day. And I have them somewhere. But
if you got a cool drum cadence, send it off to me. I'll be more than happy. And speaking of the
the comic book authors who are the writers for Lost, where the hell is Lost? I don't get it. I've been
buying the Lost episodes through iTunes. And the last one I've seen on there for the past two weeks
is the Where is Kate episode? Did they stop all of sudden or iTunes, music store not updating? Or,
you know, what is it? It's another thing here. Why can't I subscribe to the entire series?
Just like a podcast. I mean, technically, it must be possible. So just say, all right, you know,
by every single episode, hell, I'm probably even willing to pay up front the 35 bucks or whatever
is for all the episodes. And then give me a subscription so that it'll just automatically download and
be sitting there for whenever I'm ready to watch any episode of Lost. So instead of going to the
iTunes music store to see if it lost as I updated, I'll just be able to look in my iTunes.
Makes so much sense. And again, where is Lost? I mean, I don't have a TV guide and I don't follow.
I don't even know what day it's on, but usually around Thursday or Friday it shows up in iTunes
or it shows up in iTunes, music store, and I haven't seen it for two weeks. So I guess they went on
some kind of winter hiatus or something, but I miss it. Email here from David Gray Adam after
listening to Delta Sierra Charlie 296 where you mentioned Roger Smalls and his trash can diving
adventures. I went to his site from the link in the show notes. Show notes work, you see.
Looking at his profile under interest are some very normal things like music computers, etc.
And then there are some strange ones like Jim Feet and Snow Globes. But the ones that really
got my attention and they should get yours too are hiding and kidnapping. I don't know, I'm not
trying to alarm you, but based on his previous behavior, expert caution seems to be in order.
I think some people have been in touch with Roger. I think he's just a big fan.
I don't see, I've already requested he not go through my trash anymore. That kind of weirded me out
and he tried to put that up on Google base and they refused his entry.
Let me see. I saw it somewhere. I think I mentioned that to you, but I saw it on his web
log home. What is it? Roger. Roger Smalls.blogs.com. There we go. Let me see.
By the way, I'm doing this all on the on the laptop on the power book because
remember I set up a trisha with my iMac in her station in the kitchen. She's not given it back. Uh-huh.
In fact, I had another, another Bluetooth headset, you know, a little thing that you'd
hang along your ear, which I've, no, I just want to have two. One that I'd say really I
want to have one configured for Bluetooth for the power book and the other one configured for the cell phone.
And she said, oh, give me that too. So now she's doing freaking Skype calls with the Bluetooth headset.
She's out of control in my wife is before you know it, she'll be in chat rooms.
I'm trying to break out that country song, computer computer. Here it is. Roger Smalls.
Uh-huh. Hello. Thank you for submitting an item to Google base. We would like to inform you that we have
disabled your item entitled rare hair wax, which is the shitty took from my trash, because it's not
permitted by her program. Sales of human body parts are not allowed on Google base. This includes
hair follicles. This product has also not been approved by Adam Curry and therefore cannot be listed.
They never asked me if it was to if it could be approved. I don't know how that works, but
so I don't think Roger's going to be too much for a problem. He just seems like a really
enthusiastic guy. And we wanted enthusiastic people in podcasting. That's really what it's all about.
Okay. I asked and I received Jeff Smith. Man. Oh, you big time.
It's time everybody for our bio diesel segment on the daily source code. Please sing along.
We're going to sing your luxury. Oh,
Yeah, it's time to talk about the bio diesel industry. We call it our little Trinity segment.
Trinity is the egg nog yellow car that I purchased recently in San Francisco. It runs entirely
on bio diesel. It's a Mercedes 300 turbo diesel with the biodiesel conversion kit. We're not
even sure what that means yet, but it's got it. And it's an interesting industry, you know?
So today we'll be talking about throwing a granny in your tank fixing the wind shield and wind
signal out.
Yo, our first email today in our Trinity segment comes from
foghorn. That would be Nickleghorn from the Forensic Science podcast that Forensic Science podcast.
Uni, that's uniform November, India dot CC. I just got home from a debate competition as we
can along Island in New York. One of the issues was on mandating more fuel efficient gasoline
powered cars. Thanks to you and Trinity, I successfully argued that we should completely switch to
biodiesel instead of for stalling the inevitable end of our gas reserves. Interestingly enough,
the next issue was on cutting off Medicare, a medical aid to US citizens. Someone came up with a
bright idea that we can kill two birds with one stone. The increased death rate would provide
more corpses and other matter to turn into biodiesel. However, the idea of sticking your
grandmother and your tank disturbed too many people for that to pass. So thanks Adam and Trinity for
helping me win my 14th debate and keep up the good work. I'll get a promo out to you soon
as we get more shows online. Okay fantastic. Very, very cool. Appreciate it. I'm still trying to figure
out exactly what I have. Do I have a conversion? Do I have a biodiesel conversion or not? I
know only have more than half a tank left. So it's not going to be until January. Second week of
January, I'll be back in San Francisco for a long haul back on the oil rig everybody and then we're
going to go to biodiesel oasis, Berkeley's biodiesel oasis and get the full low down and really
find out what's going on with the car. Then the next stop is the detailing shop. This thing has to be
washed. It has to be scrubbed. It needs the toothbrush detailing and then we start with the pimping.
Which would start of course with the windshields. Hey Adam Steve Webb here with the life-spring podcast.
So yesterday I'm listening to Delta CR Charlie number 297 and you're talking about this
beautiful example of automotive engineering. The beautiful yellow Mercedes Ben's biodiesel
beater. You're talking about how ugly it is and things like that. And you really got my attention
when you mentioned the windshield and the fact that it had a star on and a crack on and stuff like that.
Dude that's right at my alley. That's what I do for a living. That's what I do to put food on the
table is I fix those things on windshields. I don't replace windshields. I repair them. The name of my
business which started in 1988. I've done tens of thousands of windshield repairs. The name of the
business is Stargon. Stargon.com as a matter of fact is where you can look it up. But man, call me
a man. I can help you pimped that right out and make a pod show proud. So give me a call. You got my number
and hey, thanks for listening. God bless you man. I've got bless you Steve. Cool man.
See the problem with Steve is that he doesn't live in San Francisco. I think he lives a Southern
California. So I'd have to bring him up with his kit. Which I'm not against. But you know,
we really, I want to set it all up. So we do a whole bunch of things. Christina of course immediately
said, Dad, you got to me. You got to pimped out. So it bounces up and down. I don't know. Are there
hydraulic servo kits for Mercedes 300 turbo diesel? If there are, I'll put them on. And then we need
the paint job. I put a really cool one on my curry.com weblog the other day. Which would look,
what does that say? Curry West Coast Curry Cruiser, I think is what it read.
And so we'll just plan this a bit by bit. The first test of course will be when I come back
in a couple of weeks and see if she'll actually start. If we get that far, then I'll be totally
amazed. And then from there, we're going to start getting everything done.
Daniel Davis says biodiesols have a solvent effect on natural rubber hoses and seals. While newer
diesel engines have polymer hoses and seals such as deposits of the Tom brand, older engines may
need to be outfitted with new hoses and or seals made of viton, viton, viton. Since most diesel
injector pumps don't have rubber parts directly in contact with the fuel. It's usually easy to replace
hoses and seals without an image or disassembling. So I might need that. As long as nothing's
spewing out of any hoses, then I'm good. I mentioned Andy White, who sent me an email about
Winston. And that means it's a synthetic oil made in Wisconsin, duh. And he's happy to sell it to me
at cost. Which is cool. I guess that's not a big good. That makes it totally green, you know, a total
green experience. No petrochemical diesel oil at all, I guess. And he goes on to say, I look to
your photos of Trinity, but what you say is a biodiesel conversion kit looks like the air filter.
Yeah, a couple of people have said that. The tube in the top of the positive crankcase ventilation
hose, the tube in the top in the PCV, the positive crankcase ventilation hose. You don't need
a kit into car to use biodiesel only to make it. If you want to run stretch vegetable oil,
you do need a kit. Maybe I have a kit on that for straight vegetable oil. Christ, I really don't know.
He goes on to say, you should check out this band called road trip. They have two lead singers
so depending on which song you play, that kind of depends on who sings. Okay. So that's from Andy White.
Andy, I'm going to look into that. As I said, when I get back to San Francisco,
I may be all I'll shell. I'm not going to do a Trinity report every single day, obviously. But keep
comments coming in. If you can tell me what a conversion kit does, other than I think heat up the
the SVO, the straight virgin oil, so that it so doesn't gel. I think it makes, yeah, I think that's the
only thing that really needs to be put in there. Anyway, if you're listening to serious stars 103,
Pacific Coast, Hellway is next followed by Madge Weinstein and John Andrew have fun with that.
And back here on the podcast, the real fun continues because of course I'm going to hit you
with that song that Andy White suggested. If you got suggestions from the podcast,
say music network, please drop in to me. You know what I like. Here's two days in road trip.
You will handle with love as I'm as bad with respect. You'll you think you can love me.
Oh, why? Oh, come on. Yeah. I've been living for such a long time. You know what? No, I
don't know yet. I've been living for such a long time now, I know.
And I'll be good, that's right, I feel like I'm falling
And I can't see the land on the ground, on the moon
I've only got two days to get with it
I gotta get with it, I gotta sing it
Can you give me the answer?
All right, and will you please forgive me?
It's all I want, all right, I gotta be all right, all right
I've been living for such a long time, and no one knows where it is
Now it's too easy for me to go out, yeah
And I can't see the land on the moon
I've only got two days to get with it, I gotta sing it
Can you give me the answer?
All right, and will you please forgive me?
I gotta be good, good, good, good
Two days that I'll be good
I'll be good, I'll be good, yeah
I'll be good, I'll be good
Oh, got out of me
Two days that I'll be good
I'll be good, go to your family
Hurry up and find my way
I'll be good, I'll have to pick you
Nice.
Totally digged out.
Thank you very much.
I was cool.
I liked that a lot.
They had a couple other songs and some other guys singing.
So I'm not exactly sure who this is.
Hold on one second.
Oh yeah, I got to start the week off just right.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, sources on some Matthew Ebo press, Matthew Ebo, of course, another star from the
Podsaic Music Network.
It was really interesting.
He did an interview with the Tennessean, a big newspaper in Nashville, as a part of the
money makeover feature.
Matthew says that he really pressed hard to try and get some press for the Podsaic Music
Network, which I totally appreciate and actually have the article here.
It does actually say, well, it does mention something about the Podsaic Music Network.
But really, this article is really interesting, and of course we'll have a link to it from
the show notes page.
You can find the link to the show notes at dailysourcecode.com, show notes for each
episode.
And if you go to show notes.info, it's a week easy.
So you can go in and mess with it and take credit for my show.
But it talks about all about Matthew, who has completely dedicated his life to making music.
And he really clearly wants to quit his day job.
He pays his bills with a day job, answering phones that a Brentwood mortgage company.
They pays about $11 an hour.
But he does say, he nets an additional $1200 a year from other sources such as selling
CDs and working on websites.
But his goal is to be self-employed to standing himself entirely as a performing musician.
My brother, keep the dream alive.
We've been working behind the scenes.
The Podsaic Music Network to get the purchasing up and running.
We've already selected our vendor for that.
It's got some great ways that'll make it even easier to pay and to get the music that
you're looking for.
Straight to the Podsaic Music Network.
We have a meeting also set up with Google the week of the ninth in San Francisco for
the indexing of the Podsaic Music Network in the Music Search on Google.
And I see no reason why it wouldn't happen.
But yeah, I definitely want to take a meeting with him about it.
That's very cool.
So, keep you up to speed on that.
Something else that we've been tracking is the Music Publishers Association of America
who are going after sites that publish lyrics to songs.
And there was this one little widget.
I guess it's called confabulator.
Or it was originally called confabulator.
Then widgets appeared in OS 10 and confabulators what you can use widgets for on Windows.
Let's see how this is made.
Facing an ups well of protest, Warner Chapel, Music on Friday, formally apologized
to Walter Ritter, over a letter it sent to the software program.
Her early this month targeting a helper application that'll be the widget for Apple's iTunes
called Pearl lyrics quote, the goal of Warner Chapel's prior letter to
pair works was to gain assurance that pair licks operated according to copyright
principles.
However, in both tone and substance, that means that letter was an an of inappropriate
manner in which to convey that inquiry, Warner Chapel apologizes to Walter Ritter
and pair works.
In other words, I said an asshole letter fucking asshole letter.
Anyway, they apologize.
That's very cool.
But of course, the whole point of this article, it's a wired article that talks about
this is that, you know, here, I think even Ritter says it to himself here.
I'm concerned with how I should go on with software development because this will be a potential issue.
Every time I cope with something that people like someone might say, you can't do that.
It's illegal.
It infringes copyright.
It's getting really difficult to be innovative as a small developer.
Absolutely true.
Well, I think that's a good start there for for Warner Chapel to realize their
mistakes and to apologize and just I guess be, you know, think a little bit more.
That's all.
Just before you fire off that season to Swiss Lighter, just think for two seconds.
Because it's clear the webloggers and the podcasters are watching you.
It's the crank cast starring crank and mic.
A weekly look into the minds of two comic book professionals as they discuss their
favorite comics, movies, music, and pretty much all the stuff you like to hear
when you're not talking about it yourself.
This is a really sharp middle America.
There was so much better before he went to read.
My part is the lack of teeth as there has been no time.
It's got the popularity of Garfield.
It's not as evil as a kid, like I couldn't draw muscles, but I'll be damned if I didn't know
what to help pack an absolute life.
This is the most revealing crank cast.
Yeah.
Jefferson Cranging.
I started very, very come back to mic.
You can see dolls, other ones make it ass.
Okay, pants sparkle.
Hello, this is Cranging Mike and this is dead air.
Come on, don't be a ho-ho-ho.
Listen to Cranking Mike because every time you get a crank cast,
it's an angel gets its wings.
Find them at www.crankcast.net.
In a world of mediocrity, two men, gurus of marketing, on a mission to bridge the gap between
new marketing, media, and PR.
Joseph Jaffey, bring in the juice from Westport, Connecticut, Steve Rubel, persuading
on a micro-level from Long Island, New York.
Two voices, one message across the sound, brought to you by T.J.
LaJoridio.com, all right, who's here, not valid in north or south of the Coda.
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We're earth-link.
We believe your personal information should be just that, personal, and we believe your
internet should be a friend, not a foe.
We're earth-link.
Make the smart choice, visit earthlink.net, and discover what our internet experts can do
for you.
Earth-link.
We revolve around you.
You know when I was a young boy, they told me not to quit my day job, because my shinging
shot.
Well, you know what?
I'm a podcaster now, and because I'm at a furry and podcaster, I can quit my day
job.
Okay, quit your day job, I can quit my dream.
You wightly J.
This is tv-chlipsch simply now what a f**king day job, Heather.
20 minutes?
20 weeks?
20 pounds?
This is Adam Tinkhall from Tinkhall for an
and I'm making a new year's resolution this January to burn 20 pounds in 20 weeks.
Now like many of you, I've enjoyed to eat and drink as long as I can remember.
So expect my challenge to be interesting honest and hopefully for lucky,
painfully funny. Please excuse the pump.
You can find out more about my show at burning20.com.
This promo was brought to you by burning20.com. Please do not try this at home without consulting your
high school, which doctor at local shaman or family physician. Waging will be strictly prohibited
by federal state and county law. Thank you. Burning20.com.
Scrooge was not the man he used to be. He was as cold as a dead of winter.
Starting tonight at the stroke of midnight, you will be visited.
I marked the ghost of Tech Christmas past.
We're in the ghost of Tech Christmas present.
Ghost. Tech Christmas future.
Blah, blah, blah.
A geek Christmas Carol presented by friends in Tech. Friends in Tech.com.
So I was asked to participate in the Geek Christmas Carol.
And of course I missed all deadlines and I just got an email now that says I can still do my
bit so I'm going to do it. I haven't read the whole script. I only saw a side as we call it in
the biz and it involves real acting. I'm going to have to really get into it. But I think the whole
idea is cool. You know, then I guess I can do it in episodes. I don't know if it's going to be a
if it's all going to be in one go or if it must be episodes I guess. So you can check that out
friends in Tech. I think it's friends in Tech.com. But I'll make sure to let you know all about
it once once it's done. Particularly if they use my bit, it'll be cool. And if you have an
eggnog recipe since there's like no eggnog here in the UK is something that's simple.
Yet and I want an alcoholic eggnog so I want to know exactly how much rum or whatever to put in it.
Just drop me a mail. Adamaccurry.com. Talking about the razors and shaving,
which I'm getting a whole bunch of feedback on. And I guess I am the ultimate metro-sexual
in this particular case because, you know, guys really don't talk about this kind of stuff.
You know, beauty and health care, health beauty care.
Hey Adam, are you sure? You've not been spending too many nights away from Patricia,
says Leo Vagoda. I have a feeling that you're talking about a badger hair brush. Not a beaver hair brush.
The dude, it is a beaver hair brush. I remember when I bought it, it said original
beaver hair. Not badger beaver. You know, beaver from the dams. In any case, I can confirm that
Gillette's M3 power razor is excellent. I'd be using it for months and wouldn't change. Even though I'm
unhappy using a blade, even though I'm unhappy using a blade more than twice. No greeny me. Yeah,
okay. So you throw a blade out after two uses. Okay. Shit. Patricia already left for Sainsbury's.
Later this week, I'll pick one up. I'll give it a try. Who knows? I might change my life. I'm still
really digging that Wilkinson for blade. Brand Bradley says you've always said that when you
burped on the ball of loss and say, oh, thank you, we go. Use kills shaving cream. That's
kilo India echo hotel Lima. Brushless shaving cream. It's the best. Just put a dab on your hand, rub
your hands together like you're washing your hands and put it on your face. Okay. But isn't the
whole point of the brush is to get your hair like raised up and raise up the bristles? I thought that's
what the brush was for. I mean, if you can do with your hands, then why do I run stupid brush?
There must be a real reason for it. Matt's not grass to wind it up. I was listening to Delta
share Charlie 299er and heard you discussing razors. Like the one listener you mentioned, the
Gillette M3 power razor. I too, an avid Gillette razor fan. Never want to fall for the
micro marketing hype. Let me tell you, these Gillette razors just keep getting better. The latest
one out, the M3 power is the one that Paul says has a chaves. It's like rubbing the back of a
soup spoon across your face. Excellent endorsement. Next year, early 2006, Gillette will be releasing
the fusion and fusion power. This will have five blades plus an extra precision blade on the back
for under your nose or your sideburns. That's fucking six blades. That's nuts, man.
Okay, now I'll have to something else. Dustin Moat just got the Tvo update that plays podcast on
his TV. I'm listening to you right now. Totally loving it. Excellent. He says, I've been a bad
podcast. I pulled the needle two months ago. I will rectify this immediately. Thanks for the shame.
I guess you'd stop listening. I don't know if you stop listening to this show or all
all shows all together. But that is kind of cool. I wouldn't mind. We don't have Tvo's here.
They have sky digital. I don't think there's any openness to them, which is too bad. The whole
Tvo thing is too bad. You know, people often wonder why the content is relatively restricted.
And that's because the investors in Tvo are the television networks. Go look it up. The investors
in Tvo are the television networks. I think it's actually a consortium of ABCMBCCBS. I know
a whole bunch of broadcasters are invested in it. So that's why, you know, there's a agenda there.
And that agenda is not necessarily to let all kinds of cool shit in. Rumors still that Rocket
Boom was purchased by Tvo, and Amanda has been making all kinds of insinuations about stuff.
So maybe conversations are ongoing. Love the Rocket Boom. Love it. Right up there with lost,
if it were on. Let's see. James E said, oh, this is regarding tattoos.
Okay, I think the bear in mind is you won't regret having a tattoo later. You won't. The
thing to remember about a tattoo is that you won't care about it later. How does that mean?
Just a thing on your body. No, I will care about it. I'm already have some very cool
ideas, tattoo ideas, which have been sent in to Adamaccurry.com. So definitely the pilot's wings.
Now we have like a musical key, the clef. I think it's called clef, a G.K.
Whatever in the middle. And then very to us, litter us, or some Latin word like that, which
could mean you suck bottom. I still have some stuff. You know, I have this whole thing about
performance, right in all different countries. I'm going to save that for tomorrow, because
I can't just do one. I've got five different stories to talk to you about. So we'll do that tomorrow
in the podcaster portion of the daily source code, which is always kind of the second half if you
will. We're already at 41, what almost 42 minutes. I want to play one more song. And this is what
came to me in the in the Gmail. Hey, Adam, thank you for being a voice for podcasting,
make it reality blah blah. I met you back in the MTV days when I was the base player for Vixen.
Remember Vixen? Currently, I host my own podcast. I like video podcast better, actually.
And play guitar and sing in bubble, who are on the pod save music. Now, where bubble is receiving
daily, daily airplay. That would be pod play through the PMN, which is fantastic. The video podcast
is called Rock and Roll TV, and we're currently getting over 16,000 downloads per episode.
After only one month, and we're very excited about it. That's fantastic. This is from Share
Ross, which used to be Share Peterson. And I had heard about bubble. I can't remember who I
heard it from. But then I checked out a couple of songs and I picked out one that I liked the most.
And definitely take a look at the video at the Rock and Roll TV podcast. This got
something good going on there. So here it is. This is, uh, oh, wait, man, this is completely wrong.
Fuck. The hell is that? I had something else cute. Oh, okay. I understand what I did. I skipped
over a piece of feedback for the performance rights. Okay. So that'll be tomorrow. As I said,
here's bubble. This is Sparkle Star.
Just smile in my heart. I always walk away. Every time I look at you, I can't believe I'll
love again.
Didn't mean to make you cry. But make you love so hard. But didn't mean to make you say goodbye
or find a fine try. Yeah, shaking on the floor. Come on, still not so. The world just get out
of them. And we're seeing I can't make you understand my song. Yeah, I always walk away.
But every time I look at you, I can't believe I'll love again.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, free,, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,, do
Just let it always get inside my head
I don't want you away
Cause every time I make it true
I can't believe I'll ever love again
I don't know
Maybe I'm just for you
Why will we stop your star?
Yeah, I'll be your big star, your star
Just like you
Didn't mean to make you cry
I'm making you fall so high
Burn it down and turn you crazy
Never think I'll make you feel
All I wanted you to feel
Bubble
A lot of safe music network
Music.potcho.com
More pot safe music network.com
Very cool
Just looked up a couple of pictures of Vixen
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, I was cool back in the day
Back in the old school days
All right, that's it for the daily source code for today
I'm gonna wrap it up
Be back tomorrow, Wednesday
Probably won't have a show
Since I'm gonna be off to see my mom
But then, of course, we'll have a show for the rest of the week
And I guess I'll do something on Christmas too
Cause we can figure out something fun to do
As always, daily source code.com is where you can find out
The latest podcast and the feed to subscribe to
Just copy the link that's attached to that orange
On white XML icon
And you can drop that into your iTunes if you want
You can search for it on iTunes as well
But iTunes doesn't always update regularly
So you may want to choose to subscribe to it directly
Or, of course, in your juice receiver
Absolutely, to mom
Feedback, adamantcurry.com
And still, in the works for this week
I've gotten some feedback for the strategy cast
If you have questions about pod show
Or what we're gonna be doing
Or if you have observations or any suggestions
Regarding pod casting stuff we can do
To put into the network
Email it to strategycast at podshow.com
All right, everybody
Oh, this is a Sue's lighter than I stole
Hey, that's it. I'll see you tomorrow
Bye bye
Pot show
All you need is a podcast and a dream