Okay everyone, quiet everyone, simmer down, simmer down, but just want to say thank you for all the hard work you've done.
We couldn't have done it without you.
Okay, quiet, static check, light, free, sound, sound, boom man, ready?
Is that a good position?
Ready? Okay, 10 seconds people.
Let's do this right.
Five, four, three, two, cue music, lights up.
I'm going to show you the greatest thing your eyes have ever been held.
He was a king and a guard.
In the world he knew, but now he comes to civilization, merely a captain, a show to benefit your curiosity.
Ladies and gentlemen, the eighth wonder of the world.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
I'm testing this.
Oh, DJ, are you done, next radio?
Your DJ has only just begun.
Yeah, that was supposed to be Adam Curry.
Hey, everybody, how you doing? Welcome to the Humdadish, Nick the source code.
And I know this also didn't put a date stamp on the show for today, but that's okay.
Because I think I'm just going to start doing show segments, numbers, sequential numbers.
So let's say this is shoot, what is this going to be?
I don't know, I haven't counted.
Maybe this is, let's just start somewhere.
Let's say this is show number 250.
Welcome to the daily source code.
It is a Wednesday in Guilford, overcast, not very nice today.
A little bit warmer than yesterday.
Sitting here in the cottage, bringing you the daily source code with plenty of promos,
pot-safe music, of course.
I've got a mashup for you.
And the pot cast I've been listening to, but I want to share with you.
And a couple of emails.
And I've got to kind of hurry up today.
I'm on a tight schedule.
It's one o'clock now.
Grunge meantime.
I have a meeting with Lee Wilkins,
a three o'clock at Starbucks.
Member Will, and his dogs, remember them?
That was truly one of the greatest moments in the beginning of podcasting
when Lee Wilkins created this podcast with his girlfriend,
his wife, I think, Jenny, and their dogs.
Now he had a job in the States, went over there with his, with their two dogs
and it didn't work out and he had to move back after a couple of weeks.
His dogs were basically stuck at an airport.
He couldn't afford to bring him in.
They had to go into quarantine.
He was all messed up.
And the community came together immediately.
And donated the necessary, I think,
eight or nine hundred dollars for quarantine and transportation fees.
Which is absolutely a beautiful thing.
All right.
I'm going to kick it off right now with a brand new mashup.
Something that I just can't get enough of.
Because you've got to combine a couple of people to really come up with,
get down and hollock.
Come on, Gweney.
I mean, cue.
That's it, if you go.
Attention, everyone.
You're about to hear is not the mistake.
Please do not turn off your rate.
But turn out the volume on your receiver as you play or go.
You want to get down.
Come on.
I want to go.
All of this mashup.
All of girls up and be like this.
You're right.
All of that girl, and you know how that girl is.
I want to go and do it.
You want to get out of it.
You gotta get on the move.
I want to go and do it.
Even what you find is a move.
I want to make you go and do it.
You gotta get on the move.
I want to stay in number one person.
Got him.
A shipman go through the wall.
Whoa, damn, come on, it's you back, come on, whoa, damn, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, yeah, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey mom got you, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
get down and holla cool in the gang and Gwen Stefani memo to self I have to tell Patricia
Gwen Stefani's on the list and of course information about that particular
mashup coming from today's show notes daily source code dot com or I'll
also post it on curry dot com let's see got an email here from martin woodward
and he says just thought you want to know the Peter day is about the start
podcasting is in business show become a podcast starting the 19th of May so
that's tomorrow so I figured I'd plug it today Peter day is he's been with
the BBC for I think 35 years he's the guy that I talked about him on on a
previous source code he came up to the cottage and we talked and he put together
a great hour of radio which hopefully is still available somewhere in MP3
or podcast form because it kind of goes away from the BBC streaming you know
site or their streams for their daily program after you know new one comes out
but it was really good and you and you really rocked on to the much bigger
concept of what's going on here as we grab hold of the media front cells
it's really cool so you know what I said to him at the time excuse me you know
what that is it's the sense I'll hit me again what what I said at the time
was what we really need is we need people like you sir Peter day to come
into our community and teach us stuff because we forgot and so much about what
we've never really had you know never been exposed to how to interview someone on
the radio and you know in long form and and all kinds of stuff the BBC used to
do back in the day all things we know that are completely valid we can all
bring back and experiment with and play with and you know help us not to
reinvent too many wheels so that's really really cool that he'll start off
first by making his in business program a podcast and hopefully he'll do a
little bit more I'd spoke to him a great length about how cool it would be to
provide the raw source to the interviews that he does because he interviewed me
for an hour he's interviewed other people and you know it gets spliced together of
course and edited by the sandres is producer who does a great job but you know
they only have an hour to fill on Sunday evening so there's this opportunity to
leave the raw interview right sitting there for people to pick up you know and
subscribe to it and get the show and along with it to have the opportunity
to subscribe to perhaps a separate feed that would give you all the outtakes and this would
work for anything by the way it would work for Fox News for CNN for you know Bloomberg it
would work for anybody imagine how cool it would be instead of just listening to a
short interview of an analyst talking about a particular stock imagine
you know being able to listen to the whole interview with the analyst I mean this is a
great time saver and I think in many ways it's what radio has been waiting for so
what are you guys waiting for already and if you've forgotten what Peter Day
sounds like here's an example something remarkable is happening here radio is
springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who managed what you can hear since radio is
invented it's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say
okay now this promo has to be great because we're gonna sit it out to Adam Curry who's
Adam Curry Adam Curry do you know who Adam Curry is oh that's right that's the guy that does
love line right that's Adam Corolla Adam Curry from MTV's like the god of podcasting okay
okay whatever look just let me lead the promo you just kind of play along all right sounds good okay here we
go and we're rolling hey Adam this is Don and this is Jared our man it's a major honor to
have our promo being played on your podcast yeah hey we wanted you and your listeners to know
about our new podcast it's called DVD weekly and each week my brother Jared and I are going to
cover the newest DVD releases as well as recently released titles and we do it all in our
special kind of way and you know we're not going to be as good as Adam was on MTV but we think
you'll still get a kick out of what we do that's right so join us on DVD weekly today you can find
the link on the directory at digitalpodcast.com just look under movies and entertainment do
what the hell was that all of a sudden you're like all up into Adam Curry didn't even know he
was a couple seconds ago are you kidding man it's Adam Curry MTV come on man the god of podcast
I just told you that a couple of say oh good lord you guys are full of shit it's nice podcast though
I didn't enjoy it reaching back into the email the Gmail bag Adam my name is Michael
Arlonson Arlonson I guess I'm from Sweden hope you find some time to read this mail
blah blah I guess you've already heard this from other Swedish listeners and it might not be
big deal anymore just want to let you know that Swedish national radio is also giving podcasting
a shot right now there are three radio shows available for downloading I'll actually three RSS feeds
that is and he hopes that it'll extend you into even more I'm I'm pretty happy about that you know
um well first of all anyone who jumps into podcasting is great but Sweden has some very
interesting creative talents um on the music scene it seems like every couple of years they just
come out with an incredibly large mega smash hit band I'll just name a few I know you're going to
win but Abba rock set uh Europe remember them the final countdown um oh Britney Spears hit me
baby one more time written by a Swedish guy produced in Sweden I think or at least parts of it
produced in Sweden so there's um there's a lot going on there and I haven't subscribed yet but I'm
going to and hopefully there'll be playing some uh some Swedish music as well because it's a vibrant
scene out there and it's uh particularly um I think we'll see pod safe music coming from Sweden very
quickly once they catch the podcast bug so haven't seen a lot of Swedish podcast yet uh haven't
showed up really in the directory but looking forward to um the uh public the Swedish national radio
to give in that abuse that's extremely cool and Michael ends up saying I almost forgot remember
well pink glasses might look fly on a guy uggs that swirls are strictly for girls okay
I'm lame again if you missed uh me talking about voices from the vault the other day which is uh just
a phenomenal uh phenomenally cool podcast it takes on the format of young bullets hit test and uh
a promo popped up the jury put together so I figured I'd let you in on that
from the fall feeling too old for young bullets hit test come walk with me through the audio archives
of history head over to www.voices from the vault.com and subscribe to my podcast feed
see you soon in the vault try to do is your hide the net if there are messages a great thing
it's a great thing you mustn't ever tell anybody to give us a message at all ever
feels like you're right there doesn't it?
message will self-destruct in five seconds
voices from the vault excellent podcast you need to check that one out you will not regret it
I guarantee it it's source code approved
okay jack this is the uh my Mac.com podcast promo you're the pro just run with it
in a world where laughter was king yeah that really doesn't work for us yeah I mean sometimes we're
funny but this is a podcast about macintosh the world of macintosh what you mean no in a world
well it's it's in the world the world of macintosh computing we talk about all things
yeah it's called a my Mac.com podcast you know mac is in macintosh okay jack let's try it again
one man no no sorry it's actually two of us two people both Tim and I
can't be podcast two of us chatting to him no one man okay okay okay thanks
oops sorry hit the wrong button okay try it again in a land before time
what no do know what the heck look jack we know you're used to doing voice-overs movies but yeah
yeah this is a podcast the my Mac.com podcast it's like a radio show but it's on the internet
oh you get it okay okay no seriously this isn't a movie trailer okay you know what I just don't
think you're gonna be right for this yeah I got our great sorry dude we don't want our podcast
boom to sound like some movie trailer or something so you know what this means right I'm fired
yeah free so okay let's just roll the intro to our podcast yeah that's a good idea
let's pretend just about the analyst that's not our intro music check the next generation of radio
it's the my Mac.com podcast check the rocky theme song this is not a movie trailer stop it no I like it
in here podcasting from the my Mac.com studios it's your host Tim Robertson and Chad Perry
we're so much for our promo oh well
love that I think that was that was originally parts of was it Jerry Seinfeld's movie I think
comedian or something like that and they cut up very good excellent and yet all these computer
podcasts are not just for people who use computers or a Mac and Tosh in this case but I think
it'd be great for computer manufacturers and for software developers to listen to because basically
here's your audience you know telling you about what you like and what they don't like and in fact
I've seen it myself as I've been using megaseg for putting the pod show on the serious together
megaseg is it's an interesting program it really fits what I need for for doing most of my
production work and now I also don't get like the you know the the top dog at the company
emailing me I'm getting the early releases on stuff and it's not you know because well
it's because I'm talking about it using their product you know it's a great feedback loop
same goes for audio hijack pro from roga meba a rogue a meba man that's the hardest you are
all to type in by the way rogue a meba dot com same thing they've also put in several different
features that really aren't addition for podcasting they put it in with with podcasts as in
mind even though they're application actually I do use it I use it to record everything now
and I have changed the settings you've probably noticed that I'm now at what a 32 kilohertz
sample rate and then the encoding is at 80 kilo bits per second I mean it's really you got to look
for the trade-offs I was down to I was lower I was at 24 kilohertz sample rate but that doesn't
seem to work on a lot of handheld devices so bump it up to 32 which also doesn't seem to work on
a lot of the flash players that are out there so it's really a hunt and pick kind of methodology
so maybe I'll have to you know bump it back up to 44 and then of course I'll have to take down the
sample rate I was just it's crazy it's crazy oh one will cast blaster be done and out of beta that's
all I want to know a couple of days ago I was talking about the funny log entries and aircraft
maintenance logs Bob Evans sent me an email says listen to your stories about aircraft maintenance log
entries remind me of one of the funniest I encountered during 11 years of avionics work
while in the US Air Force I was involved in I was involved in a fix to a fighter jet with a CRT-based
bomb nav display so that's you know it's basically a glass cockpit I guess and you know there's a
screen that shows you I guess the status of your bombs and the status of your navigation and so the
pilots right up was the display looks like a rabbit sitting on a fence the corrective action
shot rabbit tore down fence because we got our butts chewed out a few days later but couldn't resist
it was well worth that I totally get it and so while we're on my favorite topic which is aviation
I found a great podcast fly with me which is basically airline pilots just sitting and talking
shit about what they do and they've got recordings of of the communications of the you know
basically the radio talking to flight services and other aircraft but they they put something in
really cool I don't really have a stop point in this I'm just going to play it from from a part
in the middle of the podcast where they talk about what else pilots do when they're up there in the
cockpit on a long haul flight when we're not talking to other pilots up there what else are we doing
well eating is a popular past time usually listen as two of our flight attendants give the captain
our dining options over the inner com and that's what gave you the bat the bat's were outside the door
if you want to yeah we're fine now we do some chips and um okay what's what do you have
if you're in all the bars that's a cracker is all uh animal cracker she's a cracker oh that sounds
kind of good but I don't know why I'm saving myself we have read the press
I think I just might have an altitude that'll solve my problems appear so but thank you
uh I'm sticking to Joseph here with his pieces he's fine so you know we're going to be on the ground
and so I'm going to fight it down to an airway and we're going to be there and it's about an hour
we should touch it down in the middle okay all checking on it okay thank you bye
well that was nice some of our flight attendants take good care of us up there in the cockpit
although they're more demanding jobs to take care of the passengers as with any job where you
deal with hundreds of people on any given day the people who stick out in your mind are either the
ones who are the most innocent or the most demanding here one flight attendant tells me about
two passengers who stood out in her mind
first class passing she's on my flight as we offer her some caviar
oh okay yeah and she didn't know what it was so she asked us and we said oh she's
shakes oh I want my scrambled oh man I can live so that forever totally cool fly with me
the podcast and of course I'll have a link to um to the podcast and the podcast feed and the
show notes for today at dailysourcecode.com I just can't get enough of that I love it you know as a
almost like that yeah it's the BBC keeps calling me I don't know for some reason it's like your
name gets in the login their database and that it maybe it has like delicious tags next to it you
know so whenever they're looking for something like podcasting uh someone who is readily available
they'll always seem to call me now they've got something going on live at five you know like one
in the morning and they want me to call in and talk about podcasting I said yeah I'd love to do it but
got a lot of stuff going on some travel coming up as well I'll be going up out to the west coast
Sunday evening I'm gonna be in San Francisco for two days then in Los Angeles for one day and then
hopefully hopefully back to the cottage I should be back Thursday but everything should continue is normal
for our normal is normal can be right with with the source code and of course with the pod show on
series the international safety council has declared the following music pod safe
Buffy girl is our pod safe tune on the source code for today Boston based singer song writers
they're working on her first CD you check out buffygirl.com I really like this song like a voice
just a whole thing everywhere I go you hear it here on the daily source code
you're so ready it doesn't make sense so put the fact that it ever even asked in the past
it wouldn't be right to give my heart away
we're something is thinking and it couldn't be hope because hope could just flow away
whatever it is I have to let it slide
but I can see your pain is everywhere I go and I hear you use a plane in the back of my mind all the time
oh
I already knew that you could never be for me what I could never be for you but so many times I follow anyway
and my heart is thinking because my love's a little heavy for a man I can't explain
you leave all your windows open in the rain
and I can see your smile and every smile I see
every time I leave I turn my head to see you are smiling back of me
that alone in you yeah I can see your pain is everywhere I go
I hear you use a plane in the back of my mind all the time
oh
you're so ready
you're so right
you love that great voice love the song looking for more buffy girl everywhere I go it's
pod safe fun the daily source code pod safe if you're new to podcasting means
that this is the type of song that we have the rights to actually play in our podcast and it
works you know because now we don't need no stank and jail oh no not at all oh and by the way
I had a brief look yesterday at the pod safe music network which is being built as we speak this is
really looking pretty damn cool CC Chapman is leading the charge there and working with Chris Rockwell
and from the daily download and it's really going to be awesome and this is going to be
from podcasters perspective it's going to be great because if you're looking for a place where you can
find tunes that you can play on your podcast you know which of course a lot of places you can go
but you know this will be a place where you can also find out what's already being played
what podcasters are picking up what's hot what's in in rotation you know it's like we're actually
going to rebuild a lot of the the infrastructure that is in place for traditional radio today only
we have all the benefits of what we can do and you can be a thousand hundred thousand different
stations which are basically podcast playing shows for each song you'll have a little package you know
which includes a link you can put into your show notes with with some album art which will take
you right to that artist page I mean all the cool stuff you'd expect and it should be kicking
off pretty soon I'm very very very excited about it and that's it for the daily store's code got
a hurry got around you know press the flood thank you's the kiss you know gonna talk to the
brandy thank you very much for tuning in and staying subscribed if you don't know how to subscribe
go to ipodder.org it'll explain to you how you download an ipodder and how you start
subscribing to shows you can also get that import podcast ily dot com another great community
cycle podcast feedback out of my curry dot com if you want to submit something send it
off to submit at podshow dot com for your promos podcast but also put it in the line up for the
podshow and serious got four hours a day to fill so feel free to send it on in you got some podsafe
tunes podsafe podshow dot com and mashups that's the one I'm really looking for mashup
at podshow dot com all right everybody um daily source code dot com where you can find the podcast
feed and all the latest or the archives latest episode and of course my web log for your comments
www.cray.com bye bye