16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass, then the next generation
radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Since a share of Charlie 3-0-4, I've got this pot show, breaking out a fat sack of the good
stuff.
I've got some
Oh, I feel so dead and saved
I can't attend when I can't find out where I hide
I need a remedy
From this calamity
Somebody tell me if I'm fine
If I really want to shine
I don't think that I can find
The song that's true in my heart
If I really shine
This is a cold
On the time
Like keep on making up reasons
Why just can't find the right
Oh, I know something's got to kill
The song found deep down inside of me
That's the dying just to live
I feel it on my skin
I feel it right now
When we inhale, I feel the pain
Go tell me if I really want to shine
Oh, if I really want to shine
If I really want to shine
I'm sick and tired of holding out on me all the time
I'm waiting for the day when I can't be
I'm on a shine
Cause I really want to shine
Oh, if I really want to shine
This is a cold on the end of my life
The song found deep down inside of me all the time
Like keep on making up reasons
Why just can't find the right
Cause I really want to shine
When I can't shine
Oh, if I really want to shine
I'd put this up right there with the love
Kevin Reeves, shine
Hey everybody, it's Friday
It's December 23rd
It's going to be a free wheelen kind of show
Since there's no satellite broadcast
So it's just us amongst ourselves here
No one else is listening in
I'm really getting into this whole vibe of
Beyond just the pod save music network
Now the social network is starting to connect
So slow sent, you know, slow, right?
He wrote that co-wrote and produced
If every day we're Christmas
Pod save for peace, fantastic project
Which I'm going to play later on this show as well
He sent me an email
After I played Kevin Reeves yesterday on the show
And he says, well, of course, you'll recognize that Kevin
Sing several lines in pod save for peace
By the way, Kevin's album was the project I was working on
When I dropped everything to re-record
If every day we're Christmas for pod save for peace
Now that P for P stuff is settling down
I really wanted to finish shine for Kevin to have
Available for Christmas and glad you liked it
Trying to get the rest of it done for me
January. Now, slow didn't ping me about this at all
I found this through those emails
That I told you about that I received from
Another podcast from the audience of this other podcast
So here's how the social network start to connect
From what was it? The podcast is called No Holds Bar
So I got a message from
What is it? Fibreo
Fibreo? Does that sound right?
Fox start India Bravo Romeo Alpha India Oscar
I'm the host of No Holds Bar radio
Well, one of them just heard yeah, I subscribed to haven't listened to it
And of course he says I just heard the show you mentioned us
And I'm grateful for the mention yeah, the show is three hours long
I know it's tough to get into but well worth it
Of course he says I know him a bit biased
It's not a college radio show though
That's what I thought it was so I was wrong
We are one of eight shows on a network that I started
That broadcast on the internet
I think they've been doing it for about six years
That's NHBradio.com
Kevin Reeves the guy who wrote Shine is a member of our staff and a cohost
Of one of the other shows
So now another network has formed right before my very eyes
Because it turns out that
Well, SLOW is legally blind
I think Kevin Reeves is also blind
And if I'm not mistaken
There's also another guy in No Holds Bar radio
Who's blind? I don't know
And I feel left out got damaged
But it's so cool how you know you're interfacing with people and finding people
And the internet is just a magical place
Isn't it shit just kind of bubbles up the stuff that you're looking for
It's just it kind of appears and people send you stuff
And it works it works it works it works it works it works
Let's celebrate that today
Loving it so now we just got to get the pod save music network more accessible
I know I know Chris Rockwell is all over it
Oh man we've got so many things going on there
Well we've been working on on
Oh you know I'll say that for let me see
Well actually have a whole
PDN PM in thing I want to talk about
I'll talk more about the pod take music network later first
Yesterday I was home
What was I doing I was I was like conference calls
And we're just doing regular like office guy stuff
And the Patricia comes in I can see on her face
That you know something's up
I think I was on with Ron I said well hold on a second
And I said when you know what's going on you say well
Dad just had a minor stroke
Oh man when it rains it pours
He's okay
They call it a Tia
As in tango india alfa
Which I'm not quite sure what it stands for but it's like a miniature aneurysm
So maybe the A is for aneurysm
Apparently he keeled over while sitting behind this computer of course
That's my destiny
This is not the first time he's had a
Had one of these he had another one
About six months ago so there are all kinds of warning signs of shit going wrong
My dad and I don't have the best of
Relationships in fact we've barely spoken for years
Maybe an email or a phone call or something
But we you know this just a connection problem there which is
This I don't I think the source code is not in the place to get into that
But oh man how fucking weird is it?
You know
So soul searching to do here on this side
Okay, so anyway, I still want to celebrate all the great things the internet has brought us on this a beautiful Friday
Who did I see I got a remember I played Sean more Malo?
Yeah, I think the I mean more Malo. Yeah, that's the way you pronounce it
So I got an email from Laura
Let me see I think Laura is what did she do
Let's read the email here
I wanted to let you know the Sean more Malo I was seeing Sean she says has seen a substantial increase in sales since uploading is music to the pod sake music now working
August sales reports come through CD baby dot com or delayed so sales that were completed in October
Sean is just starting to get sales reports and payments for now. You played Sean on November 18
So I'm curious to see the impact of that
And then she says PM into where I would be down for that struggle
I think that we'll be doing all kinds of cool. You know what this is the time to talk about the pod sake music network. So here's
Here's the thing that
That we're working on so you know that we're we're implementing a payment system
Hold on a second
You know Sean sent me this. I'm on as we'll do this. Hey, this is Sean more Malo and you're listening to the daily source code with the pod
Adam Curry. All right, more Malo. Sorry about that Sean but you did again
Okay, so we're implementing
Commerce on the pod sake music network. Now there's the traditional way you go, which is with a credit card or PayPal or combination
There are you know we have you basically select whatever payment credentials you want to put in
But what I've really been all over and what I think is the right way to go looking at the audience from music and for the the impulse buy of this purchase
Is to do it through SMS very much. You know text messaging is what it's called in the states the rest of the world calls it SMS
It's just like when you vote for American Idol
You cast your vote you send a text message to a certain number with the with the number of your favorite potential idol
And it cost you like 99 cents. Well, duh. Hey, wait a minute. It gets charged right to your phone bill. This is fantastic because this way you don't lock out just so many people who
Aren't able to put down a credit card particularly kids and kids like to buy music. You know, does it make any sense that
If you have to have a credit card to buy music on the iTunes music store and you can't get that from your parents. I'm not given my daughter my credit card
And my iTunes music account no way. Yeah, I can gift her stuff sure, but you know no way just no way
But every kid has a cell phone and every kid, you know loves to buy music and they want to buy music if they can't then what's the logical response
They're going to go rip it off from somewhere duh
So they do like the ease of use now the problem with this almost second. I have a lovely cup of sense say I'll brew it up here for me
Hmm
The problem with this
Is that
The carriers the phone companies like Verizon and
Team mobile and you know all the cellular carriers
They take
45 to 50 percent of the money
So if you were to charge 99 cents per song
Almost half of it goes to the carriers right away now of course that is negotiable if you know if we have like American idol like
Traffic happening. I'm sure that we can negotiate that down, but that's basically what it would start off with so
You know, I know there's lots of people who are very smart listening to this show
And if you have any information about getting a better deal or
Just any I don't think it's there. I mean, this is really the monopoly of the
Cell phone carriers
And that's probably just the only way we can go. I mean, I can see maybe doing a double offering where if you want you can
Pay with a credit card and then we'll make sure that the balance goes to the artist
So you know obviously pod show needs to take some money for the for the processing, but I'm looking more like what CD baby does
You know, they seem to do a pretty fair deal. So I think
If it all works, then we all make out because we'll do it on humongous volume. It'll be beautiful
But so the question is, you know, do we also offer an alternative to buy for 99 cents knowing that
Basically everyone gets ripped off in the process by the cell phone carrier and I have to say
You know, there is a lot going on on their end. There's the whole processing. They're deducting it from a phone bill
And you're doing, you know, they are doing some stuff there, but at the end of the day, it's software that's just running and you're just being overcharged for it
Really how long until their investment is out or they can pull their investment out or they just using perhaps their monopoly position
But personally, I think that we should offer offer it two ways. I'd love to hear your feedback on that
Because I love the ease of use of text messaging, but you know, really hate the fees that are just being taken away
So there you go. Okay, onward with the show
I'd asked many of you to recommend songs to me that of course is how I came across Kevin Reeves and got an email here from deliberate noise
Better known as Derek as a musician from Detroit called Nadir
And the song I dig is called Slave and Derek sent me a link to Nadir's page on the pod save music network
Which of course we'll put into the show notes, not I personally, but you will
And I checked it out and you know what dude, I told you like
Well, don't you know I want to live again
Like a man, it's supposed to
Now I don't want to be a slave anymore
And I don't want to be a slave for you
The Santa American Trudgery
And don't you know that it's a crime
All the steps in the wheel
Who did a sweet tease of joy and pain?
Don't give a damn about the good time
Because we're making so hard to fail
But you're looking for another river
Now I'm alone in my despair
And I just get a record
But take you turn the key
And I'll make you in this corner
And let's break it
I'll never be here
I don't want to feel the pain in my home
And I don't want to feel the whip across my spine
So I want to be tough
Can't tell you
Change your love inside
But don't you know I want to live again
Like a man, it's supposed to
And I don't want to be a slave anymore
And I don't want to be a slave for you
And you will mother something who could be there
And I heal, heal, heal
She's got me like a crazy blade
And still, I can't get over you
And remember when you're far away
I keep remembering your sweet perfume
Instead of thinking about the look
You used to make I'm a vulnerable
And I'll pick you through
And I can still record
But take you turn the key
And let's break it
And I don't want to feel the pain in my home
And I don't want to feel the whip across my spine
So I want to be tough
Can't tell you
To change your love inside
But don't you know I want to live again
And I can manage it, supposed to
And I don't want to be a slave anymore
And I don't want to be a slave for you
And I can still record the pain in my home
And I don't want to feel the whip across my spine
There's no discrepancy, I'm let the pain in yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay yeah okay okay so I'm so officially a Patricia approved she walked in and then uh
Blair in a way on the speakers and she went, yeah, there you go, Nadir. I don't want to be
slaved to you from his distorted soul to point OCD from the Podsate Music Network.
Just staying on the PMN for a second, Adrina Thorpe, who you know from Fly Fly Fly,
which I played the other day on the show, said Adam, thank you for playing my songs
from time to time. The whole pod thing is crazy cool. I just put my stuff up here
up there on Podsate. Next thing I knew I was getting played all over on on your show,
which I know is massively downloaded on the daily basis. And I listened like, and then I can
see why she said, that's so nice. Thanks for playing me. And for that lovely intro, you gave
me. I said, the golden older of Podsate Music. That was hilarious. She says, who would have
thought. She sees that she says that she has seen a direct correlation between what she
called pod plays and sales. Although she notices something else that, and she talks about
download. So I'm going to say that's probably paid downloads from somewhere. The more the,
now, let me see if I can understand what she's saying here. It seems that less downloads on
the songs I offer on the Podsate Music Network than the ones that aren't there. If everybody
likes freebies, I'll probably take a few songs down from there. I have six up right now. I wonder,
I see, I think that as independent artists, Podsate artists become more and more,
their own little companies, their own record companies, essentially, because you have everything within
your power. We're going to see a lot more analysis done on what works and what doesn't work.
And so a dream is already thinking that way. I'm not quite sure what the correlation is. And if
maybe more tracks, oh man, it's not sale. Maybe more tracks on PMN leads to album sales,
the CD sales, and we got to get merchandise up there. It just, it doesn't stop. And also,
we really need to get some tools for independent artists to promote themselves to the pod
castors. I've been receiving a couple of emails, actually, from artists saying, hey, I think my song
will fit on your show. We listen to it, and they give me a link to the PMN, and it can link
right into my playlist. But there's no real uniform way that's being sent. There's no eye-catching
thing. We'd have four gigs of Gmail crap stored up here, and more and more piloting in every
single day. So maybe some tools there to promote it, because I go back to the simple numbers,
if you have a thousand podcasts, and that's only a tenth of what people claim there's out there
today, which is 10,000, although I'm sure we're around 15 to 20 now. If a tenth of that,
one thousand podcasts, with an average of a thousand listeners, plays your song within a week,
that's a million spins. That's unbelievable. You're going to sell off of that. There's just no
way that it just, that's, all the proof is right here. I love it. I love it. And thank you,
Adryna, for sending, for sending in that wonderful email. We'll talk a little bit more about
the blank media tax, and performance rights in other countries all on today's show.
Adam, under November 20th, I had the idea to do the Mad Money Machine podcast.
I got a microphone, a mixer, and audio software. Got the domain name. Learned how to set
up the blog and website and feed, wrote up the first show notes. I got some music from the
Podsake Music Network. I produced the show, the artwork, the ID3 tags, uploaded the show,
a notified various podcast directories. Well, by December 22nd, just 32 days since the idea first
flashed in my mind, my podcast has already made it to number 8 in the iTunes Business category,
32 days, and I'm in the top 10. Adam, just two words. Thank you. I started listening to your show
at about the SC197 and have a missed one since. You have most definitely been the inspiration
to do this, and I thank you. The Mad Money Machine podcast is simply about my passion
to help people invest wisely. Among other things, on each show I'll review the performance of
the stockpicks from CNBC's most watched show, Jim Crammer's Mad Money. The podcast also provides
lots of other investment insights and tools, including a special segment called new money,
at the end of the show for beginning investors or even kids. So check it out at madmoneymachine.com.
This is Paul Douglas Boyer saying it takes money to make money, and it takes stock to make a mad
money machine here. Do you believe anything is possible? We do. We are a flank.
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers. We're a Earth Link.
We believe your personal information should be just that, personal, and we believe your
internet should be a friend, not a foe. We're a flank. Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net,
and discover what our internet experts can do for you, Earth Link. We revolve around you.
You're now entering another world, an audio world, where the music of tomorrow is brought to you
today. A world where you can experience adventure, excitement, bad karaoke, and more.
This is Albert's mind. With your host, this is Albert.
Intersellers' world at www.saldor.com. That's Z-A-O-D-O-R.com, and see what the fuss is all about.
He's a guy. She's a girl, and we've got a bottle. A guy, a girl, and a bottle is a weekly internet
radio show for people interested in listening to an innovative wine podcast from a pair of novice
wine reviewers. Join us as we visit and review both the wineries and their wines in and around
Silicon Valley. You can find us in the podcast area of iTunes or on the web at www.gngp.com.
Yo, a guy growing bow. Thank you very much. Okay, let me just talk about advertising and podcast.
I know that you heard the Earth Link commercial zing by there, and we're really happy that Earth
Link is sponsoring actually pretty big portions of the pod show podcast network.
Just wanted to give you some grand vision, because of course, that's still a standard spot,
and it's a very standard radio-like way. Of course, if we wind up recreating radio, but leaving
advertising the same, then I think we've pretty much failed. There's still going to be a healthy
mix of the old school stuff where we figure all of this out, so I think that as we work together
on figuring out what works, but I do want, I just want to stop briefly and just let you know
what the grand vision of it is, and we've talked about this before, but I want to reiterate,
and the reason why I want to read, the reason why I want to reiterate that is because I heard
my partner Ron Bloom saying the same thing, and when I've known him for a long time, and when we
start saying the same thing, then we're on the right track, then we're working, and it goes,
it's not like any secret handshake or agreement, and it works vice versa.
And I think the concept of winding up where actually, because remember, this is not if we recreate
radio, or the entertainment VM, I don't see the podcast as radio, because I know we'll talk about
that a bit in a second, but if we were to recreate it and we come right back to the way that
radio charges, namely the CPM, or the cost per mill, in other words, the dollar amount you pay
per thousand listeners reached, which is anywhere between five and twenty five dollars per
thousand people that you reach, those are radio prices these days, then we've failed as well.
So, you know, taking into account that even if you have 10 listeners, those listeners have
a special connection between themselves amongst themselves and the podcaster, or the podcasters,
or the host, or the producers of the show, and that connection is what we're out to prove
is extremely valuable, and it's our belief that we can manage advertising campaigns well enough
that the actual advertisers will have to audition in a number of ways, including price,
to actually be able to advertise on any given podcast. So, I just want that to set in for a second,
because that is what is, I believe, I really, truly believe is going to drive this new form of
advertising. We're going to work much more directly with the creative side of the advertising business
for instance, that these earthling spots, actually, if it was a different one every single time,
and I had 30 different ones and there was a different story, it would bother me much less.
I think repetition is the thing that is one of the things that we've gotten really tired of in mainstream
radio, and you can repeat the same general message, but it can be delivered different every single time.
That would just be a start, just a very small modification, and that's done all the time, by the way,
of course, in traditional advertising. But the concept that an advertiser would have to audition
to sponsor a show is big, and it opens it up so that not only big brands and big advertisers,
but if you wanted to just show up with your credit card and advertise on Dawn and Drew, as an example,
then you should be able to do that, and you should be able to audition in the same manner.
And I think at the end of the day, the show itself, the producers, and probably the audience,
if we find the right way to involve them, will ultimately decide what is applicable and what is not.
And that's pretty powerful stuff, it really is. So I just wanted to throw that out there.
Got some interesting Gmail feedback. You know, I'm up to 98% now, I'm my Gmail account. I receive
the special geeky four gigs instead of two gigs. I'm not seeing it grow, so I think it's a hard
wire change they made for me. So I'm going to have to start begging again to get more
gigage allocated. I pay for it. I gladly pay for it. I really love Gmail. Let me pay for it, please.
Give me more space. I need more space. Leo Vagoda has heard Maya
ranting about Gmail, and he started using it for his personal mail, and he likes the way
the built-in spell checker works. I totally agree. I use it all the time. It also has,
it seems a growing list of languages that it'll check for. In fact, when I write an email in
Dutch, which I also do from time to time, and I hit spell check, it automatically recognizes
that it's Dutch. I don't even have to set it. So that's really nice. Leo goes on to say in his emails,
I check the spelling on a mail I was sending earlier this evening. I noticed they don't know
the word podcast. It's true. I've noticed this. I have told Rama, she rommed that. I said,
dude, you know, next time we talk to the Gmail guys, get me some more space. And you might want
them to put the word podcast into their spell check dictionary. It's just a minor oversight,
but it makes you look so Microsofty, you know? So please fix that. They'll hear it. They'll fix it.
Let's keep an eye on it. From this date, from the 23rd December, let's see how long it takes to get
it fixed. And I lost his email address. Dutch guy sent me an idea about syncing up Gmail to my
blackberry, and using the email push the way the way it works with the regular service that it
comes with. And he has a very good work around. Unfortunately, speaking of Microsoft, it requires
installing the exchange server. So his idea was since, since Gmail, so I guess it supports I'm
app. Does it support I'm app? Yeah, I think it supports I'm app. Or maybe the extended pop three
protocol, whatever the hell that is. And what he did is, so essentially you can set up push email
either through your cellular carrier who will have some kind of web interface for you or you can
set it up with an enterprise exchange server. And it'll also push your email out and synchronize
it. And so what he did is he said, well, once you create a connector to Gmail through I map,
or the extended pop three protocol, so that it will basically replicate the changes that you make
in your exchange email box. And so it is a chain and there's an extra step in the middle,
but it would work. Now, of course, the the big problem is, you know, setting up an exchange
server. Man, I'm afraid of that. But the idea is really cool. So it could work. Any more thoughts
on that are obviously welcome. And just got a quick email from Cass Blaster Mike. We haven't talked
about Cass Blaster Mike in a while. He has been releasing new code steadily and he's been working
on this other thing, which he hasn't even given me a runtime copy of yet, which is it just looks
really cool. It's the other side of the equation. But it's what I like about seeing the kind of
development that Mike does is he's he's out to solve a problem. He's not, you know, just developing
software. He sees a problem. He saw the problem of a simple way to record a podcast. He fixed it.
And the ties are now being made. The connections between the cast Blaster software and the
PDN, the podcast delivery network. So that's going to be cool for direct, you know, one button
click it all fires off and you're done with that crap. He said that the, um, what is it? The forum
moderator over to castblaster.com has actually started his first podcast, which is unusual. Now usually
people who are on the listening side or, um, or the, you know, or really fans of shows or software.
They don't, you know, if they're not podcasting already, it doesn't happen that, you know,
people hang around for months and then start to podcast. And so he's got a, it doesn't have a promo yet,
but it's a radioqrm.com. If you want to hear a podcast made with cast Blaster, direct from the
cast Blaster community, really go check that out. And cast Blaster is a free download, um, it'll work
for, you know, it'll record up to 10 minutes and then you can purchase a license. If you want to,
uh, um, if you want the full understricted version, castblaster.com.
Oh, let me see. Well, I was just cruising around the podcast, using network, uh, and, you know,
again, another 50 new songs in there, so another record label came online, just kicking some
ass. And, um, I found this, uh, it's kind of like a mix, but it's like rock and a little bit of
country, uh, let me see, the artist's name is Terri Lee Cobble. And I think the CD's about a year old,
but, uh, yeah, I'm a sucker for this kind of music. White T-shirt on your daily source code.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
My body now, my rugged warrior, you own this heart
I'll keep it for you, my life, my love, my rugged warrior
I love everything world, give me a life I take
You're the picture of adventure and you're the kind my name
My life now, my rugged warrior, you own this heart
I'll keep it for you, my life, my love, my rugged warrior, my life, my rugged warrior
Yeah, I should look good too
Terrily bubble
My teacher, very short code, the Christmas edition isn't it?
I'm not going to do a show on Saturday, certainly not on Sunday
Patricia's present came today
I'm glad she isn't listening to the show
But thanks to all of your comments about what kind of karaoke machine to get her
Which I know is her big wish
And I got this fantastic, it's like the professional version of the version
Version of the Mr. microphone
And it's got thousands of songs you can hook it up to the TV
It has a wireless FM transmitter
It's got to do it microphones
It's high, yeah
So the only thing I got to do now is get a good amplification radio reception system
But I'm really, really happy about what I got for
So this is the Christmas edition
I'm only halfway through the list
I don't know if I want to do another hour long show
It was Timothy Freewin
It says you add on my feel really offended about how you seem so incapable of keeping up with the lost info
And he sent me this list of lost podcasts
I'm talking about the TV series lost
That is so extensive
That once the show notes are up, I'll go in and I'll just post this whole list in
Because it's every single thing you want to know about lost in the podcast format
Which by the way, I'm starting to figure this out
Really what we're talking about here is
We're mashing up our own media
Yeah, it's a podcast, yeah, it's kind of like radio
But what is it really?
What really is this stuff we're doing?
What we're doing is we're taking each other's shit and repurposing it
And throwing good back at each other
It's like it's definitely mash up
We're mashing up songs that we're making in our bedrooms, basements, addicts
Or professional studios
We're taking audio feedback from each other
And bits and bytes and pieces of mainstream media
That have been missed and mashed and mangled
And we're putting it all together and then we're calling it a podcast
But it's a mash, it's a mash of stuff
And I think that we're going to see
Well, I think we'll see the same thing with video
Seems like and maybe with pictures we see all kinds of mashups
So the next thing I want to invent
Is the mashboard
That's what it's got to be
It's got to be a mashboard
And it got to be able to output to different places and different devices
And it's the communication that we were talking about
The podsafe music community and which interweaves into podcast community
Which interweaves into yet other communities of a physical handicapsy
But you know, so you find yourself in touch with all these great people
And you know what it's
It's
Oh, man, what can I compare it with?
It's going to be the, you know, it's going to be big
I can feel it, I can't feel it
Here's an example of all that mashing stuff
You know, when I was a young boy
They told me not to put my day job
Because my shinning shut
Well, you know what?
I'm a podcaster now
And because you've had a curry and podcaster
I can quit my day job
You can quit your day job
I can quit my home
You, why do you?
Did you see the
All the new themes song when we talk about podекотор
Yesterday I put out of the challenge
Since we haven't officially announced
We have two partners. I'm only kind of hinted it one
For our podcast delivery network
Now the the big thing about
Growth and podcasting
testing is this shit just eats up bandwidth and in order to be able to deliver reliably,
we didn't want to go and build infrastructure that other people had figured out a long,
long time ago. So we partnered up with a big player. And we want to make sure that, of
course, anyone who wants to independently produce a podcast, can at least not have to worry
about the delivery part, not have to worry about the tools part, not just not have to worry
about that stuff. So you can just get, hey, look, if you need to produce her, then that
works going to help you out, believe me. So I hinted around, and so far two people have gotten
the right Pico and Leo figured out who our partner is. So that's all I'm going to say about it
for right now. You could actually, if you did some more digging, and this is for the nerds,
you could actually find out who our other partner is. And it's also a really a network partner,
but someone who offers a very important service when it comes to networking.
And we think, January 1st, we'll have our first, by now it's probably about 50 podcasters
who will be using the PDN as well as the first portions of the network.
And I can tell you, I'm very, very excited about it. So, and they'll be talking about it on their
own shows, and they'll be letting you know about what they're experiencing. So I don't have to
to do our own horn here for the moment. But I do want to do the horn of the folks at Pod Show
who are working really hard to get a lot of stuff done before, really the Christmas week,
and also for those who have decided to shift their lives around to work between Christmas and New
years, and it's deeply appreciated by myself, and I'm sure that a whole bunch of other podcasts
who have been waiting for for great services to come online and to be happy as well.
Oh, wait a minute. Oh, yes, it's time, ladies and gentlemen, because it's Friday, so we get the
talk about the bio diesel industry, and we do it with a Trinity song.
From the bio diesel industry. So today we've got some banter on synthetic oils, some
biodiesel podcasts, a book about biodiesel, having some cow dung make a car run, and a show on the
discovery channel. It's also a diesel engine for an airplane, and is she a biodiesel at all?
These questions of many more will remain unanswered in our bio diesel segment.
Which of course revolves around the purchase of my new Mercedes 300 turbo diesel biodiesel?
Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, Trinity, I think Jeff is blind too.
I don't know. Jeff, can you send me the, just the track for that? The music, because I'd love to
continue the music, continue to have the music continue underneath me going through some of the
feedback that we received regarding biodiesel and Trinity, and I'd really love for these to be
audio feedback, and one of the things we're going to have on a new show sites as a part of the
podcast network will be a feedback mechanism that'll make that a lot easier for everybody,
including the podcast, of course. Peter Warnock, hooked into the synthetic oils conversation
and says synthetic oils help reduce our dependency on crude oil, but it's still derived from petrochemicals
as our nylon latex plastic and a variety of other products. Yeah, okay. So, again, you know,
I'm not in this, I just want to make it clear, although it has all the benefits of being much greener away
of consuming road space. I'm really in it for the independence of just being able to, you know,
my ultimate dream to be able to poop in my tank and go. BJK, BJ says you need to serve to TDI club.com.
Okay, form for diesel owners, hackers, mechanics, biodiesel brewers. These are the guys who know
all about the diesel cars. Okay, definitely. And also he says the podcast more hip than hippie
had useful biodiesel information. Okay, so maybe we can ask Dorian Val to revisit biodiesel.
That would be cool. Moving on to Ash Reed, Adam Congratulations with your new car.
I've enclosed the book I sell over at newbiodiesel.com about biodiesel. Good starting point for making
and using biodiesel. Okay, cool. So that's newbiodiesel.com. I thank you for the PDF.
It's on my required reading list that usually happens on virgin upper class. And then I got an article
about cow fuel. I'm just going to fire up a fire Fox here for a second. Take it there.
It's actually a Reuters story. And this comes from Quebec. A Canadian company has an idea for
motors worried about global warming. Put a cow in your tank. And man, what's next? Poop in your
tank? You're going to steal all my lines here. $14 million a Canadian dollar. Factor in your
Montreal started producing biodiesel fuel two weeks ago from the bones, innards, and other parts
of farm animals such as cattle, pigs, or chickens that Canadians do not eat. We're rushing. No, I'm
sorry. We're using animal waste to reduce greenhouse gas emissions said marketing director won
Ron Wardrop of Rothsay, which runs the plant. We need more of this type of thing. And he said
at the plant by the St. Lawrence River near Montreal where 189 nations are meeting this week to
work out how to curb climate change, wildly blamed on emissions of heat-trapping gases from fossil
fuels. Anyway, so they're thrown just debris, I guess. Just dead, dead animals. Okay.
Which brings us back to that original thought of your granny and your tank. More with thought.
I missed it, but the discovery channel had a show called dirty, or has a show called dirty jobs.
And in one of the episodes they featured biodiesel, I was wondering if anyone has a bit torn
or can tell me when, because I do have discovery channel here over in Europe. I don't know if it's the
same one. Just when I can catch that. I'd love to see that. And here's Kevin Mason saying,
how about having listeners send you an image? Oh, this is whether I actually have a biodiesel
engine or not. I think we're going to find out if I have a biodiesel engine, we throw some biodiesel
in and see if it works or not. But that is a good idea. If someone could put in the show notes,
a converted engine before and after. So we know exactly what pieces of kit to look for. That would
be very helpful. And see two more here. John Foreman says, actually, oh, I know John,
he says he's been in the garage building as plain all week. And he's been catching up on the daily
source codes. And he sent me a link to a site called Delta Hawk and Delta Hawk Engines.com.
Um, they make diesel engines for airplanes. He says, doesn't know if they have a conversion
for the 182, but, you know, I'm sure it's coming. Imagine that flying, pooping in your planes tank.
Oh, man, I love it. And then the final one, Chris Holman, who, yeah, this is the same thing.
Other than the stick around the back windshield, or you sure this is even a biodiesel car.
Well, I'm going back at the January 8th, I think, the 8th or the 9th. And I'll be then in the
condo for two weeks, a good run. And, uh, well, I know that I'm going to run out of fuel eventually.
So we are going to do our sound seeing tour trip to Berkeley, biodiesel oasis.
Yeah, baby, cannot wait. Hey, Adam, this is Chris with the Children of the God's Project
over at Children of the Gods that net. I just wanted to drop you a line and thank you for playing
my comment to you on your show a couple of weeks back. And again, for the play on today's show as
well, I also wanted to pass on to you that the response to that comment has been simply phenomenal.
I've received close to 50 emails from folks offering to lend their voices or various
talents with music and sound effects to the project. I have to tell you, I'm truly scrambling to
get the scripts written fast enough to give as many of these great people a role in the project as
quickly as possible. It's getting a little nuts. In fact, for those of your listeners who have
set me an email and haven't received a response from me yet, I would like to apologize for the delay
and getting back with them. Simply, wasn't prepared for the onslaught on my inbox, and since I'm
pretty new, not only to podcasting, but also to a publicized project of this scope. I'm suffering
from a bit of disorganization. I've worked hard to fix it though, and I'd like to invite any of
the volunteers who have not heard back from me to visit production.children of the gods.net
and create an account for themselves. There, they can check out the latest scripts as they are finished
and see what roles are available and make contact with me to volunteer for a particular part.
This way, it's a little more organized than I'm not struggling with people who want the same
part and so on and so on. It's slow going right now while we try to get jostled into the main
character roles and get the recorded voices all together. But once everyone's in position,
I should be able to produce a new episode, once every couple of weeks at first, and then hopefully
once a week as I get the production process streamlined. In the meantime, keep your ears open for
the sonic boom. I think this project is going to make it a podcast community. If it cracks your windows,
let me know so I can get a check to you, huh? Thanks again, pod, father. See you, Mac.
Out. All right, man. Thank you. That's Jay Mac's brother. I think, from not mistaken.
And so these projects, this is something really beautiful. It's taking place here. If you look at
what happened with pod safe for peace, 32 pod safe artists, all mixed, all virtual people who
never met each other, not before, not since. If you look at the friends and technology,
Christmas Carol, their geeky Christmas Carol, one of their in their series of, where's it,
nightmares from the server room. If you look at this project, children of the gods, if you look at
comment, have you heard of the podcast, a podcast Christmas Carol at apodcastChristmas Carol.com.
Wow, this was great. I had a small role in it. I was really thankful that I was allowed to participate.
When I heard it all come back, I was just amazed at the shit we can do. And we're putting,
I mean, this is a 50 minute drama, and it's compelling. It's good. You know, this is story to it.
And of course, it's all tongue and cheek. And we're kind of making fun of the radio industry.
But it's great, you know, and how quickly we're able to organize and and create a mashup,
there you go. Once again, you know, what the hell was that? That was a complete mashup. We made
entertainment ourselves. This is really important stuff that's happening here. I'm excited about it.
Note to self, must make the mashboard, whatever the fuck that is. And an update on the
tie. We're just going to get it through everything today. I got like six more items on my list.
Frank Yonan, by far and away, has sent in the most beautiful design for my tattoo that I've
been thinking of getting. No, I'm convinced I'm getting it now. We're now down to the final bits of
design Patricia has taken his design and has made some adaptations. I'm going to scan those,
email them back to him. And then I guess I'm just going to have it made. I'm really excited about this.
And trucker Tom, if you know, trucker Tom is, or if you don't, go search Flickr for trucker Tom
tags. And you'll see that he without a doubt is an expert when it comes to tattoo. I think 50
percent of his body or something like that is tattooed. And he sent me this wonderful, of course,
I packed it away. Now, he sent me this wonderful, like quick start guide, which was a project I
guess he worked on a while ago. It was kind of like, you know, when you open up a new gadget,
you have the manual and then you have the quick start manual. So this was a part of what was supposed
to be a series of quick start guides. And it was a 10 step quick start guide to getting a tattoo.
And there's some really, yeah, there was some really good information in there. And some some
good, thoughtful things. You know, one of the, and also some jargons. You kind of know what you're
talking about, but also some recommendations like never, ever ever get someone's name tattoo.
You know, your body bad idea. So appreciate it, Trucker Tom. Really do. And what I'll do is I'll
put the, when we have the final design, I'll put it up in the show notes, a show notes. You could
take a look at it. And then, you know, what? Now, I think that was Patricia calling for Christina
not for me. Anyway, uh, egg nog. Uh, I was waiting for this to happen. I think Patricia's
calling Christina. Uh, Amy Bugbee says, Adam, heard your call for egg nog recipes. And here's
mine actually made it my very first podcast at crime in cookies.com. Go to the cookie cast about
four minutes long. And I give the entire recipe and directions. Rum and whiskey. Imagine that. Um,
you got it, Amy. Thank you very much. I'm going to, I'm, I've chosen your recipe because you're
the first one to do a podcast of it. So, I'm going to use that. Let me see, now onto the blank
media tax. Um, and I think we should wind this up pretty soon. Uh, I think the first thing I have
here is a comment from Darrell. Let me see, it looks a little four minutes maybe long. Let's see what
it was. I think it was actually something pretty good. Hey, Adam, this is Darrell Falman with
Roscoe podcast. And this has to do with you. Oh, yeah, right. He's a lawyer or he's a lawyer in
making, but it's the law school podcast. So, yeah. So, I want to definitely listen to this because
he goes into the United States code and statutory law about who is allowed to collect money from
blank media. It's four, it's four minutes long. So, you might want to skip ahead if you're
completely uninterested, but he has some really good pieces of information that he's dealt up
for us that I think you want to listen to. Your performance rights. I tried to do some research
on this a little bit to find out what to deal with. I really cannot believe that there'd be a charge
for a digital audio recording mediums as it's defined by the United States code. But anyway,
there is a fee for that. A digital audio recording medium is any material object and form
commonly distributed for use by individuals that is primarily marketed or most commonly used
by consumers for the purpose of making digital audio copied recordings by use of a digital
audio recording device. So, that could be a recordable seating raw. Now, here we have the royalty
payments. Digital audio recording media. This is a total 17 chapter 10 subjectorsc section
one thousand four under the United States code. The royalty payment do under section one thousand three
for each digital audio recording medium imported into and distributed in the United States
or manufactured and distributed in the United States shall be 3% of the transfer price.
Only the first person to manufacture and distribute or import and distribute such media shall be
required to pay the royalty with respect to these such media. Now, under the United States code
title 17 chapter 10 subjectorsc section one thousand six, this is the allocation of royalty payments.
It's in two funds. Number one, the sound recordings fund. They get 66 and three two thirds per cent.
Two and five eights per cent of that goes to now's for a escrow account managed by an
independent administrator and also the interested copyright parties that are the non-featured
musicians. That's two and five eights per cent to them. One and three eights per cent of the
royalty payments allocated go to non-featured vocalist and then forty percent of the remaining. So,
forty percent of the remaining after two and five eights and after one and three eights of the
66 and two thirds that's complicated all this fractions. But forty percent of that goes
to the sound recordings fund and shall be distributed to the featured recording artists. And then
sixty percent other remaining of the remaining royalty payments shall be distributed to the owners.
Okay, so now we have thirty-for-one-third percent left. Fifty percent of that will go to the music
publishers and then, I mean, do I say thirty percent of that fifty percent? Fifty percent
goes to the music publishers and fifty percent goes to the writers. So, there you have it.
I just started doing some research on this. I'm interested to learn some more, find out who
the sound recordings fund is and, you know, who all these parties are. And it's just kind of
interesting, I'll post some information in the show notes from your DSC 302. And you can read
it there and also links back to my website and maybe some other links as well. One interesting thing,
I found a case while I was doing some research that had the RIA and they were basically
going wanted to go to arbitration on the amount of money that they were getting and what they
wanted was something like forty-some percent instead of like two percent or whatever and they ended
up getting about six percent from music and a couple of other companies. But anyway, interesting stuff
and cut out what you need. I know it's a bunch of garbage but the basics of this is that,
yes, there is a three percent charge on the transfer price for media in the United States.
Have a good one. I hope you have a great Christmas. Talk to you later.
Hold on. What happened? Yeah, I'm doing the show so you walk in, you're on the show.
I'm into theory. No, so I have to use your keys. Well, no, you don't have to. You can go find your key.
I know, but I have to go to sense, Barry, and by, well, you do some, will you buy something for me
while you're there? You know, there's a new Gillette G3 Razor with a vibrator in it.
Really? Yes. It's supposed to be the, yeah, yeah, I've seen it there at Sainsbury. It's
a, it comes with a battery and the whole thing. Really? Yeah. Oh. Can you go one of those for me?
Yeah. Okay, thank you. Love you. Bye. So, um, back to that, man, this is going to be such a long
podcast. But hey, it's not often that Christmas and Hanukkah start on the same day.
Thank you very much for going through all the trouble there to find to find out that information
about the code. This is exactly what your government is doing, ladies and gentlemen, and notice that
stuff goes into arbitration when they, when someone else wants to muscle in and get some,
some money out of this pool, how about just independent programmers? If it's only about
copying files and not specified as music, then anyone could delve into that. Man, man, that's, that's
what your government does. You, you wonder why Holly would donate so much money? Well, duh,
this is how they get it back, you know, by getting able to being able to cut these kind of deals
on the back end. Doesn't matter. I, I don't, I'm not interested in any of that. Let's say,
well, they're all busy, you know, meeting and going into arbitration about how to divvy up the
dough. Let's create our own pool. You know, let's create our own pool of cash and let's surprise them.
When they wake up, we'll say, well, sorry, we got everything running over here. Just find new rules
and Doug Pilgrim really takes it to the extreme and he's so right. He says, hey, isn't blank paper used
some of the time to copyright material? Can you imagine the shitstorm that would be creative?
There was a fee or a tax on blank paper? Why not? If the RIA can tax CDs, why not let publishers
tax blank paper? You know, it wouldn't surprise me if they already do. When not surprised me at all.
Okay, I don't know how this one got by my, you know, my RSS reader, but apparently Apple is selling
a podcast server and there's been some talk about that on the boards. I don't know, I mean,
it would work for businesses. I think actually is being sold as a business podcast server.
And let me see, there was a, oh, man, I got this whole PDF about the Australian version of
AskCat, the amount of AskCat. I might just take a look at it for a second. There was a reason why I
put it into my, into my outliner. Oh, yeah, they have, oh, yeah, it's the podcast license from
the RP, APRA, which is Australia's version of AskCat slash BMI. What was the thing I wanted to talk
about here? It was so complicated. Here we go. So this license is good up until the 31st of December
2006. Podcast containing music works are licensed at 1.925%. That's including a value added tax
of gross revenue. So any money you receive, all of all the money you get for your podcast.
And that would include barter as well. So if you receive something in trade, you'd have to
basically pay cash your fee. It's subject to a minimum fee of 1.62 cents per work per subscriber.
Cap.16.5 cents per podcast per subscriber. So I guess if you had to show where you had like 10 songs
or but does it even have 10 or 20, then essentially you have to pay. This is amazing. 16 cents.
Per work per subscriber. That sounds, let's just take it at the, let's just make it two cents
just to make it easy, okay? Because that's a little bit above the minimum fee. So if you have,
like I just, I'm going to have three songs in this show. So that would be six cents.
And then I have to multiply it by the subscribers. So even I would go broke.
Now it doesn't say anything about if you don't make any money,
which I think means that the minimum subject to a minimum fee that I think you always have to pay
the 1.62 cents. And those are Australian cents. I presume, Australian dollar cents.
Wow. Yeah, that's great. But I don't think it's really going to work.
And of course, the real question is of that fee, does any of that money go to the actual independent
artist who created the music? I don't think we're there yet, guys. I really don't.
What I do know is that we're definitely there for this year, for this podcast,
and I think it is kind of unique that Hanukkah starts on the 25th of December, which is Christmas Day.
And I want to, yeah, really, I want to wish you all a very Merry Christmas. We don't have
a Hanukkah Podsafe piece, but perhaps that will happen next year.
That time I went down, feels like at that time again, to me, the mistletoe, a Christmas show,
and the lighting of that famous Christmas tree, people are shopping for their loved ones.
I'm making plans for Christmas feets, learning all goes by, and I'm playing golf now.
And then we have to wait another year, while in every day, Christmas,
what I wonder more, this would be, you never feel blue, we make all our dreams come true,
whenever it's possible, we're every day.
It was time to bring out the good people. I just look around now and you will see it.
Yeah, everybody's nice and full of light, and they get to those who aren't me,
and they get everything that every day, Christmas, what I wonder more, this would be,
we'll never feel blue, we make all our dreams come true, we're Christmas, we're every day.
I'm going for the summer to the spring, I'm taking the sunshine here, I'm doing it's Christmas again,
what is every day, Christmas, what I wonder more, this would be, you never do, we will never feel blue, we make all our dreams come true,
what I wonder more, this would be, you never feel blue, we make all our dreams come true,
we make all our dreams come true, we make all our dreams come true, we make all our dreams come true,
It was so cool.
Listen, everybody, have a very happy holidays.
I'll be back on the 26th Monday.
We'll get it all cranking again.
And I'll talk about some more shit
as Mark Yoshimaru Namcoff would say.
But it really is true.
So be good everybody, be healthy, and be very happy.
Bye.
Pot show.
The pot cast cool kids go for.