Delta, Sierra Charney, 2-80-7!
There are no secrets.
Only information you don't get higher.
And I'm Korean.
Oh, $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
The next generation radio concert in my ears.
I like to think I'm sighing into this genre.
It balls you and Madalemy should.
Good morning, Madalemy.
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to the Daily Source Code.
It's Monday.
Start of a new week.
We're getting very close to the holiday season.
Which means it's time to start cranking up the Christmas tunes.
Checking out the pot-safe music network over the weekend.
I'm not the only one with these thoughts about Christmas songs.
I'm not the only one wanting something different,
something new to celebrate the holiday season.
Jill Park is on my frequency.
Do you hear what I hear?
Check this out.
Cool.
Do you hear what I hear?
Do you know where I am?
We're through the sky, shall we go?
Oh, a sun, the sun,
I am at the sea with a voice
As big as the sea, with a voice
As big as the sun, yeah
Oh, a sun,
I am at the sea with a voice
Do you know where I am?
Oh, a sun, the sun, yeah
In the clouds warm my head
Do you know where I am?
Hey, how's it going?
It's the sun, the sun, the sun
Let's be your sun, the sun
Oh, a sun, the sun, yeah
Oh, a sun, yeah
We're through the sky, shall we go?
Do you know where I am?
Oh, a sun, the sun, yeah
In the clouds warm my head
To the people of the way
How it sends you and I say
Before peace, people of the way
Oh, it sends you and I say
Hey, you shine the shine
He's giving it the power
How much asked does that kick?
Jill Park, do you hear what I hear?
I hear the quintessential Christmas song
From the pod save music network
We'll be talking a lot about that today
Good morning, good afternoon
Good evening, wherever you're from
It is indeed nearing the Christmas season
The high street lights have been illuminated
In the high street and gilford
And starting today, I hope
I still have to win on confirmation of the setup
We'll have a new feed, a new podcast
Feeders, you can find at xmus.podshow.com
Every day I'll be unleashing a new pod save Christmas song
And I was thinking about this last night
So basically I want the concept here
Is to release a new Christmas song from the pod save music network
Every single day, put it into this feed
So you can essentially just use it to fill up your iPod
And at the end, I'll make sure that we have the full complete feed
With all songs that will probably be what
25 or something, no
Almost 30 songs
I'll re-publish that so it'll be like an archive
Now it would be
I think it would be too
You know what, I'm really thinking of the radio stations that you hear
The during Christmas time
They send all the disjockeys home and they just play Christmas music
Which is really nice, although it's extremely repetitive
Often
But you can just kind of turn it on and you'll have a nice little Christmas vibe
So I'd like to give you some stuff to fill up your iPods
And you don't need to play with for Christmas vibe
And what I'm looking for is Christmas greetings short, please
Very short Christmas greetings from podcasters
And podsafe musicians as well
So I can mix those over the intros
And so when you play it back to back
It'll be like this nice, big long holiday greeting card
So if you feel like doing that, drop it into promos.podshow.com
Drop your Christmas greeting in there
Just a very generic high
It's selling so from the so and so podcast
Merry Christmas
Or any other holiday message you wish to convey
So look for that, Xmas.podshow.com
The same request, they went out simultaneously
For podsafe the queen.podshow.com
Christina's getting really serious now
About, about coma second
Just I'm still frigging around with this microphone
It's too good for the board, that's my problem
So Christina's podcast
I have a feeling that what she's going to do is
She's going to want to work on the look and feel of her
Show site first before she does the actual podcast
But she was even out last night
Or yesterday afternoon she came around home before
7, of course
At a local rehearsal slash recording
Soundstage with some local emo kids
She said we're rocking out
She says that she's going to get an MP3
From them, played on the show
So she's really, she's into it
I'm excited too
It's fun to work with kids like that
Because of course I'll be doing all the engineering
By special request
Last week we talked about free talk live
And how someone had questioned whether they're
Calling for podcast Ali votes on their radio show
If that was fair play or not
So we talked about that in In Bernard of the show
Rode and give some feedback
It says in regards to your question about our radio
Listenership, actually our week, this is the good thing
I really love this
Our weekday radio audience is likely smaller than our podcast audience
Though our Saturday show has now over 10 radio affiliates
Plus to address your email is concerned
The nature of radio listeners precludes most of them
From voting for us
Most of them are in the car, which is the last place
They're likely to visit our vote page
I disagree with that
Oh boy do I disagree
I think lots of people are listening in the car
Whether it's on the radio or on a podcast
And they just remember they go home and they vote
This is kind of the cool thing
Is if you have an RSS feed of your show notes
Eventually that will combine someone's field of vision
That's the way it's supposed to work or kind of
And then they'll say oh yeah that's right
I'm in browsing mode no I might go over and vote
Nonetheless your email seems to be missing the point
We do call votes from other sources beyond podcast listeners
That's good for podcasting
That's why we have a trade deal with podcast Ali
Because talking about podcasting on the radio can only help podcasting
Not hurt
Similarly driving listeners to vote
Also increases their chance of poking around podcast
Ali and sampling other shows
Oh you know what I totally agree
I think it's fair no matter how you do it
You know that's what growing an audience is all about
Jeez look at what some people on TV will do to get an audience
This is all stuff from last week
I had an note here to talk about
What was this more iTunes problems Allen says
Doesn't necessarily have to do with podcast
And listening to daily source code 285
And you just talked about the iTunes music store problem
I've been receiving errors that say
Quote credit card processing is temporarily unavailable
You may continue to browse the store
Please try to make your purchase later
Allen goes on to say I think I'll send an email
To the iTunes support team to see what they have
And response but I'm thinking the same thing
They must be losing a lot of sales
Well of course they're losing sales
And I'm sure that they're not happy about it
Yeah and I want to
I didn't really have the time to respond
In great depth about
Mads Weinstein's issues with iTunes
But I just want to reiterate
That you know iTunes is not the be all and end all of podcasting
Nor do I think what we're doing right now is the end all and the be all of the end of the be all
Of what podcasting can do
And I think you know look we we fought against
Everything and also corporate radio look how far we've gotten there
Now let's not let's not put our dependency on iTunes
Or any other company for that reason
Not pod show not Microsoft not iTunes not Google
There's something much bigger going on here
And good stuff
Stop well let's just say stuff that people want to hear
They find it that that's the beautiful thing about the internet
Is it just does kind of work
Of course you can always take out some television ads
That'll be better than iTunes trust me
Maybe a little bit more expensive
I think it was two trips ago to San Francisco
Where I played what was I guess is the first orgasm fed by RSS
From the horror cast
The Sacred Horror host of the horror cast
Michael Butler rock and roll geek show you might want to check out his latest episode
He doesn't interview with her and talks about the sex industry and sex workers
The Michael's quite an interviewer
He's really I'm not just impressed
I'm often humbled by how he gets his interviews to really open up
And talk to him about all this amazing stuff
So you may want to check that out
I didn't pull a sound clip from it
It's all good trust me it's all good
And boy does the Sacred Horror have a sexy voice
Oh my goodness
Brand
Hey Adam
I mean this and you talk about crazy people
Which is a movie I absolutely love
I thought of another movie that's been floating around the net for a while
Called Truth and Advertising
Oh that's right
Oh yeah, I actually had some audio feedback that I wanted to share
Here listen to this
Hey Adam this is a brand
And I hope you're having a wonderful Thanksgiving
I do the journey to the center of dot com podcast with my buddy Steven
Both of us actually work for an advertising company
I've been listening to you lately talk about crazy people
Which I think is a fantastic movie
That is one of my all-time comedy classics
And I just every time I see certain products like jaguars
And stuff like that I think about
The tag lines and things from that movie
But I thought there's also a movie that's been floating around the net
That you may not have seen
And that's called Truth and Advertising
That's just a spot on parody
Of what it's like
See working and advertising for some of the craziness that goes on
I put a link in the email that I sent to you
But if you do end up spending this on the DSC
Then I'll go over and put it in the show notes
Everybody else can check it out
It's pretty funny stuff
So anyway, thanks for listening
Keep up the good work on the DSC
And if you ever want to hear intellectually stimulating right left talk
Without the acrimonious
Invective or partisan hackery
Come check us out
At journey to the center of dot com
Thanks
Thanks Brent, appreciate it
And in fact after this show
The minute I'm done while I'm still uploading
I'm off to go get my hand jobs from women I hardly know
The cruiser is ready
The money has arrived
Everything is taken care of
I can go pick it up
I love that movie you sent me
Let's see if it works in audio only
And please do I love that
Self perpetuating show notes
So you'll put the link in
Let's see if it works if we just listen to this
It's basically a series of conference rooms
It's imagine Boston legal
That type of office
Those type of conference rooms
And then imagine advertising people
We've talked about fan
We've talked about having sex with
Oh
Oh, hi time
I'm just interrupting to instill some fear
And to humiliate Bob here
Okay
I would say John well here
Can I pop by your office
Say around fiveish to kiss your ass
Sure
Bill, do you want to shut your tongue up my ass
And give it a few tools?
Absolutely
I give you a hand job in a stationary closet
If it meant a good review
Great
Well carry on you over paid jackasses
Go to hell
Well
Sorry to be the mean in front of you
As I was saying
I've tried to come as many ideas as I can
Into this brief
Because I'm really too weak
And too stupid
To make a decision
So let me ask a question
In order to give the illusion
That I actually give a shit
Yeah
What we're trying to communicate
We hear really is near
Pairty performance
Right
Okay
Now this is a term that is used as a blatant attempt
To mislead consumers
Because we're really too cheap to improve our products
For me lish
Yes we are
So Bob I'm trying to act like I'm making a contribution
When clearly my role is
It'll find it unnecessary
No no that sounds good for a catcher
Awkward
Uncomfortable drink with the client
Anyone?
I'd love to
But I have to go snorkel
K enough strippers tips
Thanks
But I'd rather be burned alive
Here comes the pitch by the director
Basically I doubt the best approach
Would be to repeat exactly what you told me
The first call
And shout all the words around the bed
Wow
If I wasn't such a fucking hack
I'd present that thinly veiled cow
Telling
Do anything original to say it all?
Original
No
But I will make references to German expression
Ism
Use meaning as terms like edgy
And suggest
Disgustingly overused blue green transfer look
I wouldn't have mentioned swing until lenses
But I just discovered they went out for years ago
Okay
That sounds
Incomprehensible
I'm going to suggest the change to the treatment
To confirm your degree of spinal stress
I'll agree to that change
Ignore once I get the job
So you will be our puppet
Sure for the most part
Just as long as you allow me to illusion of being in control
And serve the hack failed filmmaker that I am
Great
Well
To be fun producing this way
On our culture now
I look forward to sleeping with you
Yeah me too
I hope that worked for you
You really got to see the video
It was extremely well acted
And it is so precisely
It's a fantastic translation of what really goes on
In the advertising business
In the advertising agencies
When the clients are involved
And the directors involved
It's
Oh my goodness
It's spot on really
And the more I think about it
The more I'm liking this whole honesty thing
I really am
I'm liking the honesty about the products
This crazy people had made us laugh
I mean we're still in over this movie
What 30 years after it was made
There's something there
What about you, PD Love
He had him PD Love with Lovehouse radio
Just a couple comments
One on advertising
I am getting used to the commercial advertising
That you're running
But it was really a big fan of the more subtle
advertising
In fact it's a night watching
Lost on TV
They had us in CO
And I was waiting for the nice looking lady
To burp
During the advertisement
But that never happened
But getting used to the new stuff
Still like the old stuff
Also on the topic of pod show
When can we expect some damn announcements
Very eager and anxious for
Learning a little more about that
About the pod show delivery network
Or PDN or whatever you're calling it
But interested in getting some more information on that
So if you have a time frame
Please share it with us
Let us know
And I'd be very interested in getting Lovehouse radio on board
So if it's anything like the pod safe music network
You definitely got to hit on your hand
So I love the pod safe
Love the PMM
And we'd like to see the PDN
Again thanks for everything
And talk to you
Yeah right I'm PD Love
Well it looks like
A lot of changes will be incorporated
By Christmas time for the pod safe music network
You know we're working on there
We want to go to sales
And of course the unlabel will come along with that
That'll be around
Just after the first of the year
We have a separate group working on the pod cast
Delivery network the PDN
And the first invites
I think about today
Or this week
To get people
The first batch in
These are people that we've already talked to
I mean
When you set up a service
Which is which incorporates a lot more than just a technology
There's a lot of the promotions
The marketing
Audience growth
Sales
All that stuff is in there
You know you got to start slow
You kind of make sure you do things right
And you need the right people to help you with feedback
So we try to get a good cross section to pod cast
So it's all on the way
I don't know if we'll have a lot of Christmas gifts
But certainly by the new year
When one stuff will really be up and rolling
I'm very excited
We're working
Very hard
And we've actually become
A much tighter knit group
I don't know what it is
But this last visit that I had
I just felt like
Everyone's kind of slipping into place there
And it's feeling it's feeling pretty good
The vitra
Viagra
See you
We find it's a whole studio
If this load of shit is what your inbox sounds like
Every morning
You may want to consider earthling internet services
With integrated spam, scam, and virus blocking
Earthling internet services
Is the laxative that will clean out your inbox
Earthling
Helping you take less shit every day
This promo is brought to you by the financial aid podcast
At financiallypodcast.com
The real no shit deal on student loans
Scholarships and education finance
Visit us online at financialadpodcast.com
When I said a pod father
I come to you one of this day
To ask you a favor
I am a lowly podcaster
I have a family podcaster
I do with my wife and my four bambini
And my children
We have had a trouble getting the people
To listen to our show
Pod father
We are at this advantage
We have the children on our show
We are directed
We do not swear
We do not talk about it this eggs
How are we to compete with the bigger podcast
That have the little red
Explicit logo next to their name
They are so popular
The listeners lack it to hear about this eggs
No
They lack it to hear the F word
Pod father
We cannot offer that on our show
I beg of you pod father
Please play our promo on your show
We need a little listeners
For the future
I will teach you a palar
A person in the world
For
I will give the two jobs to feed of my family
If only I could come to your pod show
And make a little bit of money
I am not greedy pod father
I only wanted to quit a second job
And spend a more time with my wife and a bambini
Please do what you can to help us
Play our promo
Let us come into your pod show fold
There must be listeners out there who want
If I am a friendly podcast
No
With your help pod father
Those are people who will find our show
We are the 6620 West Kidcast
You will find us in iTunes by searching for 6620 West
I do not see a pod father
I do not see
My son
I had big plans about creating this whole response to that
Hey
You know what I am missing?
I am missing
Yeah
That is what I am missing
So I had this whole
This whole plan
And then I got busy with something else
No worries
I think that
That is too much
I have really been considering a whole new setup here
This is pissing me off the way this thing works
It is not flexible enough
I want something
The mobile setup I am happy with
But you know this Yamaha workstation
It is still not exactly what I want
So I am going to start rethinking that
Somewhere next year I am going to rebuild the whole
Podcast complex
But anyway
In the new year my son
In the new year
Is when we will take care of all of your problems in your requests
I will make you enough for you
Cannot refuse
We have been talking about
Ask at BMI and their stance on podcasting
Versus
And really the the issue of copyrights
That you sign over to them or assign them
And I have gotten lots of feedback
We heard about the Dutch Buma Stemera
We heard about the German Gema
And now
You are not going to believe this
This is exactly what I was
I joked about this happening
I fucking joked about it
And it is not happening in the US
But listen to what is going on in the rest of the world
ERO
And ERO is from
Oh
Where is ERO from Finland
Adam if you think that Gema
Is strict on secondary rights and stuff like that
You should come to Finland and see Tiosto
Which is the Finnish version of Ask at BMI Tiosto
Tango Echo Oscars here at Tango Oscar
Let me give you a few examples how they make things hard on artists
We made a promo CD with my band a month later
They sent me a letter that's Tiosto
With this humongous form I had to fill out
Just to make sure the material on the album was made by us
And I had to send the one copy of that CD
So they can check it out and make sure of that
Okay
Well it depends on if you burn the CD at home
Or if you burn it a factory
If you do it a factory
There's like automatic processes that go into place there
So that may have been what happened
Two
We played a gig at a local bar
We alone arranged the whole happening
Which featured lots of local bands and stuff like that
All the bands played their own material
And we divided the income from ticket sales equally to all bands
Then six months later Tiosto sends me a letter again
With this gigantic form
Which I of course had to fill out
They asked which songs we played there
Not just my band but of all bands
They said that all the bands played their own copyright material
But that wasn't enough
We had to pay them for playing our own stuff in there
Point three
If I make a podcast I can't ask any rights from any band to play their music
If they've copyrighted their music with Tiosto
Even if you make a compilation and give all the profit to charity
You have to pay Tiosto their share
Which of course is sent back to the artist
Which in most cases send the money to the charity organization
In a nutshell
Tiosto sucks ass
That's a fine finish expression there
If you want some income from your music
You had to sign up with Tiosto
But that makes it impossible for you to promote your music for free
Now my band doesn't have any more anything
Any more anything to do with Tiosto
But we still need to fill a form now and then
Okay, so essentially what is happening here
With the European rights organizations
And so far we know it's the same
Also it's for the Dutch, the Germans and the French
When you sign up with their version of ASCAP BMI
You are not allowed to give away any other rights to anyone
So you cannot say to a podcaster
Hey go ahead take my stuff and go and play it for free
That will be a breach of your contract with that rights organization
This is fucking nuts
It's really nuts
So you know it's like a it's a conundrum I guess
Or yeah or the catch 22
No, it's a conundrum I think
And this is weird
So I feel you know that we need to address this issue
I'm not quite sure is there one central organization
I didn't find it I didn't find one central organization
That that works across all of these rights organizations
But this is wrong
I mean if it's your property then you should be able to change that license
However you want I think I recall properly that somewhere
It is a constitutional right of these
Of these organizations to be the only one to collect or not collect I guess
On artists copyright royalties
It's
It's fucking nuts
It's what it is
Hey Adam I recently started the Buckeye Drive Time podcast
The format is very simple three pod save songs and three promos
With all of the introductions up front
And links to the music on the website
When you introduce the promo deal on pod show
I was deleted
Now I didn't have to run around all over the place looking for promos
Unfortunately many of them are geared towards your daily source code show audience only
With like a high atom or some other
VSC specific content in the promo
It would be great if folks could provide a generic promo as well
So that I could go ahead and insert them into the show more easily
I genuinely want to promote pod cast and the show promos are the best way that I know about getting it done
Great job with the pod safe music by the way
Music.potshow.com is just absolutely what I needed to be able to get this started
So it got me up and run it and I hope to get to your promos
And as I can put one together for my own show
In the meantime, shameless promo number one is
Check out www.buckeyedrivetime.com
Fox Joe, Spock safe music and more
We remind you of this week's new music
Get into your ears
What to do with my co
Well, see knows what to do with my co
Do you do mince me
Tell me it's me how to let me pass
Open to the soul
Oh, our sugar stow
Biggest town
Just to pursue the perfecting loneliness
I miss your future co
I'm sorry
Number one fan, come on
What to do with your heart
Tell me if I have that
This music is much more
Available at the bot save music network
Just so go get it at me or say
Gotfossio.com
Hi, this is Scott from American cliché
I'm always amazed that some of the things I run across online
Read a newspapers or see on TV
Whether it's some sort of bizarre news story
A slice of pop culture
An emerging musical talent
Or some random active stupidity
I never seem to be at a loss for something interesting
That's sort of the premise for my show
American cliché
It's basically a crash course in pop culture
And obscure internet buzz for the week
Give me 30 minutes
And I'll give you enough material to keep your friends entertained for hours
Visit the website at www.americanclishay.net
Or do a search in the podcast section of iTunes for American cliché
Subscribe and decide for yourself
It's truth really stranger than fiction
Or is that just an American cliché
Hi, this is DJ pubs
For the big pubs, a boogie box podcast
The big pubs, boogie box features new music from across the web
Including pubs, safe music network
You can also find it unique with all the artists on there
Highlights so far have been 46 minutes
And a man himself, probably love
You can catch big pubs, boogie box every Friday
I have a quest reader.com.uk option number five
Hi, this is Peter from the Ultimate Mix podcast
I'll be writing you to join me on a fantastic journey
Until a pod safe music network
Every week we crawl across the 10,000 plus songs
And make up the new music revolution
And bring you the finest clats to your iPod
A desktop, a home Wi-Fi
No two songs play, we quite the same here on the Ultimate Mix podcast
Because we feature music for more genres
So for a real taste of the future of music
Subscribe to the Ultimate Mix podcast
Add onto the mix.
Dropbox.com
Or find us via our tunes
The Ultimate Mix podcast
All my favorite music
Hello Adam, I'm Dan O'Leary
And I'm a pilot for a regional airline on the west coast of the United States
And would you believe I have a podcast
It's called Hotel Coffee
On Hotel Coffee, I talk about the daily life of an airline pilot
Things to do in great places to eat in the cities that I stay
And in each episode I feature a song from the pod safe music network
So once you have a listen on iTunes
At hotel coffee
Or on the website hotel coffee.blogspot.com
Thanks for listening
And may you always have blue skies and tailwinds
Everybody around these mad at me
Because I keep recording everything
But that's okay
Because my podcast is a surf gravity radio
And that's what we do here
Straight recordings
Pads safe music
News
All kind of stuff
You never know what you're going to tell me
To come on over to suring.com
Check it out
Say you like me
Yeah well
Hey man, there's a lot of pilots doing pod casting
Use the most out of lighter
Right on
A lot of pilots doing pod casting
Hey, and I'm going to be flying Friday
Yahoo, Yahoo, yeah
Fucking who I cannot wait
Last trip before she gets disassembled new engine
A black edition gets put in
Whenever the hell that means but I paid for it
A new interior, new upholstery
So it's going to be probably four to six weeks then
It gets shuddled over here
And I get to have it at my disposal
I cannot wait
I'm excited
Is it about aviation and pod casting?
Why does it go together so well?
Or is it maybe just when you have a 10-speed bike
You see everyone driving 10-speed bikes
Could be or maybe there's really something to it
Oh, Adam, this is Robin
And this is Suzanne
We are insideworks.com
That's INSYTWBORKIF.com
Just heard your pain in the plane pod gas
We've got a good chuckle out of that
Because I had a story from my Air Force career
Suzanne and I met over in Europe
I was flying the AT&T and a body of pent-orders
And it's suffocated
We left there, got married and moved to
Southern California Georgia Air Force Base
On this particular day I had dropped off
I had VIP in Tucson, Arizona
And I was flying back
So low across the Mojave Desert
Back towards Georgia, California
But in the hour of the flight I had to pee
Well the OV10 did come with a relief tomb
AKA the Champagne class
Use for that exact purpose
I unstrapped and unzipped
And I started using that Champagne class
I felt so good but it started to back up
And overflow
I had a problem
Also at that moment I realized
I was still sitting in an armed ejection seat
Oh my gosh
Honey, that would be really difficult for me
to understand as a new bride
If there had been an incident
Why my husband's private parts were hanging out
While he's flying
I went nowhere to make it that
So I did put in the safety pin
Into the seat
I had to come up with plan B
Because I still had to pee
I crimped the relief tube
Just like a garden hose
But that didn't work
I fumbled it
And there was a golden shower
Right in the cockpit
Ew
Yeah pretty nasty
Plan C
Add some six acts
I double-bagged him
I wasn't gonna have any more golden showers
No mistakes
I started filling up the six act
It felt great
Roll it up very carefully
Set it over on the canopy rail
And I was a happy guy
About a half an hour later
I noticed two things
Something started to smell
And the bag was expanding
Why was the bag expanding
Well it was summertime
Mojave Desert
No air conditioning in the OV10
It was hot things
We're expanding
Oh my gosh
So it's like a bag of popcorn
And a microwave
That's right
It was about the blow
I had to come up with plan D
The OV10 had an overhead eyeball vent
And instead of blowing
I turned it around
And put it into the suck mode
I carefully unrolled it
Top of this bag
Helped it up to the vent
And it worked great
It was sucking here
And right out that vent
Leave it in a big ol' striped
And the top of the canopy
Well it was this time
It's golden arches over the canopy
Yeah golden arches
It was working great
I was a happy guy
Until it got to the bottom of the bag
It was sucking so hard
It tore a hole
Right in the bottom of the bag
And there was a second golden shower
In the cockpit
At the time it was not funny
But I did think
Someday
This is going to be funny
But right now it's not
Well Adam
I think this is the day
He does funny
It's funny for me
So from one pilot to another
Here's the peeing
Plains
And podcaf
And tailwind
To you, Adam
It's super new
Everyone wishes me tailwinds
Love that
Dude
That's a harrowing story
It would have been better
If you would check it out
With your weiner hanging out
They would have made the story
So much better
Speakin' of that skydive radio
Sends in for the MM50 naming context
I'm gonna wrap this up pretty soon
Because I haven't gotten anything better
I don't think than the porta potty
Uh
See Adam
The MM50 really sounds as crisp and clear
Just said
Does want to call it the logic tech
I symphony
Says Dave from skydive radio
Mmm
Ralph
Says Logitech
I live
Mmm
I don't know about that
Alex
Uh
The Logitech room mate
Yeah
That's not bad
Oh wait
We have an audio feedback on this song
Oh no
Okay
It took me a second to get that one
You just did 50MMs
Okay
Oh man
This is so lame
Melindemasons from my Maryland
Part of Pod
Uh
pronounce party Pod
Part of Pod
Pod Thumper
I'm still nothing better than pork
Pod of Pod
Yeah
Pod Thumper
I still, nothing better than pork de Pod
Yeah
I don't think last one here for today.
As Adam Curry Blastle Park, the old music and recording industry, you need to listen to it
happen on the revolutionary Adam smasher speakers.
No, I don't think so.
Oh my goodness.
Hey, I got tons of people sending me this link about biodiesel.
Apparently there's been a breakthrough in creating it from vegetable oil.
There's a link on treehugger.com, of course, that's where you'd find that kind
of news.
But it is very exciting because now all of a sudden, biodiesel is really coming to the
forefront.
Now that they're seeing an improvement in efficiency of creating the biodiesel from
vegetable oil by 10 to 15 percent, man, I so have to get a clunker diesel in San Francisco.
I promise you, we're going to do these experiments.
Hi Adam.
From the Mac generation.
I'm leaving you this message because we have a kind of a problem.
In our podcast, that is in French and about the Macintosh.
We feature every week, Potsiff Music from the Potsiff Music Network, of course.
And we realized very quickly that there's not a lot of artists, French speaking artists,
registered in the Potsiff Music Network.
So with Xavier, that does the podcast.
Hey, get me Vanessa Paradie.
Okay, get me Vanessa Paradie.
As you really unclear, get them into the Potsiff Music Network.
With me, we recorded a message in French for your French speaking listeners.
So it would be nice if you could play it.
Bonjour Siril.
Bonjour, vous avez bien?
Bonjour, vous avez les auditeurs du DSI.
Bonjour à tous.
Bonjour Adam.
Bonjour.
Alors Siril, je crois que tu n'appell, alancer, en direction des artistes francophones.
Oui, exactement.
Sur le podcast de Macgineration, on passe à chaque épisode.
Donc chaque semaine, de la musique, d'un artiste francophone, c'est possible.
Eh bien, je l'ai un certain oeuvre.
Bon, des maybe sing, l'am just a big hair, the fact.
Donc, on choisit la musique, Potsiff.
Donc, indirectement, on a choisi le Podsiff Music Network,
que pour aller chercher toute cette musique.
Comme ça, on est sûr que la musique correspond
en licence qui nous permet de l'utiliser sur le podcast de Macgineration.
Et le problème qu'on a, c'est que les artistes francophones,
bah, on en a vitefeltour, il y en a très peu.
Alors, la pelc, on a, c'est à tous les artistes compositeurs,
interprète, chanteurs, qui aimerait mettre leur musique en Podsiff,
de rejoindre le Podsiff Music Network,
de manière à ce que le Pods-Cas de Macgineration
a aussi les milliers d'autres podcasts qui sont à inscrire sur le Podsiff Music Network.
Puis découvrir vos œuvres,
et, bah, qu'on puisse les passer les faire découvrir
de ma neexie de môme dôditeurs,
et, en vous faire de la pude, interactément.
Voilà la pelc, doncl'ancé à vous direp embôle.
Les bases doivent votre Sean.
Nous attendons que vous, nos rejoignés,
et nous on seront, très heureux
de diffuser vos œuvres
dans le 4 de Notre Pods-Cas, et àilleurs.
Ciao.
Okay, okay, that's it all right cool. I hope to hear some French pod save music popping up on the PMN very very soon
Here's one from music dot podshow dot com gradient rewind on the daily source code
Yeah
Take to the back want to push underneath job off to the grass one pops with bees
Tell you that I'm sorry for this now and get in the by without you
What I did couldn't take it out along the way think about down so to meet it's random now
There's all the rediscover scum and fell and all right
You've got to try everything and the book to make you forget if I said
For the steaks that I made were in the past if I could take it back
I would do this all the way out in my core
Oh
Back relax keep track of the fact that I'm using the means of it. I'll say the least
So can't drop the keys me in from a little way
I don't know what I did swear I didn't need anything
Could have you back one day all the things that I want to say
If I try everything and the book to make you forget if I said
For the steaks that I made were in the past if I could take it back
I would do this all the way out in my core
I will
Realize
You
Makes you want to hear
Before you tell someone
Where I've tried everything and the book to make you forget
For the steaks that I made were in the past if I could take it back
I would do this all the way out in my core
You know I will
If I could I will
I would do this all the way out in my core
Hope you coped that a young bullet
Content is expat light update earlier
New feature told you yall on gonna be back
Now is working with CC Chapman. I got this great show that coming out
Paulette, concert music spotlight update earlier.
New feature, I told you, y'all gonna be back.
Now he's working with CC Chapman.
I got this great show that's coming out,
which we'll be doing all kinds of stuff
with the Pots of Music Network.
It's gonna be a show by itself
and then we'll have all these cool flash boards
and flashbacks.
So we really get more of the music out there.
Very, very excited about it.
And yesterday, I unleashed a promo,
which was my acting attempt at Howard Beal,
if you remember the movie Network,
got a lot of interesting audio responses to it already.
I had him.
This is Ed from Ed's Mixbag.
I was getting up out of my chair.
I was about to shout
when an inner voice took over and said
but I soon got a hold of myself,
when I realized it was just another Adam Curry pod show.com promo.
Hey, Adam, it's Zen from the Zen Show.
Listen, right after the release of your most recent promo
quit your day job,
I practically went freaking mental with all of this hype.
Now, I'm waiting as patiently as I can,
but you gotta check out this segment from my show.
It went into today's episode
and what I'm gonna do here to kind of set this up is
I'm just gonna play the tail end
with the part that really caught it hooked me.
And then I'm gonna launch into about two minutes of comment.
I know that's a lot of time to ask,
but just hang with me.
Check out this is from today's show.
Are you ready for the audition?
Step up and take it.
Yes, God damn it, I'm ready!
I'm telling you,
I'm gonna sound like a maniac right now
because up into the last like,
I don't know, ten seconds,
it's like, okay, this is kind of strange and weird.
And then they tell you all about it.
You know, quit your day job,
start doing this for a living,
and however they're gonna have you do it,
I don't know.
I hear that last part and it goes from, yeah,
yeah, okay, yeah, whatever this is going on.
Oh yeah, you know,
and it's like totally takes off for me.
And I'm like,
tell me what the hell to do!
Because I wanna do it.
Well before I was ever in the internet,
right out of high school,
this microphone became my best friend.
And I had a lot of good friends and people's,
but I mean, you know,
you do it through high school,
you make the date tape,
the love tape,
or you just start screwing around with recording your voice,
you start creating tapes with other friends
that are doing the same thing.
Yeah, we were gags,
but it was expression.
It was the way we expressed ourselves.
It was the only way we could not be judged
by the people that didn't freaking understand us.
And then you leave it behind.
And you start with your life.
And you move on,
and you do the daily doldrum,
and you forget where your passion is.
And that's a tragedy.
So now I've been doing this for over a month now.
It's gonna be coming up actually on two months here.
And like a blink of an eye, two months.
I'm ready to quit.
I'm ready to quit my day job,
and do this,
or do something like it,
or just follow this thing,
to wherever it takes me.
It's a little frightened,
because I sound crazy when I talk about it.
But, yeah, there it is.
It's out there.
I'm just, I'm ready to scrub toilets
for the opportunity to do this.
All right, so.
Adam could teasing me.
I'm ready to do it, man.
Whatever it is.
For the complete unidentified version of that commentary,
check out my website,
triplew.xenshow.net.
Adam,
we're all waiting with Bated Breath.
We're hyped up.
We're ready to take this audition.
Tell us what to do, man.
Take care.
I'm mad.
I want to quit my day job.
Hi, Adam.
This is Rich Palmer,
from the Miami Valley Music cast.
I just wanted to let you know.
I'm mad as hell.
I want to quit my day job.
And the good is,
just keep doing what you're doing.
Nothing else is required.
Another pot show pot cast.
Stick it in your ear.
I want to quit my day job.