Daly source code for February 21st 2005 transmitters, we don't need no stinkin' transmitters!
The podcast is a generation of rockers!
Autistic, it's Adam Curry!
Alright, that kind of sucked, doesn't matter.
Hey everybody!
Alright, I admit it.
I'm someone who needed it.
It's all on the fingers.
I just got back from the Dawn and Drew Shindig.
Everybody get your daily source code.
It is technically Monday.
It's February 21st 2005.
Work with a daily source code coming to you from San Francisco.
Actually it's Sunday night, so technically we'd have to say it.
It would have to say it's 20th, but when I get this up on line, it'll be the 21st in certainly in East Coast and all of Europe.
So, only us here on the West Coast are lagging a little bit behind.
Hey everybody, it's good to talk to you.
It's been a couple days and left in New York, obviously, and have located to San Francisco.
We're kind of downtown, and it's beautiful here.
Except for the weather, but it's nice and yellow, you know.
So, this evening, at 7 o'clock, when it started, was the Dawn and Drew extravaganza, the Shindig, the Hoda.
Oh my god, I'm trying to...
Let me just make sure I've got my wires all crackling and messing it all up there.
Wow, I mean, what a great fan base, what a community Dawn and Drew man, this was awesome.
Let's see, PsychoFam Jeff was there, PsychoFam number two.
Oh man, parts of the Pod Squad, Steve Bielmore, Michael Butler, Michael Gohagan.
We see Dawn and Drew obviously.
Oh man, the folks from young who were on the cover of the New York Times with their cooking podcast.
Our friend from Apple, who has been...
I'm not going to mention his name, because, you know, I don't want to jinx it.
It's been so good helping us with the recent dot Mac problems.
Oh man, some people who were interested in doing a podcast about...
It's an introduced foreign film to US audiences.
It was just, you know, wow, a lot of really interesting people all in one spot.
It was without a doubt, invigorating.
So I'm back at the hotel now.
In my hotel room, and we haven't spoken to each other for a couple of days,
didn't really get a Friday source code in there, because let me think,
I mean, geez, we have so much to talk about.
Let's see, the Bitties.
Let me see, go back that far.
Hooked up with the Bitties on Saturday.
And they came over to the hotel in New York.
Had a great time. Oh, took a great picture, which Lian sent to me.
So I'll get that up online as soon as I can.
And we hung out, we talked about the Bittie cast,
and they told me all about their plans.
And, you know, these girls, they've got it together.
So cool. I'm so happy for the success of getting the show at Joe's Pub.
And just, you know, having a final day in New York with them was really nice to kind of wrap things up.
Particularly since I had a, it was like the end of the day, right?
Or the afternoon.
And so I had one, and I'm not really a drink at all.
As you know, I mean to other things.
And what I have, I had a, a vodka martini, pop my goodness.
Whew. Also on Saturday, I hooked up with Cindy,
squipper from the Ken and Squip show.
Of course, I used to work together at my company in New York.
And it was great to see her and, you know, reminisce about some, some good times.
Yes, some good times.
And talk a little bit about her, a podcast that she's doing with Ken.
And it's, it's really, it's been, often on.
We just been talking to people, of course, the New York Times article.
You probably heard about this on the front page of New York Times,
a big podcast story.
My phone started ringing at like quarter seven in the morning.
Because we've been talking to all these people in New York about podcasting.
And there it was, you know, boom, front page of the Times.
Wide magazine came out with their special about the future of radio.
Really nice.
So I guess there's three avenues that, that they're looking at, which is a satellite radio.
Then there's some digital audio broadcasts to a terrestrial, digital broadcasting.
And podcasting.
And it was just like, wow, you know, they're totally predicting this as,
What's going to ruin radio?
Or perhaps I would, you know, say, what's going to reinvent it and reinvigorate it.
Because boy, there's still a lot of creative people in radio.
Maybe just we've kind of, kind of lost track of how many cool things you can really do with it.
And most of that is purely because of, you know, commercialism.
It's when you're dealing with a finite resource at just time.
That's when you got to cut stuff down.
And I've been talking a couple of people who were talking about Howard Stern.
And, you know, I read about, oh, and now once he's on serious,
you know, then he can say anything he wants.
But, you know, that's not what it's about.
Howard Stern has never been about, you know, how wrong she can get.
But about honesty.
And it's a fact.
Most guys, you know, if they're straight, they get off on,
Lipstick lesbians.
And if you're honest, then you'll say, yeah, that's true.
And all guys will.
And that's all Howard Stern has done.
He's always, he's just been honest.
I think he's been honest most of the time.
And that's what podcasting is about.
It's the honesty and there's no fake voices.
And, you know, as we know, that life is just indecent.
That's why life never gets into the mainstream media.
Because it's fucking indecent.
We talk indecent.
We act indecent.
At least according to the broadcast standards,
none of its decent.
That's why it's fake.
That's why they have to, you know, be so careful and it's just boring.
It's, you know, and life is also funny.
Life is just funny.
Like tonight.
Great.
Great time with everybody at the Don Andrew Shindig.
There's people, I think I'm really bad at names.
He came in from Tampa, Florida.
I was flying back at 7 o'clock this morning.
Oh, well, it was there.
It was, I know him for getting all kinds of people who,
Sam Levin run around like a maniac as usual.
It's just great.
Great community.
Great to everyone come out.
A lot of fun.
All right.
Let's get some cranking here in the podcast.
I've told you about Sid, my Pimp Daddy,
who has been known to send me a pretty cool mashup.
He sent me this one a couple of days ago.
I didn't kind of like it for a month.
I get in the mood.
Apple Levin versus McSleazy.
Yeah.
Come on, baby.
Buddy, come out.
Do you know?
use the set since I last refreshed the batteries. I really pissed of myself because I thought
I'd bought my eye a river because I was totally planning on doing some sound seeing here
there and you know, I thought maybe San Francisco would be nice and costed so many different
opportunities I've had but I can't find it either. Either I've lost it or I just didn't
bring it with me. I want to go on with the window now. There's no much going on here. Earlier
there were some sirens and stuff going off could have been a little bit of some street noise.
Hotel room was really nice. Psycho fan Jeff hooked us up with hotel rooms that friends and
family price and he had a you know like a little welcoming envelope for everyone who's come out to
see Don Drew. It's just has been it's like we've come to Mecca baby. It's beautiful. I'm sorry.
Let me just get it. Water here. Did they uh I thought they had brought new coffee pods. What does
you know they have coffee stuff in your room but they give me like two regular, where's my
fucking sense? Two regular fresh brew coffee and then one decaffeinated so I had run up and
so we drank that while we drank the regular. There's still tea. I could have that. I've got a water now
so I'll be good. So um flight this morning. I want to talk about that for a second man. It's
you know I haven't been in New York since before 9-11. Been in the States obviously but not in New York
and so this morning Sunday flight granted it's you know a very busy day considering you know it's
Sunday and it's the holiday weekend and then everything. But I hadn't flown from JFK or any
really New York airport in a long time and let me just talk about this Homeland Security business.
Now I know a lot about aviation. I'm a pilot so I'm going to have to say that um you know
I know what's going on in the air and I know what's safe and not safe and you know what you can protect
from what you can't protect but I was really just blown away by the amount of bullshit the
citizens of the United States of America are putting up with to fly. You know it's a fucking show.
I mean you kind of carry your bags to the scanner and then the scanner to the bomb detector
and then you go through one checkpoint and another checkpoint and then you take off all your fucking
clothes and you know and and I know as Americans we're like yeah but you know we got to do this
for safety and against terrorism but if it were really helping any in protecting us I'd be all
for it but it's crap it's you know this is the people I see running the scans and you know
now they're government officials right they're Homeland Security and you know that's great
and I'll do in their job and it's all patriotic and all that shit but come on it's not it's not
protecting us it's really not it's not making your flight any safer just you know think about it
logically okay so maybe you can't have the exploding shoes you know she's it's not hard to get on
to a tarmac anywhere any airport and do whatever you want to do you know the whole point
about the the the the nine eleven terrorist attacks is that no one expected them to do it this way
so you know you can go on protecting this crazy it's crazy it's really slowing everybody down
the economy would grow and speed up if we got rid of some of that shit or why don't we just
make a big red gate at the at the the door of every single airport and you walk through it
and you hear all these lasers and scans and retinal things going and lights flashing and
robotic voices talking will all be really fucking convinced that we're safe and you've been sniffed
and did nothing can explode or dangerous or pointy or whatever and we look inside your DNA and
your brain and just tell people that they're safe but hurry the process up okay gosh and in
New York itself I mean I hadn't been in New York so I used to go to all these buildings and you know
meetings and I've been to these places before and now in New York you have to go through
it's like the terrorism is broad and a tremendous industry there must be hundreds of millions
of dollars worth of scanning equipment and wet logic tech Jesus Christ everywhere I see these
fucking logic tech webcams there and you know when you come into the country at customs you
have to look into the webcam and it's all logic tech which is kind of interesting and it's
tremendous money was made on this terrorism business let me tell you any same thing at the
buildings you're not secure this can you're bag but you know you can you can always
go detonate yourself it's just well anyway end of rant Jesus Christ I can't believe it and
apparently it's not that bad at every airport in the States but I could believe it and it was
a flight from New York to San Francisco just it's crazy crazy I tell you magic has been traveling
Madge Weinstein have been following everyone's favorite lesbian on a trip down to to Gussies Place
in Miami and by the way also I'll be sure to check out Feast of Fools which is Madge's friend
Faustos podcast very interesting very funny very very funny Patricia's gonna love it
when I get back home I'm gonna totally turn around to all these pie now she's she's
listening to Madge before but I think she'll like Feast of Fools as well but you know Madge was
basically reading all these big billboards and these big signs driving down I guess it's
not A1A is it maybe it is A1A or the Ronald Reagan highway I think is what it was
and she ran across a sign which well it was a clear channel sign and let's listen together
to what Madge said because I heard this I think late Friday night or Saturday night maybe
yes on the Friday night in my hotel room and I was just laughing out loud when I heard this
and on this has to be the post disgusting thing I've seen even in Florida a billboard that says
God give me a sign and it has the clear channel of icon right below it or the clear channel logo
on the clear channel name on the sign not just the advertiser of the sign it's also the advertiser
on the bottom of the sign is the sign owner but it specifically says God give me a sign clear channel
so that is the most fucked up thing I've ever seen what the fuck does that supposed to mean
that up God is what's making a clear channel on half the planet as far as radio is concerned
well listen to this fucking sign this is Madge Weinstein on the god damn podcast
okay I'm your fucking sign you in his holes I'm your sign take this
lovely Madge Weinstein use radio on useradio.com totally trippy love that very much
got an email from a blast from the past was in New York you know again I'm looking at my
my Gmail on red count 500 exactly on red so it's hard I'm trying to pick stuff out and
archive stuff that I want to get back to later and you know this what happens when you're on the road
email from David Weiss a blast from the past you may know him better as David was of was not
was and he said that he was reading about podcasts and he was thinking of getting into it and doing
something so we'll be talking to him in the next couple of days so that was not thought that was pretty cool
moved servers just in time for the big the big onslaught from the New York times
learn some really interesting stuff though you know this is all paid is hosted on frontier with Manila
and it was hosted on the on a windows machine and I moved it over to an excerve which is
Macintosh OS X put their server version and you'd expect there wouldn't be any difference and that is
normally that would be correct but have discovered something very interesting in frontier
although it's a great you know cross platform
well it's more than just an application right it's an outliner it's a it's a web server it has a built in
scripting language it's an object database I mean I love this I love frontier there's a San Francisco
Siren's for in the background anyway it doesn't do very well with different character encoding sets
I don't know a lot about this other than that there are different character sets for different
countries and keyboards and you know basically if it's not unicode then what the fuck I don't
understand but I know that it's incompatible and the opml directory which has all these different
nodes linked from you know well at least 40 well more than 40% of the directory is now maintained by
other people totally decentralized which I love a lot of those opml feeds were made with
you know notepad or you know other other programs and so there's all kinds of weird characters
and some of the nodes which unwindos wasn't a problem apparently but on OS X is a problem so
Marcus Muller who's been working with me for a long time was trying to figure out how he
can sanitize some of the problems we're seeing now isn't as an intermediate fix and then I guess maybe
we're all going to have to you know use radio user land or something like that or you know
at least something standardized so that we all can kind of get the same opml
at least habit compatible and actually then I was you know talking to Marcus and thinking about it we
should really work on expanding the directory work on let me see you know making it this people
who own the nodes in the directory there's so much more we can do with that and so I really had some
thoughts about that anyway so know that if if it's see you know if you're using it in perhaps
in the iPodder or if you're using it in Doppler radio or if you're using it in an
in a pandemic by the way I wanted to say that I had checked that out and I talked about the opml browser
and immediately Ed got all over some of the some of the things with the links it turns out I didn't
see the the links in the opml directory they were down below in the browser and so he's he's
also took that a little bit to make it a little bit more obvious and it is a great iPodder client I
got to say it's sweet it's short it's you know it's minimal but it has all the bits in there and all the
advantages of you know some some smart management of your files it's definitely check that out
and I am I Q so anyway working on it working on making that better so bear with me there is
also there's a if you want a static version of the file semi email if you're using it in
an application or if you're using it in a directory or if you're having some troubles with the
feed as it is now just shoot me an email and put it in the subject opml directory and then I'll
send you a link where you can get a fresh static copy of that file so we can keep everything rolling
all I do a little bit of experimentation okay so that's the iPodder directory what else oh yeah
I have to talk about dot Mac so I got a beautiful long email from from a friend who works at
at Apple this is a friend now I didn't know him previously and he had been following along the
rants of you know all of a sudden these problems that we were seeing with dot Mac I disk hosting
people like me putting their podcasts on the other I disk because for some reason the way their
web servers are set up they weren't returning the size of the file which is something that most
of the iPodder software is looking for because if the download breaks you have a reasonable download
and you can only know what to resume if you know what the total file length is so that wasn't
showing up anymore on not for any podcast any MP3 file that was hosted on a dot Mac server on
I disk and it does turn out that there was some you know some code that you know that they had
running some legacy stuff that kind of broke when there was an upgrade of something else and they're
aware of it and they're working really hard on it and they're actually they're quite proud of all the
all the podcasts that are being hosted on their infrastructure and they really came to at least these
guys you know in the in the dot Mac server center I guess sort of network operations center they
really want to help us podcasters so the word is probably another seven to 10 days for it to be
completely fixed and then we can go back to using our dot Mac for hosting which is good news
let me see we have here man it's so much to catch up on oh got a plug Clark's podcast
you know Clark he came to interview me for for NPR and also for BBC and there was a great BBC
technology feature on their website so the radio program is called the world and they have a podcast
now so you should check out the world dot org and the podcast specifically is the world dot org slash
rss slash tech dot xml and of course that URL in the show notes as usual hi Adam this is rena Marie
from bandtracks.net and the association of music podcasting we thought you might like to hear a little
taste of the pod safe music that's playing on the amp network right now yeah on the $250 million
radio show the pledge from story of blue from the accident hash podcast tale of the rain and the
moon from Jeff bird an insomnia radio taste of the good life from chance
from in over your head radio Eric rinso with gloss
on indie feeds alternative rock channel ikea from Jonathan Colton
not a bodega not a mall and this is thankful apartment smaller than mine as if there were
apartments smaller than mine ikea i love that song and from the bandtracks podcast at
bandtracks.net the muffs with really really happy thanks Adam be sure to check out all the
great independent music shows that make up the association of music podcasting at music podcasting
dot org where you can find all the links to great independent music you've probably never heard
oh man i love hearing a female voice on the podcast that's so nice i've missed it hey that's
pretty cool the association of music podcasters i've been following that i like it i dig the songs
too and i love that ikea too i think did i play that on the source code one's good song
and a great way to sample tunes so bring them on and that the length of that is great you know
thank you very much appreciate it Adam this is Michael from visit my Las Vegas podcast
you've been talking about Vegas a little bit on your show and so i decided to take up the
challenge of going out and creating a sound scene tour the neon museum in Las Vegas we have a lot
of neon in the city obviously and neon signs are one of those few things that are saved around
here before we upload something i just walked around and talked about the signs they described the
signs and so it was fairly easy although i did have some wind noise and forgot to take some photos
the night i went out oh i got all the neon signs those are lit up i just forgot to capture a few
storefronts i posted the mp3 and the photos at audio dot visit my lasvegas dot com you can
listen to the mp3 and your laptop and then follow through the photos and when Elvis says thank you
thank you very much you flip over to the next photo yeah i know it's cheesy but we are in Las Vegas
so really i made you a sound scene of the banana gift snacks this this huge super biggest
glit store it might be fun to walk through and talk about dice clocks and all the statues and fuzzy
dice anyway have a listen to the uh sound scene tour and let me know what you think thanks
excellent also added to the sound scene tours podcast sound scene tours dot com and i got to get
i got to get Patricia de Vegas man that was a bummer last time we went i was actually that was just a
little bit before uh i started podcasting i was actually already learning apple script at the time
i think that i'd written one or two uh XML like parsing things at a part of it uh and i did a
live radio broadcast actually uh mary i am a ordained minister mary uh was it six couples was it six
were seven couples live on the air for a Dutch radio is doing then and that was a lot of fun
and Vegas you know if you haven't been there in a couple years it's just amazing and uh but Patricia
couldn't go a doctor would litter at that point but uh i think she's she's ready and uh yeah
well i'm ready for vacation no matter what uh the three of us are you know we're scheming
christina's gonna figure out one or next vacation is from school and uh we're gonna we're gonna do
some fun we're ready it's been uh it's been a year since we went on vacation and you know with the
move and everything uh yeah we're ready and it's it's still you know we're still living in Europe
so it's not like we got all this yeah we got sunshine but not like real sunshine that's just
beating down and soaking in your skin you know let's see what do we add uh 28 minutes on the podcast
right now um and still only about oh shoot halfway through boy um let's see Michael Jackson
anything else to report on him i was kind of sad uh you know where he fell ill he got the flu
flew and he was puking in his limo and he drove to the hospital and i was watching Fox News at
the time and you know they got Michael Jackson's mom on the phone and it was it was i wish i had
a sound clip of that because she was like she was almost in tears you know just you could hear
her mom so frustrated about all this stuff that's happened and then of course i saw some of
the leaked testimony on uh smoking gun and i don't know i don't know it it's hard to say
and things people will do for money you know i i have some experience with that
i do people will do the craziest fucking things for money so anyway uh let's not forget that uh
innocent and top proven guilty and uh damn it's still a very talented guy
uh okay i'm like losing some energy here it's been crazy it's been a crazy week
it tomorrow got back to back meetings um then Tuesday it's the um the wired
rave awards in the afternoon when's day uh trying to hook up with some people then uh Thursday
i'm going up to uh Seattle and then uh they oh i got that which reminds me i should really
book a flight back i'm trying to figure out if i'm gonna fly from Seattle if i'm gonna fly from
San Francisco uh and then it'll be good to be back home finally after uh
after once i'm like 10 days big big big mega trip for me now let's take a podcast
yeah my mama always said the hit test was like a box of chocolates you never know what you're
gonna get time by the curry to take the hit test right to go with yon hold it
yo baby hi Adam hey yon how you doing buddy this is another edition of the hit test
i am ready and some changes have been made so um please let me know what you think at the end of this
um i listen to your suggestions and the intros are not as long as they use to be
oh shit it's gonna be hard very short and i think i'm gonna play them two times for you so
okay there's also other news the hit test has to get its own RSS feed now right on uh you can
find all information about uh the RSS feed on my new blog and you can find my blog at uh
yonfolet dot block spot dot com that's jan b-o-l-e-t dot block spot dot com and i hope
Adam i'm putting a drone out into your shield just wrote it in there uh well let's try
the new version of the hit test this is number one
and this is number two whoa whoa whoa whoa what happened to my two
my two uh two clues oh it's he dot block spot dot com and i hope Adam um you can
put this link into your show notes uh well let's try the new version of the hit test this is number one
somebody's like oh what's the number two then she's this is number two
shit oh stop stop stop stop stop stop
this is it uh is that uh canny logins this is it yeah i think it's canny logins and number three
oh uh uh um i think i think i think i was talking here and then this is very short
yeah it's one more time number one all right okay i'm going to go with Stevie Wonder Master Blaster
Dan and uh uh I know it's wrong but number two okay that's uh this is it
and number three
that's definitely talking head if you want to hit them again go back uh a little bit and uh
play again yeah rewind this is answer number one you know i had this one wrong I
know Stevie Wonder is oh okay this is Master Blaster yeah all right i had it right i thought it was
good and the second answering today's hit test it's Kenny Login yeah
this is it's got it nailed it
that makes you about three
and the third and final answer the talking heads with slippery people
okay so i didn't get the title that was harder i like that challenge it
i love you
answer number three in today's hit test we're talking heads and slippery people
well Adam that's it for today um please let me know what you think about the changes i've made
and again all information about the hit test can be found at
yonpo let's dot'sblockspot dot com okay see you next time for another edition of the hit test
by Adam thanks yon appreciate love the changes much more challenging totally cool they're going
it and you can even uh try some uh sixties and fifty shit i mean i'll be fun too because
although just what everybody likes listening to the hit test uh too much 80s uh makes it a little
narrow because uh i do get a lot of people saying hey you know i've uh 50 no let's say not a lot
people Steve Gilmore says you could do 56 these maybe even some 70s so uh you can you know
shaken up a bit but i really do like the shorter bits that's uh maybe you do the you know do the
bit and then do a two to two play each clip two times after each other with a little bit of
breaking between maybe that's even better so that i don't have to stop and yeah and i'll just let
it run through um and then either i guess it or i don't right so i get two chances to guess it
with the audience that's probably the best way to do it thanks again yonpo let and it's in the show
notes yonpo let dot blogspot dot com oh dot the present hey Adam this is Neville Hubson and Amsterdam
a nice place you might be familiar with and this is shell holes in San Francisco uh Neville and
I are both fans of the daily source code and you've inspired us to produce a twice weekly podcast
called for immediate release the Hubson and Holtz report for immediate release is in the ipodded.org
directory under business our focus is the public relations and organisational communication
business we cover goings on in the online world of communications we interview interesting people
we talk about the issues of the day we even play some pod safe music and any of your listeners who
might work in the communications business should visit for immediate release dot biz and subscribe
and who knows one day we may even have occasion to throw in a little
alright guys thank you very much time to throw in a bit of pod safe music myself here
this is um let me see where to get this from this is Harvey King from i guess the CD
best of money can buy or uh maybe just an online album it's the best of money can buy
gonna play it as the last bit for today source code to kick off your week for monday
of your eight twenty first
i'm talking about the best now talking about the best yeah talking about the best
That money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy.
Money is the rule of evil if the good book does not lie.
Yet the shepherds must increase the flock to get the best money can buy.
Hope on tiff of the kates and postulates says birth control must be denied.
See its conference pennies feel cathedrous, the best money can buy, or the best.
That money can buy, that money can buy, the best, the best, that money can buy.
The economy is the issue, don't get the best of money can buy.
Go get yourself some leadership, the best that money can buy.
The internet of the lobby is the best money can buy, and you've got yourselves a government.
The best that money can buy, who or best?
That money can buy, the best, the best that money can buy.
The magazine TV and movies glamorize the best money can buy, and the showroom folks are killed again.
The best that money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy, the best, the best, the best.
That money can buy.
I'm talking about the best now, talking about the best year, talking about the best that money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy.
Every time I got to working hard to get the best money can buy, yes, you must have the final thing.
The best that money can buy, so you trade it off your kids, the oceans, mountains and the skies, and you've got yourselves a slice of life.
The best that money can buy, that money can buy, the best, or best.
That money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy, that money can buy, that money will sing the blues, nobody wants to run, everybody wants to be hanged with you.
But nobody wants to die, just spend that money on a third world, honey, let the rest of the world go by, just along you know you can always get the best money can buy, or best.
That money can buy, the best, or best, that money can buy.
I'm talking about the best now, talking about the best year, talking about the best that money can buy.
Do, yeah, the best that money can buy on your daily source code, that is Harvey King, and that is going to do it for Monday the 21st, start of a new week, have a good one, everybody.
Thanks for subscribing, thanks for tuning in, and you're just finding this somewhere, you can find this show, the archives and the podcast feed at dailysourcecode.com.
I'm just with the little XML button there, copy that link and put that into your eye product.
Adam and Cory.com is my email address.
I'm pretty sure that my Gmail entry 3 feedback at Gmail.com account is filled up, so I'm going to, thanks by the way for all the suggestions on what to do.
It really has a sure fire fix. I guess it's just going to open up a new Gmail account to make it work.
My web blog is www.curry.com. The iPodtern.org directories where you can find all the fresh new podcasts and podcasts organized by directories, nodes, categories.
Hey, I'll see you tomorrow, everybody. Take care.
Thank you.