Daily source code Episode 190
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear since
radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
I think I'm signing you to the future.
Hi, this is Rachel from audiocollective.net.
You're listening to Adam Curry on the Daily Source code.
Hey everybody, it is Tuesday.
It is June 7, 2005.
Welcome to the source code.
How are you?
A beautiful Tuesday, I might not have the sun is shining.
It's just how man, it couldn't be more perfect.
The weather is beautiful, the trees are in full glory, flowers are in bloom.
I'm feeling pretty horny myself.
This is your Daily Source code at the start of 190.
A lot of cool stuff to talk about.
Lots of promos on today's show may even run a little bit long.
Might even be a 40 minute podcast.
So, as you can tell, probably immediately from the quality of the microphone.
I'm back on the regular mic.
I decided I just need a new windows machine in order to test the cast glass.
So, this is tablet or crap with as I call as just such a piece of shit.
Particularly because you'll hear later on, young polette used cast blaster to do the hit test
that ain't as sensitive to awesome.
So, until then, I'll just roll that out on the Mac.
Now, we start off a little bit rough this morning.
Christina had lost her glasses.
Turns out she had lost them for over a week, but had she really lost them.
We're had she lent them to someone.
It's another one of those fine parenting kid moments, you know, just better load that.
So, and I was going to go to the gym with Patricia.
The deal is now we go Tuesdays and Fridays.
However, we'd forgotten that the work crew was going to show up today to start fixing the windows.
If you've been listening to the source code for a couple of months, you'll know that the insulation
of the house is not exactly what it could be and gets really, really cold in the winter.
So, they're fixing up the windows, I guess they're doing double pain glass and stuff like that.
So, if you hear any banging in the background, no, I haven't moved temporarily to the
Bunger and Amsterdam, or the sex club, it's just the plainhold cottage.
Let's kick it off with a mashup, shall we?
You'll like this one. Black IP's versus the stellar project.
Send to us by Martin Peters.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's what you want me to use on you.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow,
wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow,
wow, wow, wow, wow, wow,
wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
Martin sent us such a wonderful collection of mashups.
If you've got something you want to play it on the source code,
press a promo, just send it to submit at podshow.com.
OK, so something really exciting happened yesterday.
In San Francisco, it was the 2005 Worldwide
Developers Conference for Apple.
And as its traditional Steve Jobs did a keynote,
it wasn't done live the keynote, but I guess
delayed for some reason.
And today it showed up on the Apple homepage.
And of course, I was already
learned to the fact that Steve Jobs did his now infamous
iTunes podcast demo, which he'd already
done from me in a private session.
And that sounds kind of scary, doesn't it?
Private session, means D.
And now I did it for the Wall Street Journal
DeConference, and I did it for all the developers.
And a lot of developers there, like two or 3000.
Let's just walk through this for a second, because it's
I just want to play some of the audio.
It was probably about just about this time last year, right?
Yeah, it was around June.
Dave Winner was at the Democratic National Convention,
I think, maybe a little bit before that.
He started to add MP3 recordings that he was doing
on the street and at the convention in different places
into his RSS feed.
And we've been doing this for quite a while together,
sending back audio, mainly video I have to say, as in closures.
And so I was receiving these automatically
through radio, user land.
And I was thinking, oh, man, I really
want this to go straight onto my iPod.
I'm so sick and tired of dragging it over.
At the time, I had an early commute for the morning show.
And that was kind of what planted the seed to build the first
iPod or client.
And look at where we've come in less than a year, really,
just about a year's time.
Look how far we've come.
It's unbelievable that as users of a technology,
users of a platform, users of, in my case,
a Mac user, of course, it's gone way beyond Mac and Tosh
at this point.
I wanted some functionality.
And thank God there was capability.
Thank God for, I never thought you'd hear me say this.
Thank God for Apple script.
Because that's why I built the first iPod or it.
But thank God the Apple for listening, for paying attention,
listening to what their customers really want.
And yeah, I may be a loudmouth customer,
but I'm still a customer.
And I've been a Mac user since I had the Mac 2 or the Apple 2.
Didn't really do much with it.
It was really the Mac Plus that the company started, obviously.
So let's just have a listen to a little bit.
Not linked to up here and there with a few comments.
No, iTunes goes with the iPod.
And we just recently crossed 430 million songs sold
and download it in iTunes.
We're thrilled with this.
And by the way, I think I've mentioned this before.
The entire percentage of downloaded paid for music online.
As a percentage of all music sales.
So it's 430 million songs sold through the iTunes Music Store.
That and the other music stores that are available
represents 2% of all music sales.
So let's just keep that in perspective,
but it's still an amazing amount of downloaded song.
And that is again reflected in iTunes Market Share.
We've gotten a lot of competition over the last nine months.
And what's happened?
Our market share is going up.
It's now 82% in the month of May.
Right on.
Now, we recently announced something new for iTunes and iPod.
And it's called podcasting.
As you know, the podcasting phenomenon is exploding right now.
And podcasting, of course, is a concatenation of iPod and broadcasting.
And what is podcasting?
It's been described a lot of different ways.
One way has been a TV for radio.
Yeah, I like TV for radio, although I hate what happened to TV.
Their business model didn't work out very well, but the functionality is definitely
TV for radio.
And by the way, explain TV to someone.
That's almost as hard as explaining podcasting if you're talking about subscribing to a
show.
But it is indeed, TV for radio.
If you have a TV, then you get it immediately.
Download radio shows and listen to them on your computer or put them on your iPod any
time you want.
So it's just like television programs on TV.
And that's true.
Another way it's been described is Wayne's world for radio.
He's been listening to too much Don and Drew, which means that anyone without much capital
investment can make a podcast, put it on a server and get a worldwide audience for their
radio show.
And that's true, too.
We see it as the hottest thing going in radio, hotter than anything else in radio.
I'd really like that description.
Boy, does that put all of us in a really cool category?
The hottest thing in radio, congratulations, y'all.
And as you know, what podcasting is is that you can not only download radio shows and listen
to them, you can subscribe to them.
So that every time there's a new episode, it automatically gets downloaded to your computer,
you can listen to it there or it automatically gets synced to your iPod the next time
you dock your iPod.
There you go.
Perfect explanation.
So it's very, very exciting.
And there are over 8,000 podcasts now.
Now that's interesting.
Pay attention to that because it's going to become very relevant when you start talking
about the directory.
8,000 podcasts.
I just looked today in iPod.org, we have 6,000 and I think 72 podcasts currently listed.
So Apple clearly has a few more or found a few more or has registered more or whatever,
but they're talking 8,000.
So that's good.
It's a bigger number than iPod.org is currently tracking.
So that is good news in my book.
This is growing really, really fast.
So that's pretty exciting.
I can't wait to see a pie chart.
Next time Steve does a keynote, we'll say in June of 2005, there were 8,000 podcasts.
And today, and then I'll show the pie chart and it'll be like 80,000.
Now, it's not just amateurs doing these things though.
These 8,000 are not all amateurs.
The pros.
Okay, that's where it comes up with the 8,000 number.
I got you.
I don't think we're tracking all of the, quote, pros in the iPod.org directory, probably
because they just haven't submitted it.
Have realized that this is huge.
And here's just a list of some of the companies doing podcasts now.
All the major radio broadcasters, the network broadcaster.
That's kind of cool.
The serious was up on the board.
Major news papers, even major companies like Disney and Proctor and Gamble and Ford and General
Motors.
Yeah, what's that?
So it's pretty exciting.
And so what we're doing is we're going to make this even easier because you're not
going to have to go download other applications and get all sorts of stuff together to
make this happen.
We're going to build it right in to iTunes and iPods.
Okay, so here's what I, if, and I'm a big fan of Steve Jobs and his keynote, I'm a
student of Steve Jobs and his keynote speeches.
I love the way he presents.
I am you late a lot of, a lot of his presentation style.
I just naturally have ever since you could follow these keynote on in quick time.
Man, when that started, it was 2001, I guess, 2002, when it really started to, you know,
when these keynotes were just the biggest thing, there would be watching and have them
up on on projectors and we'd have watching parties and it was fun, fun to watch the
really what like watching and present something at this point though, it would have been
nice to just made a brief mention to the hundreds of people who helped foster this,
who developed it, who, particularly the developers, man, the developers worked and this
was a developer's conference, so it might have been a very appropriate thing to mention.
There were so many independent developers who were creating iPodder functionality with existing
software such as iTunes, but also others Windows Media Player, of course, he's not going
to mention that.
So that just would have been really nice and not just the developers and the software
sense, but also the developers who've been developing podcasting, have been working tirelessly
together to come up with naming conventions for file names, how to use your ID three tags,
which are all messed up anyway and are intended for music and not for podcasting at all.
That just would have been a nice little note and would have been very appropriate.
Okay, we continue.
Can subscribe to any podcast and we're going to make it really easy and so right into iTunes.
Fantastic opportunity, by the way, to have also said, hey, this is our customers, our
customers love our stuff so much that they're stringing stuff together.
We hadn't even thought of that would have been cool.
Very simple, but one of the most important things is how do you find these podcasts?
Do you want people typing URLs into iTunes?
Well, they could do that.
There you go.
I know I've said it before, but now we can talk about it openly.
Of course, you'll be able to subscribe to any podcast you want as long as it has an RSS
2.0 feed, it'll work in iTunes.
But we're also going to build right into the iTunes Music Store, an iPodcast directory.
Right on.
So, you know that when I first started the iPodot org directory, it was built on OPML meant
to be open, so they're doing exactly the right thing.
They're taking the iPodot org directory, I'm sure they're going to be taking podcast.net
and podcast alley, and you name it all directories that are open and available through
OPML or other means that the data can be accessed.
They're going to be sucking that in continuously, by the way.
It's not going to be a one-time deal.
And they're going to bring it all in to make, I guess, the biggest directory they can,
which is exactly the way OPML directories are intended to be, no one owns the top level.
In fact, I want to have my own personal directory, a directory that only has categories
that I'm interested in, and I can track that myself, and hopefully Dave Winner's OPML
software will facilitate for that.
I think it will, hopefully we'll see more of that at NomeDex.
He's already hinting about it on scripting.com, so I guess something's coming pretty soon.
I got a register and get my hands on that.
So the directory is going to be pretty big, it's 8,000 as we've heard, and they're all
going to be in there.
So I think pretty much everyone who has a podcast will be listed.
If not, I guarantee you, there is a way, and there will be ways for you to get listed.
D-listing, on the other hand, will kind of happen, I think, in the way that makes sense
to Apple.
I presume that the way it's going to happen, of course, if I told you what's really going
to happen, I have to shoot all of you, is that people can complain about a podcast or send
a note, and then it might be reviewed and could be removed from the Apple directory.
Out of course, as they're prerogative, what I hope and what I am pushing for is that
at the back end of the Apple directory, they will output a file that can be used by other
directories to suck into that directory as well, to essentially become a node in a global
directory structure.
Not quite sure if that's going to work, but I am pushing for it.
So we're going to list thousands of podcasts, and you'll be able to click on them, download
them for free, and subscribe to them right in iTunes.
So I'd just like to give you a quick peek of what this is going to look like.
All right.
So this is the point where I pull my pants down.
Let me bring up iTunes here, and I'm going to go to the podcast homepage, and this
is the podcast directory, and we're going to list again, thousands of podcasts.
Let's just go ahead and listen to one.
We can go to one here.
This is Adam Curry.
He's one of the inventors of podcasting, and you could listen to his episode 107.
Hold on.
I have to touch myself.
So you could listen to an episode here, but it's much more interesting to subscribe
to the podcast.
And we've now subscribed to Adam Curry's podcast.
It's flipped us up to this podcast thing, right in the source list.
It's downloaded the most recent one if I want to download another one.
I can just push a button and go download one of the older episodes, and I can listen
to an episode.
The source code episode 187, something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who managed what you can hear since radio
was invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
All right, he's laughing because he's thinking, you've got $16 million worth of aircraft
strapped to your ass.
I got $43 million worth of aircraft strapped to my ass.
Oh, let me give you another one.
Adam's great.
Oh, I got touched by self again.
Yeah, that was very cool.
This is, this is case.
And notice by the way that what Steve calls the amateur podcast, get all the big laugh.
And then he goes into demoing some of the pro stuff.
Our W, this is a show called The Treatment There, a public radio station in LA, so let me
go ahead and subscribe to The Treatment.
And again, here's another one I can close this one if I want to.
And let's go listen to the treatment.
This podcast of The Treatment is a production of KCRW Santa Monica at 89.9 FM and web
casting at KCRW.com.
From KCRW in Santa Monica, this is The Treatment.
So you can hear a pin drop that's like crickets go on now because it's boring.
Hello.
Welcome to boring.
But you get the idea.
Really cool, summer amateur and summer pro of interesting, very interesting.
What's amateur on what's pro and does it really matter anymore?
More I want to just highlight and but I think what basically what I just, the message
I just got subliminally, it's subliminally, subliminally is amateur, fun, cool, like it,
pro.
We're going to do one ourselves because we have new music Tuesdays when we put new music
on the iTunes music store.
So we decided to do a podcast.
This is just a test.
Mm-hmm.
But you can, is it pro or amateur?
Subscribe to that and, you know, get to, so what's really cool about what you showed
here is something that I saw as well.
I guess I can talk about now.
Art work changes too.
Basically, yeah, with this new set up that I, that iTunes will be using.
Go to different chapters of this thing.
You'll be able to synchronize the track of artwork and the artwork is hot, clickable.
It's linkable to any kind of URL to another podcast, oh man, how fucking cool is that
going to be?
If I roll out a promo for a podcast, you'll see the artwork for that promo and you can
click on a link and that link will either, I guess I could do multiple links, excuse me,
I get so excited since I was acting up.
Cool links, one could be to listen to that podcast or one could be to automatically subscribe
you to that podcast.
I think about what this is going to do for sound-seeing tours.
God, this is going to be so cool.
I think you can actually, the artwork could also be a quick time movie.
Imagine the shit we can do.
I haven't seen the whole SDK, the software developers kit yet, but I will.
But I think there's going to be a lot of really cool stuff possible with this new combination
of iTunes.
Sorry, it's rolling through the chapters, very, very simple.
And we think it's going to basically take podcasting mainstream or anyone can do it and
really easy to find these podcasts, really easy to listen to.
Right, so that has been the entire mission that I've been on for a year, taking it mainstream.
Now that may seem like a nasty word, taking it mainstream, because we speak of mainstream
media, but I think really this is going to open up a universe of people who will be able
to listen to our shows, who will be able to enjoy it, who will be able to laugh at the
amateurs and fall asleep during the pro stuff.
It's going to be fantastic.
Sorry about this.
I think it's going to be one more way to sell iPods, and there you go.
Digital music community are really at the forefront of this stuff, bringing the innovation
into the marketplace.
Okay, no, that was kind of the thank you.
That was nice.
The innovation into the marketplace, and I personally want to thank all of the developers
once again, everybody who's been working so incredibly hard to get to this point.
And there's so much more we can do.
In fact, I'm looking out west, looking way, way, way out west up to the northwest.
I'm, wait a minute, can we do some, uh, one of you can, uh, hello, hello, redmond,
redmondy, read me, redmond, come in redmond, redmond, we are waiting for your podcast
functionality.
Where are you?
Hey Adam, and all the daily source code listeners, this is Tracy from the vegan cooking
school podcast, where we introduce listeners to a vegan lifestyle and had a prepared vegan
dishes.
You don't have to be a vegan to listen to this so though, but you do have to love delicious
new trishes meals.
So listen to us, download us at vegancookingschool.com.
Thanks Adam, bye.
The motitudes went forth and cast their pods in the direction of all who would listen
and casting their pods in this manner, they were henceforth known as podcasters.
This is Chad, and this is Erica, and we're getting married, and it hasn't been
easy.
Airlines strikes, hotel plumbing problems, we've changed the date twice, and all of
us in the span of 21 days.
Join us for our countdown to chaos, as we plan the happiest day of our life.
And we live to talk about it.
Here we have had to face so far.
Hey, stick around, something else could possibly go wrong.
Yeah, dot org slash wedding cast, that's www.weaca.org slash wedding cast.
And crap, I think four boards have been pulled up to the front of the house.
Oh man, you know I'm going to subscribe to that, when that's going to be great to follow
Chad and Erica on their on the way to wedded bliss, that'll be cool, it's the wedding
cast.
Of course, all of the URLs, the places to subscribe to these podcasts can all be found
in the show notes for today's podcast.
We still have some great pod safe music tune on the way, a little bit too much reverb
down, and just tone that down.
We've got, oh, a hit test, young pull, that's been added again, and shoot, man, I got
so many promos didn't play any yesterday, got to catch up.
Hello, ham, which a towel wrought the first five minutes with which a towel, and I'm here
to tell you about the podcast, 4-1-1 podcast.
Now, Rob, he interviews other podcasters to find out what they've learned about doing a
podcast, and it's been described as, he inside the actor's studio.
He's having this for podcasts.
His past guests include Alan Curry, he's the pod father, Senator John Edwards, C.C.
Chapman, P.K. and J, B.B.B. and he asked Chris Rockwell, and yours truly, which is
the towel wrought the first.
That's just naming a few of them.
Now, if you want to learn more about podcasters and your podcasters, then you go
on vism at podcast4-1-1.com.
And remember, listen different with podcasters 4-1-1.
Thank you.
He's just so precious.
podcasting.
He's Adam Curry.
Hey, Adam, it's Mike from Weird News of the World podcast.
We're available at Weird News of the World.
We've got Vlogspot.com.
Each week, my buddy, Jim and my other buddy, Jim and I.
We need and discuss some of your weird news stories from around the world.
We also have some pod save music.
And, you know, we try and put in a little bit of trivia in there.
So, please come out and check out our website again.
It's, you know, weird news of the world.
Vlogspot.com.
And, hey, Adam, we're interested in testing cast blasters.
So, let us know when it's ready, okay?
Thanks.
Right on Jim, Mike.
Most definitely cast blaster is on its way to a public data release.
I've had, well, as you know, I've had my, my minor issues with the, with the craplet,
getting that to work perfectly.
Of course, I had the cheapest piece of shit out there.
But it looks like we're very, very close.
We're going to get the website up and rolling.
We're working on the, well, I call it the front-to-back process,
which means you record and you hit save and all the rest is taken care of.
Your RSS feed, your show blog, everything is all done.
Your file is placed on an FTP server.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
So, stay tuned for that.
That's coming up either the end of this week or the beginning of next week.
We'll have everything ready to roll for the, for the big public data.
By the way, all the promos you hear on today's source code have also been played.
And we'll be replayed on the pod show on serious satellite.
And thanks to PW Fenton for, for all the tireless hours he's putting in,
sifting through all of the promos, making sure they're cleaned up, making sure they're,
they're ready to be put into, into the pod show.
And of course, you know, he's basically helping me out now with the source code.
Because, yeah, I just, I'm exposed all this stuff.
And I've got someone helping me on finding the promos.
I really appreciate it.
And I put out a call, I said, please, let's have shorter pod cast some longer promos.
Particularly for the pod show, that's great.
Because it gives people the opportunity to, you know, listen,
make a decision about, hey, that sounds kind of interesting.
And then rolling off and basically subscribing or auditioning to it on the website
and then subscribing to it, or, you know, however else you want to get them.
Soon that'll be made easy, of course, in iTunes.
And the longer promos, you know, so shorter pod casting, that's just necessary.
We already have 8,000 according to Apple.
And I think we will have 80,000 by this time next year.
So you have to find ways to, to get your audience.
No matter who it is, you have to, you know, if you, even if you're just doing a wedding
cast, you can have to find that wedding audience.
So promos are a great way to do it.
I love the example of which a Todd doing the promo for pod cast four on one.
So this, like, two promos on one.
You guys are really getting good.
I don't think we can call you amateurs anymore.
Since the creepy sleepy show began pod casting, public opinion has been bitterly divided.
So we decided to take it to the people to find out their reactions.
Rolling off the blunt.
Yeah.
Sir, what are your opinions on the creepy sleepy show pod cast?
I just, in a nutshell, think it's a bad idea to promote something that I think is not good for society and the public.
Sir, the market research on the creepy sleepy show has to this point Ben.
In conclusive, what are your opinions?
Well, I think the medical center of research has been done to show that it is less offensive than alcohol.
Whereas alcohol is legalized.
No.
Market research, not medical research.
Ma'am, do you think the creepy sleepy show is actually bad for people?
It's not as dangerous as stuff like cigarettes and stuff like that.
You get high off of the creepy sleepy show.
Are you sure you're not talking about something else?
Yes, I may have smoke weed.
Like, ma'am, some people have equated downloading internet content and podcasts like the creepy sleepy show to piracy.
I think that's the issue.
I think the issue is a lot of people use it a lot of people find it enjoyable and they've been forced into being criminals and it's ridiculous.
Ma'am, I'm not sure.
Are you talking about the legalistic implications of downloading internet content like the creepy sleepy show or pod?
Oh, yes, I smoke marijuana.
Maybe two or three times a week.
What?
We're talking about pod casting, not marijuana.
Ma'am, how do you feel about the social implications of the creepy sleepy show pod cast being able to reach a worldwide audience?
I think it's a bad issue when someone's on the ticket.
The little one says, you know, coming up.
But in other words, as a one for dad, they're not that think it's okay.
Have you tried to download the creepy sleepy show pod cast?
Do you think it's habit forming?
That's right.
But I'm not saying that made it so bad.
Try it.
Wait.
Are you talking about weed too?
Sir, you've indicated that you really enjoy the creepy sleepy show.
Can you tell us what the creepy sleepy show has done for you?
I'm smoking grass now.
I guess we're about five years or so.
Really?
I think it's helping me more than anything.
I really become creative when I get high.
Sir, we're talking about the creepy sleepy show.
Not marijuana.
Do you have any comments about our show?
So I'm in a music a lot.
So I can really get into a more run and firm stone.
And I really don't think that it's hurt me.
In a way, at least nine physical symptoms.
I can't find it hard to breathe or anything.
I don't think it's hurt my memory.
Do I have to tell you I'm subscribed to this podcast?
Well, yeah, I'd say yeah.
I'll leave you either.
The creepy sleepy show.
Pod cast for potheads.
No, I mean, it's not weed.
We're broadcasting all's live.
Adam Curry.
Why are we even filming this?
Playback.
And action.
Our airways are under attack.
Who will save us from the lane DJs and crappy music of conventional radio?
I'll save your body.
It's part-tastic to the rescue.
Cut.
I'm sorry.
Can we cut Sean?
Could you come here?
What?
Sean the line is I'll save you.
Not I'll save you.
I said, shave, you're filthy bastard.
Well, is there any way we could just get you to do it one more time?
Yeah, with what money?
You only paid me for 60 seconds.
Yeah, I know that's kind of all we could afford.
But I was just hoping maybe one more time is like a favor to us.
I'll do you the favor of not ripping your new actual.
How about that?
Just get me my job.
Okay, so that didn't quite work out as planned,
but please listen to our podcast.
Anyway, it's called Pop 4 and we'll be talking about TV music movies.
Everything in the pop culture as well as cooking, technology,
all kinds of random ship that we come up with.
And we think we're going to have a good time.
Listen to it.
We hope to have me even better time making it.
You can visit us at www.pop4.net.
P-O-K-W-H-O-R-E.net for the podcast feed, the blog,
and info about what we're going to be doing.
Hope to see you soon.
Right on.
Back to you, Adam.
Thank you very much.
Okay, Pop 4.net.
Oh, man, I love this stuff.
Oh, man.
I think the amateurs have it.
Amateurs for pros, niddles.
Patricia just walked in and she came back from the gym.
And guess what?
We're now signed up as a couple.
Well, after I post the show and the show notes,
I'm off to the gym.
Okay, Pod Safe Music Time.
Let me see.
Are you going to love this one?
By the way, this is the point in the show where I would say
if you're offended by strong mature language,
I really want to tune out.
But then again, why the heck are you listening to this podcast
in the first place, huh?
Amateur Transplants.
Just talk about the Northern Birds.
Spot Safe.
Is that okay?
And my name is Stephen Business.
Where amateurs plans?
This is a public service announcement for women.
If you go to Baltimore,
if you go to Manchester or Crue,
you cause a risk or a bribe,
your cost comes for Bradford Barnsley too.
Or Grimsley,
Listen up to what we have to say.
Northern Birds are lazy ugly horses,
smell of burgers.
So don't have too much to drink,
or you might fuck one,
and end up getting aches.
There's nothing fun
to be found of the M1.
Northern Birds are lower claws,
slacks who take it up the hours.
There in the sack,
after one side there and black.
But they're fucking awful rise,
and you'll take won't such the sights.
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da,
more than men's da-da-da-da-da.
If you really have to go up north,
then follow our advice,
fight away the women.
Or you'll find yourself with cubicle eyes,
and her knees,
you're much better staying in the south,
Northern Birds are desperately hippos,
dressed in burberry,
with a peanut for a brain,
and an accent that makes you want to die.
Now you've been warned,
there won't physically deform,
Northern Birds are all obese,
and they're riddled with disease,
try to escape.
Northern sex is worse and worse.
Stay down south,
and mark my worst,
still well clear of Northern Birds.
And this concludes our social studies as a class for today.
Regarding UK socio-economics.
Oh man, that's horrible.
Now before you go start writing the emails,
of course, it's only partially pod safe.
As long as you're paying ASCAP and BMI fees,
which you can legally do now,
this is very much the way cover will cover,
cover,
the very much the way cover will work,
it's Brian Abbott from Colorado.
As long as you have the permission
of the owner of the master of that song,
in this case,
I have the permission to play the song.
You can play any hit record,
basically, as long as it's a cover,
as long as it's done by someone else,
it gives you the rights to play it.
You still have to pay for the rights
to the composer of the music and or the lyrics.
So that is another route around that you might want to be thinking about.
There's a karaoke cast somewhere, isn't that?
I saw that.
I think I'm subscribed to that.
Thank you very much, guys.
Amateur Transplants, Northern Birds.
Lovely.
Pod safe, but not Chelsea.
He's back.
Hey, Adam.
This is hit test number 41.
Recorded with a cast blaster, better 14.
All right.
Again, three intros and three answers.
Sounds great.
This is intro number one.
Oh yeah.
That song makes you happy.
That would be Rolling Stones between a rock and a hard path.
This is intro number two.
That's my music.
Okay.
I know this one too.
That's shines sweet freedom by Michael McDonald.
And the final one for today is number three.
I know I'm going to say, oh yeah, when I hear it.
I don't know that one.
And your time is up in this is answer number one.
The Rolling Stones.
This is between a rock and a hard place.
Yeah.
I'm going to go straight.
We're stuck between a rock and a hard place.
And a hard place.
The Rolling Stones answer number one in today's hit test.
And this is answer number two.
From the movie running scared.
This is Michael McDonald's and sweet freedom.
You are the magic.
Now what was number three, y'all.
Sweet freedom Michael McDonald's answer number two in today's hit test.
And this is the third and final answer.
It's a dance classic from Cheryl Lynn.
This is shake it up to us.
Yeah, I told you to go, oh yeah.
Hmm, remember that?
Where were your young friends?
I've been known to shake it up.
Cheryl Lynn, answer number three in today's hit test.
Well, that's it.
By the way, like you with the crapless, I have the same problems with the low volume output of my notes.
So I think I will be looking for a headphone amplifier.
There you go.
I've noticed there are USB versions, but also external versions with power adapters.
So I don't know which ones right.
So if there are people that have experienced with these kinds of amplifiers,
please let me know.
The address is hittest at gmail.com.
That's also the address for feedback about the hit test and hit test podcast.
And of course, all information can be found at yompolets.com.
That's J&BOLIT.com.
Well, then, that's it for hit test number 41.
See you next time.
Bye-bye.
All right, y'all.
Thank you very much.
Sound good, though.
It sounded much better than my crap.
Thank you young palette for the hit test right here on your daily source curve.
And that's it for today.
What'd we do?
Oh, man.
43 or 44 minutes.
Whoop.
Long one.
All righty.
Comments.
Email them to me at mcure.com.
Your audio feedback is more than welcome, of course.
As long as you don't mind me slicing and dicing and put it up into the source curve.
Here's what you do.
If you got mashups, potsafe, music or promos, you want to submit.
It's potsafe and potshow.com mashup at potshow.com.
And for everything else, submit at potshow.com.
If you want to find the podcast feed for this podcast, go to dailysourcecode.com.
You can find it right there as long as along with the archives and, of course,
the latest show and the show notes.
Other places to find show notes, just to make it easier for you,
www.curry.com.
I'm out of steam.
There's been a long show.
I got to get off to the gym.
Okay, lots of exciting stuff coming in the next couple of weeks.
Beyond the lookout for the grand premiere of the potsafe music network.
I know I've been talking about it.
CC Chapman's working on that.
We got Chris Rockwell working on that.
It's a lot of cool stuff coming down the pike.
Great place for not just people who have potsafe music.
They want to share, but are placed for potcasters to go and get potsafe music
and find out about it.
Find out what's being played, what's hot.
Yes.
It's just like those big guys, the pros.
But the amateur's still got it, I think.
Alrighty, I'll be back tomorrow for the Hum Day edition of the Daily Source Code.
Thank you very much for listening.
Stay subscribed.
And I'll see you later.
Bye-bye.
Thanks for watching.