Delta Sierra Charlie, 236
There are no secrets!
Holy information you don't yet have!
And I'm Korean!
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass!
Transmidders?
In the next generation radio content in my ears!
We don't need no thinking, can't we?
I like to think I'm flying into the future!
Fantastic!
It's a battle curry!
And coming to you from New York, it's the daily source code for September 6!
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
I am, uh, well, first of all apologies. The show is late.
Uh, that has a number of reasons.
Uh, I really had planned on doing it last night.
Uh, mainly because the upload here at the wonderful Essex house sucks so bad at swallows!
A little ode to Christine for that one.
Yeah, I've got like a perfect mega bit download speed, but for some reason, uh, well,
I guess most people only need to download really, uh, in hotel configurations.
So for some reason, the upload speed, I'm getting about, you know, like,
analog modem speeds.
I wanted to have it uploaded during the night. So it's, uh, that was yesterday.
It doesn't seem like the, uh, connectivity has gotten any better.
So I guess this will be the daily source code for Tuesday, and for Wednesday,
depending on what part of the globe you reside.
I could tell you, I'm so happy.
I brought the Yamaha Professional Audio Working Station AW-16G and it's performing
Just it's fantastic. It's really outstanding. I've done let's see one, two, three, four
days worth of serious satellite radio recordings. Did I'm all here in my room? I've got
the new microphone with me. Everything, you know, not Godhood is gone well and arrived
perfectly because it was just packed in the suitcase wrapped in a in a dog blanket, which
is great protection. I'll tell you about what's been going on today and what I've
been up to, but I have to say it's very, I find it very hard to get into a really upbeat
and happy mood with everything that's going on with the Gulf Coast and Hurricane Katrina.
And even Agro 1 is affected. Check out his mashup to race funds for Katrina relief.
Just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know.
And just don't know, just don't know, just don't know.
Just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't
just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just
don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don
just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't know, just don't...
I wanna be with you, believe in me
Can you run away on the sixth night?
I wanna be with you, I wanna be with you
I wanna be with you, believe in me
Can you run away on the sixth night?
I wanna be with you, I wanna be you
The only one that I brighter
I wanna survive right
Oh, I am
I wanna be with you, yeah
I wanna be with you
For my own sake, for my sake
Boil fire
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Well it's a bundley clear that Agro 1 is affected as well.
In the ID3 tags of this mashup to raise funds for Katrina Relief, it even says that and
also begs you to visit www.redcross.org.
Actually I'm glad that I have a little break here because I want to start up the file transfer
P-dub is in Tampa, Florida and he's waiting for some more pod show stuff to come his way
so he can complete the production of that and I'm really if you listen he can probably
hear my G4 hole and I'll put the mic next to it.
That is the unmistakable sound of the fan in high gear because it's doing a lot of work.
I just want to maybe I should tell you a little bit about this while I'm doing this
transfer the setup that I've got running here.
I'm very pleased with myself because exactly what I wanted.
I wanted to just be able to kind of unplug, like 8 or 10 plugs really and just throw this
thing in my suitcase and take along my power book which I do anyway.
This is actually a pretty long migration path because I had a pretty static setup at the
cottage and that means that I had an external drive with all my promos and mashups and
pod safe music which by the way is a mirror of everything that Tepito has in Tampa.
Until this point because we are in the process of hiring someone for this job he's taking
all the submissions categorizing them putting them into our database and then he's compiling
the shows.
I had a mirror of that on a relatively big external hard drive with an external power
supply.
The first thing that has a copied everything over to that fire light 100 gigabyte drive
that I got at the Apple Store which is no bigger than shit man.
It's smaller than my phone really and it packs 100 gigs and so first I made a copy of that
then I had to adjust our database so the database was aware of the new location of the
files so I did all of that hold on I'm just dropping this into the appropriate folder here.
Let me say with the upload speed is as a Julia okay so I have my FTP program open I use
transmit by the way on on the Mac I really like it so now it's just sitting here saying
idle it's not even putting it I connected to the server okay I drag the two folders over
and okay we'll see if that kicks in in a second.
Then on the hardware side I have everything running through an M box interface so I can also
hook up the workstation to control MIDI slider faders on my second machine at home.
So basically now what I've done is I've just using analog inputs and outputs for the
G4 using the speaker output and the line input and those are coming out of the mixer.
There's one other piece of gear that I use at home which you may be able to tell the
difference I can definitely tell the difference it's the stereo valve processor and I route
that you know route the signal through that back into the mixer before it goes into the
into the actual recording and so I've just patched those two with two little short those two
channels to each other with two short patch cables and then in the workstation itself I set up
a compressor limiter and I'm pretty happy with the outcome now at the hell so it looks
what let me just see what happened here okay did it disconnect is that what happened oh man
my Mac is freaking out you know when you deal with really big files okay here we go connecting
so that worked that worked okay it's definitely connecting now let me just drag one foot maybe
doesn't like me dragging two folders over okay creating a new folder oh there we go okay
what's the upload speed this'll kill you so far we've transferred 32 kilobytes
oh it's a whopping 2.2 oh it's gone up to six almost it's stupid 7.3 kilob is a kilobit
I wonder it's a capital b's it would be kilobytes hmm I don't know who the hell knows it's slow
it's I'm moving very fast at all okay so anyway so I got everything set up here in the hotel room
as I said I got a nice one of the dogs blankets I used that to to wrap up the the workstation
put my diddy bag is that what you call it by the way your your toiletry bag I call the diddy bag
and that kind of you know I was used as a spacer so this so the mixer board was was pretty much safe
very very very pleased with how things go I you know maybe it was just and by the way the
flight once again I you got a love you got a love uh virgin and you know I pay a regular full
price for flying I'm getting things for free but it's it's such a it's such a groovy service it really
is and this time around I got a letter from Sir Richard Branson stuck in in one of the
inflight magazines I guess they do that once every so full trips and he so of course everyone
up her class got the letter but it was it was you know high quality bomb paper and it said
Sir Richard Branson and so I hope you're enjoying your flight and you know just drop me an email
give it give out his email address and he said I will personally respond to it so I'm gonna send him
an email and tell him how much I love the service and and I'll think if there's any improvements
I'll send that along to him so got in last night wasn't very hungry of course time differences
have me a little bit messed up cut some serious shows actually prep the show for today and and
I was like you know then I just got all wobbly I saw like the David Letterman's monologue and I
knew that I got an email from from Cindy from the Kenan Squip show she said that she actually invited
me to dinner but I would I even got you to late to have the dinner she said that Aaron from
Parkney of Bitterman's circle was in town because Weezer was performing on Letterman and they're
gonna have a late dinner and so I didn't even I didn't get to have dinner didn't even get to see Weezer
so and in this morning I got it bright and early work time presentation I had a couple meetings today
the most important one was at four o'clock it's all advertising agencies and they're all over the
stuff and they're coming in and and the consistently what I've heard this is this is I'm really
loving this news what I've heard consistently from the advertising community in New York and we're
up and down Madison Avenue and of course you know we were there 11 years ago when we were
hawking this thing called what was it oh yeah the internet that's right so we've got a lot of
friendly faces this time around um the consistently they're saying um our advertisers the you know
the clients of these agencies our advertisers and I think that the agencies also mean themselves
to some degree to certain degree are saying they don't know how to they don't know where to find the
audience they don't know where men are young men and they don't know where moms are and they don't know
where dads are and they don't know how to reach him and I'm like wow have you heard the mommy cast
have you heard 101 uses for baby wipes have you you know heard any of these six seven eight nine
what is it I've lost count 10,000 podcasts that I have attracted millions of listeners I'm telling you
for those of you that are interested in reaching big audiences and um and maybe uh making a career
out of doing this I absolutely I'm even more convinced than I ever was it's gonna happen and and
advertisers are looking for new ways to do things that's another um consistent thing that I've
heard you know they they're tired of the 22nd commercials great we are ready to change the face of
advertising I'm personally very very ready hi everyone this is Paige and Gretchen from mommycast.com
our hearts go out to the victims of hurricane Katrina we're sure you've seen all of the pictures
of the devastation there are millions of people who've been left homeless many of them women
and children and families the hardships these people are suffering is unimaginable
Gretchen and I encourage you to lend a hand and do whatever you can to help the victims
you can make monetary donations to the american red cross or to salvation army you can find
direct links to these sites at mommycast.com even the smallest gesture will help if we all pull together
we can make it better Paige and I thank you from mommycast.com
hot Joe content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother
hi this is gotten from patterns themed songs podcast at ktsb.net to show that we as podcasts
are sympathized with the victims of hurricane Katrina I urge you to visit redcross.org or call
1-800 help now to donate money I also call upon other podcasters and podcasters from outside
the united states visit your national red cross website and make it donation don't just think
that America is a rich country and can help itself this is a disaster you cannot prepare for
and cannot recover from without help the victims need our help now thank you thank you very much
cotton nice fade cotton does the kind of theme song podcast which is not always that regular
but sometimes she has it hits it once a week every single week usually on sunday saturday
as a sunday's over the weekend I love putting that that podcast on you know sometimes last
about an hour and it's a great music and it's all in a certain theme and she is an English teacher
I believe in the Netherlands and you know I was listening and you know despite the the somber tone
of the message that she was sending she's got a real sexy voice so being here in the states of
course inundated with media about hurricane Katrina I love to turn on the TV and see what what I'm
not missing when it comes to the way the media well just a television general and you know so
then they're all on the same trip of this couple that the god married and one of the
one of the evacuees shelters then it's just you know it comes in waves of what they're
reporting on and really the cameras can pull back wide enough to show the devastation you know
and if anything and there's a lot of finger pointing and blaming and you know and what should we do
and you know why did this go so horribly wrong and and it hit me on the plane
that because this is the same thing with with terrorist attacks it's the same thing with
airplane disasters any kind of natural disasters tsunamis you know I really have to
blame television and our hypnosis or I had not extinct because what what what happens
is that you discover that you know you don't have a right a god given right in whatever
country you live to be completely safe you know people always particularly in the US you know let's
let's sue because I got fucked you know because someone did something wrong or something went wrong
or wasn't explained to me properly because we're used to it you know we're used to all the
problems of the world being solved in 23 minutes and another seven minutes of commercials and
if that doesn't fix it then either judge duty or Oprah will you know this is this is what
is the problem we're used to this happy you know life and look at any movie once the last time
you saw a movie that ended you know on a downer note actually I'll take that back I saw
dissent a fine fine English production about a group of women girlfriends who go cave
exploring and run into all kinds of horrible things and basically they all die and and no one
gets out but then there's still kind of like a slight a slight you know happy note at the ending
and it's a very frightening movie by the way I made in silverwood so silverwood studios in the
UK yeah all shot on location but otherwise every single movie ends perfectly you remember
with 9-11 you saw what was happening to for me it was like okay you know Bruce Willis can
come in any minute now and save us and and that really was an automatic reaction I was waiting for
the scene change so I think that's a that's a big part of our problem is that we've gotten
very complete is it complacent maybe the right word lazy you know we're like hey you know it's
going to be fixed because there's always some superhero or you know some John Wayne guide that's
going to come in and save the day and we'll be okay and we've come to expect it but we're expecting
it not from not necessarily from our our own experience but but from television so maybe we should
think about that's why it's you know when you maybe that's part of what's so compelling about
reality television is that's that whole new experience of real life you know it's you know we
used to get our thrills from rollercoasters now you can get you you can get your thrills from real life
because it's a lot going on and what you see on television is not real life almost none of it is
and well yeah and again the XNTV experiment none of its real whenever there's a technical moment
a zoom a pan oh no a pan I think no a pan is okay a zoom or a because you can't do that with your
eyes you can pan with your eyes but you can't zoom jump cuts any kind of editing means it's not real
means you're not I just saw a date line NBC date line and Harry Connick Jr was going through
the streetwear's dad lives and it was caught up into a little it was really it was a beautiful piece
and you know he pulls a guy off his porch and and make sure he gets the safety and and he's driving
people to shelters but it was cut into drama you know it really was and essentially making
Harry Connick you know are our hero and which is fine but it's please this is not real reality is
the real heroes will never be seen on television because there was no one there to capture it to
capture those moments so let that be part of the lesson I think at least it was a lesson to me
and something that I've discussed with Christina and Patricia quite a bit now you know it's like hey you
we expect to be safe for all kinds of reasons and then you know another plane comes
now we haven't really spoken about it but 140 people done but 140 plus people died
it was a jacarta you know what is it well is it pilot error is it you know mechanical you know
what shit happens you know not every single airplane it's gonna fly forever you know
man what time is it it's 10 p.m. I'll display some more problems hello this is Chris Rockwell from
the Daily Download I'm here to ask for your assistance on behalf of the victims of Hurricane Katrina
we have all seen the terrible destruction that Katrina has caused hundreds of thousands of people have
been forced into homelessness thousands are feared dead and even more are dying as every day passes
these victims are not getting the help they need to survive and they are reliant on us
to help get them through this terrible event please help provide relief to these people
make a donation to the American Red Cross you can donate by clicking the American Red Cross logo
on this page or by calling 1-800 help them out Chris thank you Chris Chris Rockwell from the Daily
Download from his studio which is his bathroom I love it the way everyone is I mean you know
I love playing promos on this show this is what my inbox consists of it's all promos to raise awareness
and call out for help and donations to help the Red Cross and I'm very happy that this you know we
we've had lots of you know almost call them back channel conversations about you know there
was some thoughts about doing some kind of podathon or a telethon and and I'm not a big fan
of you know even when was tsunami relief I'm not a big fan of of doing that I think that's a
little bit it's passe because when we only had few media outlets and a few TV channels that we
didn't have the internet and news traveled much slower awareness was it was much harder to get
information in a timely basis it took a long time before you really knew the severity of a situation
or not and and telethons are very we're very important and raising awareness for that but in recent
years as you know you can get all the information very quickly and simply and you're on your own
and you can you know really slice and dice and make your own decisions based upon multiple just
thousands millions of different pieces of input to me it's almost like hey look how much money we
raised you know look look look what we did and I'm very happy that the Red Cross you know of course
the other work at the right organization to help out and in these these types of disasters
you know so there's no telethons there's no no big artists superstar gatherings because
it's unnecessary you know we can we are raising lots of money this way and I think it's probably
much more effective oh and we're talking about heroes a couple of the heroes who really helped out
in in the beginning in this of this horrible disaster are the ham radio operators I've received a
couple of emails from some of them because you know communications really got wiped out and for
all the the great communications that we have I mean take this podcast for instance you know I'm
recording this in the hotel room in New York which by the way has a partial park view if you
press your nose up against the glass and and look to the right you can just about sea central park
and it's you know it's came maybe it came automatically to your iPod if you're using iPodor
or if you're using iTunes we've got emails instant message cell phones but when it gets wiped out man
it's wiped out and you got it was you actually have to go back and you have to use the old school
technology which is radio radio frequency ham radio and in any disaster the ham radio operators are
always there they're setting up phone links and phone bridges and communication lines and open lines
and slow scan television pictures and the commend all of you you've done you've done a fantastic
job keep it up and you know it's kind of you know you probably left to learn more scode
to become a ham radio operator you got to know a lot of technology it's not you know you really
got to set out to do it if you want to get your license and and you've got to do it regularly
to maintain your contacts and here you go this is a great reason why and you know those are
networks that we often don't think about anymore and overlook but there's a lot of technology
going on in that space as well particularly when it comes to data communications and I don't know
all of it but I'm sure that mentioning this I'll get some email with some examples and I'd love
to hear some of the stories is to how the ham radio operators are kicked in on helping out and
perhaps that's a group that should be involved in conversations as we talk about you know getting
better getting better at handling disasters like this oh I got some some cool pod save music
which which will play in a second and also today in lieu of a hit test we've got the back tracks
podcast this is Andy and Matt from this skinny on sports athletes aren't the only ones that
can help out the people that have been devastated by hurricane Katrina and New Orleans although it's
great to see athletes like Kenny Smith hosting a charity game in Dion Sanders urging all athletes
to donate at least $1,000 to the hurricane Katrina Fund they're not the only people who can help
everyone can help out in every little bit counts you can head on over to redcross.org and you can
make your donations there to make sure that the money gets into the hands of the people who need
it the most while to have a link on our site at skinnyansports.com that you can follow to get to the
redcross and make a donation thanks to everyone who's helped out. Hi this is Don Misselli and
Drew Donk is from the Don Andrew Show Hurricane Katrina was a true tragedy and now the victims
need our help so many people are generously donating their hard earned money to communities they
may never even been to but you've got to be careful because many of these nonprofit organizations
are run with green in mind. So before you make that donation take a moment to look at charitynavigator.org.
Check their administrative costs they're pure analysis and if you simple pie charts that tell you
how they spend their donations. Make sure your donation gets into the hands of actual victims instead
of lining the pockets of the wealthy CEOs that are in close to a half a million dollars a year in salary.
For more information head to charitynavigator.org or our site donandru.com. Please help but please help
smart. Thank you. Thank you. That's Don Andrew always surprising me with a different message and
sorry for that little dip in the audio there that was I was at crime scene investigation audio clip
that I keep forgetting to replace. So it's over the pod safe music network last night when I was
putting the show together and you can also browse by genre and I thought to myself let me try
something that I'd never ever listen to or select and I selected Latin and there's like pages of
Latin pod safe music. I'm totally totally amazed and I like it too. Flamenco passion makes
of come away he's arc and hell the sky is dirty people forever. Brace falling up and the streets are wet
and your thoughts are drifting side to side while you watch a thousand dreams go by the eyes of strangers
they keep asking you. Hey what's your name number what you do and you'll love right through
them every time you just want to leave this place behind. Come away with me come in time with me
to the night come away with me that's what we let's show up me
the time is dripping from a set of light the TV's on fading into white let me travel in
your soul and mind at least for far from days and time you feel the blood running through your
veins alive and real ready for a cheap all you have to do is close your eyes pick my hands
and let go for a while come away with me come and dive with me into the night come away with me
dance with me let's show up me come away with me come and dive with me to the night come away with me
dance with me let's show up me
come away with me come and dive with me to the night come away with me
dance with me let's show up me come away with me come and dive with me to the night come away with me
dance with me let's show up me
come away you also be Isaac Angel flamingo passion mix from the pod save music network at
pod save music network dot com music dot pod show dot com and i've written on some notes here
home oh yeah i'm so looks like so i'm going back tomorrow which means i fly through the night
and i'll be arriving Thursday morning but then i should have slept on the plane so i should be
able to just put it in a full day then Patricia and Christina are leaving Friday after school
they're going to go visit family they'll be back on Monday and then i guess Tuesday i'm going to fly
to first we're going to go to Virginia for some meetings then we're going to go or Washington i'm
sorry then we're going to Chicago then to San Francisco i'm basically in the states until almost the
end of the month wow so it's going to be a mega trip but i'm really excited about being in San
Francisco because we're really moving moving ahead quite nicely on really on on two tracks one
is for podcasters and we have a whole offering that we've been hinting about and we've been talking
about and we're getting very close to you know be able to make some dam announcements on that
as well as for the listener side which is as you know we're out to get at least a hundred million
listeners and that's only times time what we have today so i think that's very doable
and and a part of that includes we've talked about this before tools for the node manager's
really cleaning cleaning up the directory and things are moving along you know it's like so frustrating
from not only for myself but for a lot of people for Ron as well he's you know okay we've got the
funding even you know we're hiring the right people and we are one of done tomorrow dam it but of
course that's impossible particularly when it comes to development but we've got some great
great really smart people working on it and we'll be doing more job casts and and also introducing
more members of the pod show family as they join up and they'll tell you what they're working on
and a number of them already do their own podcast and so we should probably put together a list of
those as well because you know this is going to be a very very audible company I didn't mean
to come out that way we will be very vocal let's put it that way because hey we're in the podcast
in business you know backtracks podcast so you think you know your hits backwards so far you said I do
yeah right you're listening to the backtracks podcast exclusively on the daily source code
with Adam Curry hey Adam hey let's get right into this week's quiz let's rock it are you ready
Adam I sure am okay here we go number one oh that's easy I get to our you can you can play that
upside down and rock it nice and we go crazy bad a sharp grass man it is GG top
panema number two
oh okay I couldn't figure it out
Pimeson number three
It sounded like we got the D from the go-go
Pimeson okay, you're the answer all right number one
I
Sharp dress man
And here's number two
Don't destroy this group. I will number three. I wouldn't go now
Doesn't time to go
The bugger video killed the radio star
So how did you do Adam?
One out of three thanks for joining us on this week's backtrack five dash quiz
You can visit backtracks podcast on the web at jackspotcast.com
Catch you next time
Backtracks podcast spin it back
Man, I love that no, and I'm sure we'll have a young pull-out tomorrow, which of course
I'm gonna try and do tomorrow, but that may maybe Thursday when I get back and that's it for the source code
Thank you very much for tuning in at September 6
In the lit here of our Lord 2005
Daily source code dot com. I'm sorry. There should be daily source code dot com is where you can
Always pick up the latest episode of the show where you can listen to the archives and there's also an XML button there copy that link that is the
podcast
You could face that into ipod or lemon you could even paste it into iTunes or they just go to iTunes if you have it from macar windows
Go to the podcast directory search for curry daily source code either one or work and then just
One click that's the only other step you got to take is click and you'll be subscribed there is no step three
Feedback, uh, well, you know, I don't say many feedback
I've been hitting a hundred percent on Gmail like every single day. I've had to you know download
In closures and then our attachments and then delete them just don't send me email for the week
Our
Unless you really got some interest in this
Submit at hotshow.com that's where you can send your promos
Hotsafe at hotshow.com for your hotsafe music submissions and mashup at hotshow.com for your mashups
And that'll get you to play all over the place if you put people in the pod finder on the serious
Series satellite hotshow
program five days a week and of course the David source code. It's a little showy
Make it our bedrooms all over the globe
I have yourself
Well, I have yourself in great day. Thank you very much for subscribing if you do it if not consider it
Thanks for listening take care everybody
Redcross dot org
Another pod show podcast stick it in your ear