I want to be very much more than just any old girl
I want to have eyes as blue as the sea
I want all the people to look at me
I want my own show on TV I want to be that girl
I want to be famous, eat out at sardies, hard parties, that's fine
I want to be famous, go to Paris on private flights
I want to have lovers buy the score
Movie producers knocking down on my door
This is the fate that is in store for me
Oh and I'm famous, I will wear a great trench coat and fake red hair
So they all will know that it is me
When they see me, how they'll smile
And me photo grass to sign
I will say sorry babe
Talk to my assistant
I want to be famous, stay my tabloids will bring what I eat
I want to be famous, who I do will be news on the streets
Then when I'm old, I'll have a ball
There'll be shocked that I'm living at home
When I enter the gas, we'll fall to the knees
And then I'll stand the throats of my enemies
But all I don't want one in cheese when I'm famous
Spameless, famous, famous
So exhausting
I want to be famous, stay my tabloids
I want to be famous, stayed my tabloids
I go that imagine I'll be
When I'm famous, not I will give
For the little people, I'll never give
When I'm famous, I'm famous
I'm famous, I'm famous
Olivia's Bitties, get lucky
Famous at the start of
Daily Source Code for this
What are we adding now?
Thursday coming to you from Northern California
from Curricondo
I was a lovely little angel who whispered
in my ear that the song was now available
on the pod safe music network.
That of course was
Leon Westover who shot me
Little email
It's just about a year ago
that this whole pod safe music thing
kind of came into view
When I found this song
by the Lassivius Bitties
I found from the site I believe
and I shot him an email
and wound up at Leon Westover
in her inbox
that sounded wrong
and I said, can I play this
on my pod cast
Yeah, yeah, we call it a pod cast
by them. She said, sure
and I played it and then other people
jumped on it and loved it and played it
and they started selling records
and man, it seems like
they've been on the road
nonstop since then
and now this song
in addition to Betty
is available on the pod safe music network
music.podshow.com
They've also got their own...
I'm sorry, I'm storing my words
Once again, it's a very early Thursday morning
they also have their own pod cast
the Bittie cast
so you can check that at Bittiecast.com
What a day
I gotta tell you, I am completely wrecked
I'm so tired
I don't know, I just never got around
that's my tea
No sense sale here in the condo
got the tea going
I never got around to getting
turned around from the jet lag
and I'm almost on my way back
and see we have today
and then Friday
Friday evening
we have our first annual
podshow Christmas party
which is just for the folks at the office
which by the way is now
almost 22, 23 people
Gosh, it's just unbelievable
and we had our board of directors meeting today
on Sandhill Road
with our investment partners
and it was
we had a lot of fun
I'll tell you, throughout the show
I'll take a couple of anecdotes
from the meeting
but it was great once again
to the same table with some of the most powerful men
and to look on that
maybe feel really good
Let's see
Jo Dion
You may now call him Captain Jo Dion
I got a little update pod cast
if you've never heard fly with me
you definitely have to listen to this pod cast
Jo flies for a major airline
I think he does a lot of trips to Hawaii
still
like it would be wrong
usually from LAX
and he
records
but not just what's going on in the cockpit
but he really does interviews
with
Stewartuses Stewart
or just a flight attendants
his own colleagues up on the flight deck
and he
in his update
which is a short two-minute little pod cast
he said that he has passed his check ride
and he now can officially sit in the left hand seat
and call himself Captain Jo Dion
Congratulations, dude
I know what that feels like
The question is
when you do a check ride like that
do you actually
fly a real plane
it's not really expensive to do a check ride
and what do you guys fly seven
I think he flies seven forty-seven
or do you do that in a simulator
as I could have expected
plenty of feedback
on
Trinity
my wonderful biodiesel beast
and I just want to share a couple of these different
different pieces of email that I got
outrageously informative
as first one is from Thomas
and he says of course that
he heard the pod cast
and he
I see what is he
he is a
for some reason I thought he knew all about
he had a reason for knowing all about this stuff
anyway he sent me a whole bunch of different links about
biodiesel
I'll just name him real quickly
you'll find him in the show notes if you go to
daily source code dot com or show notes dot info
he has biodiesel dot org of course
biodiesel america dot org
veggie van dot org
and Joshua tickle
ck and e double l dot com
and he sent another link here anyway
he says he's been running biodiesel
in his 2000 Volkswagen
since 2000 now here comes
the info that he sent along that I wanted to share with you
he says biodiesel
because you know really
understanding what this stuff is and the difference between
vegetable oil and biodiesel and
you know being 99
biodiesel is a product called
methylesters
derived by reacting vegetable oil with
potassium hydroxide or sodium hydroxide
these are also known as potash or lie
and lastly an alcohol like ethanol or methanol
as a catalyst the chemical process from
making biodiesel is exactly the same as
making soap which is called
saponification
but you terminate the reaction before you get
soap uh-huh makes sense this is part of the reason
the biodiesel has a mild solvent action and usually
cleans your fuel system
okay Joshua tickle whose website is above
wrote an excellent book many years ago called
from the fryer to the fuel tank and you can still
buy it from him explains the whole process of
making biodiesel in detail
interesting okay
so I'll make sure that some of that shows up in the
show notes and again besides
Michael of course who's who maintains his whole
show notes dot info I really
appreciate the show notes
Wiki system so much
the contributions that are being made there
on every single show is just it's really good
and actually Ron and I were talking
we uh we had a quick drink after uh
uh was after four I hope
and I was after like seven o'clock
or something like that and we were thinking about
you know what is this you know what can we do
what else can we do with show notes you know we've
already
seen quite an amazing thing happened here with
these collaborative show notes and so we're
thinking about more ideas and if you have any
of course I'd love to hear from you
David Patrick
check this out
he sent me a link
apparently
uh this coming's racing dot com
god this is great come it I'm sorry
come in's racing double M
a 170 mile per hour dragster running on
biodiesel
also look out for oddies new diesel race car
planning to race at Le Mans that's a 24 hour race
next year alongside another biodiesel
engine car this stuff it's happening it really
is it's so amazing just not to be
dependent upon upon the petrochemical
industries so incredibly nice
alright one more thing that I just wanted
hit from the feedback because it's been so
much reaction I mean this is just a small
sample of all the email that I received
about uh shaving
so if you're just tuning into this to the
podcast or if you're listening to us for the
first time in serious satellite stars
um I just said you know what are you using
what kind of razor are you using and why
and how long is it last
and apparently what I'm stumbling onto here
is that blades don't really get
dollar the more you use them yet they
dollar at a certain point
but you can use them for a long time
and they will still be effective at least
that's what some of the your fellow source
code listeners are saying
Steve Harlow says my experiences that a single
blade disposable big razor will last about a year
after a few weeks it isn't as sharp as it
wasn't first but it stays about the same
for months and months I like it that way
best eventually however it doesn't seem to
cut anything anymore well yeah it doesn't
mean that okay but still a year
I bought a bag of a dozen raises for five
bucks five years ago I still got several
just depends on how close you want the
shave and how thick your beard is that doesn't
make any sense how does that work
I mean I think they just
are they just putting us on with all this
stuff
Trevor says that when he was taking
mechanical engineering classes at Penn State
one of his professors told him that the
hardness of a razor blade is much harder than
the hair on our face so theoretically
our hair would not make the blade dull he says
the reason a blade goes dull is because it
oxidizes which of course is rust
you may not see the rust but it causes small
pits and roughness in the edges of the
razor if you were able to look on a
microstope you'll be able to see the pits
so if there was a way to prevent it from
rusting you might be able to keep the
razor blade longer hey man I didn't use to
think that that little strip that you know
that blue strip on the razor that once
that was kind of gone and white there was
time to throw it out I think this is
I think we've been bullshit all along
Alan Wages says that I'm a lifetime
Gillette user the original sensor came out
right around when I started shaving as a
teenager and I think I've used every
gelette model since once after I switched
the mock three I went back and tried
the sensor and there was no going back again
but a year ago I started using the M3
power it's fantastic I get about eight to ten
shades from each carches is that the
one that has the the hell is that the
M3 power is that the three
blade with a motor in it or something like that
I've read so I got to collect all of these
things and I'll just really flesh them out
and one big show I think someone else
was saying that he still uses a straight
razor it's pretty amazing and what
it's a billion dollar business by
the way it's unbelievable so I
have a big complaint for a fellow podcaster
I've said it to him privately
and now I want to say it publicly
because I really want to turn up the
pressure on this guy because he's
well he's done really a bad thing
once you get your audience hooked
you just cannot pull the needle out of the
main line I'm talking about the daily download
Chris Rockwell who works at pod show full
time has not done a daily download
poop cast for over two months
and I for one am severely severely disappointed
to let this be a call for all pod casters
to get Chris Rockwell to drop a low
some people go on smoke breaks
others surf the web
some people get up and grab a coffee
but I'm not one of them
I don't like being a net
and all I smoke is grass
I've heard a spend my time sitting on my skinny white ass
I've read some lies all around the room
just right before I start
sometimes I'm in there for 30 minutes
and all I do is fart
so if the facts machines on the fritz
and that'll cop here is going berserk
don't ask me to play Mr. Repairman
when I'm taking a dog at work
oh I'm taking a dog
I'm taking a dog
I'm taking a dog at work
I don't bother me
because I'm taking a dog at work
I go in a round of left
and a clock
I go back in after lunch
every time it comes out right on the dam
and it looks like a nestle crunch
and I'm afraid to you
who's the Johnny
but that's all my floor
there'll be a 10 minute layover
before it almost shit up with the door
I'm taking a dog
but taking a dog
but taking a dog at work
I don't bother me
you can't see
I'm just taking a dog at work
and if I'm not in my disc
I'll be on the porch of the throne
I'll waste my day on the crapper
until this time to go home
I do talk to me
through the storm
and you break my concentration
the last thing that I need right now
is a case of constipation
and I'm a fan of the courtesy flush
I like my ass tape
a three-plot thick
you know I sat on the shit of this afternoon
and read mail bills won't be a dick
twice
so you can call me Ishmael Bitch
when I'm taking a dog
but taking a dog
it won't even
I don't bother me
you can't see him
just taking a dog at work
I don't care
the boss is looking
the phone is ringing
I'll be in here
dropping a news
and you'll probably hear me singing
that I'm taking a dog
we're taking a dog
we're going
we don't bother me
you can't see him
just taking a dog
bad boy
oh
I'm roundin' down
I'm roundin'
he's puffin' his head
and then there's cool back here
oh
hhh
no
dammit and you're real
ONA
terminus
so the next time you're in your office
and your stomach starts to jerk
get out of your chair and drop
And take you and don't let you leave.
Stucky and Murray, taking a dump at work with my special plea to Chris Rockwell to get back to podcasting, please.
Dude, don't you want to quit your day job?
Got that song off of the comedy section of the Podsake Music Network.
And if you look through it, this is something I didn't know.
Lots of comedians are uploading their entire routines.
It's not very, I mean, this song falls under or has been tagged as a comedy genre as well as some of these routines.
So that's not really an efficient way of finding them, but they are there.
And it seems like, well, if we can get some comedians into podcasting, wouldn't that be nice?
Man, what a forum for comedians.
I don't know.
But to me, it's exactly the same as Podsake musicians.
I think it could really help you in your career.
Maybe not for selling comedy albums, but wow.
What a way to get some exposure and get some gigs.
Of course, you'll have to keep the routine fresh if everyone can just download all your jokes.
Let me see what else I was going to say about that.
Now, okay. So after the Board of Directors meeting today, right there, there's a shopping mall,
which is, I don't know, was it the Palo Alto shopping mall.
It says really upscale stuff.
And Ron and I did a little bit of Christmas shopping for our spouses.
And of course, that meant that we spent a lot of time at Sharper Image.
And what I bought is a Tom Tom Go GPS Navigator for Trinity.
So officially now, the equipment inside the car is about 20% of the price of the entire automobile.
But it's great. And I'm really, really impressed with this Tom Tom Go, which I believe is built by a Dutch company.
I'm going to second I got my, I got my T here.
I think it's built by a Dutch company sold over the world, very, very successful.
Touch screen, small, little unit has a battery, lithium battery inside.
You can plug it in a adapter into the cigarette lighter.
It has a regular power adapter.
You can put it in walking mode.
So it ignores all of the one-way streets.
So it knows that you're not in a car.
You're walking, you put it in a bicycle mode.
It's just really good.
It has multiple voices unbelievably sophisticated, very, very impressed with it.
And it boy, it looks great. It looks great.
It's, you know, snapped right onto Trinity's window there.
And so, of course, I had to test it out.
So this was a big trip for me.
I, after work, I programmed in the nearest whole foods location and drove her over.
And was able to get a lot of the stuff that I really didn't have.
I needed some brooms, you know, but also wanted to get just some regular groceries.
Oh, you know what I found?
Oh, man, I'm so happy.
My wife, Patricia will be so jealous.
I found Eggnog, which, of course, I only have recently come to understand, is not available
in the United Kingdom, or at least not readily available as it is here in the States.
And I got back and I had a nice, you know, cup of Eggnog.
Even though it was, you know, it's store bought.
And there's no alcohol on it.
It's still, it had that taste to it.
You know, it was really, really cool.
And just one more thing here about a pod save for peace.
I got beginning a lot of email back and forth over the past two days from Slaw.
Westwood 1, not only debuted the song on their network.
That's the Westwood 1 radio network.
But they're also putting it into rotation on their 24 hour day holiday programming.
So this includes 65 stations, as well as the armed forces network.
Let's see, Mike Tanner Westwood 1, heard, heard Slaw on Marilana's ACB radio show.
And immediately wanted to get a copy.
So it was FedEx and Boom.
There you go.
So as, as hoped, it's now getting play outside of the pod casting arena, which is great,
because it can show what pod safe music is all about.
It can get people interested in pod casting.
And ASCAP performance royalties will go to UNICEF.
And of course, people can buy the song at podsaferepiece.org.
And in our board of directors meeting today.
Yeah, I didn't mean that we were somewhere between infrastructure and finance.
I can't remember what, you know, what we were discussing at the time.
And then Ray Lane, who was really, I'd have to say, the lead partner from Kleiner Perkins
from our investment team.
He said, you know, I just guys, have you heard this?
He called it a Christmas mashup.
And so I didn't quite get what he was talking about at first.
You know, all these, these pod safe music artists.
And he had heard it.
He had purchased the song.
And he was turning all the people in the room onto it.
And he was so, so nuts about the idea.
And I hadn't told them about it.
I hadn't sent it to him or tip them off to it.
He had just found it.
I know he listens to a whole bunch of podcasts.
He may have heard it through the daily source code, but more likely through something else,
because he definitely serves around a lot.
But that really, it just, you know, like, whoa, it kind of gave me a little chill there.
You know, something really, really working across boundaries to what you normally think would be
some pretty boring people, which they're not.
The way switch done.
If you're listening to this show on a serious stars 103 on serious satellite radio,
coming up next in the pod show lineup.
We've got from the pod squad, Pacific Coast, Hellway, followed by yeast radio, then Dawn and Drew.
PW Fenton fills in the next half hour with something.
It's always a surprise.
And I never know beforehand what he's going to do.
And then, of course, we got more pod safe music to round out the hour.
We do it every single day from 6 to 10 Eastern, from 3 to 7 Pacific on stars 103.
And if you want to hear more of the daily source code, well, then really what you should be doing is
subscribing to the podcast, downloading it, because the satellite window is closing,
and the people who listen to the podcast.
Well, they get all the extra bits.
Man, that blue chunks.
Hi.
Are you looking for a heart?
Do you need wild podcap?
This one has it all.
Three sums?
Four sums?
One episode even had a six sum, and you never know who's going to pair up together.
Everyone here is a player.
These people go at it late into the night, and cubby even pulled a 24 hour marathon.
Here, the women are looking for pole.
And the men are looking to stick it in the hole with this little effort as possible.
This podcast is all about banging, getting it in the back door, and sometimes playing
with yourself.
Everyone here is looking to score.
How can this podcast be suitable for all agents?
Well, we're not talking about sex here.
We're talking about disc golf.
We're the players throw their frisbee at a pole, banging the cane, and deflecting the
disc into the basket to finish the hole.
There won't be any sex in this podcast, but it's all about passion.
So listen to cubby's disc golf world podcast, and check out all the actions.
I don't know about you, but this is getting me hot.
I'd love to play around with you and cubby's disc golf world.
Come listen now.
Meow.
Love you disc golf world.
See ya.
Nice to meet you.
We'll see you in the future.
If this load of shit is what your inbox sounds like every morning,
you may want to consider earthling internet services.
With integrated spam, scam, and virus blocking, earthling internet services is the
laxative that will clean out your inbox.
Perfect.
Helping you take less shit every day.
This promo is brought to you by the financial aid podcast at financialadpodcast.com.
The real no shit deal on student loan scholarships and education finance.
Visit us online at financialadpodcast.com.
We'll see you in the future.
Hey Adam, this is Nick.
And Jay.
And we're from Nick and Jay.
And Jay and Jay.
Yeah.
Okay.
So we made you a promo.
Just to let you know that you are existing.
Yeah.
We just want to wish you a merry Christmas.
And all of your lives.
And the holidays, guys.
Yeah.
So without further ado.
A promo.
So give me a more fun.
For like seven.
I've got a whole sitting next to me.
It's been the congenio.
I love you.
The coolest teen podcast in the Southern Hemisphere.
With hot guests.
I am the man for you.
Hot music.
I told you we love hot kids.
And hot accents.
I'm not Australian.
I don't want these because this is how Australian Thor.
Brought to you once a week, every week.
Congenio.
Yeah.
Nick and Jay and Jay.
And Jay and the spell.
Jay.
Hey.
Yeah.
It's mad down the door.
It's a big quiet.
And now.
And back to the Daily Source Code.
Ah.
Spallion.
I love like.
So what I'm trying to do with this new format.
We're I'm only doing a 24 minutes and 30 seconds for that'll be in the serious satellite window.
And by the way, I yielded the rest of my time.
The other half of my time to the distinguished gentle woman from Chicago.
I had to find steam.
She's not doing an hour.
She was, oh man.
She was complaining.
So that's so much about that.
You know, I wish we had more time and serious.
There's so many more shows I'd like to put on.
Well, working on it.
Okay.
So far, they're repeating the shows in the morning.
From six to ten Eastern AM.
But of course, it's the shows from the day before.
And I'd much rather create fresh shows in the morning and have fresh shows in the afternoon.
I mean, what else do they have on the channel?
Because it doesn't go across the cousin Brucey.
Come on.
That by the way, the of the three questions, there's only three main inquiries that people have when
they call up serious.
One last second.
And it's questions about Howard Stern about the Pod Show and about cousin Brucey.
I don't know if it's in that order.
I don't know if it's good, better and different.
But that's the truth.
Yesterday I was wondering where the ultimate mix pod cast went and
You know, this is the guy who does a podcast that ultimately makes dot blogs spot.com
Which is the ultimate mix. It's like a weekly show of pod safe music
I really like listening to other podcasts to pick up on cool pod safe music
And so what usually what I do is I do a run of a couple of shows that I like I look at that on the PMM
And otherwise I'll just refresh the home page a couple of times and usually the songs that show up there
I've been played at least once on a podcast. I'll check those out
But I do like listening to the ultimate mix and right there on his home page
It said no podcast. I'm sick. Sorry everyone. No podcast this week
I'm on my back enjoying the flu. Hopefully I can squeeze two in the next week
All right, dude. Hope you feel better for sure
So the new format. I'm trying to put together here for the source code
It's had that first you know the first kind of like 15 20 25 minutes have that be you know much more kind of you know
Stuff that I've been doing in source code like stuff
Or human source code like stuff and then once the satellite window closes is really where I want to focus a lot of the pod casting stuff
Because that way you know a lot of new listeners coming into this space
They'll probably want to know about what's going on with pod casting
But you know you really want to get some feel for pod cast as well
So that's kind of what I did yesterday with Trinity, you know first I did all the biodiesel stuff and then we talked about
What other stuff is going on in the podcast industry
Because I know there's still lots of pod casters who
who check out the show and
The pod pimp Aaron Brousel from pod show sent over an email that I just got it's I sent a link to a survey
Which was done amongst podcasters
According to the link survey results described in this story 40% of podcasters
Have monetization in mind and excerpt almost two fifths of people producing video blogs and podcasts are doing so with some sort of commercial motive according to the study
The study was based on two surveys of 351 mostly US based podcasters and video bloggers and
Found that nearly 40% were producing the content with an explicit or quasi commercial motive in mind
Dr. Peter Chen and
Assistant lecturer in media at Monash University and author the pod casting and video blogging
Oh an author of pod casting a video blogging a production site analysis study
Says that while he found the result surprising it should be qualified in the sense that most producers probably didn't expect the podcasters video blogs to provide a
substantial income
Interesting, okay
I will put the link to that in the daily source code show notes, so it can be copied over to the to the wiki show notes
I know it wasn't me see 351. Well, oh man, I could argue forever about stats, but
Is that a good sample of 10,000 is so two so they did 700?
Well, they almost did 10% of the registered podcasters if you if you take like a
As less than that is probably because of what we have now at podcast alley 11 12,000 13,000 so
Probably more like seven eight percent, but still very very interesting
And thanks to the miracle of pod casting. I'm actually I want to play this because in the future some day we're going to be able to
Use pieces or be able to refer back to pieces in podcast that'll be I think become relevant
Maybe I should put this up on the web somewhere else or
Maybe Pete the Mac geek can do it for me because it for the first time
He really gave me a great step-by-step analysis of my Macintosh hard drive now. This is like a three-minute geeky piece
So if you're not into you know how to fix a Mac hard drive when it crashes and what steps to take
Please please just shuttle right past the next three minutes and seven seconds
I think you mentioned your upstairs Macintosh again during a DSC 298 and I thought I'd finally go for my fat ass and come and see me some audio feedback
You'll have to excuse the audio quality. I'm using the built-in mic on my laptop
Maybe you could pipe my audio through that fancy compressor eels
Anyway, Adam, I heard you mentioned you really want to recover the data from that drive so I thought I'd give you a yellow
You see I spent my days working as a technician at an Apple server center down here in New Zealand
I've had to recover data from many a host drive over my time and I thought I'd throw on a quick one-minute run-down on the steps
I go through and the hope it might be useful to you or one-year DSC listeners
First of all, you need to determine if the drive has suffered a harm to your failure or a software failure
But software, I mean the make-up of the data on the hard drive to retry structure
There are two possible types of harm to your failure from our perspective
Mechanical failure or controllable failure. If the drive makes loud clunky noises other than the normal
Sort of power on self-test start-up noises then this most likely indicates a mechanical assembly failure
A complete lack of spin-up also indicates a mechanical assembly failure
Although sometimes the symptom can also be caused by a controllable failure
If the drive spins up okay, but doesn't sharpen disc utility when you look for it
Then you most likely have a controllable portfolio
Controllable failures are far less common than the mechanical assembly failures, but they do happen
I've got a stack of six good quantum drives that work that have all had the exact same chip fail
And they've all got a boom mark on them to prove it
If the drive spins up okay, and you can see it in disc utility
But it doesn't mount on the finder
Adam, this is you from what you've told me
Then you most likely have a corrupt retry structure
That's a software failure and not a hardware failure
Great, so now you know how to distinguish them how can you fix them
Well, the mechanical assembly failure is by far the worst failure of the lot when it comes to repairing the drive yourself
Usually there's a little hope although sometimes a drive will stay out long enough for you to mount it and copy the most important data
I your users folder
One trick that is worked in the past is to stick the drive in a fridge
Adam, I heard you're mentioning a freezer once
But I've definitely had better results just using the fridge
Leave it in there for at least a day so that it can chill properly though
And mechanical failure that you can't recover from will probably have to be sent away to a special
Sorganisation like drive savers
Who although expensive are generally do have excellent results
If you have a controller board failure, you'll need to find another drive of the exact same make and model with a good working board that you can borrow to put onto your drive to get your data off
You literally remove the board from the good drive put it onto your mechanical assembly
This is why it's good practice for technicians to keep the controller boards from failed drives that they've obtained over time and
Case that I've used to somebody else later
And finally if you have a corrupt directory structure, then I'd have to agree with Kurt Lewis the best tool for me
I was tending to retrieve recovery as dyskoria
Not and doesn't need as he puts it suck the sweat off right not so russes testicles
Well, I hope there'll be a few of you still have you holidays and keep the DSC's coming
You know, it turns out apples are pretty cool companies still isn't it?
I mean they got guys in New Zealand who are sticking power books and fridges and sparking up
Yeah, that's the company. I remember you got it and wind it up. What to do with Michael can be butchers
There's they dealt this year at Charlie
She was there studying abroad. He was on tour playing in another time
They potted hard and they potted wings
A little north of the sand
He dreamed about her in so many ways
She dreamed about her in France
Well, she knows what to do with Michael
She knows how to make him feel
That he's the one he's mother son
Not like anyone just needs time to heal
They met in New York a few months later
He was still living alone
Hugging the ball in masturbating
Never answer it's fun
Death first date was a movie together
Outside it Brian Pock
In the spirit I've seen Louis just went on forever
Till they drank wine until they saw scars
Well, she knows what to do with Michael
She knows how to make him feel
That he's the one he's mother son
Not like anyone just needs time to heal
They finally hooked up for the first time
The night before the Fourth of July
He felt so awkward saying goodbye to the girl who just changed his life
Now my friend they are in separate ball
She even gets that boy to go to the gym
Now if you don't think that's love you must be cynical
Oh, maybe man you're just dreaming in France
Yeah, because she knows what to do with Michael
She knows how to make him feel
That he's the one he's mother son
Not like anyone just needs time to heal
Well, she knows what to do with Michael
She knows how to make him feel
That he's the one he's mother son
Not like anyone just needs time to heal
Yeah, he's the one he's mother son
Well, that's right. He just needs a time to heal
Big bad hell this one would have been one you'd love
Just listening that song and there's this legendary radio guy in Holland out Alfred look harder
And anyone who is in the Netherlands who knows him will know exactly what I'm talking about
He would have loved this song. He would have I know he would have he passed away
Oh, man what about five years ago five six years ago
He was only 50 but he was he was the oh, and he was not
That's what he was
What amazed he lasted until 50 but still I really really do miss him and hearing that song kind of brought some some good memories back
That's it for the daily source code for today daily source code dot com adamant curry dot com for the feedback
Kind of just say one more time now that I'm at 96% of my four gigs on go on Gmail and I really love Gmail
I know I can get more space anywhere else, but please put your feedback on a server and just send me a link
Okay, I'll be back tomorrow with the thank god it's Friday edition of Delta Sierra Charlie
Another pop show podcast stick it in your ear