Delta's here at Charlie 211.
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who managed what you can hear since
radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
I'm warning the content of this podcast may be not fit for worker kids.
It is July 19, 2005.
Hi everybody, how you doing?
It is the daily source code coming you from Curry Cottage.
It's a little bit chilly today.
It's just in the mid-low mid-20s.
That would be a stomach rate of course.
And I think I stayed up too late for the past two nights.
I got those, you know, because really tired chill.
Last night was particularly brutal.
I'll get into that.
We're going to talk about three topics in today's source code.
I still have to get my piece of paper to find out what they were.
I'm going to talk about the pod finder podcast.
We're going to talk about yesterday's daily source code and
Accomi and bandwidth and stuff like that.
We're going to talk about iPod at org.
I guess it's four topics.
And the war on pods.
The pod wars.
We'll come for the better name as we go along.
Your daily source code.
It's your audio directory.
It's my break during the day.
Hey, kids got to do something.
I got some promos.
We're ready to roll out for you.
Exciting news, by the way.
On Friday, this coming Friday for the very first time.
We will be playing the podcast at the top 10 on serious, serious satellite.
Which is cool.
Because we're claiming a top 10.
And we'll get published.
Hopefully we'll get it in some magazines.
We'll be a weekly feature.
Maybe in the USA today.
So it's going to be even cooler to vote and be voted on.
Podcast dollar.
Podcast.
What's the rationale over the place?
You know what?
Let's get things rolling right away with some happy music.
This is a few choro.
Mix this mash up.
When I saw it, I was like, those two songs are going to fit together.
And then, hey, when I heard I said, oh my goodness.
It's freaking perfect.
I also got some great pod save music on the way from the pod save music now.
But first, now that we found music.
We started dancing.
Let love for us.
We sing to our bro.
As soon as we started to move.
We played while our bodies are swayed through the dance.
Then I'll break those down for a moment.
I thought it was clear that the plan was clear for sure.
The feeling is between us.
But when the music changes, the plan was clear.
We started dancing.
Let love for us.
We started.
We started dancing.
We starts dancing.
We started dancing with anti-evil armmeness.
We started mass gymnastics.
We started dancing.
It is our first time.
V later, our evolution.
We started dancing.
Our fifth time.
We started dancing!
We started mandating.
We started comping.
We started dancing.
Good Lord, there's so many hell in Potter, K-Potter.
Our new gay lesbian directorate site.
For all gay lesbian podcasts, I'll go there.
Q-Potter.org.
Hot, Joe.
Content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
Hey Adam, this is Nick Carver from the No Ittle Fretz.
Jazz Guitar Podcast.
Back in March, I started a podcast of a kind of an audio block sort of thing.
One of the things I shared about was my interest flow for jazz and in particular jazz guitar.
So, in June, I thought, hey, let's start another podcast.
One dedicated to the thing that I love.
Jazz Guitar.
So, the No Ittle Fretz Jazz Guitar Podcast.
On this podcast, you'll hear straight ahead jazz like this.
You'll hear old-time acoustic jazz guitar like this.
You'll hear some fusiony stuff like this.
But in all case, what you're going to hear is, Todd's safe, Jazz Guitar.
So, check it out.
It's the No Ittle Fretz Jazz Guitar Podcast that's No Ittle Fretz.blogspot.com.
Thanks and we'll talk to you later.
Yeah, like in that, in Carver, No Ittle Fretz.
F as in FoxDrop, Romeo, Echo, Tango, She's in Sierra.
Oh, man.
What was I going to say?
I was just thinking about something really prolific. I'm sure.
I screwed.
What I was going to do, well, I don't remember.
Let's listen to what Apocalypse D.S. does say.
Hey Adam, this is Brian from the Apocalypse D.S. O Podcast,
which is a couple of comments.
So, on your last show, you mentioned a podcast
or who was having a bit of trouble submitting his show to the iTunes directory,
because he didn't have access to a credit card.
It sounds like his problem kind of relates to the problem I had when iTunes 4.9 came out.
Because I live in Japan, and there's no iTunes music store for Japan.
So, from Japan, I can browse the US store.
I can browse actually any of the stores in the world.
And I can download podcasts, thank God.
But I can't buy music because it's illegal.
And I can't get an iTunes music store ID.
So, without that ID, I can't submit a podcast.
Now, since I bought my iMac in Japan, and since Steve Jobs comes over all the time for T,
Apple knows exactly where I live, and a message comes up.
You want to try to register saying the music store is available in my country.
A listener mentioned the same problem.
This guy was from Korea.
Nothing. To Adam Christianson on the Maccast.
So, I emailed Adam. I said, hey, I'm having the same problem.
I agree with this guy in Korea. It is a problem.
And then Adam actually submitted my feed for me.
And two days later, I was up in the directory.
So, that was cool.
So, I guess my advice is, if you live in a country without iTunes music store access,
or if you can't get access to a credit card, send Adam Korean email.
No, no, you're crazy.
Adam, that's not work of course.
Oh, no.
Well, maybe you can just try to get a touch of the friend,
one of those countries who has access to the music store.
Please don't do that.
Also, before you continue there, a pocket with style, a pocket lips dowel.
You know, I was talking to Madge Weinstein last night.
Yeah, we do talk once in a while.
And because I was up so late, and she pinged me, and you know,
this is typical Madge, you know, angry, angry, Jewish bloated lesbian stuff.
Like, you know, and complaining about the indie podcast, not being listed on iTunes anymore.
And this is a meme that is going around.
And it's interesting because you really have to consider the source of these stories.
These stories are coming from predominantly mainstream media publications.
And it just makes me, me, me, in a way, it makes me laugh,
but it also makes me angry when I, because, you know, I read all the podcast,
Ali, message boards, I'm on the podcast, or mailing list, and the group at Yahoo.
And there's so much complaining and bitching about this.
And you're seeing it all wrong.
Let me take drugs, for instance.
Drugs are illegal. It's bad, you know, but it's a, it's a 100, 100 billion dollar industry.
Everything from the growing to the sale to the jails that people are thrown into.
Now, not that I'm advocating that, but stuff that's illegal is always attractive.
Stuff that isn't supposed to be heard by you.
Stuff that is sanctioned, stuff that is not presented because, you know, it's, it's, it's that other stuff.
That's beautiful.
So we should be proud of the tag in the podcasters, just like independent music.
You know, this is for us. That's fine. Well, it doesn't matter what you call it.
As long as we're all calling it the same thing. So this indie podcast or thing is stuck.
And I think Apple for that, because at first I was a little negative about it because, hey,
it's our word, right? We created it, but then like, no, it doesn't matter.
As long as you call it something, then people will know what it is. Now,
this is why I've been working so hard, really, on two projects.
One is the podfinder podcast, which, and this, this episode that was released today,
is 57 minutes long. I think I was able to cram 16 different podcasts in there.
No, no, not from, from our own pod show podcast network.
In fact, I put Madge Weinstein in and what is it?
Michael Butler's rock and roll geek the indie cast, which is a completely non-commercial show.
And we just pulled out, you know, all the stuff that's, what I could basically,
saying every single day, four hours a day on a weekdays that is. That's 20 hours a week.
We play podcasts, promos, and podsafe music and also mash-ups, but predominantly the promos,
and every hour there's a featured podcast, which you play in its entirety on serious
sidelight radio. And the response is overwhelming. Now, they have, I think they only have, like,
a little under two million subscribers, but that's going to grow. You know, they're going to have
five million in, in a year or two. And when Howard Stern comes on at the end of the year,
lots of people are going to be signing up. And people are finding it because it's like, hey,
that's not good for you. That's, that's like that podcast, and what they say,
shit piss fuck, cock mother fucker, cock sucker. I warned you at the beginning of the show,
didn't I? So people are going to come looking for stuff like that. People are going to become looking
for, you know, for great music that is outside the norm. You know, don't, let's just,
the, the, where our own worst enemy at this point, you know, bitching and moaning and, you know,
so when someone types in indie podcast at a Google that come up to all these bitching and moaning posts,
you know, stop that. In fact, um, I think that I, I want to do something pretty radical here.
I'd like to change the name of iPodder.org to indiepotter.org. And I'm going to make a commitment to
you right now. Now, it's no secret that there's been all kinds of flakiness on the server going on.
And we have a couple people working really hard right now. We're going to put down a real investment
in money to have a team put on to indiepotter.org. I'm just going to call it that for now.
Haven't changed anything yet, but let's call it indiepotter.org because that's what, that's,
that's where we want people to go. Um, it's so cool that a nom dex Dave Wyner and I hooked up again,
because now he's putting me on the beta of, um, of his OPML editor. It's great software. It's still,
you know, it's, the capabilities of it are so vast, but it's a great editor for a distributed
directory. And we've seen first hand now, first hand. Yeah, we may not have the server shit
all taken care of because it's just, I mean, it's falling on its ass completely. It's, we're getting
that fixed ASAP. I promise you. Um, but we don't have a problem with the content, you know,
there's over 100 people who are maintaining individual nodes on this thing. Some of them are actually
writing up their OPML files by hand, which, you know, that's dedication right there. So we've
talked about this before, but now we're really going to put our money where our mouth is. I personally
am going to make sure that, uh, we have a team so that there's someone to go to if you're having
issues, um, with your node. We're going to make, uh, it faster. We're also going to make it prettier.
Give you some tools for node managers to maintain your page if you want, you know, that's really
easy. The infrastructure stays the same. And let's just, you know, let's promote the crap out of
indiepotter.org. Let's, let's show people if they're looking for the cool stuff, they could say,
what's that indie podcast? What do I find the indie podcast? So now I'm not going to break anything
that I put it or domain name. I wouldn't break that, but indiepotter.org, I think is the brand that,
uh, that I'd like to change this to. And, uh, I'm going to need your help, basically. So I'm going to
need your help in, uh, in working on nodes. Uh, I'm going to need your help in, um, in posting and pointing
to it. And, uh, we're going to keep it, uh, you know, a dot org site. Well, uh, there's just so, so much
incredible opportunity. There's just sitting there waiting for us. And, uh, don't sweat it, you know,
it's, uh, it's just press and press or just, you know, it's like a victory for them, you know.
First, it was the bloggers now. Let's try and kick the podcasters down. You know, it's like,
you're 15 minutes of fame or over. It's just not true. I mean, I'm seeing the numbers coming through,
not from my own podcast, but for other podcasts, we have tremendous, tremendous amount of
listeners. And remember, this is not because we all said, oh, I really want to create a show
where I really want to say something. No, it's because radio blows, because traditional radio has,
for the past 20 years has just turned into a completely packaged, formatted playlist of crap.
And they don't have the spectrum. They don't have, uh, the, the broadcast reached to do anything
near what we're doing. And they don't have the balls to do the stuff that we're doing quite honestly.
You know, when would you ever see a Q-patterr.org site, you know, done by mainstream media?
It's not going to happen. Remember, um, if it's crap on the radio, it's going to be crap in a podcast.
It is. It's bullshit in his bullshit out. So, um, people have, uh, have found podcasting
because there was something different going on, something remarkable going on here as Peter
Day would say. Um, and they've, they've come and they've subscribed and they're sticking with it.
So, let's pull together a little bit here and, you know, let's stop all the whining and
moaning and bitching about what somebody wrote somewhere on an online version of a newspaper or
whatever. It's just not worth it. You know, we want to show, we want to lead, we want to really
give our listeners a great experience because that's what they've been, been clamoring for.
Okay. Hey, Matt, thank you very much for, uh, for, uh, getting me on that tangent.
And, uh, let me get back to, uh, apocalypse dolls comment. I'm sorry about that.
Also, uh, a different point is, uh, I teach English here, uh, kind of like, uh, Robin Williams in, uh,
good morning Vietnam. And, uh, tonight I was talking to some of my students about, uh, the
terrorist attacks in London. Uh, so one of the students, uh, seemed surprised by how strong the
people in London have been. And, uh, later another student commented, you know, like, he said,
maybe that's just how the media is portraying it. Maybe the people aren't really strong there.
And I thought, you know, that's a good point, but, uh, I really thought about, uh, listening to
your show and, uh, that you've been talking about how strong and, uh, how resilient the people of
London have been. And, uh, and that, um, like, that's podcasting, man. That's, uh, let's get into
truth out and, uh, finding out the news, straight from the people who are there. And, uh, you know,
with, with all this talk recently from people who've been arguing that podcasting isn't really
a viable, uh, former media, uh, you know, it makes it kind of seem ridiculous now, like, uh, it's real.
That's how you can get the news. Uh, anyway, love the show. Keep it up. Thanks a lot, Adam. Take care, man.
All right, buddy. Thank you very much. Um, and you should go over to SoundSyncTours.com.
Call me. I can pull it up here.rum moment. Come on. Sorry, this is totally lame. I'm so
unprepared. Uh, SoundSyncTours. There was a, uh, a sound scene tour, the day after the bombings and
London. Let me see. Here it is.
Perfect path. That's right. Perfect path. That's the guy who made a star box. It's a great little
podcast. And you can really hear what the vibe was like right after the bombings. And you're right.
You're absolutely right. You know, the real voices are here. And we actually have real voices. And you can hear
him this time, which is fantastic. Hi, this is Jeff. And I'm Pat. Hi, this is Rob from Podcast 411. Hey, Jason here from
Insomnioradio. Hi, this is Birlafordie from the Geek Food Action Group Podcast. Hi, this is Brian
Abbott from Coverville. This is Bizzooka Jeff from Small World Podcast. This is Jeffrey Tee from the Good Beer Show.
Hi, this is Tim from Radio Speljamer. Hey, this is Chanymacham from SportBloggersLive.com.
I feel like Chulin like the Cryptopillean. I got a Dave's lounge, and I'm hanging out with Dave's
lounge. Well, hang it out, at Dave's lounge. Come to the place where all your favorite podcasts
for your hanging out.
Come to Dave's Lounge.
Subscribe today at www.daveslounge.com slash RSS.
Drop by anytime, y'all.
We're always open.
Most of our high spots were coming to us now.
My TV is central.
We're not this one.
Sirius 148 Adam Curry's pod show.
Experience the unexpected.
Tell the world.
Tell us everybody wherever they are.
To your central 148
RadioWC found that www.radiowc.com is the podcast where you can finally
tune in to hear the truth.
Controversial opinions of the disaffected minority.
Liberals.
Heavy control by Republicans here.
Liberals are an endangered species in Warren County, OIO,
or upwards of 70% of the population brought into the Bush administration's lies.
Anyway, WC basically means toilet.
Join your hosts.
Uncle Dan, resident tech wizard, liberal, and all around weirdo.
I know the double entendre, but if there's a triple entendre, you might want to explain that.
And Abu Snookham's left wing activist.
And a proud Muslim, making him even more retarded.
And a new can wasteland of the WC.
And the WC is all about a couple of misfits in the middle of Bush country here.
Join them at www.radiowc.com as they try to fight their way through the lies and the
ever present bullshit of the new county revolution.
In fact, their show is so controversial.
It has attracted the attention of President Bush himself.
Listen to this recent interview with a president about radioWC.
What is it you see the people behind radioWC as a threat to the country?
We're facing a group of folks who have such hatred in their heart.
But Mr. President, you must understand that they are exercising now right to free speech.
Wouldn't you agree?
This were a dictator shipping the hack all out easier.
Just so long as I'm addicted.
Okay, but if you do the Uncle Dan and Abu Snookham's, what would you say to them?
We won't detain them.
Mr. President, exactly how did you find out about radioWC?
On the internet.
And sir, what do you think when you listen to radioWC?
A quiet, unyielding anger?
What did you think to yourself the first time you ever listened to radioWC?
President, I'm sure report.
Well, there you have it.
This is the podcast, the Bush administration.
This is not one to two years.
So point to your browsers to WWW.
That radioWC.
That's come.
And your podcast software to feeds.
That feed burner.com slash radioWC.
Before the new podcast, shut them down.
See, that's exactly what I'm talking about.
Now this may not be a podcast for you, but it's a hell of a, that's probably what?
49% of Americans who might be interested in that podcast.
This is good.
I feel good about this.
IndiePotter.org.
Yeah, that's kind of working for me.
Hey, let's play some happy tune, shall we?
Pull this one off.
The pod save music network and pod save music network.com.
Music.podshow.com.
I think I'm the first to play it on a podcast.
So I'll make sure to register that.
Sound scientists, the group is called Bill on the daily source code.
Coming in so loud and clear.
I've once gone trying to steal my ear.
Stopping me suddenly in my tracks.
And I appreciate the facts while I'm here.
You say I'm a sound scientist.
You can do a value with the evidence.
On a close case.
Highly classified.
Come potential in a race against the clock.
Music.
You look like you could use a break.
You said as I lived in my head.
And I'm a looking from a danger.
Now to show how long I was out for.
Looking for the girl thought I saw her on the show.
We went and looked together.
Bell that had been mistaken.
Looking in the wrong direction.
I can question tape because to the answer.
I can't a chance.
Cause when I hit the walls.
From the back.
Send me up on the ball.
I'm allowed to go with somewhere to go.
I know I'd rather stay.
Music.
Mix it up.
Stir it in a cup.
Turn it like that.
Quick fix it.
Open to the public.
Free sample.
Music.
Thank you so much for watching this video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the
next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see
you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next
video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you in the next video, see you
in the next video, good.
I'm drained, but I feel really good.
I was a nice chat we had today.
Thank you very much for tuning in.
Tomorrow, no source code, because I'm traveling off to San Francisco.
Now, I may do a source code, but it'll be much, much later.
Nah, I'd probably wait for Thursday.
That's about the best I can do.
Off on Virgin to the Valley.
I love it all, I love it all.
So I'd love to hear from you.
Adam at curie.com, you can send your voice feedback if you want some Gmail as slowly
counting up.
I got to think of somehow responsible for that.
Slowly, the Infinity Plus 1 is growing, we're going from 2 to 3 gigabits, which I'm very happy
about.
If you want to submit something for this, the pod finder or the pod show in series, it's
submit at podshow.com.
Same goes for your pod, save music, pod, save a pod show.com, and of course, you can always
go to the pod, save music, network at music.podshow.com.
So by now, you definitely know where to go for this show, triple ride.
DailySourceCode.com for the podcast feed and for the archives in the latest show.
If you want to find out more about cool indiepodcast, it's indiepodder.org or podcastallie.com.
That's where the community hangs out and talks about all kinds of stuff.
And I just heard they're going to stop bitching about people right about indiepodcasts.
Alright, everybody, I'll be talking to you either late tomorrow or Thursday, thank you
very much for listening.
Stay subscribed, take care now.
Another pod show podcast, stick it in your ear.