Hey everybody how you doing this is Adam coming to you from San Diego, California
Hold on a second I was just checking out the Rockin' World Beach show here hold on
There we go
I figured I'd do a little update podcast from the road more for my girls Patricia and Christina
We're at home then for for anybody else
Because I kind of ruined their weekend. Here's the deal
Ron Blumen I was supposed to meet with a whole bunch of people in San Francisco Monday and Tuesday
and then go off to
Los Angeles Tuesday evening or even Wednesday I think and then
We had one meeting scheduled for Wednesday and then fly back from Los Angeles
Let's move some of the shit out of the way here and then fly back
I would fly back straight from Los Angeles to to London and
Then I got a couple of calls actually
Thursday
Saying hey, you know, there's this conference in San Diego
It's the
Wall Street Journal
Was it everything digital conference
And
There's a whole bunch of interesting people here
And a couple of them
I said well, you know if you're up in this in these neck of the woods once you or actually up once you come down to
San Diego and
We'll chat for a bit so
That's happening tomorrow Sunday you're probably hearing this Sunday actually it's Saturday night
It is
10 after nine
Local time. I got this great new watch from Patricia
I really love it. She gave it to me last week
It's it has three times on a three three clocks basically there's a main clock
Which I still have set to London time so it's 10 past five in the morning
Then I have two smaller
dials
At the bottom left hand one of course I have left coast
Which is west coast and the right-hand one is the east coast so it's 10 after midnight in
Well, basically New York or Florida wherever you may be on the east coast and
wrong was coming in from
From Miami
So he had a whole bunch of different flights. There's no direct connection by the way from will London to
San Diego
We changed planes somewhere or you can go to Los Angeles and drive. There's probably about
100 miles or so
So I decided to take a
United what is it sky west or whatever you know a small commuter play? I love those little planes
You know the width of propellers
Which basically has like 11 rows. I love those
You can't put me in enough of those
I really like it
So I've been here for about an hour how to quick shower just to freshen up because man that was a long traveling day
Basically pissed away the whole side of a traveling and it's it's a bummer because
Usually weekends are pretty holy for us
Back at the cottage and we all you know like to chill out hang out do stuff, you know do some shopping together or whatever
And so that just wasn't possible. So what I figured I'd do is just take you outside for a second. I have a
Ground floor room. This is the kind of like a little terrace
And I walked through the
To the brush here and
And I'm right by the pool
It's almost a completely full moon. It's beautiful actually
I'll just have the quick walk around the premises with you
So I'm using the
The stereo lapel microphone which doesn't have the great dynamics that I usually like from the wireless transmitter
But it's so easy to set it up. Oh, what's that a rabbit? It's a rabbit right here on the path
He's sitting there in the light
This too bad you can't hear the rabbit because rabbits don't really make noise
That was a baby rabbit hey
He's pretty there he goes he's off
Someone's uh
Cleaning up pool area
The rabbit is still there and just move a few feet
Oh, such a petite cutie hey
Oh, there he's gone
hiding in the brush
So I'm walking towards the back of this is the I should have mentioned this this is the
Four seasons resort
Which
It's very chic
Man there's nobody outside see what I have a view of here
Quite sure what water that is I can see cars and some hills on the other side
It's kind of nice
Let's walk around the other side and I'm safe distance from my room
Don't have to tell you what that is
By the way
Once again
Showed up at the airport eat ticket one way get that four S stamp on your ticket man. That just
That really that sucks
They really pulled me apart again, but they didn't even find my lighter
Which of course is contraband these days? You can't travel with a lighter on US flights
So how good did they search?
Listen to that
Crickets road noise all kinds of stuff
So anyway, so
Just gonna stay overnight here. I guess I'll wait until Ron comes in I probably don't think he lands until even quarter to ten
So probably get a quick bite to eat and we'll catch you up haven't seen each other for a couple of weeks
Although we talk almost daily on Skype with everyone else who's working hard on
Getting stuff up and running for pod show
That's not the same CO burplates in gentlemen. That's just a regular old my god. I've been traveling all day
Oh, he's a road that goes down. Let's uh oh
Actually this is a complete road
Wow
I wonder what's down here
Not much just some nice night sounds that I've been to San Diego. It's beautiful
Although it kind of feels like you're on the edge of the world about to fall off
I don't know if this is what I want to do
Because this going down is really steep
Which means that
inevitably I'll have to walk the steep bit up the hill
Fuck that I'm going back up
Okay, so
There's lots of
Interesting people who were here. I don't even think they're here. They're probably showed tomorrow
I don't think this conference even really kicks off until tomorrow. We're not gonna stay for the conference
I think it's held by a guy called Walton Mossberg
Who is the technology writer for the Wall Street Journal and this and he's accredited as
Like the most powerful man and the universe when it comes to
Technology
Reporting I think I've seen some of this stuff on
About podcasting maybe I don't I mean I recognize the name
But I think that
There was a time probably in Silicon Valley when
Guys like Mossberg really were really powerful until of course the internet gave us so many different ways to find
News information software et cetera
And I think it costs three and a half thousand dollars per person right
I don't think so
It's a beautiful hotel. It's really it's a resort more than a hotel and can see that there's
Wow big sweet down here. That's beautiful
It's really nice rooms
Great art on the wall
But it's pretty dead. Let me see. Oh, that's nine
What is it nine 15
Maybe everyone's eating or inside or whatever
The Wi-Fi is also a little funky here. It doesn't really work in the room you have to step outside
So it only works. Maybe that's just the ground floor or maybe it's just my room in particular or it doesn't work
So I'll have to put this on
On the 17 inch power book
Compress it get it ready and then walk outside to actually upload it and do all the
All the entries for the weblog
I guess we could technically call this a daily source code
It'll be show number 181 and we've done exactly
Let me see how many minutes
Oh perfect 10 minutes just a short little update and then tomorrow I can give you more I'm
Actually was considering doing a strategy cast with Ron while we're out here
That may have to wait until LA if we even have enough energy to do it
That travel and it really takes it out of you know, I basically traveled for
I don't know door to door
18 hours something like that you can tell now about the acoustics that I'm back in the terrace part
And through the sliding door back into my luxurious room
So that's it. That's what I'm up to
I'll be checking in from the road. I'll bring you a full source code on Monday of course
Which I may do Sunday night or I may do Monday afternoon west coast time probably trying to do with Sunday night
From so tomorrow night
We go to
San Francisco, which of course you can't get there from here directly, right?
So I think that's why I'm the Las Vegas for some stupid shit like that
Anyway, quick 10 minute podcast
y'all have a great weekend and I'll be updating you tomorrow
Hopefully with the some information or some interesting news about some of the people in that here so take care