Actually, I got a message for all you old school radio cats out there who are going, what the hell
is this?
You see, this ain't clear channel robot radio, spineless, big looking like a motherfuckin
sanitized, no guts, no glory, edgedless boring my ass off, pathetic copycat, pastie butt
think you're so hot shit, pantyweight shitty same shukira song playing, Ryan C. Christ
hosted Coldplay Worshping M&M mixed into an all-rock format YouTube-flating Lincoln Park
and Limp Bizkit-Poser angry douchebag playing, your trash want to be trend-following
solace, rush-lim-boss indicating Howard Stern canceling, fucked-tard encouraging lowest
common denominator, sonic shit spewing waste to the airwaves that ever pissed off the broadcast
equivalent of a moldy white bread shit sandwich with pale advertising dollars for
lettuce that you'll force feed down the mouth of every hick, local, and hayseed that
lives in cowfuck town USA where you own every fucking radio station in the region so that
you can continue to shove your tongue up the ass of whatever bullshit right wing candidate
is running for Senate, Congress or dog catcher who give you more licenses so you can spread
your cancerous disease field, pussin-crusted, mucus-dripping, scab, jambalaya that you
call your fucking programming, so welcome to the future everybody, welcome to podcasting
music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music
music music music music music
music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music rooftop music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music
I don't care what anyone thinks about me
I'm not afraid of what you say or do it doesn't hurt me
Then you say I'm going to be doing all well and feeling like I should
I'm really, really glad I'm really, really, really happy and I'm really good
I'm really, really glad I'm really, really, really happy and I'm really, really, really happy
I'm really, really, really happy just like me
Hey everybody, how you doing is the Daily Source Code episode number 300 and I have absolutely nothing planned for the today
For tonight's episode the only thing I could really come up with was just the opening
Last night as I was snuggled up in my bed here in the condo
I flipped on Pacific Coast Hellway episode 142 and I heard that rant
And I almost couldn't sleep after it
More particularly because Mark Yoshimura Namcoff was up at the office today
He came up from California from Los Angeles
The land of Hollywood, he came up to Valleywood and I actually told him I said man, that's the best rant I've heard in a long, long time
Probably the best show I've ever heard from Pacific Coast Hellway
That's a perfect way to kick off today's celebratory episode
What is 300 really?
Isn't that like a cardboard celebration or does that fall under aluminium foil?
Oh, did you hear that? I said aluminium foil and not aluminum
That's the UK rubbing off on me
Yeah, so of course the muffs with a very, very happy because I am happy even though I'm dead tired
I can't tell you
So just one more night here in the condo
Then I'm back home, back with the girls, we're going to celebrate the holidays
And I probably won't be back until the end of the first or the second week of January
So I'll be back on a different time schedule
I'm just tripping out over the jet lag this time
It didn't work out very well
So today, lots of stuff to talk about
Even though nothing specific to 300 episodes
Maybe we'll celebrate the 500th episode
It'll be what maybe 7 months from now
So let's say July, maybe August, something like that
And that'll be something we can really, we'll put on a show
I don't know, we'll do something cool for the 500th anniversary of the daily source code
So for today, we're just going to crank out through a couple of things
One thing that I've really been enjoying recently
is listeners sending me or fans basically
Send me links to bands pages on the Podsake Music Network
Please do that more often
I mean, you know what I like, you know, as listeners, you're hearing the songs
You may be skipping past songs, you may think I'm totally misguided
But feel free to send me a link to something that you think is really, really good
Because I'm constantly looking from music
And by now, there's so many tracks in the Podsake Music Network
I go in and I look at what's been submitted during the day
That's sometimes 50 tracks, you know
So there's no time to really listen to everything
So as you know, I hunt around and listen to other podcasters
But I'd love to hear from you guys what if you have anything
I see lots of people are telling me that they're bringing friends into the networks
Hey, you know, you should put your stuff on the Podsake Music Network
And send me a link and if I don't play it, you know, don't get all pissed off for anything
I still got to kind of like it myself, I guess
Otherwise it might as well go work for the man, you know
Lots of feedback as well about the story I told about the motorcycle accident that I had
I guess I don't know why so many people are surprised that I used to ride
Or like this email from Eric Lickness
Man, the story about the motorcross
Wow, how did you ever not kill yourself?
I've given more respect for you than I had before
Oh helicopter's fixed wing and MX
That's sense for motorcross, my God
No wonder you were also into cars for a while
You love fast things and I've ever figured you for a gear head
But it all makes sense, the interesting technology in horse power
It's all part of a continuum
Well, you know what the fast stuff
I'm not really always been into fast cars
I've had...
That's actually Patricia's been into fast cars
She had a Porsche 911, that was nice
I drove that for a while, but it wasn't, you know, a 911
A late 80s 911 is when we had it
It late 80s early 90s
And it had manuals, stick shift
And that thing was like shifting a truck
I've had, you know, a Ford Explorer
I had a Rolls Royce, that was nice for a while
I drove it into New York City every single day
It was like having a force field around you
She guys, they used to have those back in the day
You come out of Lincoln Tunnel
Coming in from Jersey and they'd be squeegee guys
And they immediately just start putting their dirty ass nasty water
And squeegee it off for your windshield
And then they'd stand there and wait for you to give them a buck
So, and most commuters into New York
Wouldn't want, you know, nothing to do with it
And, you know, they'd honk or they'd turn on the windshield
Wipers to indicate, please don't touch my car
And I wouldn't even have to do that
These guys would look at me and they'd say
Oh, my brother, I wouldn't touch the car
But why don't you give me a dollar for the thought
Which, of course, I gladly did
Fantastic, the force field of the Rolls
That was nice
Good times, good times
And so, yeah, the Audi wasn't the A8
Studio A8 actually
That wasn't for the speed of it
But it was just a very safe car
I had to do a lot of traveling
It was just the right car at the time
I like to get things that are right for the mission
You know, right now, the Charlie 1802RG, the Sessna
It's the perfect plane for the mission
I don't need anything else, you know, yeah
I could get twin engines and get my rating for that
You can get jets, you can do whatever you want
But, you know, I like getting the right machine for the mission
And, clearly, the motorcycle accident
Was the wrong machine for the mission
And for my experience
Some exciting news from Google
If now launched the Google Music Search
Which I checked out
And it works great
What a fantastic way to drive music sales
Now, here's where our investors, our Silicon Valley investors
Investors are just fantastic to have
I fired off a note to one of our board of director members
Now, as you know, we have pretty much the same team
That invested initially in Google
And I fired off a note, I said, you know, wow
This is perfect, we need to get the pot safe music network index
And, you know, when people go searching from music
They'll be able to find it and go straight to the websites
Into the PMN sites and so now I've got to hook up with in Google
And I'm going to be working on it
I don't see why they wouldn't do it
Our board member, Ram seemed really excited
He thought it was a great idea
So, wow, just think of all the more exposure
We can get for pots to be made
And I hope that I don't see why they wouldn't do it
Our board member, Ram seemed really excited
He thought it was a great idea
Wow, just think of all the more exposure
We can get for pot safe music
And how easy it'll be for people to find it
If you hear of a name or if you hear something
You can just go into Google Music Search and find it
And it'll have all the music there
And all the information categorize
I guess they take a
Some kind of, it's probably an XML feed
Or some way to store it into their database
It's definitely structured data
So, whatever they want, we will obviously make that available
That's going to be extremely cool
Daily source code, episode number 300
It seems almost like yesterday doesn't it?
This is the moment where I actually go into it
I should play some old clips
I should have played episode number one
Yeah, yeah, Karamba
You're a producer for this show, man
Hey, Adam, it's Derek Miller from the Penn Machine podcast
at podcast.penmachine.com again
I wanted to congratulate Slaw on getting
If every day we're Christmas into that
Westwood one radio network
And WR radio in New York
And we managed to get it on CBC here in Canada too
One thing I want to bring up is
I'm not sure if you've noticed this new
Google Music Search service
You can go to it at google.com
Slash Music Search
Interesting thing about it is you can search for artists
And if you search for an artist in Google
It pops up with music results at the top
You can go see albums and lyrics
Interestingly enough, even those lyric sites
The R.I.W.A. is going after
But I did notice that it doesn't consider
Podsake music at all
If you look for a brother, a lot of you will find
Brother Love in the iTunes Music Store
But you won't find his Podsake music network listings
He won't find Slaw, he won't find anybody else
His Podsake
So maybe we better get on Google about that
What do you say?
I think so
I'm looking forward to show number 300
Right
So if I want a radio station at this very moment
The phone which would be to the right
Left of me would have a little red button on it
A special line it would be blinking
And that's called the hot line
I would pick that up during a record
And it would be the program director
Basically the boss saying
You know I'm at curry curry man
You fucking idiot man
You screwed up the bit man
You're supposed to play the feedback first
And then talk about the Google Investor thing
Shmuck
But then of course it'd be on the radio
Okay, Derek you totally motivated me
So I'm done
I immediately acted upon it
I mean how cool is that
The Google Music Search comes out
I get a feedback about it
I fire off an email to
One of the original Google Investor
In fact, Ram was
You know pre venture capital bun
He was like an angel investor man
And
Immediately there's a connection
That is true power
All right everybody
Feel free to sing along
You're gonna be here in this tune
A lot in the future
I don't see
Has fallen for
Trinity
A car with her
If you'll be in style
If you take her out
On the miracle mile
Her stunning sexy yellow you
A handcrank son
Move one of you
An extra cylinder
Can give you likely one
Point two five times
Feel like it's in
Yeah
Trinity
A quintessential luxury
Oh
Trinity
By a diesel industry
She could talk
You hear her thank
Adam for pooping in her tank
Oh
Trinity
It's so good
Everybody
So that's almost perfect
Jeffrey Smith
Thank you very much
I love the Trinity theme song
That of course
Will for the foreseeable future
Mark a small discussion
About biodiesel the bio industry
biodiesel industry
About Trinity my biodiesel beast
I'm so excited about everything that I'm learning about this
What I really need though Jeff if you have some time
I need kind of like a donut
We could have the the first half of the Trinity song
And then just a whole bunch of
Do you do you know maybe in the background
Trinity
And then it would end up with a big finish
You know I could do the whole
The whole item the whole biodiesel item in the show
Could be completely packaged
It would be just beautiful
It could almost be a podcast within a podcast
Quick couple of bits of feedback
From the Gmail bin from Michael Rubin
I already see this received this off from Steve way
But I haven't heard back from Steve
Maybe maybe the email got lost somewhere
But I'm sure he's working on some audio feedback
He says
Oh not Steve but Michael Rubin
Says that he's a sales area
Eris sales manager for a national auto glass repair
And replacement company
He listens to the source code
Fan of podcasting working on his own podcast actually
I guess he oversees 300 offices
So he's a pretty busy guy
But he feels that a podcast for those 300 offices
would keep all the offices connected
And he would like to do that on a business
A level which is great
He's in St. Augustine, Florida
Let's see
One of the classes that I teach is about windshield repair
Our company repairs over 10,000 windshields
Every week saving them insurance companies
Saving insurance companies millions of dollars
Versus the cost of replacing them
I would be happy to have our company to send out a rep
Who does the same for our company
To help you to explain the process and perform a demonstration for your
Intrinity
Wow that's a great offer
It's not really anything that has to do with the bio diesel industry
He can per se
But he does have a pretty cool information
And you know what
Let me see if Steve is able to come up in a couple of weeks
And if not a gladly take up on that offer
Because we have to start
Painted the bitch out
You know
We've got to represent for the bio diesel industry
Email here from Peter Jardos
I guess that is
Some finding Trinity, she sounds awesome
You mentioned though
That she had the necessary conversion to bio diesel
I was under the impression that ordinary diesel engines would run
Bio diesel with no conversion necessary
Do you know exactly what the previous owner did to convert her
Do you know if was actually necessary or just makes her run better
Very interested in bio diesel
Wonder if there's a bio diesel podcast
I don't think I think there are
Podcasts that certainly deal with bio diesel
I would be pretty gay
To participate
I don't have time to produce it
And we don't quite have our production company all set up yet
But there would just be fun to participate in it
One way or the other
Maybe I could donate my Trinity segment to a bio diesel podcast
You know I really don't know
Now I'm confused
It was sold to me with a bio diesel conversion on it
I'm pretty sure it's not
A heating element that allows you to pour in
SVO or straight vegetable oil
And in fact I really don't understand
anymore I'm so confused but
I have three quarters of a tank left
So we'll have to wait until the second week of January
When I'm back and then of course we'll go out
We'll do a sound seeing tour of the Berkeley bio diesel
Oasis and we'll learn
We'll learn you know basically straight from the closest source I have
And finally email from Andy
About time you got a diesel car dude
If you're interested in running full synthetic oil in the diesel
Which will last you a whole year
Please check out my website
With with an oil
Whisky India Sierra Yankee November Oscar India Lima dot com
Be interested in the best synthetic oil in filters
Is that a bio diesel thing or is that just
I guess if it's synthetic oil then I guess it's
Stuff that makes you makes us all less dependent upon the petrochemical industry
Is that what it's called?
This petrochemical industry I think it is
And that's again
That's what I'm in for
I mean look at all the opportunities we have
We could make our automobiles run on something other than gasoline
Or should I say petrol to be completely proper
So we had one theme song and you know it's not just one
The the goodness keeps on coming
Maybe there is something cool about episode number 300
Are you tired of going into shape in the morning?
Only define that you're endlessly scraping your face with three
And four blade razors that just don't measure up
Well more is better
So it's time for you to discover
Gigashay
Gigashay is a revolutionary new shaving system from Zcast Labs
The Gigashay system incorporates over a million tiny blades
That all act in unison to give you a close smooth shave
That's more than one blade for every hair on your face
Gigashay
The patent the Gigashay system was developed at Zcast Labs
To ensure that all the stubble on your face could be removed
In one swift motion
Ah
As well as sometimes other flashy o-cropping such as noses and lips
But your chin will be as smooth as a baby's bottom
So I use over a hundred strokes to shave in the morning
When you could do it in just one
With the revolutionary new
Gigashay
Gigashay should be used only on the face
People who are distraught from a recent break-ups should not use this product
As it could cause bleeding from the wrists or jugular
Keep safely out of the reach of fuzzy-lipped adolescents
No babies were harmed in the making of this ad
Gigashay is a registered trademark of Zcast Labs
Void wear prohibited by law
Oh common sense
So I've been setting aside portions of this daily source code podcast
For us men to discuss shaving
And for no particular reason other than I'm just kind of interested
It's something we all do and we really ever talk about it
It's not like we're hanging out at the water cooler and say hey
Hey Ron dude, what you're using these days to shave your face
Something guys just don't do
The women talk about the different shivers
If you shave your legs or other other parts of your body
I'm a big fan of of nair and beat by the way for all that stuff
But for the face I don't like burn in my face
So Jonas Nielsen said out of my took your advice
And bought the Wilkinson four blade to change for my mock three
What an amazing change
The difference is incredible
I for one advise everyone shaving with the mock three to try the Wilkinson four and see for themselves
By the way West Coast customs is a shop that does the pay my ride for MTV
I'm sure that's where they told you to go for the for Trinity
Absolutely
So I've really been you know paying attention to all this feedback that's coming in
Some people really like this M3 the mock three razor with the with the like a vibrator in it
That's I've seen it on sale at our local Sainsbury's which is our
Supermarket nearby
I'll make sure that I get one to test it out
I really am still digging the Wilkinson four blade though
It's yeah, it gives a really nice close shave
So let me know I know that sounds incredibly lame
But again, I never get an opportunity to talk to other men at all about our shaving experience
By the way, I'll I use Gillette the Gillette gel shaving cream the foamy stuff
And I use a
I use a beaver hair brush
Beaver hair brush to put the shaving cream on my face
And let me tell you there's nothing
Like nice bristly beaver hair on your face first thing in the morning
Yes indeed
Hey those of you listening to the show on serious stars 103
This show is about to end at least the put this portion for you because our satellite window is closing up
Oh, man, Pete up sent me the lineup so I could sound freaking intelligent about what's coming up
Hold up, let me just go to my Gmail real quick
So
Oh, man
After this show it is specific coast hellway
By the same guys that you heard opening up episode number 300 of the daily source code
Followed by
Magic Weinstein with yeast radio for now. These are all podcasts and you can find more information about them at podshow.com
And here we go, view is HTML
I've got the rest of the lineup right here
I know the Don and Drew come after Madge Weinstein
And it being Friday
Let's see Don and Drew followed by Steve Gillmore's attention tech after that
Which at all rather third with an extended five minutes with which at all and that will be followed by CC
Chap and I presume it's either going to be answered hash or the you turn cafe
So stay tuned for all of that right here on serious satellite stars 103
And for the rest of you the podcast continues
This is where we're going to talk a little bit. Remember I talked to you about format changes
How on the source code
Definitely want to do some of the more podcasting podcast community related stuff after the satellite window closes
So we kind of have a good mix of letting people know about you know just what we can do with podcasts
And also we can talk amongst ourselves once in a while in a little private area
So everyone listening to this podcast right now
Please raise your right hand
And wave goodbye to all our satellite listeners
Okay, there we go
So Google launched I don't know if it was recent but someone sent me a link today
A Michael Shono Michael sent me that actually
Google now has a mobile version of Gmail
And you get to it by going to m.gmail.com
Not bad actually
You know that I'm a big fan of the blackberry
Particularly because of the push email now using the blackberry browser
It was a pretty nice experience to be able to go to
My Gmail account, but there's one thing that's missing from it
You can't add labels and that's a really so being able to search the email is important
But being able to add a label is it's it's how I organize my thought my shit and my shit my thoughts and my shit
Hold on, you might as well finish rolling it now that you're on to me
So that's unfortunate, I've been really, you know, the more I think about it
I know it's not a trivial thing because the blackberry email service is kind of a close box
And you can forward email to it, but you know with the blackberry with this push email
The beauty is when you can actually you delete something on a device
And then it also deletes in your email accounts
So what I'd love to have and I don't know if Gmail and Google can hook that up with the blackberry folks
I mean it seems like we're both of them
If I could, you know, essentially
When I delete something in my blackberry or if I could label something in my blackberry
That that would synchronize up to my Gmail account
I know it's a lot to ask for but that would, you know
I wouldn't need any presence for Christmas for years and years and years to come
If I could get that little feature implemented
Hey Adam, this is Glenn Garnes and I was hoping that you'd do a promo of my new podcast
Addicted to Eggnog
Of course I'm kidding, but probably would make a good subject for somebody's podcast
Listen, actually the reason that I'm sending you this message is that I did want to talk about Eggnog for a minute
I've been addicted to Eggnog for years now, I absolutely love it
And I guess the bottom line is that I consider myself to be somewhat of a kind of sewer of Eggnog
I've had it from a variety of different sources including homemade and some store-bought stuff that's actually better than some other places
But I wanted to specifically tell you that if you can get your hands on a product that's made by rich foods
It's called Colonial Custer
This is an Eggnog that's just like drinking a milkshake
And so it's perfect if you're going to mix it with something because by the time you get something else mixed with it
It's just about the consistency that it should be
But if you drink it straight with nothing in it, it's like drinking a milkshake and Eggnog milkshake of course
So check out your grocery stores out there, see if you can find some
I got a case in the refrigerator right now that should last me through new years
So check it out, let me know what you think
I can be reached at www.webradioUSA.com
www.webradioUSA.com
And also my email address is Glenn 2Ns and Glenn at Glenn Garns.
G-A-R-N-E-S.com
I hope you have a great holiday, I'll be tuning in to the Daily Source Code as I do every day
Talk to you later
Do you believe anything is possible?
We do.
Where are flink?
We believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers.
We're Earthlink.
We believe your personal information should be just that, personal
And we believe your internet should be a friend, not a fo.
We're Earthlink.
Make this smart choice, visit earthlink.net
And discover what our internet experts can do for you, Earthlink.
We revolve around you.
I want to thank you all for coming out and celebrating with me and for all of you listening and home
that have been such a huge part of the success of the Zadecast of the last 100 episodes.
Wow!
I...
What I really wanted to say to you all tonight was...
Well...
I have a confession to make.
This is not my 100th show.
It's not even my 50th show.
In fact, it's only my 18th show.
Yeah, and the first one was a test, so it's really only my 17th official show.
I'll come on guys, I mean, all the great podcasts I was listening to were celebrating
their 100th show and their 50th show and, you know, Adam Curry, he's about to celebrate
his 300th show.
Wow!
Yeah, I know.
And see, I just didn't want to be left that far behind.
Oh!
Well, thank you all for being so understanding, and I know you're all just people on a
special effects loop, but feel free to stick around and enjoy the virtual champagne.
But while you do, raise a glass and celebrate with Adam Curry on the occasion of his 300th
Daily Source Gold.
Congratulations, Adam.
Merry Christmas.
Have a happy new year, and here's to 2006, the year of the podcast.
Yo, Bruce.
Thanks, my brother.
Thank you very much for your contributions.
Thanks for remembering Bruce Cessent and those two bits that you heard on the show.
That's very nice, dude.
Oh, my goodness, my God, father down.
Oh, I went down the wrong tube, man, so sorry about that.
Oh, my goodness, I have to catch my breath for a second.
More on the blank media attack, so we've been talking about, and I just kind of threw
that out there, and you'll see what would come back, and got some interesting comments.
Eric Abelson, just a quick question to pose, where do audiobooks fall on the scheme of things
according to the RIA and ASCAP?
It would seem that audiobook producers would be affected by piracy as defined by the RIA,
as well.
As far as I can tell, the only difference would be that they aren't broadcast on the radio,
and I have audiobook producers who are profiting from the levee, I don't see how podcasts
could be excluded as well.
The only difference would be that audiobooks and music publishing materialists for
sale-to-find prices.
Now, the theory behind the levee is that it's supposed to be used to offset revenue
loss, so it would be tough to justify podcasts, as revenue loss since the podcasts are offered
freely.
Hmm, that's interesting.
Well, maybe if we find out more about exactly how that levee works and how the money
is distributed, then maybe there's something there.
I mean, it's not that I'm like, the whole, let's go chase after that money, it's just
interesting.
It's interesting to me how things change, I think, as situations change, rules should
change, or at least should be looked at.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Fred Rico Avers is from the Netherlands.
He says something interesting here in the Netherlands as an organization called Stichting
on the Hondling at Taiskupi for hooting it, better known as the SONT, the Sont.
That's basically the home tape, rock against the home taping motherfuckers.
The lobbying to tax MP3 players up to 25 euros, which is, what is that now these days
about?
27 bucks.
Minister of Parliament, we obviously said it would be useless to introduce taxes and MP3
players as they can be easily obtained in a neighboring country where players aren't
taxed.
Another comment that Fred Rico heard, heard from somebody from a consumer protection
organization, it would be unfair because people buying music online, i.e. with iTunes, would
be doubly taxed because Sont downloads already have a tax on them that go to the record
companies and the artists.
All right.
Okay.
Interesting.
Just continue to keep all right.
It's not a big deal.
You know, it's not bust anyones balls over it.
Here's something that I thought was very cool.
The BBC is starting to understand podcasting more and more, and I'm subscribed to a couple
of the BBC podcast, most notably in business, which I don't think I've received a new
one a long time.
Maybe they're in hiatus or something.
The BBC really is a public broadcaster, and although you can't make all people happy
all the time, I would have to say that they're doing a fine job, and BBC radio one, it's
just kind of like the popular, you know, the pop station, top 40 station.
One of the air towns there is Chris Moils, and he puts together a podcast of all the
best bits of his show of the week.
But it's not just like, you know, music stripped out and here's a bunch of bits.
It's produced.
His crew, I have to admit I haven't listened to a show, but I shall do so now.
I mean, you know, I can't receive it.
I might as well check it out, and I'm definitely subscribed to the podcast just to get
a taste of it.
He really puts it together, you know, and there's a beginning and end, and there's this
banter in between, and it's really something that's being produced in addition to the
radio show.
And I totally appreciate what's going on, and it was pointed out to me that he gave me
a little shout out.
Anybody that you'd like to load to?
Well, we do this podcast.
Do you actually Chris?
Really?
Hi, Chris.
Hi.
It's a bit wasted time.
I'd like to add him curry.
Oh, and my flatmate Mitch.
Yo, and Chris.
Howdy back at you, my brother.
And know that you are more than welcome in the podcast community.
And we'd love to hear some of the, you know, some of your ideas and some of your stuff,
the absolutely can't do for the BBC.
It may be you, you might even want to consider doing it under an assumed name, but, you
got some funny bits on there, but let's hear it without any restrictions.
It would not be nice.
It looks like the slap cast went dark today.
I'm not quite sure if it was a bandwidth issue or if it was a DNS issue, but I got a whole
bunch of frantic emails from Trucker Tom and from Michael Dell.
He says, Adam, any chance the pod show, pod cast delivery network is going to be open
real soon.
As you might have heard from others, such as Trucker Lou, Trucker Tom, and a few more slap
cast.com is down.
They were a podcast host.
Looks from the who is data that the guy, Roger Strickland, didn't pay his domain fee
in time and the registrar put their squat page on there.
I guess we're all fucked up and Trucker Tom had noticed the same thing.
And indeed, to me, looking at the dates, it may just be a domain, name, renewal thing.
But also Trucker Tom, in his email, shared some of his data transfer with me.
And I happen to know, pretty much what the prices are for that.
And I'm thinking of myself, man, if I think they had like 17, we looked at the podcast
alley, Chris McIntyre, who was now in charge of the meltdown life raft project.
Immediately, checked in the database, sawed there about 17 pod cast, who were hosted through
slapcast.com.
And he's getting emails out to everybody, offering all of those pod casters, immediate
shelter, we're kind of breaking off the team from doing some other things, so they take
a day or two, but we're going to jump in anyone who needs help will definitely help
out no obligations whatsoever just to keep you going, because that really, really sucks.
Oh, man, this is the second time it's happened.
What was the other host, the soccer girl in corporate was on, they were like, I don't
know, a whole bunch of the queue potters.
So I have no idea how many people we brought in from over there, but let's hope we don't
see too much of this.
I think that there still is a gross underestimation of the cost of bandwidth, because
the stuff is not free.
And actually, Ron and I want to talk a lot more about what we're doing, about issues
in pod casting, about where we're going as a community, where we're going as an industry.
We call it a strategy cast, and we've done, I think, two or three before.
And we were planning on doing one either last night tonight or having something up over
the weekend.
And we had a meeting today and we talked about the format of the show and what we're
going to do, what we're going to discuss.
And also based upon some of the stuff I've seen written on pod cast, I was thinking, maybe
it would be interesting before we do the show for you to set you as podcasters who are
interested to send in your questions as audio comments.
Now send them into us, and then we can answer them to the best of our ability on the
next strategy cast, which we will then put together as soon as we feel that we have,
if the question starts to repeat themselves, then we'll know we'll be ready.
So that should only take a couple days, and I do have a travel day in there, but we're
very excited about sharing our strategy and our thoughts with podcasters who are interested.
And you can send off and check this out, a change now, feel free to send it to a
attach your audio comment to your email and send it to strategycast at podshow.com.
So questions that you have comments, anything you think that we contribute to a strategy
cast, but we can address a send it off once again to strategycast at podshow.com.
And I really appreciate it.
Finally today, an email from Greg Tan and Adam Howie-Doin, Andrew Darlow gave me your
info.
I met him and I met him and saw when we were all on the Joey Reynolds show.
Oh, of course, that's when when a slough got podsafe for peaceplayed.
So slough suggests that I drop you a note, I'm new to the podcasting thing, but I heard
about your show and took a listen, cool stuff, really love to have you hear my music
for consideration, and he put in a link to what he says, his brand spanking new podsafe
pages.
Well, dude, thank you very much.
Welcome to podcasting, welcome to the podsafe music community.
Like your tunes.
Trust me, I wouldn't play it if I, if I didn't mean it.
So this is from the CD Coney Island, Greg Tan, and this is It's You.
It's You.
Takes my breath away, they're all the things you've helped save, and that's that
it's your name to stay, it's you, it's you, darling it's you, dick Jack, now we'll be there,
take a tumble through space, and I'll see that I'll always care to have, I'll have
filled down and run it around, be led to the things I do, it's you, takes my breath away,
all the things you've helped save, and that's that's your name to stay, it's you, it's you,
darling it's you, take a plane, I will follow, drag my heart out on the solid, through the
clouds, through the rain, through the stars, and back again, every day, every night, for the darkness and the
light, and it fades so far, and it will, I'll be there, it's you, it's me, you, takes my breath away,
all the things you've helped save, and that's that's your name to stay, it's you, it's you,
darling it's you, darling it's you, darling it's you, darling it's you, darling it's you,
darling, it's you, it's you, you, it's you, it's you, it's you, it's you, it's you, you,
It's a year, it's a year it's a year, it's a year, it's a year it's a year it's a year, it's a year, it's a year, it's a year, it's a year, it's a year, it's a year.
Ain't that pretty song, it's you Greg Tanon, brand new, to thefaughtsave music network, paughtsavemusic network.com
music.podshow.com. And that is it for episode number 300 of the daily source code. I
thank all of you for listening. Thank you for staying subscribed. If you are subscribed and I
look forward to many, many hundreds more daily source codes because damn I'm having a lot of
fun doing this shit. Podshow. What would you do for a podshow?