And I'll just share it Charlie two, three, five, and good morning everybody.
If you're in the United States, hope you're enjoying your extended holiday weekend.
It is Monday.
Today is the fifth of September, 2005, and I am going to be leaving the cottage in just
about an hour and a half on my way to New York for a couple of days.
I'm taking the portable workstation with me, so I'll be able to bring you hopefully a
full-blown daily source code every single day, except for today, and today being
a holiday, I figured I'd do something a little bit different.
I am going to relinquish my feed and my time to something that is going to come to us
from the pod show headquarters in San Francisco, California.
We now switch over to Michael Butler.
I'm here with Ron Bloom, and what's the other person's name?
Brian Longus.
My name is Michael Butler.
Hey, Michael.
So what are we doing here right now?
Well, we're here at the offices, the entry offices of podshow.com, and when it started
a couple of weeks ago, it was an empty space, it's now full of very talented people.
And as we grow our company, we realize that podshow has some more needs and a couple
of areas, and we want to talk about it, so we're creating our first job cast.
Now, what's a job cast anyway?
So job cast is when Brian Longus, who's ahead of operations, starts to pull together,
a list of the kind of talent we're looking for over here, and we sort of support the links
that you would normally see on a website, on a website, you would see a typical company,
you would see something like job inquiries or employment opportunities, and we think that's
a little boring, actually we kind of think it sucks, and we're appealing to a different
type of person.
We want innovators, hustler, starters, dreamers, entrepreneurs, really motivated people,
and we're starting with some opportunities to round out our engineering side, and there,
we wanted to make sure we let these engineers know that over here, we think that they're
sort of the undredties and the superstars and the heroes of the whole podshow organization
along with those podcasters, and we want to make sure that the quality of engineering management
that we get are sort of driven and dedicated people.
That's number one.
Number two, if we were to go any farther, we wanted to talk about something because this
first job cast is coming out at a time of deep concern for a good part of the United
States as a result of Hurricane Katrina, and I know you're a Florida fella.
Yeah, you're from Florida, but we had hurricanes all the time.
Yeah, hurricane suck, and this one's such a really bad, and for for anyone who thinks that I
read something that people, a lot of people are not familiar with that coastline down there,
it's it's it's beautiful, incredible place full of warmhearted people, it's the birth
of music as we know at the United States and then fluency entire world, so we're supporting
giving of yourself and giving of your time, but also giving of your money, we thought
about putting up our own fund, but it's just too complicated.
So we're driving people to just go right to the redcross at redcross.org, we're going
to make a contribution as a company and individuals.
We have links on the websites, podcasts, there's a put you made a promo, didn't you?
Yeah, I made one last night, I knew a lot of people have, and just about why not
everyone, but a lot of podcasts are not putting banners on their site, and you can actually
make a donation through PayPal, I believe.
They probably great.
Anyway, you can do it, please do it.
If we can help you let us know if you're a podcaster, and you want to run somebody else's
promo send us an email, and maybe we can mix them and people can have a little more
excitement about it, but we sure support it, and please do a good deed and find your
way to the redcross.org or anyone else you think that you would rather support.
That city is like one of the greatest cities in the country too, and it's like pretty much
destroyed under water.
And from those of you who have lived through that in the economic times when you were economically
underwater, imagine your whole life just basically being flooded, and that's what's
happened to those people.
And there's every single one of them down there are brave, and they're going to require
all the help we can give them, so please reach down deep and help them.
All right, so that brought the job cast to a kind of a bummer section, but let's pick
it back up.
Okay, if you're an engineer, and if you're the engineer, and if you know how to create
the best programming, the best, you know, with the best and fun people in the world.
What kind of engineer are you talking about?
Audio engineer.
Right now we're focusing, I want to actually introduce you to Brian Logas, our director
of operations, Brian, how's your podcast coming, Brian?
I think pretty well.
What's the name of it?
We're working on it.
I'm thinking about it.
So you're a behind-the-scenes guy here at Podge.
Yeah, behind-the-scenes, engineering, operations, everything, and you are a CEO of your own
company prior to this, right?
Yep, not too long ago, about four years ago.
And as I recall, because I was down there, you had a big old offices in Washington, you
were having, you had all kinds of SQL servers, serving up all kinds of stuff, a couple
of million registered users, I think you had a couple million registered users.
Actually, we were number 157 on the web in terms of tracking.
That was with PC data online.
So you were, we had an incredible site when it came to traffic.
I mean, that was these cuffs, and now we're building it on the west coast.
So Brian's out here looking, he's really running the show of helping us find this great
talent.
What kind of people we're looking for?
Well, we've got our A team and we're looking to grow it.
So we're looking for software engineers and database engineers or all-com designers.
So let's say we had this A team, we're putting the band together.
Do we need, second stringers, do we need, like, lead guitar players, lead vocals?
Do we need front men?
Yeah, we need front men.
We need the rock stars.
We need rock stars.
Absolutely.
So what's a rock star in database programming to you?
What are those qualifications?
Someone that's worked in extremely high transactional volume.
We're talking about, you know, when it comes down to per second or per minute, the amount
of transactions is phenomenal.
Because this site, in what we do, we've got registrations, people who come, people who
register, and the hits to the database from one person every time they come could be phenomenal,
just on a per page basis.
And as we're ramping up, and we bring in millions of millions of people, it's going
to come down to optimization and being able to structure and design something now, so
it's ready for tomorrow.
So you want to guy, a little gal, guy for us is gender neutral.
You want a person who has built out a larger infrastructure, who understands, it'd be
a great, like what Michael said, who understands what an audio file is, you know, can
make a deal with audio.
It understands how important that is, and who can sort of make that connection of bits
and bytes and sort of get an understanding of it from the user perspective.
Absolutely.
So you need super senior and middle-level people, the UDS person who's run a team before
or a data person who develop inside with their own team and also knows how to work outside
the company and bring in health from outside.
Yeah, we're looking for a little bit of both.
So when we're looking for a senior engineer, senior architect, that's someone who's worked
with, for instance, any modeling language, like a UML, not only can they design it in architect,
but they can also assist with actually writing the code and doing some of the work, we expect
everyone to wear many hats, many hats.
Not just sitting a corner, they're involved in everything, and our staff here now, you
think it's a room for that kind of, you know, someone who really is a type A to come in
and make their mark on the company, absolutely, and it is a type A, it's really, this
is something that's going to grow with them and grow with us.
So it's positioned in an ability for someone to come in now, really make a difference.
And I would like to apply, except for, I don't really have any skill in that category
but the job sounds, maybe.
So how many people you're looking for anyway?
We're looking for definitely two, a senior system architect, designer, and someone that,
as Ron pointed out, some of them can also bring it outside talent if we need to.
It's a media company, not a technology company.
So we need core people that are going to be here and help build an architect for tomorrow.
And where is here?
I know where, but tell the audience to go.
So we just go and south of market, actually one hour temp offices now, and we're moving
within three, four or five weeks, I believe.
We got our space, we got our new space, we just got to fix it up, and we're
waiting, there's a, I don't know, what is it, a gazillion square foot office, we have
in mind for this person.
It's a gazillion close to a gazillion because they're big delivering multiple
big abides of information, as I understood it.
Yeah, big abides is what we're designing for.
Okay, so we got a gazillion, a gazillion square foot campus.
Nice, there are big screen televisions with videos playing all the time.
Wet bar.
Wet bar definitely a wet bar.
Very much.
So next, over there, you can see it to the left, next to the jacuzzi, sometimes
you miss it because they're lap pool, they'll chase lounge by the lap pool.
We have a skate park in the back there, if you bring your skateboards, bring your skateboard
to skate, sometimes there's some traffic, we lend it to the city of San Francisco.
So there probably are some programmers who are skaters, so maybe if they're, if they're
into skating, so if they live in New York, they'd have to relocate in San Francisco, obviously,
you guys.
We'd help them out.
If they're the right people, you know, here's what we discovered.
Also if you're really talented and you want to work with us outside of the city, that's
a different kind of job we'd love to hear from you.
But we found out that if you're in the same office, the same physical space, that's where
the green glow comes from, that's where you walk down the hall or in this case, you
just shout down the hall and you say, I've got an idea and someone else goes, I've got
an answer for that and the next thing you know, you've got a little groove thing going and
you're building stuff.
And we, in just six weeks, I mean, we've done some monumental accomplishments in technology,
we haven't even been able to release him yet.
And it's all coming from the synergy of people being in the same space.
So we're really focused on people who might want to be out here with us.
It's also really high energy and actually, to your point about relocating, we've got a
software engineer driving up here this weekend, packing up his youth home, he'll be here
Monday evening.
And not to mention, San Francisco is one of the most beautiful cities in the world, besides
New Orleans, San Francisco is probably in the top three tourists destination.
This is Kevin.
Probably, yeah.
And a fact that I can point my microphone, I think you can see it over, oh, yeah.
Nevermind.
It's a comedian, not only is he owned the company, it's a comedian as well.
All right.
No, it is an, and I relocated here just to just help it out, I'm curious, relocating here
Brian.
I relocated here from the youth.
And you brought with you a pretty large family, right?
I've got a big family, twin boys and a new one two months old.
So we're in Michael Butler, you haven't relocated to San Francisco, but you're going to be
relocating into our office, right, helping us build Pod Show.
Yeah, let's hope so.
That happens.
You get permission from the CEO of your organization.
Why?
Yeah, the wife has to give me permission.
And my CEO approved the move, so I understand how that works.
So we, and we've probably got five or six more people relocated, and we have a couple
of guys.
Like you said, one guy with the youth, I'll come and end them in the engineering side, we've
got another guy relocating from Virginia, and you San Francisco, I'd be heard.
You people down there and Silicon Valley come on up here and work for us because the
community is easy to sit back on the train and listen to your iPod and the next thing
you know, you're in the office.
And there's, as you can, as you know, by me, I have super long hairs.
If you, if you have feel like a long hair, a grateful dad or a rock and roll looking guy,
you're welcome to come in and have a job as well as long as you know how to program.
Man, would you just be good people?
That's right.
Hair and no hair.
Yeah.
Okay.
Right.
But it's a bit, no, be good people.
And we want to work as part of the team.
We have a lot of fun here.
We work.
I'd say we work really hard, but we have a lot of fun.
And we, we, the core people that help build the business.
They're the rock stars of our business.
And in engineering and programming, it's just as much reason to, to be respected for your contribution
as a, as a number one podcaster would be.
So there are all part of the family.
Everybody's voice counseling.
We're looking forward to finding some great folks.
So if you're interested, what do you do, Brian?
What do they do if they're interested?
We've got email address and send along the resume jobs at podshow.com.
That's not going to Steve Jobs though.
It's going directly to us.
So I should point out our environment.
We're a lamp environment.
Linux Apache MySQL PHP.
People with CC++ background.
That sort of thing.
Anyone who, not only has that skill set or can learn that skill set.
So, so I'd bet right now that someone will listen to this.
That is sitting somewhere that says, you know, I've been contributing where I am.
But there's people above me.
There's people beside me.
They, they have a destiny in this company.
Maybe my destiny someplace else.
I wanted someone who's done enough for the place where they're out and wants to move along.
And, uh, I hope they find the right person to find their way here.
And there's a lot of tech podcasters out there.
And I would say probably maybe half of them at least are probably programs, right?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Or no somebody.
And no somebody who fits this description.
And that will be ideal guy because he knows what podcasters is about.
And he's into podcasters.
And, yeah.
Which is why we have one of the famous podcasters and most famous ones in the whole
Dang business.
Michael Butler.
You know, you know.
Well, that's part of the fun of the environment.
You know, last week, C.C. Chapman was here.
C.C. Chapman took a break during the day and did his podcast.
Chris Rockwell took a break and used our sound studio.
The toilet.
Did his podcast.
So you've got people coming in and out Michael Butler's here today.
It's an interesting environment.
It's fun.
And that's what we're going to be doing.
We're going to be launching a, an online.
And we're going to be launching a,
an online.
Jobhunt advertising campaign created by some very strange people inside our own organization
and featuring a person from our engineering department,
whose name we will not reveal.
So you may be on the lookout for that.
And I think it's pretty dang interesting.
And it shows that we're, we're just not your ordinary cubicle.
Not at all.
Okay.
I think we wrap it up.
That's the end of job cast number one.
Do we have a theme song?
I'll find something off the page.
You did a job.
What does that mean?
I'll find something off the page safe music network and music.pidesure.com.
Plug, plug, plug, plug.
Thanks for a Michael.
Thanks so much for coming over and producing this for us.
And we hope we didn't worry about you too much.
No.
Thank you.
Okay.
Now, all right.
So, I hope that was,
even if you're not looking for a job in San Francisco,
that was interesting enough to listen to.
And another note, you can also go to podshow.com.
Obviously for, for the job openings,
but also you'll see that podshow.com slash relief has a page up
with public service announcements cut by podcasters,
by pod squad members.
You could upload your own.
And of course plenty of links to the red cross
to donate to the victims of Hurricane Katrina.
All right.
Now to hear, I'm stepping on my favorite virgin upper class
to Newyville, York.
I'll be there this afternoon,
so I'll be sure to have a podcast up for Tuesday morning
as I said, I'm taking the full gear,
still to be the first trial by fire of the digital audio
workstation and the new setup and taking everything on the road.
So, I'll see tomorrow.
Enjoy the rest of your holiday weekend, everybody.
Those of you that can, and we pray for the rest who can't.
Bye-bye.