Daily source code April 27, 2005.
Yo DJ, are you done?
Me too!
Your DJ has only just begun.
$16 billion worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Do you know me?
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky drinks, man.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Hey everybody, from the cottage in the UK, it's the Daily Source code.
And we're back on the air.
What a bunch of crap yesterday.
Oh my goodness.
I had completely underestimated the amount of bandwidth I would need.
When he switched from my dot mac hosting infrastructure to the pod show infrastructure.
But we've opened the floodgates.
So now we've got the bandwidth up and running.
Everyone's able to get the show.
Hopefully you're able to listen to yesterday's show.
I realize that what happens often in these cases is
some iPodders will either download half the file or
some portion of the file and then skip over it.
Or not download anything and skip over it.
So you may have lost yesterday's show.
Of course, encourage you to go immediately to
dailysourcecode.com and download it directly for that's up to you.
Today, more pod safe music, some promos and news about my upcoming trip.
Actually, when I say upcoming trip, the trip starts tonight.
Right now it is 11 o'clock in the curry cottage.
11 a.m. that is on Wednesday morning.
I leave tonight.
I think it's 815 or 830 when I hop on the big red virgin bird
and jet off to Nueva Yorka.
Two days of meetings, then the weekend.
And then we're going to kind of see if we can go out to the west coast or not.
I'm still trying to firm up those plans.
Figure this and some people wanted to see us.
It would be easier just to stay in the states and then do a Monday and Tuesday meeting.
But it doesn't happen, then I'll go back and I'll be back in a couple of weeks.
Hey, New York's where all the publishing money is.
That's where it's all coming from.
Oh, and of course tomorrow, we now have a firm commitment tomorrow.
Ron and I are going to do another strategy task because we're getting pretty close to some real announcements.
I know, I know I'm stringing young, but you know, we've been building up steam and getting everything set.
And you're seeing a bit by bit pieces are starting to happen.
Cast blaster now in beta.
Although not all of the beta invites have gone out.
Of course, if you've downloaded that application sent in your mixer statistics, your computers mixer.
Then you will be hearing about the beta test.
I think it could be up to a week.
We were just delugeed with email and one thing.
We were talking about blind people.
And oh, yes, we've had the conversation about the politically correct way to say it.
The politically impaired is that the blind community doesn't matter.
You know, you are.
And by the way, I'm getting there myself.
Dan, you know, without my glasses and it keeps getting just a little bit worse every single time I haven't checked.
I am completely visually impaired if I don't have my glasses.
So lots of feedback about many, and I talked about this yesterday.
Many, many different initiatives.
And of course, now there are lots of folks who would love to jump in and start reading newspapers
and magazines for the blind and podcasting that.
And there's all kinds of intellectual property issues there, obviously.
So I would of course encourage, you know, these types of publications to figure out a way to service
this rather large group of people who apparently are very interested.
But perhaps even more interesting is getting the visually impaired to podcast, helping them out with that.
And I was talking to Mike, one of the developers of the cast blaster.
And we're talking about, because apparently there are all kinds of hooks and stuff that you can put into
into your applications that hook into Windows accessibility, API or something like that.
Something I definitely have to delve into a little bit deeper.
And although we haven't done any of that in the cast blaster as of yet,
we do, of course, have Jan Palette, who does the hit test.
He's also a cast blaster, beta tester.
And he's giving us a lot of information on what we can do because he's visually impaired.
And, you know, I hope to make not just, you know, all applications I'm involved in,
but also websites, much more visually impaired friendly, VIF, if you will.
And today, a first on the Daily Source Code, I'm proud to present a paid commercial.
Now it's possible to get close to Paris Hilton, even without your passport.
Beginning April 29, tune into Paris Hilton's podcast and spend some time with Paris on account
down to the house of wax.
That's right, all Paris all the time.
To get the Paris Hilton podcast, go to www.houseofwexmovie.com
and click on the podcast link in the mountain.
It's the biggest season, but yeah.
Okay, the Paris Hilton podcast starts as she counts down to the house of wax.
That's the opening of the movie.
It's a remake, I guess.
The house of wax.
And, you know, despite the promo, which is very slick, very professional, like the singers.
I think you're going to see a pretty raw, well, we've seen several sides of Paris,
but I think you're going to see a very raw side, very unedited single voice of her.
Because that's one of the things that I talked to a lot of the folks over at Warner Brothers about
is they were thinking about doing this podcast or approaching Paris about doing it.
She jumped right on, she totally gets it.
And I hope that they won't be doing any post-editing of what she's doing,
but I know that she'll be walking around with a recorder.
I was supposed to interview her, and this has nothing to do with commercials or anything.
This was just a request we put in.
The interviewer about the podcast.
This was supposed to happen tomorrow.
She's on David Letterman.
I presume then tomorrow night.
And she's going to call me from the green room.
Now, since I'm going to be in New York,
of course, I said, well, why don't I try and do a sound seeing tour
from, you know, the, basically, the entrance of the building.
Oh, no, it's not Rockefeller Center, I'm sorry.
At the CBS Broadcast Plaza, that's what it is.
No, no, no, no, no, wrong again.
It's the Ed Sullivan Theatre, that's where it is.
And hopefully just do a one-on-one with Paris in the green room,
without having to deal with the telephone line.
And of course, I have it all set up, in case she doesn't want to,
but it's going to be kind of silly.
So I hope we get that worked out.
And we'll ask her, we'll ask her straight up,
what the plan is, and what she's going to do,
and how is she putting it together?
I think we could all be surprised by young Miss Paris.
So daily source code today, I want to celebrate
a great piece that aired on CBS,
Evening News yesterday.
This was the thing that I was interviewed for,
the piece that I was interviewed for in January,
if you can believe it.
Four months old, unbelievable,
actually almost five months old now, this footage.
And my hair has already been cut and grown back since then,
it's almost the same length.
And it was obviously much shorter than all of the stuff that I,
you know, put in there,
but what was really cool is Sharon O'Fancy,
and her producer, the lovely Linda,
who now, of course, I'm going to have to take out the dinner,
because she finally got this thing on the air,
and it's all of the Dan Rather controversy
and changing of hosts.
And I have no idea how, you know,
they must have had a couple minutes left over in the show,
and what the hell can we put?
Oh yeah, let's grab this thing off the shelf.
They really skewed it towards the music aspect,
and I'm really happy about that.
I put a link on Curried.com today,
so you can actually see a piece of the video,
or the whole piece that aired,
and they totally clued right into those serious bitties,
and how that worked when I first stumbled across their stuff,
I started playing it,
and other people started playing it,
Brian from Coverfield didn't interview with them,
and they started selling CDs,
because, you know,
they can sell them directly online,
they press their own CDs,
they've got their own little company that handles all of that,
and of course they all work for the company themselves,
but, you know, they've got all the elements they need,
and they're putting 90% to 95% of the revenue directly in their pocket,
so a couple hundred CDs sold,
and it's a big deal,
particularly if you're hungry in New York.
But it was great,
no pieces of interview with the bitties unfortunately,
but it was very clear,
and I hope that,
I hope that the people who need to know this kind of stuff
were paying attention,
and particularly that's the artist,
and I did get a lot of email from people saying,
okay, how do I do this?
How do I get into it?
That's part of what Ron and I will be talking about
in our strategy cast,
which will do Thursday.
It'll be about something we're calling
the Pods Safe Music Network,
and it's going to be extremely cool.
Right now to celebrate the bitties,
one of my favorite songs,
Hello of a boy,
on the Daily Source God.
It's not like,
he doesn't know just what to say,
to make you feel right,
stay up nights,
think of him all day,
where his song is true,
but his head key,
getting in the way.
No, it's not like,
he's got a nasty disposition,
wants to keep you locked up tight,
knock the bright,
barefoot in the kitchen,
he's a hell of a boy,
on the,
only half of a man.
No, it's not like,
the boys about it,
born on the wrong side of town,
under the wrong moon,
on the wrong day.
He's a hell of a boy,
but only half of a man.
Half of a man.
Just what do you think you will get,
if he persists thinking,
this is the best you can do,
say no to your life girl,
I'll be fine,
I'll know it,
your life's going to say no to you,
easy call,
life's too short,
to live it so,
now it's not like,
it's more than you can stand,
to have that pretty boy,
sitting next to you,
kissing you,
holding your hand.
He's a hell of a boy,
but only half of a man.
Oh man,
sometimes it's just close my eyes,
listen that song,
think oh yeah,
they're singing about me,
the Bitties.
Check them out on the show notes,
and go buy their CD,
will you?
The lascivious Bitties on your daily source code.
Working for someone else sucks, doesn't it?
It doesn't have to be that way,
that's right,
time to take control of your business life,
time to bust out of that cubicle.
I'm Jonathan Brown,
and I'm Matt Compton,
stop working for the man and start working for yourself,
listen to the cubicle scape pod,
visit www.cubicleacape.com,
that's www.cubicleacape.com.
Okay, yeah,
good podcast.
We'll help you escape,
working for the man.
Would it be great if we could all just sit around
and be podcasting all day,
working for ourselves,
and make enough money off of selling
Senseo,
coffee machines,
and promoting other people's podcasts?
Oh, wonderful world.
Hey, by the way,
the weather today sucks mega.
It's even worse than it was the past two days.
It just all of a sudden,
actually it was a little sunny this morning,
it's got overcast and cloudy.
Now it's raining,
not a nice day.
A nice day to travel though.
I always like to travel when it's raining,
you know,
because nothing else you can do,
but sit inside.
Ivan and Roxy,
my sister-in-law and my niece,
they'll be leaving today as well,
going back to Rotterdam,
where they live.
So Patricia and Christina
will be alone for the next couple days,
and they'll be catching up on
all the stuff that we've kind of left.
You know,
there's lots of hours of work to be done.
And we're trying to get Christina to do it all,
let me see.
What are the things I need to talk to you about today?
Hmm.
I haven't seen the entire magazine.
I saw the cover of one of the gossip magazines
in the Netherlands.
I'll put a link to it in the show notes,
so you can see it,
that remember the paparazzi was hanging out
in front of our house.
So I'm sure there's an in front of our house
picture or a house picture inside the magazine,
but they also got a shopping.
It's so funny.
It looks like they're shopping.
And we're walking down the high street in Guilford.
So they must have followed us,
which of course isn't that hard to do.
It's a pretty close-knit community,
close proximity really.
So what was the headline?
It's like Adam,
you know,
the prefay that's the name of this magazine
has found Adam and Patricia.
They've been hiding away in England.
Yes, we have.
We've been hiding from you,
Docs.
Didn't you realize that yet?
You're listening to the Johnny B.
Show podcasting.
In Minnesota.
It's the Johnny B.
Alright, Adam,
this is Johnny B.
And with me is Jason Gears,
part-time,
done so the Northwest Noise podcast with Tim Germer.
And I'm with the Johnny B.
Show,
and we're doing a live show at Burnsville High School in Minnesota,
where we recorded some drum lines.
Adam, we missed you.
And please come to Minnesota,
keep us both warm.
Thank you.
Yeah, that's great.
And I'll put in all the junkies stuff.
Okay.
No, I love it.
So go to JohnnyB.com and check out my shows.
They're new,
just starting kind of rough,
playing with mics,
interviewing people, friends, family.
Just having a good time with sounds,
and the whole podcast,
dilemma here in Minnesota.
So stay tuned.
That's J-O-H-N-E-E-B-E-E.
Right on.
Go ahead, Ben.
Play with sound.
Get some stuff going.
I hope we can get better recordings of the drum lines, though.
I love the drum cadence.
Haven't done that in a long time.
If you got a drum cadence,
one that we haven't played,
shoot it off to adamaccurry.com.
And if you have a promo,
you'd like to play.
And of course,
I can't play the mall.
I do have to make a selection based upon
ones that make me laugh,
smile, cry, whatever.
It's adamaccurry.com.
Putting the subject line,
D-S-C,
promo,
and then the name of your podcast,
they'll get routed into the right bin.
And when I found in the bin today,
specifically stated,
play before Mother's Day.
So I said,
all right,
I definitely will.
It's kind of,
it's a double,
it's a promo,
and it's a pod save tune all in one.
But good enough to let you join in the fun here today.
So you're the power of pure stupidity,
the banknabbagebjson.com.
All right,
I'm Jason.
I'm Lisa.
And we're from Dagnabbit,
available at bjson.com.
Say hi to Adam.
Oh, Adam.
Yeah.
He does this show.
He does the show.
He called a daily service code.
You ever listened to it?
No.
You do?
Did you remember Adam Curry from when he used to be on MTV?
No.
You don't?
I didn't watch MTV.
Why?
I was a little Christian girl.
My favorite kind.
Well, he had lovely hair,
and he was a tall, lovely hair.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
And it's funny.
Because we do have a saying in the Netherlands.
I'll show her my hoodset.
As long as your hair is all right,
then no one will notice anything else.
It turns out to be pretty true.
That's nothing now.
And he was a tall, a donness.
I remember.
You do?
Did you do like the ball?
Yeah.
He didn't have head bangers ball.
And he shouldn't have been on there.
Because he looked too pretty.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Oh, okay.
I get it.
So if, you know, you have to be ugly.
Oh, okay.
Now I understand.
Yeah.
They were saying that at vh1.
What?
Really?
Yeah.
They were saying that he shouldn't have been on that head bangers ball.
Because he was too pretty.
He only watched show that was on vh1.
So I know call somebody.
These people have absolutely no respect for their elders.
God dammit.
Oh, it's not very nice.
Oh, it's not.
I thought Ricky Rackman was a poser.
With that.
This is the guy who replaced him.
Mother's Day is coming up, you know.
I'm a mom.
You are.
I'm mom.
Ain't he be well at?
Yes.
How old is he now?
I was 16 months.
Oh, be 16 months on two others day, right?
Yeah.
That's right.
Do you remember the present?
I gave you from Mother's Day last year.
It was a beautiful, beautiful song.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What was it about?
Mother's Day.
Yeah.
And what was it called?
Mother's Day.
No.
We wanted to put on a parade.
He decided to hold it on Mother's Day.
Come to honor the greatest mom in the world.
He had called on the animals in the zoo.
They all made him just wanted to.
To honor them greatest mom in the world.
Come to honor the greatest mom in the world.
Because you got me from it.
Because you went my tears away.
Who is he giving me Carlos?
And we're Mother's Day
In cold all the marching bands in the state
You said it's starting to be and now don't be late
We're gonna honor the greatest nomin' moon
Because you won't be gently
Because you make everything okay
Because you're right beside me
Happy Mother's Day
Because you kiss me slowly
Because you won't waste my day
You're the whole world too
Happy Mother's Day
Yes, you can't be wrong
Yes
Yes, yeah, yeah
It's Jason
It's Lisa
It's incredibly vulgar
It's Dagnabbit
Very cool
And indeed it is Mother's Day
So surprise your mom with a special podcast for as an example
That of course comes pre-loaded under iPod Mini
Or I River, I have P799
Complete with sound seeing tour kit
Just a thought fox
Thanks Adam
Wait a minute, you can't say thanks Adam until I say
Hey, FML Judebox Podcast promo, come on in
Thanks Adam
Hey everybody
I really enjoyed taking a break from all the wannabe shock shots on the morning radio
By listening to Adam's daily source code on my way to work
I'm JT from free musicianless.com
And this is my contribution to the material for the 5.4 million podcast listeners in the USA
All the one my calculations is 5.45 million
I'm the host of a weekly podcast called FML Judebox Podcast
Where I play music from independent and local musicians from around the USA and beyond
I know you're trying to appear in the same top 40 songs over and over again
So I've provided songs uploaded to free musicianless.com
So you can hear a West Bank play live in your areas
And I occasionally throw in some live performances recorded exclusively for our podcast
I'll also tell you when the artists are playing so you can go see them live
So come listen to some good music at htp, clone slash slash beats dot feed burner dot com slash FML Judebox Podcast
Adam, thanks for your insight and pulling together all of this technology and making it available and the useful way for all of us to take advantage of
Good luck with posture dot com
Oh, thank you very much
Alright
I'm just a gap closer man. I just help close the 5% gap
But there's more gaps out there to close
There really are in the infamous words of Peter Dave and the BBC
Especially with the music business
We are creating our own route around
I'm really excited about what's happening
So we just need to pull more of these things together and get people like
You know who making podcasts like the FML Judebox podcast
And give everyone a place not just to put your songs up and make it available for purchase
But also a place where podcasts can go and find out what's hot, what's being played
There's a lot in there. Oh, by the way
Was it the beginning of the week we were talking about
Like a community access type channel on a satellite radio
Station
Where you could basically do like an open podcast dot org types thing and open it up and anyone could have a shot or a chance at
Having their whatever their podcasts basically played
On a free to free to air well for bigger audiences put it that way just in other way to get
To get your podcasts out there and get your voice heard
I'm making some headway very interesting got a couple of interesting calls and hopefully in the next couple days will have something to report on that as well
But first it is time
Go one and only
I'm going to be multiple choice
Every test is multiple choice
This is a new hit this
Hey, but again, I'm using a new headset with a new microphone
So I'll just have to see how this one holds up
There's one alternative left and that's a headset from by the mimic and hopefully I'll get some information today
And also the price because it should be more expensive than this one. Oh, we love that
Okay, but we'll have to wait for that
There is a hit test with again three clips and here's number one
Right on
I know it's not one
I love that song
That's Robert Palmer the best of both worlds
Excellent choice young like a lot
And this is number two
Oh, you're hitting my every single right nerve ending
Dream on aerosmith no doubt about it. I'd recognize that anywhere and the final one is number three
It's a derandoran view to a kill I think from James Bond movie times up these are the answers this is answer number one
It's Robert Palmer and it's a song from 1978 and it's called the best of both worlds
Love this song
And I miss you man
Robert Palmer answer number one
And this is answer number two. It's an old song
It's from 1973. It's aerosmith and dream on
And so number two aerosmith and dream on this is a chance
We got it from a James Bond movie. It's derandoran. This is a view to a kill
Remember the fair light dude in it
You can't wait to get to the fire
Right always see
Derandoran and a view to a kill
Well, that's it for today. Three out of three
I enjoyed this one the good few heard were created by a friend of mine which at least don't you know
Just because I don't have the time right now to create a hit test
I'm also very much behind on my own hit test podcast
And I still don't know when I'll have the time to create a new one
I'll keep you up to date through my web lock
It's www.nipoleth.nl or com
Doesn't matter it's J-A-N-D-O-L-E-T-D-N-L or dot com
And of course feedback is welcome to hit.nstategmail.com
Thanks for listening and talk to you soon. Bye-bye
All right, John, thank you very much once again. Good luck, man, with everything you're you're going through right now
And thanks to Reese for pre-cutting the segments there
And if you got a chance, just you know, record a hit test podcast
Tell us what you're doing. Tell us what's going on. I get lots of email from people who want to know
And it doesn't have to be you know filled with your hit test stuff
It can just be your your typical young poet talking
Talking for 15 minutes like that a lot and I hope to do some more that myself
I'm I'm quite excited. Well, if it if it doesn't work out for Thursday with with Paris Hilton
Then I'll think of something else do different hotel this time
So maybe we'll do a new elevator setting to or without interviewing people without letting the know of course
But uh, man new new hotel offers new perspective and new opportunities
What do you hate?
Hey, how you going? Come on in here and talk to us. We're going to read you.com
Hey, the radio
What's here?
Hey, I got a crib
That's what I say when I talk talk to me. What do you feel like?
Oh, my back
Yeah
Just here at the same end. Was it the finalist?
Hello
So we're now called for all
Let's get ahead eight thousand steps
So what do you hate?
What do I hate?
So she's like, her legs are going around in a circle and her body state in the middle
Do you think that we ought to bring the cows later back around anything interesting to listen it?
Yeah
No, why do you think about reasons like me just watch two girls
Do you see some vomiting that continue to show?
Well, now you understand why I do a pouring show. So the blood pressure will go down
WWWWD I'd hate the radio dot com
Yeah, that's really what makes it great radio show.
Used to be the morning shows before they were all packed with jingles and lots of commercials
And really, really tight formatting, you know, with okay, you can do a two minute talk break here
That's the beautiful thing about what we're doing with podcasting
You know, if the joke is rolling keep it going, you know, that's what nice it was really nice
And when you get a couple people just talking in normal people voices
You'll see you get some really exciting stuff
That's what the podcasting is all about
That's going to wind it up for today's show on a plane and just hours from now
So I'll be checking back in from the next location
Which will be New York City
It may not be Thursday morning unless I get some incredible inspiration and opportunity to do
Some kind of sound seeing tour on my trip
I get it late tonight, so we'll have to see how that goes
But I do have the cast glass with which means I can do it from virtually anywhere
So you should have no problems retreating today's show through your iPodder
If you don't have an iPodder go to iPodder.org
And we're going to go to software
And then I'll help you get set up
You can also just click it downloaded right from the website
Who knows where it'll be next, right?
Mycurry.com is the place to send your feedback
Have you got a promo, send it with the subject line
DSC promo, the name of your podcast
Still can use a couple more pairs, held in questions
Match, I've received yours
Don't worry, I know what you want to know
You can find the podcast feed at dailysourcecode.com
And of course you can leave a comment at www.curry.com
Okay, be good, make sure you subscribe to some new podcast
New ones coming up every single day
And I'll also go and check out podcastalley.com
And by the way, it's also the best place to
Or the place, I guess, to find out where you can subscribe to the Paris Hilton podcast
So that's podcastalley.com
Everybody, I'll talk to you tomorrow from the states
Bye-bye