The Lays there began as you reach web to tackle.
There were chances this hit shut out of your Texas Ranger's final score last night at 9B.
First on 635 OVJ.
It's Adam Curry and it is your daily source code.
And when I say that I'm meeting my friend, my family, my lovers, my world leaders, this is your daily source code.
Coming to you from South Beach, Florida, from my bed.
On the top of the bed, that is from the hotel room.
It's the source code for Wednesday, January 5, 2005.
Okay, I got a one year front. I'm completely unprepared.
Yes, I got some show notes, the typical stuff that I basically collected an outline as I prepare for the show.
But I haven't really done any shifting around or positioning or really haven't formatted it.
I just want to fly a little bit by the seat of my pants because quite honestly, I'm tired.
And it's good because the tiredness comes from all things good.
My body said, yeah, we can do a podcast. My brain said, hmm.
Look at what you want to do, body.
So, it's like a couple of hours.
I just want to wrap a little bit, give you a little update where we're at right now.
Today, as I said, as Wednesday is January 5, 2005, it's about quarter to three in the afternoon.
And got back about 45 minutes ago from breakfast, slash lunch.
And now it wasn't brunch because Dave and I actually intended to get some breakfast, but could not get served at the big pink sucked.
Actually, I got into like a something I never do.
I got angry, I got irritated that we just couldn't get any service.
I don't know, I think with the position the table was bad, but then there was like no apology.
It's just, you know, fuck you.
It's kind of, I guess that sometimes that is a little bit of the attitude, certainly in the extremely hip South Beach quadrant.
But we're having a good time and really good time.
We had a, what I consider, I think, break through day yesterday between Ron, Dave and I.
We really got to a point where we said, okay, yeah, now we've got, you know, now the shit's starting to click.
It's falling into place.
We, you know, this is exactly what we were, we're hoping for what we were expecting.
And, and so that was last night until 11, then I got back.
And really, I intended to go to bed, but I couldn't stop listening to yeast radio.
And I'm glad I did because 33 minutes into the show that, um, aired the day before yesterday.
Mad started talking about Dave.
And, um, if you haven't heard it, let me share that with you right now because, um, this magic is a smart cookie boy.
I tell you, I have to blow my nose and I have the lava layer on.
So cover your ears.
I've got, now I sound like Dave wine and sneezing all over the, driving the car.
I love his podcast, by the way.
I think it's, it's absolutely one of my favorites.
Because it's just, you know, very down in the car.
The way he sort of has this hippie accent and the smell.
And those kinds of, kind of, but let's face the guys, you know, he's, he's got an amazing mind.
And it's sort of like what I was talking about was Nicole Kidman.
And, oh, that's a horrible comparison.
But, no, wait a minute.
I think that's a beautiful comparison.
Dave Winner.
Nicole Kidman.
You know, it's like Nicole Kidman is so beautiful.
It doesn't matter what she does.
It doesn't matter.
Because she's beautiful.
She can be a Kant.
I don't care.
Because she's beautiful.
And she's got a little bit of talent.
But you see, Dave, why?
She got a little bit of talent.
She got a humongous amount of Botox and that forehead match.
Come on, be honest there.
Hmm.
I wouldn't exactly say he's beautiful, but you see, he's got a good brain.
And that entitles him to be kind of, you know, nuts.
And a little bit of a mess or whatever.
And I don't know the guy, so I'm judging him.
And I'm just making examples.
But I'm just talking about what I've, you know,
from what I'm guessing based on his personality.
I guess I'm guessing that he tends to be a little overbearing.
I certainly can relate to this sort of thing.
I have relatives that are overbearing.
I'm certainly not.
I've always tried not to be overbearing in my life.
Because I don't want to repeat the mistakes.
My mother made it.
So you know, I get the impression that he's a little difficult to deal with.
He seems to rub people the wrong way at times.
It sounds like this RSS business was a bit difficult for him,
because a bunch of people basically.
I don't know, but see, this is all.
This is what I'm hearing basically from Dave's own podcast.
And from, you know, that's just the impression I get.
And since I am a lesbian, I'm a little psychic.
So I'm reading this.
It's sort of a reading that I'm giving him for free.
If he's listening, which he probably isn't.
Oh, but match.
That's why you're wrong.
Because of course we're listening to you.
Of course we are.
And well, maybe he isn't.
Because now that I think of it,
I've never seen Dave and Madge together in the same picture.
I don't know.
But anyway.
I don't forget what I was talking about.
So then Madge, unfortunately, did forget to continue the comparison
between Nicole Kidman and Dave Winner and to continue with the psychic reading.
I was totally into the psychic reading.
So anyway, I heard this.
It was like 130.
And I was laughing out loud throughout the whole podcast.
It wasn't just a David.
It was fabulous.
It's almost like Joan Rivers, Howard Stern, and Rush Limbaugh,
not his politics per se, but they had a love child.
And out, you know, pop, Madge.
And I sent Madge an email.
I said, Madge, you know, I worship you.
You are so awesome.
The stuff you say and how you present it,
it does it for me.
And the only place that a podcast like East Radio
would work is in a podcast.
It doesn't work on radio.
The way she talks, what she says,
how she presents it, the language,
which is, you know,
it would never make it past anything.
It couldn't even make it up to
Michael Powell's front door.
He's the chairman of the FCC, by the way.
So I was just totally digging it and I said,
you know, would you please make an appearance on a daily source code?
Could it call you up?
So I was hoping to be able to do it today,
but it's not going to work.
So just a timing issue.
I'm going to call Madge later tonight.
We'll record it and of course we'll use that on the source code for tomorrow.
So you can look forward to that.
I'm certainly looking forward to talking to Madge.
I think it's going to be quite a hoot.
So anyway, this morning at 9 o'clock,
Fox television showed up.
This was pre-arranged,
pre-read, Fox television in Chicago.
Although it wasn't the Chicago folks,
I had spoken to the producer Nina over there at Great Length,
and previously before I even left for the trip,
because they wanted to interview me.
Well, you know, it's like shoot.
I'm here in the States, mine as well,
but I'm not going to come to Chicago.
That's no problem, because what they do then is they send their affiliate,
their local Fox affiliate, which is,
I forget what the call sign is here.
And they said over a really nice young lady, producer,
and she had all the questions.
And I could tell that this was well prepared,
and they did a good job of really lighting the room.
Of course, you know, they want me to, you know,
after you do all the questions,
then they need what they call B-roll.
The term B-roll.
Yeah, I guess B-roll comes from the term,
well, if you look at, you have the A-roll and the B-roll.
So the role, of course, used to be the film role,
and A is pretty much the interview role,
and B-roll is like all the stuff,
you know, of me walking on the street,
of me sitting in front of my computer,
typing on the keypad, you know,
the shit that you've done a million times
when people want to put together a nice little package.
It's really the only reason for the B-roll
is to cover up the edits that they do in the interview.
So of course, they're not going to air the hour and a half
that we spoke about all these different things
about podcasting and about enclosures
and users and developers partying together
in the daily source code and morning coffee notes,
and all this.
So they're going to take a little snippet side of it
because, yeah, who knows how much, you know,
can be made out of the item or how much time
they'll get, maybe, a couple minutes tops.
And so is to not see me, you know,
jumping all over the camera because you're cutting
right in the middle of my, of what I was saying,
or my answers, that's when they paste a bit.
It'd be roll over it.
So you basically hear my voice,
continue underneath the B-roll.
Now in this particular B-roll,
they need a little bit more than just me
working on the computer.
Every single television program,
including the BBC,
always wants to video me doing a podcast.
Personally, I'm not a big fan of this.
I really don't like it.
And why?
Because I believe in theater of the mind.
Theater of the mind is,
if you're good at it,
you can kick ass on radio.
In fact, we used to have theater on radio,
and it was a bunch of guys stay.
I'll never forget my dad.
One of the things I remember that my dad told me
is that he will never forget the day
that he went, he was taken by,
I guess his dad,
to a radio studio to see how they did the old-time drama.
I think I don't know if it was loan-ranger
or, but he was going to be in the studio audience.
And it was so disappointing.
He said, you know, had this entire vision
of how the actors looked and, you know,
and the sound effects.
And, but really, he was pretty much imagining a movie
in his head, which was the theater of the mind.
You know, they created this reality
of what the show should look like.
Very much like when you read a book.
You know, you have a movie that plays in your head
and you see the pictures,
and you can kind of envision that,
which is the beauty of using your mind,
which, by the way,
doesn't happen when you're watching television.
You're polluting your mind,
and I know, because I come from television,
and I used to be a big,
a big polluter, major league pollution dude.
And, so, of course,
they wanted to see me podcasting.
I don't want to, you know, it's like right now.
I say, I'm laying in my bed in my hotel room,
and you have a vision of that.
You know, and maybe you think in this big rest,
waterbed, and have a friendship,
named Jerome.
So maybe you think that,
or maybe you think a fuzzy bed,
or maybe you're thinking,
like, one of those honeymoon porn sweets,
or who knows what you're thinking?
You know, that's your thoughts,
and you have an idea of how I'm sitting or laying down,
or what I'm wearing,
and I want that to be,
you know, that's the magic stuff,
that is a big part of the magic of radio.
Who was it, the other?
It was an article,
and I forget who wrote it,
who said, you know,
I don't really don't want to see Adam set up,
because I have the idea of him sitting there with the headphones,
and a big fuzzy microphone in front of him,
and kind of like a dimly lit room with the,
you know, smoke, whisping up from the astray.
You get the, like the Dr. Johnny fever vibe from WKRP,
and Cincinnati.
And so the minute kind of show that,
a lot of it goes away,
and then also basically I have to fake doing a podcast,
because they needed the audio,
so I was wearing my headphones,
but they weren't really plugged in,
because you were hearing the audio coming through the speakers,
and yeah, so it's not entirely,
you know, the stuff I like to do,
but I think with a little bit of luck,
we will get the Sylvia Speedy's played on this,
because I talked about him in the interview,
and I played him in my faux podcast.
I want to be famous,
I want to wear minks and sattens and pearls.
more than just any old girl.
I want to have eyes as blue as the sea.
I want all the people to look at me.
I want my own show on TV.
I want to be that girl.
I want to be famous.
You got it's art, it's not part of you that's spy.
Got a pair of some private flights.
I want to have lovers buy the score.
When we produce this knocking down on my door,
this is the faith that is in store for me.
Oh, when I'm famous,
I will wear a great trench coat and fake red hair.
So they all will know that it is me.
When they see me,
how they'll smile,
and me photo grass to sign.
I will say sorry babe.
Talk to my assistant.
I want to be famous.
Stabloids will print what I eat.
I want to be famous
who I do will be news on the street.
Then when I'm old,
I'll have a ball.
There'll be shops that I'm living at all.
When I enter the guests will fall
to their knees.
And then I step the thrones
on my enemies' bed.
All I don't want one in cheese
when I'm famous.
Spameless.
So exhausting.
And then I step the thrones
on my enemies' bed.
Spameless.
Into a whirl whirl whirl
Every morning I don't get high on
Colored hills, Margines dry
A little wee and just a touch
I wanna be my famous better than all of my fellow much better than all of her
I wanna be famous, lonely and alone at the end
I'll hand up bitter and ugly and old
Not just my body, but also my soul
But a legend is my goal and a legend of being
When I'm famous, not I will give for the little people
All their teams, when I'm famous
I'm famous, I'm famous
So we're freshing to hear the Bitties once again
Check them out at Bittiesforever.com
That's B-I-D-D-I-E-S for number forever.com
And I'm talking to their production manager
On email, who by the way is also a pilot
And he's been recording all kinds of live shows
And he says, standby, I'm gonna bring it to you
I'm very excited about some of the CBS Bitties live music
And just excited about them getting famous
You know they will, you know they will
That's so good.
Talk about music for a second
That seems to be a topic that we've been hitting here in Miami a couple of times
I've been talking about
Now you have to understand that Ron has had quite a
Quite a career as a producer and a writer
A little bit as a performer, certainly as a musician
Oh, by the way
Don't tell anyone
Ron actually lived with Princess Stephanie of Monaco for about two or three years
Okay, don't tell anyone I told you that
He actually produced that horrible record she did
I have to say it wasn't a horrible record
It was a poppy record, that's for sure
I remember because I met Princess Stephanie of Monaco
When she was like she's like my age
And I was 19 or 20 just starting
Television, music television in Holland
At Veronica doing the show Countdown
She came to promote a record
And I did connect with her, she was really nice
Very sweet, you know she spoke very limited English and my French will
Now, as Madge would say
Yeah, French, that's what kind
Right, Madge
Um
But yeah, so anyway that was the long long long ago connection that I had with Ron
But Ron has done some, he done some good stuff
And he's working a lot of different people in the music industry
He's a great musician, he plays guitar and plays piano
He actually, the piece here, the the The La Civius bitties
Let me see if I can pick that piece up here this little
Intro Ludes
All of my thoughts
Yeah, this bit
Yeah, this bit, this is the piano
This is pretty wrong, can play like this
I was imagine Ron playing this before he got married
And I gave him
Don't you come over here to go for your friends when I play a little bit of fun?
Yeah, I will.
But I think we really see, and it's great, because Ron has such a take on how the music industry works.
You know, he actually gets paid from ASCAP via my. That's where he does get money.
In fact, after every Christmas holiday season, after the air supply records, the Christmas
album has been out, you know, Ron received a check. So that system is working for him.
And he approaches it as a musician who's getting paid that way and where the system is working for him.
And we've really gotten deep into this. And we're all very excited about the possibilities.
Did I see Dave post something that he wrote in 2000? Yeah, 2000, I think. Let me just see.
How was it? It was a quote he put on the scripting today.
Um, I'm going to be fine at for you.
Uh, okay, yeah, this was April, April 7th. Was that July 7th?
Oh, dates are such a hard thing to do, man. When it comes to seven. No, that would be
January, March, June, July, okay, July 4th, July 4th.
With that, we'll come new music, a new ways to play it, new ways to explore the emotions it brings up,
and new kinds of community, deep ones, far deeper than those who've been able to create
on the silent web. That's right, ladies and gentlemen, the silent web is no longer silent.
We've gone from silent to talkies. And I think we could be in the space for a little while. We don't
necessarily have to go to video just in just yet. Nor can we. Sure, on a personal basis, you know,
if I wanted a couple people to subscribe to a private podcast feed where I put a, you know, a
500 or 600 megabyte file for for you to enjoy. And I'm not talking about a movie that I'd rip off,
but just maybe something I created, right, or a Mad Weinstein as all kinds of videos.
Problem is, um, that's just too much bandwidth. We don't have the hard drives. We don't have the pipes,
uh, not if you're going to go over like those five people. If you're going to go over, if you
want to have 50,000 people grabbing it, it's not going to work. Not yet. You know, that's, uh,
that's a very important part of what we're doing here. Yeah, sure. This solution is all kinds of stuff.
We've been talking about that, too. You know, I think Bitcoin will play a role in that. So anyway,
regardless of all that, um, it's just been interesting to, to work through all the different issues.
And, you know, I want to work with these people. I want to work with the biddies. I want to,
I really do want to make them famous. I seriously do. And, um, God, we have such a unique combination
of people in this, uh, in this community. And it's going to be great. That's all I can say. God,
dammit. It's just going to be great. See, a man just rubbing off on me. I'm starting to get rank and,
and, and talk crappy and shit. But anyway, I got a, um, an email from Susie, uh, Susie Puggsley
says, uh, I put together this podcast called Hotline. And, uh, of course, in the show notes,
you couldn't, uh, actually have the, the podcast feed right there. And I caught the show before
or she sent me the email, actually. I'm going to just play a little bit for you. Because I think that
this is a podcast that, uh, would probably be very interesting to listen to. And, uh, it's the
type of podcast that needs a little push, um, because, um, well, you can't really have an, you know,
an interaction if you don't have people to interact with. So check out Susie's idea for her podcast.
Hello and welcome to my first official podcast. My name's Susie. S.U. Z. Y. And now what I'm going to do,
I'm basically your, one of the mill average human being, but I just happen to be good
giving advice and helping people out. And it's what I like to do. Um, so basically what I'm
going to do on a weekly basis, I am going to try and help those people who may not have anybody else
to talk to or, you know, just going to problem that they don't, you know, the thing embarrassed
about talking about. And I'm, you know, completely open minded. You can't really shock me,
or, although I'm always up for a challenge. So feel free to try and shock me on that one. I'm sure
it'll give everyone out there all that. Um, so what really I'd like you to do with, if there's
anyone out there who would like to talk or if they've got a certain problem or anything that they're
fascinated about and want to just go. So, you know, just end all, anything general, you know,
topics or problems just give them any mail. And, uh, I'll talk about it or, you know, problems, I'll
help you out and I'll give you some advice of what I think best. And instead, I'm not a doctor.
I'm not qualified in any way whatsoever. But I'm a good human being and I'm honest. I'm always
honest, you know, however hard the situation may be and however, you know, complicated the problem might
be. I will give you my, you know, my utmost best to try and help you out. Uh, so my email address
is Suzy at SuzyP.co.uk. Um, feel free to email me with anything, however small or however big.
And I'll talk you through it and mention it next time I do a podcast. I'm going to try and do it
on a weekly basis. So, once a week, once I get all the emails back through. And we'll just see where
we go from there because obviously I'm, you know, I'm free and easy. I quite like helping people.
So it seemed a logical step. So there you go. So my name's Suzy. And if you've got anything you'd
like to talk about, then please feel free to email me. Take care and I hope to have your response.
Okay. Thank you, Suzy. I'm pretty sure that Suzy is going to get some comments and it's kind of like
the idea of a podcasting, right? You're Suzy. I'm pretty glad we did this. Uh, it's kind of like off
the cuff kind of like un-unprepared type show for today because it's, uh, it's even more creative
than it usually is for me. Rick Resowitz, who does the ICM RAW podcast, um, and, um, as you remember,
I played Rick Deringer, played a couple songs, uh, including Hang On Slupee, which started
an entire slupee cover, you know, Mania in podcast space. Oh my god, I said space in podcast
lamb. He sent me a press release with some excellent news. He says that, uh, watch of this press release
came from, uh, Rick Deringer. Uh, he and Rick has the, uh, a request which has the connection with
Rick Deringer. He recorded those live tracks February 5, 2005, Rick Deringer in conjunction with
the John and Twistle Foundation, John and Twistle from the who will present the musicians for
hurricane relief benefit concert. I'm just reading from the, uh, from the, uh, the press release here.
Superstar guitars, Rick Deringer will not only perform at the concert, but as executive music
director, he's been the driving force behind the event, gathering many of his famous friends
joined this very worthy cause. All proceeds from the concert and CD DVD of the event will go to
Florida hurricane relief in the American Red Cross. The event will be held at Universal theme park in
Orlando, Florida. God, wrong month to be here. Um, and, uh, what I understand is that Rick will, uh,
Rick, our Rick, not well, Rick Deringer is also our Rick now. We've been deared him. He's, he's totally
our Rick. Rick Wesowitz is, uh, I think he's going to record this live and, uh, as far, what I understood
from his accompanying email, it will be, um, pod safe. So we'll be able to play anything we want.
And of course, we're going to work on the honor system, uh, and, uh, you know, we're going to
expect that if, you know, if you're listening to that particular podcast that you are, or have donated to, uh,
to the, um, hurricane relief. Why does it say hurricane relief? Right. Okay, a Florida of course,
hurricane. They've donated to the hurricane relief. Now look at this lineup. This is going to blow you away.
Actually, let's play a little game here. Let's play a little game of what does Adam have in his iTunes.
And I certain this is, by the way, is not my entire library. Um, Erasmith's Steven Tyler's going to be there.
Um, hold on. Why did my iTunes start up? What's going on here? Uh, I say, I don't want to
read the, okay, here we go. Because in iTunes, like you can just basically just search and let's see if
anything pops up. Let's see if I had the song. So we can do a little promo here.
God, this is like, fun. Okay. Uh, erasmith's Steven Tyler. Do we have anything by Erasmith?
Yes, I believe we do. Let's see if we have my erasmith. Oops.
Right, sweet emotion. I have another one by erasmith. I got this one.
It's don't pop. I got to come and run DMC here. Oh, okay. Uh,
Banjovies, Richie Sambora. God, do I have Banjovies and, uh, probably do.
Banjovies? What do I have? Oh, yeah, we got all kinds of Banjovies.
I wanted to see this one. Check it.
Okay, we got some Banjovies. AC DCs, Brian Johnson.
Man, this is a great frickin' lineup. Okay, let's see if I got some AC DC. AC DC.
Ooh, how come we don't have AC DC? Oh, please. Please, don't tell me I don't have AC DC because
of course I got some frickin' AC DC.
Banjovies, Banjovies, Banjovies, Banjovies, Banjovies, Banjovies, Banjovies, Banjovies, Banjovies,
One, two.
Okay, uh, else we have almond brothers. Dude, do you think Adam Curry has almond brothers?
Oh. Uh, nope. No almond brothers. Okay. Uh, three dog night.
Uh, who from three dog night's coming Chuck Negrin? Uh, okay. So do we have any three dog night?
Three dog dog. Well, of course we got some three dog night.
This is like the show that's totally gonna be for me. It's gonna be such an awesome show to see.
Let's move it along here. Grand Funk Railroad. Okay, there's anyone who knows a great Grand Funk Railroad
tournament. Well, of course you do. It's some kind of wonderful, oh man, these sounds.
I wish I could play them all for you. I don't need a whole lot of money.
You know how, um, you know how, um, you know how you can mess up the lyrics and you think that
for years sometimes that they're singing one thing and and and you're basically singing another
thing. Let's just see how I do with the rest of the lyrics here.
What have we missed here? Chief trick. Uh, of course we've got my favorite team, Chief Trick
track here. I want you to want me. Okay, uh, Michael Bolton also on the ticket. My
old neighbor, Michael Bolton. He lived next to me, uh, at the apartment on the 56th and Broadway
and when we lived in the symphony house. He was a nice guy. Really nice guy. In fact, I got him
on MTV when he was so totally not frickin' hip to be on MTV. They all wanted him to be on VH1
and uh, after that he got it. He had the big hit with Doc of the Bay and that was kind of
then unfortunately. This is, uh, what was that? That's what loves all about.
Oh, wait. I have a different one, my Michael Bolton. What's that? This is Michael Bolton.
Nobody's home right now, but at the time, please leave a message and they'll get back to you.
I don't know why I have that. Oh, this is, this is possibly, I've done many appearances with,
with this guy. Uh, oh my god, I can't believe it. Don't tell me,
don't have Eddie money in my iTunes. Where's two tickets to Paradise?
Oh, this is horrible. Don't tell me, I don't have shit. Okay, no Eddie money.
Joan Jet, we shared the same manager, Kenny Laguna, Kenny Laguna, uh, used to be, uh, in, uh,
in the Shondales, I think. But Joan Jet's gonna be there. Of course, the classic Joan Jet,
I love rock and roll. Doing pretty good so far, only missed out one.
Um, what do we have? Pat Traverse. I don't think I have any
Pat Traverse. No, no Pat Traverse. Sticks. Yeah, of course. I got some sticks. Of course. Do
little, little, little, little. Yeah, that's my favorite song. It's like three minutes and two seconds.
It's the song you always played at the very end. It's like, babe, I'm leaving. Must be on my way.
My time is drawn in the air.
Just get the first line there, just to enjoy it there.
Oh, here comes the due to the loop loop part.
By the way, as a podcast that does this, uh, the podcast is called as it was played to me.
And it's in the iPod.org directory, and it's essentially the guy does the same thing. I'm doing.
Just talks over the records and, you know, and sings one with lyrics.
Beautiful. Okay. Let me just see what are we doing on time here. Okay. Good. I do have a
couple more things I want to talk to about, but I'm almost through the list. I just
giving you an idea of how incredible this show is going to be on February 5th. Spencer Davis,
well, of course, I could play Steve Winwood and get away with it.
But that's always good to have the original of that give me some love and maybe
the Ham and Oregon man would be three, I guess. When I kick them, this is just
giving me goose bumps. Look at that.
Uh, so we had that. Oh, rig deranger. Okay. Now, I'm going to play something different from rig deranger.
Of course, we, we played two songs, including Hang on Slopey, but the one deranger song, of course,
that I grew up with was rock and roll, whoo cheek, whoo baby.
I asked him, I probably could play the whole thing, but we'll just leave it at this for now.
It also sounds like Randy MC.
Okay. Uh, Connie Wilson. So, Connie Wilson, we'd have to say Wilson Phillips, I guess, right?
Do we have any Wilson Phillips? Uh, yeah, of course. We got hold on. Yeah.
God, that thing was huge. That was a big hit.
So it was Kanye.
I got flock of seagulls, shoot. The only song I would have by flock of seagulls is I ran and I don't have that one.
Lauren Hill, uh, don't have Lauren Hill.
That's it. Plus, many more surprised guests to be out of between now and show time. Please join us
and making a difference in the lives of tens of thousands of Floridians who've been forever
changed by the record breaking tragedies of the summer of 2004. My sincerest thanks, Rick Deranger,
executive music director, musicians for Hurricane Relief, excellent. And of course,
I'm going to support you, Rick. You know we will. See, quick email that I got from Stuart Hunter.
We were talking about Tim Bird, the Birdman, everybody. Just the other day. I'm, uh, I'm a sure.
We're talking about real voices and, and, uh, well, oh, no, it's talking about VH1. That's right.
With Tim Bird was on VH1. And Stuart sent in, uh, little note and said, uh, Adam,
Tim Bird, the Birdman is a DJ on sunny 104.3 FM in Palm Beach County, Florida.
I tried, I couldn't receive it on the on the radio here in the hotel room, because I would have been great to
record a little bit. Hey, everybody's Tim Bird Birdman, I just want to go 4.3 FM right here in Palm Beach,
Florida. Rome, Rome, cadence of the day. Today's cadence comes on the USC Trojans to go along with a big
game in the Orange Bowl.
I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I'm, uh, I
I'm, uh, I'm, um, uh, oh I'm, uh, I'm, uh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh Oh, oh, oh, boy.
I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it
I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to
do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm
going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it, I'm not going to do it,
what we need now is we need a drum cadence of the day, specialized podcast feed and
I've been in touch with Taylor who puts us together and has actually been putting his out
on overpodcast.org, which for Anna, you can subscribe to OpenPodcast.org and you'll get the
drum cadence of the day, but I wanted to have it zone feed and so I'm going to help them set
that up and work on that because it clearly has accents to the stuff, there is an audience,
I know that because everyone says the drum cadence is even day, and I thought the
Dave just loved it kind of for walking, but here's the story that Dave Wiener told me,
he said that he actually is pretty good at drumming because what happened was when he was
back in the day when I guess right after punch cards, when computers actually needed
to compile, he had to wait around for quite a while where the shit was compiling,
it's none of this like F5, and it's compiled business, none of those would take hours
or 10, 20, 30 minutes, I don't know, and to pass the time he would play the drums, and
he can say he got pretty good at it, and there's something about the cadence is that
people just totally dig. Also, I think it's a very American art form, it's probably
the closest thing culturally, it's probably very close to Africa, don't you think?
I mean, I've seen lots, I used to live in Uganda, I was very young, but I remember the rhythm
is kind of the same, digging it, digging it. Alrighty, so what's on the agenda for today?
I think we're going to see if Dave is a welcome from his Nat, then we're going to do some stuff
together, I think, well, maybe a little bit of, look, he's going to work on a podcast, I'm
going to work on some programming, that's what that's basically what our relationship is,
and it really works. That was the drone room cadence of the day.
That's right, and leaving you with this final thought, mad, I'm going to show it tomorrow.
Alright, thanks everybody for listening in, but what are we going to do? Just about right
for me, a little different today, a little different, not bad at all. Okay, oh by the way,
if you didn't see my weblog, the bandwidth has arrived at home. I could not be happier.
I'm going to try and get Christina to hook it up tomorrow and see if it actually works.
So, it looks like the easy net guys that are really good by me, then, of course, I expected that.
Hey, if you've got to comment, leave it for me on the weblog, www.curry.com,
or adamantcurry.com tomorrow, as said, be busy, we've got some people flying in,
that we're going to be talking to here, but on the phone or on Skype, the one, the only badge
I'm staying from you is to radio on the daily source code. Talk to you tomorrow, y'all. Bye bye.