Daily source code 1-26-25 Transmators, we don't need no stinkin' Transmators!
Get ready for the generation of rockin' world!
Autastic! It's Adam Curry!
It's the hump day edition of your daily source code, everybody!
It's the power of the door!
It's the Wednesday, January 26, 2005, coming to you from Curry Cottage.
I'm Adam Curry, it's a 122 in the afternoon sitting here on the Louis Vuittie Couture's couch.
Man, we're bumping all over the place today, aren't we?
Hey, good afternoon!
It's the power of the door! It's the door!
It's the door! Good morning!
What evening, depending on when you happen to be checking the show out?
Another 40 minutes jam packed of podcasts, promos, podsafe music.
Everything you get you into is what's going on in podcasts today.
Yes, it's kind of a show about nothing.
Although that would be stealing Jimmy Jetside here.
It's just like any other Ed Sullivan type show.
Your daily source code, with good news today, because just arrives by a courier.
The good Charlotte tickets for March at the Brickston Academy.
The power of the door, the power of the door.
That, of course, is for Christina, who asked me, I think sometimes around Christmas,
she said, that good Charlotte, her favorite band,
are playing at Brickston Academy, and she sent me a link.
Where to get tickets.
And I forget the name of this outfit, but it seemed pretty reputable,
so I just ordered them online.
And then we didn't hear from them.
It was like, oh, well, you know, the tickets are coming,
but it may take up until two weeks before the show.
So we started to get a little bit worried about them actually showing up,
and of course, but now the show is completely sold out.
So today they arrived by courier.
March 20th, good Charlotte Brickston Academy.
That's going to be a sound seeing tour.
I'm definitely taken by recording equipment to that gig.
And the last time we saw it, or the first time, and last time,
so far that we saw them was in Holland at 13,
and I think that's Tilburg, or Tilburg, as we would say.
And I was able to get the Christina and her friend,
I ship backstage, because, well, I know, I know people at the location,
I know the big promoter in Holland, and I said, hey,
you know, can you see if you can get these girls backstage.
And then once they told the band's manager that and the band,
they said, oh, Adam Curry, well, of course, you know,
we grew up watching him.
Thank you for making me feel so fucking ancient.
Now, this time around, of course, I want to be super dad again,
but I know no one at the Brickston Academy.
I don't know anything about the venue, the promoter, etc.
So if any of the source code listeners in the UK,
happen to have an in and can get word to the manager,
the band that we'll be waiting to go backstage,
turn me into super dad again, please, that would be really cool.
And this morning is a drop Christina off, you know,
what we do now these days is fill up the iPod,
got the iPrip.
I take her to school every single morning just to,
you know, really just to get going to start my day,
then I drive by the new stand, pick up newspapers,
and I listened to a podcast.
We listened to the daily download this morning,
and I'm going to play some bits of that later for you.
It was the fucking hilarious Christina loved it.
On the way back, I noticed there was a new yeast radio,
my friend, Madge Weinstein.
And the whole show almost like started off,
you know, with her talking to me,
which was trippy, you know, I'm sitting there,
and the car and Madge is yelling at me,
and yelling at everyone else, and other people
joining the conversation.
Let's just go through this,
so you can kind of hear what it was,
and maybe it can address some of Madge's issues.
I'm trying to have a podcast.
I can keep forgetting to say that,
hold on a second.
The daily source code is often not safe for work.
Everybody, this is Fausto,
and we're with Jason Smith,
and we're taking pictures.
Hi, everybody.
We're all auditioning for you.
I was talking gay TV show.
That sounds like there's a lot of fun going on there
in the East Radio Studios.
What's the sound I hear?
Ah, it's all kinds of crap going on.
I'm still at the window open here.
I'm sitting underneath the window in the...
Hear that?
Oh, okay.
Well, we'll just have to live with that.
That's someone rebuilding their house, I guess.
I'm not, I'm too old.
Listen, so, um, here's the deal.
Now I forgot what I was going to say.
So, I'll time for this.
I'll play this wonderful interview with John Farmy.
But first, I need to talk to Adam Curry.
Alright.
I immediately go, huh?
Alright, here it comes.
Okay.
Adam, what's the fucking deal?
You're taking all the goddamn publicity for yourself.
Everybody's calling you,
because you're the one with the hair.
Well, I got a hair too, Goddamn.
And I want to, the next time,
some fucking network calls, you send them over to Madge,
because that's the least you only after that goddamn wine
of bullshit on laying on the couch masturbating
in South Beach, Fias.
Hold on.
Oh, yeah, maybe I was, you know.
So, you'll give a mine number.
That's Madge Weinstein.
The loaded at Mad.com.
That's how.
Send them by way.
I'm funnyer than her anyway.
Well, Madge, you know I love you.
You know you're funny.
I wish you didn't live in fucking Chicago,
so I wouldn't have to stay up until two in the morning
to call you.
Well, Madge, I will certainly do that.
And I'm sure that will really promote Madge Weinstein anyway.
Time for the interview with John Vaughment.
I told you this was going to be a quickie,
but I had to get that little pronouncement
announcement out of the way,
because I'm sure I'm speaking for a lot of podcasts
as when we say, why should she get all the attention?
By the way, when I was at the vlog of Tharn,
I did run into a couple of people that were resentful
of the podcast.
Because I'm like, listen, why are you so against podcast?
And we said, well, it's all about personalities
and it's basically all about Adam Curry.
So, Adam, it's all about Nick.
Show hold on, hold on.
I hear some beages in the background.
Stick an up for me now.
This is getting interesting.
I'll tell you fucking kisses.
Yeah.
Kiss it, baby.
Show.
Faustos taking your side as usual.
And fucking a, of course she's taking my side.
I'm taking your side manager, just not hear what I'm saying.
I don't want to hear what you're saying.
All right, what do you say?
What?
Self-loaded.
Oh, sorry.
It wasn't paying attention.
Like most of their audience,
imagine.
They're probably scanning past this part.
I have to make this point.
It's okay for it to be about personalities
because this is like early cable access.
It's people expressing themselves.
That's a good picture.
That is a good picture.
Well, of course it's about personalities.
Absolutely.
And it's all about Don and Drew and Mad Weinstein.
And, and of course, Dave Weiner and the Daily Source Code.
And yeah, it's all about personalities.
It's about, it's not what blogs are about as well.
It's all about personalities.
Absolutely.
In fact, if there's anything that's the problem with regular radio,
go turn on any fucking radio station, except for a few
personalities who still work that way.
Everything has been homogenized.
You know, sanitized for your protection.
Everyone's sitting up there, clear channel, sitting in the DJ farm.
And it's, you know, and they all have the same name.
It's, you know, all above the love sponge.
And, and hey, it's Gary Brian, everybody.
They all have the same fucking names,
but they're all promoting their station and the corporation they work for.
Not the personality.
So absolutely.
Um, but I'm sure that, you know, exposing the world to this wonderful
banter on yeast radio, yeast radio.com is certainly going to help
Mad Weinstein's personality get more exposure.
No, this is an advertising photographer.
Are you be perfect, by the way, for USA today, Mad?
Absolutely perfect.
I love like I just couldn't sleep.
This will get me an advertising job.
Are you recording this?
Yeah.
Okay.
We're doing a photo shoot channel.
I just want to just say one thing before Fausto but it in,
which is that Mike Kent stinks.
No, um, what was I going to say?
Oh, so whatever.
And no hard feelings.
I'm just joking.
I know.
I have to tell you when I'm joking.
You take everything.
I do not.
I'm in the hair.
I got to talk to your wife for a second.
She just left to do shopping.
Okay.
I'll, I'll vouch for her.
Go ahead.
What's up?
Why am I talking to you?
This is my podcast.
Why am I talking to Adam Curry?
Am I fucking podcast?
Because you can't get around me, Mad.
Your wife Patricia was kind of a bitch the other day.
When she was saying that she was basically berating you about this haircuts.
Now I have a whole on a second.
I think she feels horrible about the haircut actually.
Because let's just respin the the events here.
She took me over to Sam and Dave's or Tony and Guy.
And normally if she'd been feeling better,
if there wasn't this time gap,
if I didn't have to go, you know,
felt's broadband off of Starbucks,
she would have stayed with me and then we would have been protected.
Because when once I got my glasses off,
and once I'm sitting there with these people who are way to hit for the room,
I get in trouble.
I don't pay attention.
And I couldn't see it.
And it was too late.
So she feels bad.
I don't think she was berating me.
She feels horrible.
I feel horrible.
It's shitty.
And my dear friend,
I'm not going to say his name,
but he used to work for Tony and Guy.
And they're a very good hair salon.
Oh, please.
I'm not saying that they're not.
I think that they're all superstars at Tony and Guy.
You know, everyone wants to be the next Sam and Dave superstar,
and they do whatever they want.
You know, I, what I should do here's something I'll do.
I'll see if I can find the picture that we showed,
and said, here's what I wanted to look like.
And then I'll do a picture of what it turned out as.
And then you tell me if I got my money's worth.
So don't dis them because you're not hip,
and you don't know what's a hip hairstyle.
So I say post the picture,
let's the audience decide,
and particularly let Madge decide if this is a good haircut.
Okay.
Because I think your wife is just being nasty.
She has a reason to feel superior to you.
But she is superior.
But not Madge.
Madge feels that we are equals.
By the way, I got a little secret for you, Madge.
My wife's a lesbian.
No corporate radio crap.
No major labels.
Only the best music you've never heard on the insomnia radio podcast.
How cool is that, eh?
That's a great sweeper.
Let me see.
That was insomnia radio.
I can't remember where this all came from.
I'm looking through my show notes,
and it's already messed up.
Madge completely messed me up there.
I think what I wanted to say about this.
First of all, is that I got this email.
Yeah, this is Jason from insomnia radio.
He says that he's hooked up with,
what is this?
The service, which is called radiodaddy.com.
I've seen other people talk about this before.
It's kind of like a way you can,
a place where you can go swap and get sweepers done.
I guess it's kind of like a database or something.
I should check it out.
Maybe I should go to the website and check it out.
But you can get these really cool professional sweepers done.
And it's kind of like on a barter basis, I guess,
and this radiodaddy.com.
You should check it out, because it's a good resource for podcasters.
Not quite sure what you have to do in return,
if you have no voice, I don't know what you can actually contribute.
Let's check it out, hold on.
Let's stop this insanity.
Let's go to radiodaddy.com.
If you're at home, follow along with me by all means.
Let's see if we can find out together what this is.
Okay, radiodaddy.com.
God, it's great to have bandwidth again,
and actually have stuff coming in when you type.
Size being developed is a free site to allow
to change your voice overs between radio stations worldwide.
Prime is the simple.
Need a voice over recorded.
You come to radiodaddy.com.
Post your request and a member of Courage
of Voiceovers and MP3 upload it back to radiodaddy.
You return to your site, download, blah, blah, blah.
Absolutely free.
All we ask is you do some voice overs for our members as well.
Okay, interesting.
I think I'll donate to that.
I'll do a couple of sweepers for some people.
Okay, let me see.
Got an email here.
What was this?
Oh, this is some indie music.
Shoot.
I'm just going to leave that in the show notes.
You can check that out for yourself.
I already played the promo here.
Okay, bound unto the daily download.
And this is a great podcast.
This is a podcast about poop.
And it's really great.
The host of this podcast does a show from his studio.
What he calls the studio, which is basically his bathroom.
And he had a great guest on this morning.
And I guess he's doing this through Wi-Fi and his laptop
and through Skype.
It was the maker of,
it was a shrink to ring.
The minty fresh feeling.
This is a very interesting product.
Let's just play a little bit of the daily downloads
so you get an idea what this podcast is about.
This is what Christine and I listened to this morning
on the way to school.
Crack this up.
Gather round children.
It's time for the daily download with Chris Rockwell.
Welcome everyone.
This is the daily download.
And I'm your host, Chris Rockwell.
It's January 25th, 2005.
Just one day from when I shoot coffee up my ass.
Oh, joy.
Well, we have a great guest on the show today.
And I have a filling.
It's going to be a long show.
We better get into the studio right now.
Last night for dinner, we had hamburgers and raw spinach.
Hmm.
Seriously, didn't the fucking blast?
I know.
I received some spink terrain in the middle last week.
So let me just talk about this spink terrain.
This is an actual product.
And I want you to listen to the daily download.
I'm, in fact, I'm going to put it into that cast plaster feed
that I've been talking about, which you can subscribe to.
So anything I drop in there, you'll automatically get if you subscribe to that feed.
So I'll drop in a daily download.
Because here is a podcast actually promoting a product which can only really work in this realm.
I mean, sure on the on the web as well.
But this is a series of business.
I'm going to load down on this product.
So I've invited the inventor to come on the show to answer some questions.
I'm joined now with Bruce last.
Wow, that sounded like an edit right there.
There is spink terrain.
Welcome to the show.
Hey man, how's it going?
You know, if you want to like get on the inner circle, I like to be for it to as a Thomas Edison of ass.
Thomas Edison.
This whole show is filled with ass and poop references at one point.
Question is, you know, so what is the target audience for the,
I should find find that home outside.
But right now, we have a, you can move or get in deep.
You know, when I was squatting,
and of course, let's see if I can find it.
195 Gs for a common.
And you can.
Great.
Wow.
Yeah, it's a big demographic.
So, you know, here it is.
There's got to be a product that could address this situation.
And that's when I went into the lab and I developed spink terrain.
Wow.
I think I'm one second.
I need to push a little bit.
All right.
This whole world.
No problem.
Is there a demographic for citrus?
Who uses that?
Yeah.
My demographic for the product is anybody with an ass.
I love it.
MindyFresh.com.
And the daily download you can find it.
And I put it on not org in the podcast directory.
And of course, I'll post a link to this in the show notes.
He's a Dutch band called Tracker.
Brand new podcast music on the source code.
Oh, me tonight.
Turn up the light.
So space we have to fill.
And all the ghosts we have to kill are not the ones to break our will.
Forevermore.
And so it's coming out today.
So it's coming out.
Screaming out just coming back to sleep.
Now that you're freaking out.
All the way.
We'll be there until we're free.
And make me stay.
Call me tonight.
Turn up the light.
So space you have to fill.
And all the ghosts you have to kill are not the ones to break your will.
Forevermore.
So it's coming out today.
Yeah, it's coming out.
Screaming out just coming back to sleep.
Now that you're freaking out.
All the way.
We'll be there until we're free.