Well, here we are.
Just finishing up my touch interview.
Excuse me.
The one on a sec.
At the infamous Groucho club in the UK, London.
On a moment, let me just get my, who's the paper here.
It's a beautiful, beautiful day in London.
I mean, you could not believe how nice the weather is.
I mean, I brought my leather jacket with me, which is really too warm, actually,
but just leave it, leave it dangling open.
I'm on Dean Street, and I need to go to my next appointment for today,
which is the TV Center, BBC TV Center, Wood Lane,
and that's W12.
I'm not quite sure where that is, but what I'll do is I'll grab a cab.
So I'm going to see what the best place is.
Okay.
I'm crossing Old Compton Street now.
Hope that we're good on the sound.
It should be okay.
I cranked up the mic output a little bit.
And just walking down everyone's in a good mood today.
Lots of people on their cell phones as well.
Maybe they're all the week sound scene tours.
By the way, today is Friday.
It's the 18th.
Is it the 18th already?
Yeah.
Friday the 18th of March, 2005.
This is your daily source code for the weekend.
You see, I'm going to go over to 2005.
Now, I'm sorry.
I thought someone was correcting me on the date, but he was just confused in the digital.
Let's see, Shafsbury Avenue.
Let me see if I can grab a cab here.
Is that the interesting?
I think they should cross the street and get on the near corner.
Holy moly.
A little bit confused in Guilford.
We don't have as much traffic.
And I haven't really gotten used to the look right, look left thing.
Oh, and there's a cab.
Let's see.
Wow.
It's a great source here.
That's...
I forgot how hard it was to find a cab in London.
Let's take a look.
Is that a cab coming up?
Nope.
See, dropping someone off or is he picking someone up?
See, come on over here, buddy.
Shoot.
Okay.
I think I'll just stand on the corner here for a second.
You see, if I can pick up a cab,
there's three cabs coming my way.
See.
Nope.
All full.
The time is three o'clock, have half an hour,
to get to my destination.
It might even be within walking distance for all I know,
but I really can't be bothered.
You know, just stand on the corner here.
See if I can grab one coming from the cross street.
Nope.
Good.
It's just difficult.
And everybody's full to the max.
So anyway, I just did this interview with the Dutch news program,
today from Dough, which means basically two today.
Channel two today.
I think I explained that earlier.
It was a long interview, but it was really nice
because the interview or case, the reporter,
who had come over to interview me,
had really done his homework.
And he had a lot of really good questions.
He'd really thought about it.
He didn't ask me as many questions about Holland
and the Dutch podcast scene as I thought the key would
or that he could have done.
I think mainly because it was interested in all the bits of pieces,
because he once put together his own podcast,
but it seemed like the name.
Okay, this is not a very lucky corner.
I'm just going to cross over.
Two.
Cross the street.
We're crossing.
What is it?
War, door streets.
Nope.
It's not all a man.
Every single cab is full.
It gives two cabs to come up.
Looks like one of the maybe empty.
Yeah, that gives the one.
This is my man.
Hello, TV Center.
It's wood lane.
Yeah.
It's a beautiful weather today.
It's a lot better.
Yeah, it's great.
Is it going to stay this way or?
No.
Can you stay slowly?
Can't wait.
Oh yeah.
I know.
But you have the knowledge.
You have the knowledge.
Well, it doesn't acknowledge encompass everything.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
Yeah.
Now I have to follow you on.
Let me see if I have any more information on the TV Center wood lane.
Yeah, I'm going to the studio.
Yeah.
Yeah, fantastic.
I appreciate it.
Wow.
You have the radius that is very tight.
I'm already.
How much is that?
No, it's okay.
Can you find that?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Okay, here we are.
Did you see television center?
Interesting.
Great.
Thank you.
It's your table.
Hello.
Adam Curry for Richard Taylor.
Taylor.
Yeah.
Yes.
Thanks, though.
Let's look online.
That's the name of the program.
I'm not very helpful, Emma.
Yeah.
Thanks, though.
It is BBC World.
I have a cell phone number.
Adam Curry.
I said send him away.
Right.
You know, actually, it's not bad.
But thank you for the compliment.
My wife just bought this for me.
Yeah.
And I was planning on being shit weather today.
So now it's just a style and fashion statement.
That's all.
Is it working?
So I went one of those Beckham jackets.
Sign my name.
Okay.
Yeah.
No kidding.
And it's gonna be beautiful this weekend, I've ordered it.
I know, just, I'm just a, I'm so tired.
I'm working overtime.
Why are we, do you want me to make it rain, then, and that course?
Will that be better for you?
Yes.
I'll talk to the man.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I've pulled out the trusty cell phone again to, so I won't be so obvious
than I'm doing something to another, like talking to myself, and so I'm in the waiting room
here. It's actually pretty modern. It looks very cool. The guard, by the way, is half asleep,
standing there with his eyes closed. Whoop, they're just open, man, this guy's tired. So
it seems like there's a lot of people waiting here, a lot of young people, sorry. It's probably
like, maybe there's auditions going on today. It's funny to have a cappuccino of cart here in the
lobby. It's not really up for right now. Honestly, I could use a bit of food, but I think about it.
I haven't really eaten since breakfast. Let's see if Richard will show up to pick me up.
Yeah, I think there's some kind of auditions going on here for sure. What kinds of young
energetic people looking pretty bored, waiting, waiting around for God knows what.
Yep, watching TV, buzzing you here is the locks on the doors from the lobby.
Okay, I bet you this is Richard, he's coming down and it looks like a producer. I'm going to put
the cell phone down. Let's see if this is it.
Yes, Richard, how you doing? Nice to meet you. Likewise, I just got your voice
emails that you sent me. Well, first of all, I try not to get my past here.
Yes, in here. Whoa, okay, this is an experience. I try not to be tied down by the mobile too much
to be honest, and I was actually at an interview for Dr. Television today, so I had it on silent.
So I understand what you want. Yeah, you certainly have something to speak to about the past
and we're having some visuals and what we can do. In fact, something else has come up. So anyway,
we've got news interactive people seem to use our lives. Who is a no-doing podcast? I'm interested
in doing some interview with you as well. Okay, so the way I thought I'd like it. And you're
told on the price and everything? Oh, yeah, we'll figure that out. I have to take our cut. Okay,
right, exactly. I said, they can nip in first, and she can ask all the questions and give
me the only one who knows how to do the camera work. I'll kind of be listening and just make sure
the frame is okay. Okay. And there's stuff that they don't cover, like the real basics,
which for our viewers, you know, they don't know. They're nip in after they've gone and asked
some, okay. Perfect. But are you up for me or one of us coming down and seeing you do the podcast
well, here's, no, but let me tell you why, because for the drink, oh, I'd love a drink there.
For the past, yeah, for the past nine months, yeah, I've done it at least ten times. My house
has been trampled on ten times. Really tired of doing that. So they come with a kiss of
smaller hours, like literally a small dv kit. It's not talking like three man, five man. No,
I understand, but also, to be quite honest, let's say what I said, I was like, what do you like?
Uh, a coffee, a cup of chino? Yeah, be great. I find it quite fake. Right. And the last time
I did it with CNN, I was like, it's just, it's not, it's, it's so contra to what podcasting is about.
And it looks so silly. If it's real, it looks so fucking silly because I sit there in front of a
laptop talking. Right. It's like this. However, what I did do for you, I have to notify you.
I'm doing a sound scene tour of the BBC. Okay. So if you want to talk about that, or if you
want to do something with that, I'm happy to do a sound scene tour outside, which is a big part of
podcasting. Okay. Well, that's a good interest to you. Okay. Uh, we might like this, um,
see what we need is pictures. I understand. Well, I'm so pretty though.
Well, probably this podcast doesn't bring that out enough. Well, here's what we could do.
Here's a podcast and we video. Oh, we'll get that. What we could do is, in a beautiful thing about
podcast, when you can do it anywhere, I brought my entire kit with me. Okay. So if you want to say,
hey, we'll go and do a podcast or a piece of a podcast somewhere else, other than my house,
and we can even do it today. Okay. That might be, that might be a fan. I'm glad you're
going to need to help us with that because if I'm going to be, you know, yeah, we can maybe
work because that is the beauty of it. Yeah. I got my laptop. I'm going to do anything.
Uh, the chinos. Okay. So what we're doing is we'll do the interview with them upstairs.
Mm-hmm. Dark room. It's fairly dark. It's quite creative. Dark room.
It answered them. A dark room has a whole different meaning. Yeah.
I'm like, have those here in London as well? Not the BBC. Oh, I'm worried. Yeah.
BBC. It's on to. I like the BBC. Yeah. Now you must know. I'm thinking about this. You must
know Ken recounts you. Yes. He's a WBVH. Well, no, Ken, he may have been. I mean, Ken,
have you checked out Ken radio? Do you know about Ken radio? I've heard of it. I haven't
listened to Ken radio. I've got in touch with me. I mean, I've been doing this job
about four or five years now. And Ken got in touch with me about four years ago. And he said,
oh, you've got to check out Ken radio. What he got was in a sense was, he's not hot casting,
but basically he was, you know, getting his own radio station. Right. He was on the road. Right.
Right. Right. Streaming. Right. Streaming. Yeah. To the next. I do a number of this.
Thank you. I think he has a show every single day. And he's a podcast.
Well, now. Right. I think it's, yeah. I haven't checked out. I mean, he has daily Ken's
daily tech news, you know, feedy hands. Right. Yeah. I'm thinking, I haven't. I saw Ken
of C. S. briefly. I thought I would have thought I just thought he must know of him. I don't know
in person, but I have definitely heard of him. I think I've seen Ken's radio go through the
directory somewhere. I saw something like that. Sure. And basically he was in a sense.
I was thinking about podcast. I was thinking what you did was not necessarily anything hugely
technologically revolutionary, but you just saw that. Yeah. That's exactly right. I'm not a programmer.
I'm not a, I'm not a, I'm not a technical guy. It took me a year. I asked program, please,
you make this program for me. I want, you know, to, to download shows that are in as
enclosures in RSS file and put them on my iPod. That's all I want is. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's not
how difficult can it be. But asking a software developer to do something is like asking someone
to do your homework. You know, so, and, and it's right, you know, as I went through that from month
and did it myself. But yeah, people like Ken and, oh, man, there's a, what's the guys up in the
Alaska, a whole week radio? We've been doing this stuff for years. This is where the kind of
genus, at least on this level. I mean, so you're right. This stuff has been going on for years.
How much is it? Yeah. Creating the final, the final part of the distribution mechanism was what I really
did. Yeah. So, I stand on the shoulder of giants. That's basically it.
What you did is it's very clever in the sense that you just saw that that really sugar here, over here.
I told the people about the things they did. So, you picked it right on. I didn't invent.
People are bloating in the trees. I mean, I suppose it's creating that community. Well,
yeah, I would, I would place this for people to go and, you know, we're still kind of the, the, the
Pied Piper, um, in respect to, you know, this is my, my show has been a podcast, you know,
as one, you know, as long as this is as any of the podcasts has been out there. And so you kind of by default,
you get a lot of people tuning into you. Yeah. Um, no, but you've, you've, you've picked it. I mean,
this was, this was no, not brain surgery. Let's put it that way. I didn't need it. It's
someone with a 10, I mean, I wouldn't have been doing a 10, I would just say four, five years. I wouldn't have
a clue about programming. I mean, it sounds like you made a pretty decent crack. It's actually once,
once you get into it and you get into the zone, yeah, it's like doing a big ass spreadsheet, you know,
where you kind of know what, what's going to happen in cell F39, but you still got to kind of put
the little bits in there. So once you're into it, it's just like a different language. You know,
it's an, and I did this apple script, which is intended to be English, um, the kind of weird
sort of type of English. But yeah, so, and you know, you Google, you say, okay, iTunes apple scripts.
Yeah, I was like, oh, you got all bunch of scripts, you look at it, you stare at it, and you're bang
against it. Yeah, and then stuff starts to, and you know, you put something on the mail list,
or my weblog, hey, I'm stuck, and then people will gladly help you out. So, yep.
I'm loving it already. Thank you. Beautiful carpet. Hello. Hi, Adam Curry. Hi, nice to meet you.
And this is our dark room, which isn't very dark at my moment. I was excited about the
dark room idea. It's a cold room as well. Mm. Right. Um, if you want to just throw my stuff on
not one of them. Oh, totally digging the temperature. Very nice. No, it's cold. It's
eaten. No, it's not really warm, but it's just, it's perfect. Oh, here, I want to be cold.
Yeah, that's nice. Yeah, my office, we don't get to see much of the outside. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm way in the other side of the room. I don't get to see much of the office,
you know, I'm like, you're not nice though. That's a nice one. Exactly.
From where the students dressing them. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm just, are you a couple?
Are you okay? That would, like,
liberal here at the bases. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, making some.
Yeah, let me just decouple. So you can, uh, okay. Thank you.
Yes? What's the name of the show?
The blunt cast.
Be. L. U. G. G. Oh, that's you guys. I know, I fucked it up. Did. No, no, no.
Yeah, he did the bow-coder thing whatever. Yeah, I'll bring this up on this one. Yeah, sure the blood cast sure
That's cool
Excellent
It's outside of the BBC's with me. Yeah, yeah, yeah, right good power to you
I'm just gonna put this up because you got my mic too, right?
You don't think I'd come to the BBC without doing some form of some form of sounds seem to order you
It wasn't rogue. I was telling him that I was doing it
Yeah, and he and he and he was yeah, it was like you guys got a stop swearing and
Now just do this this is what I was talking about
Yeah, so check this out so we they came for eight hours. It's a to Belgium and I said now
I'll do a little show for these guys. So I got the helicopter out did the whole thing, you know
And it was just like you know everything was stayed everything was set up, you know do that again the whole podcast that we did was
Basically fake, you know, so it's kind of perpendicular to what podcasting is about and then they called me like two days later
This would drop out on all the tapes
We got to come back and like I don't think I can handle it. I love you got. I don't think I can do another eight hours
I think they finally fixed it, but
Wow, so the blood cast. Yeah, all right
I love it. Oh, it's so nice to meet you guys
That's it that's trippy for me, too
You know to put faces to the sounds and this is
The blood cast only been around for we've done four we made it all right
Life got in the way
Man, it's art. I love it
It's
Whoops crunch
We'll just record over that another interview
I'll promise
It's an outrage but it's taken so long. I can't believe it. I watched click on left click on yeah, yeah several times sure
Yeah
You know, it's very hard to explain simple concepts. It's just hard work and luckily I've been doing it for
You know since well about a year now. I'm explaining it to people so I'll try I'll try to make it
Okay, really
Okay, can you explain in some of the songs then podcasting what is podcasting and it's in its bare essence
It's broadcasting to MP3 players
Are you gonna yeah, I'm gonna go downstairs. I don't know why we're gonna get probably the whole show or something or somewhere
I'm sure where we can
Anyway, we could go if you
Wouldn't mind us walking five or something there. There's a start-up road. Why fine?
Gee, I'll feel ready to come and talk about fake
Okay
And there's a button we can just get a few shots of you sure. I gotta go
Pleasure. I'll be listening to the show. Are you coming with me?
I've got to head over there for me to now in here. So walk with us for a little bit. Cool
So you don't have to go to Manchester
Monday is Monday the big day is that the
That's horrible
I've been following the whole the whole of the whole of the thing
I
Manchets is looking pretty good
I have no idea what manchets is like
And thank you. They're very very very friendly
Of course
So
If you walk down the street, you'll be like the hearing English accent
All right, all right
There's a Manchester
You don't it's out of four-year or it's not isn't it's certainly not for me. I'm a country boy
Right, I can feel it in a new way
I want to try to work my way back
Yeah
With concerts
This is what we should be doing
Yeah
Concus your man. I'm about to switch
I built my first mode
75 bar
Acoustic I buddy had we both had Commodore VIC 20 and we literally you know little boxes with a telephone receiver
Broke up and then put those in there put the phone on top hit a key and blip it would
Yeah, the Acoustic couple
I had the ZX80 before that I wanted a ZX80 one
I'm a dad wouldn't buy me one. I was 13 at the time. I was so upset that you were and I must have been 11
Oh my good hey, remember the programs that would they play on the radio and you recorded on your cassette
Yeah, and then you'd be that it took at night
Even put the cassette in and have a program on it. I love that shit all you wouldn't because it would just
Fuck off, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Wait, you just like
It was stooling
Good times good times
Dude do I remember that yeah, and how it's time for the program of the week
yeah
Yeah
I dropped out after the 64 and I started doing TeleBasian and I remember telling my then girlfriend later fiancée
now wife she she in my bachelor pad she said oh what's this it was my my 64 I said put it back
because if I get started with that thing it's like I lose track of all time and dimension
and I just need to play together and you get the game that was it but I've computers that they suck you in
another game why aren't we doing websites with people? why aren't we doing CD rocks
right and my god said there's not money in there and said go like that absolutely you're that boy
yeah it was just literally a source of new space that yeah so how do you need a wife that
I said I was gonna ask you dude that's a long story okay well we actually met years before we met
I was 17 and she was 23 and something like that and I was doing a pirate radio
a show in a pirate radio station in Amsterdam in English as John Holden this uh I was 24 and I
wrote a Harley of course was at 17 and wrote a fucking moped and and these guys had just done a movie
called Hot Pursuit it received a fully erect penis award from hospital magazine
and they had hired this British guy to play the lead role and he had the equipment but they didn't have
the voice so they wanted like this uh you know rough tumble American voice
and so I was basically I oh did the whole oh they're oh yeah baby so I was in studio two
in this because it was a big budget you know it's a real it was a real movie
when you were 17 yeah so I was so I was in the studio doing the other ooze in the eyes
I was in some tinio to watch the time so yeah sure of course there is just that boy just
down the wall I baby how I yeah so Patricia's in the next studio doing her album she did at the
time stars on 45 which was the Andrew sisters medley and so she you know was walking it out
the studio she had to get this oh she went in and so that's when we first met and what was the
interesting that's that song so like two weeks later her producer called me at home and said
I need I need this bit I need an all-time American like you know 40 40 45 radio announcer
come in and do it so I came in and he's like hey and grab your gown hit the floor and
here's a beat you remember wanting to swing to you and he spun it up and everything and it became a
million seller the record and we never really we'd met once but she didn't even know that that was me
and now 18 years later those gold records are on our our our wall together so um we both she is
podcaster now she hasn't really done anything for five or ten years she built a really great
cosmetics company in the Netherlands which is just fantastic stuff and now we're kind of now she's
Dutch yeah and now we're just kind of chillin up it's really nice to be not known
are you having fun over it and I love it you guys are great humor yes we did
yeah I'm not American I'm not really American yeah should we um well how are we gonna do this
as you wish I can do it anywhere anytime anything you could do it right here if you want
yeah yeah I'm sure they'd say that oh they do is there uh this is still BBC ground
okay dokey so it's unbelievable that we're sitting here you got what are you just doing this for
pictures or something okay good good not just talk like I'm actually doing something which I am
so we are a podcasting no this is actually quite real because I'm recording it so it's nice
and I got my my stogi it's I had no idea that I thought we actually walked out of a gate and it
turns out that uh we're still on the the ground right uh current first so all of the BBC
current first I've come out of there uh huh well we were as TV sensors which is far more
impresses what were the studios are for the news is um and as various BBC sites dotted around
this part right so this is this is the new kind of media center areas and it's really far away from
waterloo station yeah that's what I'll be doing on my way back okay actually while I'm here it's
good that everybody is listening I wonder if I have a blood cast I guess I don't I have let me say
have so many interesting things that I bought along with me for for the ride for the uh for the
show today and now I've actually opened up my uh my power book is beautiful we're sitting in front
of a uh a nice Starbucks which is kind of on the grounds here at the BBC and yes they have Wi-Fi and
I think somewhere I'd probably have my uh my account actually uh I don't know if I have my BT account
this is one thing I wanted to play for you guys this is a guy named Hank and he's got a site
called podrazer.com which has been the source of a lot of controversy recently on some of the podcast
so this about the way he's been providing a search results and he actually put a promo on an
open podcast.org let's have a listen to this for a second hey everybody to take I just want to let you
know that podrazer.com has finally launched that's p-o-d-r-a-z-o-r with podrazer is a search engine
for podcast and podcast only so why don't you surf on over to podrazer.com check it out
what does know what you think. Take care. So since we talked about them multiple times today
during the uh during the uh interview I figured I played a little bit listen to these bitties
one of my favorite tracks I want to be famous. I want to be famous I want to win minks and
sattens and pearls. I want to be famous more than just any old girl.
I have to pay a license for this you know.
I want to be famous. Go to Paris on private flights. I want to have lovers by school.
How I love those girls I tell you. Let's see uh what else they come across today. Oh you know there was
a new raster web that came out. I haven't heard anything from Pete in such a long time. Let's see what
he's doing. He's always got something funny going on. This is the now-see here edition of the
Raster web audio for 2005-03-17. Okay folks well tonight we're going to be a very special
bit of I believe they call it a sound seeing tour. There you go. Of the office here in
really building. So first thing let me look that chair out of the way and now I don't have a
portable device so I'm just going to leave a computer recording and I'm going to have to let
us see. Of course you carrying the computer around.
There's a furnace back here and there's a lot of boxes and the next thing is some
more computers and it's like that and again back at the desk. If I go over here
there's our first right right here because we've got required right now to have the next night.
Over here like this is around the light. There's uh open the door and let's
go in here. Yeah you can always count on Pete to put everything into perspective. Can't you?
That's perfect. Okay let's go from that to uh what is it? A sound of the day. That's always
fun to hear what the sound of the day is. Let's see what Hans has got going for us today.
So what is the sound? Oh okay. All right the sound of the day.
Something else I like to check in on by the way since podcasting is pretty much
international at this point. It's kind of cool. You can listen to Virgin Radio. They podcast
their morning show. Pete and Jeff. I don't really like that too much because it's just a rehash
of what they're doing already without the songs because well obviously licensing issues.
But I always like to keep in touch with what's going on back in the Netherlands radio station there
has a called North Sea. They have a a show biz report which they do every single hour and they're
podcasting that as well.
Yeah just what I thought boring but then again we've got my buddy Rev Tim for the
inspirational message of the day. He's even stalled on my rant while not my transmitters.
He'd use the transmitters bit. It's great.
Sorry. Can you just talk me through what you've got on here with a different set? Sure. Well actually
a couple of things. Let me just get rid of this. Okay the way I record actually is quite simple.
You know I'll open up my, oh this is no one's really seeing this. Okay this is how I prep my show
that's why it's called DSC Daily Source Code Temp. It's an outline. Some things don't change at the top
so I've got my my show details that may change just the date so that's clearly an old date.
And these are all individual files. I usually start off with one of these. Now what's cool about this
is all I have to do is hit command and a comma and over to the left. You'll see
or it's starting up. You'll see that it opens up a quick time window. Do you want to do that again?
Yeah sure. Sure. So I could either double click this or I could just hit a keyboard command
which is the Apple key and a comma and immediately opens up right there. It opens up a quick time
player. So what I'll do is now open up my sweeper and then I'll open up my power of pure intellect.
So I kind of line these up in a row and then I've got a mash up here as an email about it.
So I haven't actually downloaded or put that one in so I can go to my
my tools menu over here. I'll say load new files. Now it's going to load up new files and bring
it my file library. Oh this is no one's ever really seen this. I'll tell you this is a
fine. So what this program does is it basically scans through a folder of MP3 files and pulls
out the ID3 information and puts it into my playlist. So a young palette which a lot of you have
heard of, he has his hit test. So it's basically there's hit test groups. There's hit test number
26. So these are all the new files that I haven't played yet. So what I'll do is I'll see there's
also an unknown folder. I don't know what Burger King is but I put it into for a reason. So we'll take
all these, we'll just copy them, close that window and we go over to my rundown. I paste them in
and I just put those in a line up. Usually I put the young's hit test a little bit later.
I don't remember what the Burger King thing is. Let's see what that is. So I'll just
click that. It should then open up a player window. There you go. So just as an audition, let's see,
what is that? Yeah, I'm over here. I'm over here at Burger King. I haven't done for many.
It sounds like a sound scene tour or something I wanted to let people here. So anyway,
so I'll take this mashup, which is called, they got an email about it. The drop system
versus Adam Curry. So that's digital interference. So I'm going to bring that over.
So you see, so there's the song. I'll open that up. So the way I would do it,
it's I start usually with, I hit that and then I hit that and then I say, hey, I think I
got it's right everybody. So anyway, there's this great mashup that came through. It's called
the drop system versus Adam Curry. Let me let me see what that's all about. This is something that
came through. I haven't listed as a TSA mashup. I'm not quite sure what that means. Let's check it out.
This is a digital interference. Oh, it's about, it's a mix, it's a mashup of me complaining
about airport security in the States. It's really cool.
It's really funny, actually.
Not protecting. I won't do a PML, not this.
OPML, oh boy. OPML was the language that this outliner talks. So,
if I want to export this, it actually is exported as a version of XML. So it's structured data,
even though it looks kind of kind of unstructured. You can make these nodes all kinds of
exciting things. So as you can see, in this case these nodes, when I click on them, they open up a
sound file, but a node can also just have other stuff behind it. So for instance, pod safe is
like a collection of pod safe music that I haven't played yet. It's only one or mashups,
for instance. I got several of those. So, and it's all cut and paste and you can move stuff up and down.
It's just a way of organizing stuff. It's, you know, it's what we do in the broadcast world, right?
We have a rundown of stuff. So every day, young polette, blesses heart, sends me the hit test,
and I think I can play it right now.
Want to play? Ready? Ready? Okay. Okay. Because then you got to play along. You got to guess the song.
Now, your eye tag here doesn't actually, is not playing any role root hall. No. You're recording
your podcast and I need some shots of that. Yeah, yeah, you can do it with that. I agree with her.
So have you been continuously recording for the last 4-8? You just left it running, can you?
Yeah, I remember. Two and a half hours. How long is the battery?
Well, it's still full. So, I put a fresh one in before I, before I started.
Haven't found out yet. This is the longest I've actually done this.
But I'm to edit this down because there's no way, you know, there's absolutely no way this feels.
That's okay. I mean, the cab ride was half an hour of nothing. I talked to the cabbie for like
10 minutes. You know, it's like, and then I'm just looking for anything that you could put into your podcast.
Yeah, sure. Just hear aware of this. No, no, no. So I felt really self conscious of the back going,
I hope he doesn't hear me. All right. But he'll think I'm an idiot talking to myself.
All casting star of dishes is basically taking anything you want from the world around you.
Yeah. I know you can put it online without having to ask anyone to mention all. Well,
No, I don't know. I think the BBC is covering me on this one. So come on, play along with the hit test. Let's see if we can
We're going to get you all the time for the hit test.
Hello, yeah.
Oh, it is a footstep edition footstep edition. I did the five, the next three trials by the footsteps.
Okay, Michael Jackson's thriller. That was easy. That was easy.
How are we get it again?
Okay, and this is number two.
No, no, you know what that is. That's, um,
rocks your music. Love is the drug. I think this is a good one.
What is that?
Very good. Very good. You don't know if it's right. I mean, but I'm pretty sorry.
Okay. Time's up. And these are the answers. This is number one.
That was easy. If anyone in the world would recognize that one. Yeah.
And this one's legendary. And what else could it be? The Michael Jackson.
Sorry to miss this guy. He's a young pull-up. He's a Dutch guy who just does this every day.
And he has his own hit test podcast. It has really interesting guys.
All right, on the number two.
It's really different. There's just a few seconds to
15 minutes to 45 minutes today somewhere in there. Yeah, love is the drug.
That's a good idea to do this story.
I'll tell you though. He did a hair band guitar solo hit test.
I didn't know one of them. I didn't know one of them. It was horrible.
Now, now it's a few seconds or three.
I think you're right. Yep.
That was the bass. The bass line gave this one away.
And club chopper canna.
Extra points for knowing the lyrics. Yeah, very good.
I think you just did.
It's not me.
Did you get? Yeah, he came out. He used to come out dressed in his dressing gown.
Well, the first time I showed him the scar I went with my friend and we were actually there with a tape recorder.
In fact, this was 20 years before you were doing this. Yeah, sure. We were on the tape recorder.
And we said that as a school project, we were doing, we need to do some interviews and stuff.
And we were amazed. We got his number from the phone book. He's a dress.
And the phone book. That was great. I found it from two years earlier before he'd become famous.
Right. We didn't go to see. We went down to Chilton Avenue where we knew his parents did.
Not to install and learn. But hold your hands as the door and it's dressing calm. That's great.
And we're standing there, two, 14 euros. Can't take a good one.
Yeah, that's what he's like. I'm going to help you. I said, yeah, we're doing a school project.
Yeah, I just want an interview. I said, I've made this scrapbook and he was so taken with this scrapbook.
He said, do you mind if I keep it for a couple of weeks? And he said, yeah, he was picking through.
He said, I haven't seen half of these photos. Wow. So he goes, come back in a couple of weeks.
And I re-went back and he asked the door again. He gave us a little interview on the door set.
Yeah. And he gave me this scrapbook back and when I was at that, I guess in a cab or something on the way home,
I looked in the scrapbook and he'd cut out piece of paper and he put some blue tack on the back of it.
Put it in the scrapbook and he put two Richard, thanks for supporting us. Andrew and she
got George sign up as well. Wow. That's great. And I met him again years later.
Did you remember it? Yeah. Well, I said to him, I was the kid. And then I kind of struck up a bit of
relationship with him and I had a remiss one after the team. And my parents, very cringe-worthy,
asked Andrew, turned out that Andrew's mum, you might want more something. And so my parents asked
Andrew and George to my profits. Did they both come? They didn't come. They sent me the biggest card.
And I've still got it to stay. It says to Richard wishing you every happiness and life
at Andrew and George Michael. So you're later when I met up with Andrew and George didn't remiss and
really met him. Andrew, I said to him, I was the 14-year-old that came in. Yeah, yeah, I remember.
And he was still as friendly as ever, a very humble guy. I mean, you know, I don't know what he's up to.
You just gave me the best part of the whole sound seeing towards the bed. That was a great story.
It was fantastic. I mean, I was literally, it got some of it. Andrew is the best guy in
George. It was a very, very strange look at the bed. Yeah, I met him a couple times at the height of
the, you know, like, see, it was, um, I'm talking about it. It was the faith CD. Right.
Well, I met him in 88. 88. Yeah. Yeah. Well, he was struggling with a lot of personal issues. He was.
Because I knew his manager, Michael Lippman. Yeah. Um, because he managed trying to
countner Gray Slick's daughter who was working on MTV. And, uh, yeah, George was very, and he's
pretty open about it now. He's got all men. I was such an asshole back then because, you know, he,
he really knew his sexuality was taking one way. His career was taking another way. And he was,
then he got a little messed up there for a while. Absolutely. And, um, because it is saying,
I mean, basically, we're all staying at hotel in Hawaii. This is where he kicked off his faith for
an 88. Yeah. I remember that. Yes, sure. And it was at the Kahali Hill in Hawaii. And, and he didn't
bite an Andrew to do it. Dude, I was there. No, so was so as I. And, uh, Andrew was there.
Elton was playing. Yep. Yep. Elton John was there. John Reed, Elton's manager. Yeah.
Uh, and George Michael and Andrew Richie. And we, um, I'd rather than I started talking to Elton
John on the way to the tennis courts as you know. Of course. And, uh, and then Elton says,
I want to come with us to the, uh, come with us to the concert. Uh, he's right. He was like, hey, Richard,
you look pretty hot. Well, yeah, maybe. Come on. And, yeah, I was 17 at the time. And,
Brian, but not that naive. Where what might be happened. Um, but he said, how are you?
That's what I said. I said, but somebody here for us said, we're all over the country. So,
one of the things in the concert, I'm playing there. Cut long story short. He ended up taking
to the concert. Really? That's cool. Uh, stropping out before he actually went into the concert.
Stripping out, stropping out. He had a fit. He had a hissy fit. Oh, okay. Really? Yeah, because
he was walking in with my brother and I into the backstage entrance of this, uh, blood. And
uh, of the, uh, of the concert venue and the concert didn't recognize him. And he pushed him
up. He said, uh, so you actually use another, you know, drums, like, right? Do you know I am?
And I go, sir. I don't care who you are, right? Yeah. And he kind of nudged it. And Elton has
a freak out. Yeah. Mm-hmm. I mean, this story just goes on and on and on. And, um, it's great.
But it was an unbelievable time. And anyways, I said to Elton, just get back to you. I said,
what's the deal with George White? There's a guy who's not okay. And what he said,
she doesn't know what she is. Yeah. Yeah. That's great. I found out how they would reach
all these quick, these weird, great names. Oh, yeah. But you were there as well. Yes, because I was
working for MTV and we were covering the tour, which I know kicked off in Hawaii. In fact,
that was, uh, I'm going to tell you the date. It was, uh, the cool ATA, I reckon.
No, I think it was later. Was it? I seem to remember it was April, ACA. Oh, seven seconds.
No, you're right. It was, uh, I think. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Because,
and, uh, no, it was April. I'm sorry, you're right. April,
because April fifth, Patricia and I got married at Town Hall, the City Hall in New York.
Literally, it was like, hey, how about today? Yeah, good idea. Because otherwise,
she would be deported, right? And she wanted this contract with me. Right. So what happens if you
don't like me anymore? I gave up my career and everything and you can kick me out and I can't even
stay in this country legally. So what we can make, like, you know, some kind of a green, but
say, well, why don't you just get married? That's a lot easier. And she said, you better get down
in your knees, boy. So, and literally, uh, so we had agreed to do that and it was a beautiful Friday
afternoon. Um, and, uh, I called her for MTV and I said, how about today? She said, yeah, sure,
you know, and so I pulled Steve Leads, uh, the talent managers, and you're a witness, went down,
got married. And the next day, um, I went off, uh, to cover the George Michael tour. Was that flashing?
That means I have about an hour left on this flashing, depending on how long it's been flashing.
So the next part is I'm building this little box that, uh, I just want to be able to mix this in
so that while I'm talking, I could, you know, hit a song and it would report as well.
So I don't, so, uh, I don't want to, I don't, yeah, it's an iPod.
Well, how many gigabytes? How many gigabytes? 400. Isn't it a wonderful question?
This is a 30 gigabytes. How much is it in the book? I'm not selling it.
I'm not selling it. I'm on camera. Yes, you are. Sorry. This is mine.
Why are you, what are you doing? Is that beautiful?
Oh, I'm just, it's not an advert. That's, isn't that horrible? It's not, hi, buy this iPod.
Why are you doing something from the ads? You like that, huh?
Why the side? Is it just a game zone?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, no games. I'm not a gamer.
You heard, have you heard of a podcast? Yeah.
Yeah. What, what make is iPod? Yeah, but listen, let's, uh, that's, uh, I river is what that is.
What's that, what? Run, that was you. So, you think you could run away then?
You could run far around here, mate. You could run far around here, mate.
There's a security guard. It's about 300 meters.
You guys work for the BBC? No. Yeah, we're the time.
Careful. It's recording. Careful.
Oh, so you're saying, you're about why you shouldn't be for that purpose in there.
Because, hey, you think they could run faster than me? Yeah.
I don't know, but you were saying, I mean, I'll hold on to everything.
You guys look pretty dangerous to me. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So, it's just, is this, is this the BBC grounds?
Uh, you just calling me. No, this is technically right.
No, this is like three there. This is like the plot where the bomb is going to go.
Oh, this is the spot? Yeah.
And when does that happen? When does that, uh, scheduled?
About five seconds. Yeah, I love these kids. Yeah.
Two guys. One, get the record.
Grab the iPod. What? Get set.
Better not. I'm holding on to it. And these guys are worrying me.
But I'll see you. Okay.
What are you doing this for?
Oh, I'm doing it. Just a little interview. So, you actually have heard of podcast?
Yeah. Have you listened to any? No.
No. Do you have an iPod? No, no.
Do you have an MP3? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to sleep there.
I was going to get you an iPod. Which one do you have?
Um, so you didn't just go get it.
Okay, it's on. Is it on? Is it on? Yeah.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. I'm just going to go get it. How much?
How much? 512. Yeah, that's good.
I'm going to do a lot with that.
Cool.
That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it.
It's good. It's good. It's good. Is it fake? I'm pushing you.
Yeah. That's good. That's good, actually. Yeah.
Okay. So, it's a mock. I'm just going to watch you now.
It's a, it's a cold cappuccino. That's it.
These looks like cigars.
Whenever I can, I'll play something for you guys. You'll love this.
This is what DJ you don't want to fuck with.
Go heat on and radio very often. Do you?
What are you guys listening to? You listen to radio?
You listen to what?
You said. Sorry?
You said. I didn't.
You got on the on that sound swore.
Didn't that horrible? No. No. It's.
Yeah. This is what DJ you don't want to fuck with.
I'm corrupting Britain's youth. I'm so proud of myself.
Yeah, we got it.
Okay, guys, take care.
Oh, seriously, were they going to nick something and run off with it?
You handle that pretty well because they did it in another world they might not.
They might have. Oh, yeah, they might have.
They're just kids. Yeah, and they're just kids.
Kids who like making laptops.
But he's right. There's someone around here actually.
This is not a nice part of town.
Around here, it would be known to literally grab open passenger doors.
Take bags. Yeah, sure.
Doesn't, I mean, okay, this is London a bit.
That's happening right. This isn't really.
This isn't really.
It's not really up above like the real.
Yeah, and there's comfortable stages around there.
Mm-hmm.
And they're occasionally close to London.
Sure. This is London. This is like.
Yeah, that's, that was pretty real.
And, uh,
What, the, uh, the underground? Yeah.
You think? I don't know.
I was going to take a cab because they're on the ground much faster
or probably a little bit faster to be honest.
At this time of the day, the best way to get to Waterloo.
Yeah.
It's, this goes straight through town on the central line, uh,
Waterloo is on the Jubilee.
So you basically just change up on the street, it's two stops.
It will take you from here to get to Waterloo
maximum half an hour.
If you're trying to get to Waterloo, um, at this time of day,
you'll take you close on it three quarters an hour an hour.
By cab, you're there. Okay, it's it.
So I want to hop on which you want to go, um,
eastbound, yeah, into central London.
Yeah.
A bond street, yeah.
Which is about eight and nine stops a minute.
Okay. Southbound and it's about three stops.
Okay.
Couldn't be easier.
It's been a pleasure.
I like that.
And, um, I think, you know, this isn't going to go out immediately.
It's going to go out probably next month or so.
It's got some editing work to do out there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But Joe is going to want to be some, uh, on, uh,
news and subtracting.
That's right anyway. So cool.
And that's going to go, you know, hundreds of thousands of
getting to Waterloo.
Lovely. So, um, okay.
Well, let's, uh, let's stay in touch.
Okay.
I think, uh, anything going on or whatever just let me know.
Definitely.
I hope you do.
And I have a nice whole day as well.
Thank you very much.
Uh, we're going, uh, 12 days, I think.
Yeah, oh.
Whereabouts.
Miami.
Nice.
Yeah, down the south.
You're my partners down there.
So, uh, we got infrastructure.
Okay, I'm walking.
All right, take care of you.
Right.
I'm actually going to do this with the, uh,
underground, the tube.
I mean, the tube.
Um, uh, let me see.
What's the time?
I got it.
Yeah.
Six o'clock.
Oh, I'd like to go to Waterloo Station.
Can you tell me how to get there?
You go to Bonds 3.
So, okay.
But it would be a lie.
So, uh, can I purchase tickets for that trip here?
Okay.
So, the barn street, and then I change on to what?
It should be the light.
The?
It should be the.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Okay, okay.
Like I fucking know what I'm doing here.
Okay.
See, he's down.
It's about three and four.
Okay.
So, they're going for me.
They've got to put them.
I think I've been in a subway in 20 years.
Okay.
I love you so much.
I'm the cell phone here.
So, I'm at White City.
Station, White City station.
And, uh, taking these subway for the tube to
on street and then hopping on the
Jubilee line, which should take me to
water station.
Boy, now the real adventure starts.
It's a busy one.
Welg.
I might start coming in a bit earlier.
This is the first time I've ever seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my
I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a woman in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I have never seen a man in my life, I've never seen a man in my life, I've ever seen a man in my life here,
We'll be toasters and other advertisements, so we may have a plan some music.
Given the pound, always support your local musicians.
Maybe the RIA will come down to crack on him for performing that song in public.
Okay, now we're out.
Wow, do you believe that?
Yeah.
In this way, you're going to have a great day.
I'd like to be part of that bridge.
I'd like to have a long escalator.
I'd like to weigh down to the depths.
Thank you.
Man, could be any visitor.
An action that construction will take us any attention to.
Yeah?
In the right of the center of the wall.
Thank you.
We'll be back.
I'll be back.
Yeah.
We'll be back.
That's the same thing.
You got to be back.
I'll be back.
Okay.
Take it around.
Thanks.
I'll be back.
Yeah.
Oh, we're going down.
I'll be back.
I will be back.
Well, we're going down.
What a loo.
Three styles perfe.
Dude, I can get used to this year.
I'll be back.
If you get it, you'll be back.
For the end of the year.
I'll be back.
Okay, I'm a little worried that we're gonna, not, that's still good, let's see, how's
the, that's the still recording, yep, we're good, we're just going to let it run out.
Or until I get on the train and actually start to edit some of this stuff down.
We've done it in exactly twenty-five minutes, which are right.
Very right, and the last idea is this way.
So, here we are, people just dashing off.
Let's see, they get the train, we see Northern line, no?
I think I gotta go up.
That's indeed up we go, and hopefully that'll bring me right to water illustration.
That wouldn't be great if I had a connection at the train waiting for me.
Just as I have arrived, we're going up a very long, very steep escalator.
Really busy.
Plenty of people trying to get home awake for the weekend, couldn't be a busy time on them.
These are your day, but everybody's pretty happy, it's been a beautiful day outside.
Nice sunny, and we're looking forward to a very, very nice weekend.
Now, what do I need down?
Where the hell am I?
Waterloo, okay, right out.
More escalators, man, this is almost like Universal Studios.
The Russian metal look, kind of funky.
It's almost like the Star Wars ride, really interesting.
That's design, or if it's just falling apart.
It actually looks like, well, stay down the right, it was small, okay.
And we were really far down, I couldn't hear my ears pop as I'm ascending.
More people brushing by on the left, in a hurry to get home.
Or just wanted to exercise on the escalator.
That was pretty interesting.
I had the phone up to my ear, and a voicemail came in, and the bling deafened me.
All right, let me see, what'll we do?
I think we've done it, now we're going to eat them.
Hey, let's get going now.
When using the voicemail, always touch it, and then I'll get it here, especially when you can.
Here's something interesting.
There's more gates to go through.
I don't know which ticket I have to show.
I have was my return ticket.
I don't tell me I lost that.
Shoot.
All that I said.
This is not good.
Just pull everything out here.
Here, no, that's not even a shit.
I thought I had my return ticket here.
All right.
Can you replace that?
I'm going to wash down.
Oh, boy.
That really sucks.
I didn't even lose it.
Okay, I thought I put it in my wallet here.
I've been working on it for a long time.
Really?
I've fucking misplaced it.
I'll damage it.
I can't help it.
Put it away.
We have legs on the bamboo.
It's longer than that.
Take a tour.
I've just made the ticket.
I'm going to try to encircle my exercises.
We can't have various problems.
However, we have good services.
Operating from more of their own plans.
Go fucking.
Oh, there it is.
I knew I had it.
I didn't put it where I thought I had it.
Okay.
Excuse me, which ticket do I have to use here?
This one here, mate.
That's what you know I went up.
That's the show that you paid when you've come in there.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to encircle this one, mate.
Okay.
Into one of your stations.
See the departure is good for us.
It's over it.
One, two, one.
You can't stop breathing.
You might spill the ground like something.
6 years, we're gonna be qualified to come now, I'm gonna do the walk on the left, let's put it over here.
Now it's me rushing in and out there, flying too, but take me to the field.
I have to do the walk on the left, it's me, it's me, it's me, it's me.
Now to find the first class carriage, which of course is going to be completely at the
other end of the train, time now 1835.
Perfect timing, love it when a plane comes together, and then we can sit down and edit out
all the long silent bits, and maybe I'll even have to show it ready for uploading when I hit
up, see where's the first class carriage, hmm, there isn't
I'm going to turn off the recording now, have a great weekend everybody, bye