Deltis, Jared Charlie, two, eight, three.
I said three.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
And it's Monday how you doing everybody.
I have the cold of the century.
So we're going to have a fun source code for today.
Kick it off with some mojones.
Can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough of you.
You're going to be stuck.
Trust me.
You're going to drive this car.
You're so I'm going to be played on radio.
Trust me.
Here's to the rear of the fence.
I trust you.
You're going to travel the road.
Anywhere the wind blows.
This town's much too small.
We're going to get them all.
The world's a little tiny bowl.
Trust me.
Can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough of you.
Nice, smiling baby.
And what you do is made.
You got it.
You got to move your hips.
Fill up your lips.
Take silicone tips.
Now you're going to make it.
Trust me.
You got it.
Go and start.
Follow my advice.
One day you realize I am always right.
Trust me.
You'll be fine.
Can't get enough, can't get enough, I can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough.
Can't get enough, can't get enough of you.
Can't get enough, can't get enough, I can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough of you.
And if you can't ignore what I just said, you got a different story.
And if you can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get
enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, can't get enough, God's from equivalence, not listed on the pot's sake music network he had, but... it doesn't quite long.
They declared a pot's sake, for me, to play a good morning, or could have to learn whatever you are as you can tell even the PR-40 microphone can't to conceal the fact that just about the worst cold in the world...
Then this thing hit, see, I came back Friday morning, here in the cottage, did my show,
fell asleep on the couch for a little bit, of course, the typical jet lag symptoms.
How did a good night's sleep and then Saturday I took Patricia and Kristina off to Farrowks
to our local airport where the wind commander was waiting for us.
Actually, we had to wait for him as he was going to take Patricia and Kristina to
rotted him to surprise her dad who turned 80 just a couple of weeks ago, so it was a surprise
visit for them and they were staying overnight.
So, of course, I couldn't go, that meant also I couldn't fly them over there because
someone had to stay here with the animals and with the house and just a short, it was
completely fogged in 10 a.m. and it was just a piece soup and really just around the airport
to be quite honest.
And that's the wind commander for you, man, he just showed up and he just circled around for
half an hour until he saw a whole big enough and he threw that puppy down.
You could hear people at the airport saying, hi, there's a crazy Dutchman flying around.
That was the wind commander, but Saturday morning is when it really struck and it always
happens, I knew it would happen.
When you're on, I must have been on six different airplanes in the past, in the past
week and must have shaken a couple hundred of hands at the podcast Expo and this is exactly
what happens.
And you can almost count on it, particularly this time of year and you're in a situation
where an Aaron Broussell, the podpim, podcho, even gave me some of that stuff to wash
my hands with periodically.
What's that stuff?
You don't need soap and water.
You just poured on, it's kind of like alcohol based and still I got it and it's not flu or
anything.
At least I don't think it's avian flu.
It's just a horrible head cold, it's just like just dripping out of my head.
So I've decided for today, we'll let promos and feedback help me along as a nice podcast
crutch.
It's a podcasters like Adam Curry's Platum, IT Conversations, Canada CBC, South China
Morning News, Seen Z, F1 podcast, more than 40 podcats actually, maybe yours too, can you
know what?
I've decided to put the songs together in an album, you know, an actual CD to make
it a bonus.
I'm going to add a data DVD that's got all the garage band files and original audio material
on stuff, plus pre-ripped versions in MP3, WMA, AAC, Og Lorvis, whatever I can get my hands
on.
I'll be selling it independently, if it's a good price, it'll have a nice artwork, I think
you'll like it.
Even if not, you can go or get songs right now and you'll like them anyway for free.
They're not competing because they think they can sing.
They're not competing because they think they can survive in the jungle.
Alright, you better get me out of here.
Hey, guys, guys, guys, guys, they're competing because they think they've got what it
takes to make it in the biz.
The biz is a new kind of reality show, only online, watches nine finalists battle for
the best job in America running a one-armed music record label.
They'll take on tough challenges and even tougher.
Each other is they try to impress music industry heavy hitters in artists like Fallaw, Jason
Rassie, Aac, and many more.
The biz, it's serious competition and it's only online free as AOL Music.com and you'll
never have to miss one minute because every minute of the biz has and present is on demand.
Episodes are already online, go to AOL Music.com now.
Watch show removes 99% of all offensive pet orders.
Aloha Kakko, this is Keola Doniki of Nahena Hey.net, podcasting from the winward
side of Hawaii Island out in the middle of the Pacific.
Adam, I have a question for you.
What pops into your mind when you hear the words Hawaii in music?
Don, of course.
If you think Don Ho or envision Elvis Presley standing in singing afternoon, it's time
to remove that of the 1960s and join the rest of us come in here in the 21st century.
The music scene into what he includes all of the different kinds of music you'll hear anywhere
else under rap of rock reggae new age acoustic instrumental jazz world country and more.
You'll get a taste of the best of all of them in the Mahemahinet Hawaiian music podcast
along with news, reviews, interviews and special features and even a touch of Ola La Hava
Iik, the Hawaiian language thrown in.
But best of all, you'll get a healthy dose of real Hawaiian music.
So what is real Hawaiian music?
It's whatever I say it is.
Heck, it's my podcast.
Seriously, in my first half dozen podcasts, I've featured music from artists such as Kiela Beaver,
Ramiya Ward nominee, Ken E. Rai-Shell, Ino Allah, Kiela, Mahemah, Mahemah, Makah, Sons of Meho,
Pali and many more.
So tune into the Mahemahinet Hawaiian music podcast, post it every Sunday on nahenahey.net,
that's nha, nha.net, it's the next best thing to be in here.
Aki koko koko hui hua, I'm not a normal bundle until we meet again, take care.
Alright, my buddy.
I gotta go to Hawaii again. I was there once with, no, I've been there a couple of times.
I went there with a Patricia Christina Christina was really tiny.
I was a baby. It was a long-ass flight to from New York. I'm never forget that one.
But it was beautiful and I've been to Hawaii for MTV a couple of times. I think I was there for some kind of
indoor skateboarding extravagance. Maybe I didn't mention this before. But all I know is we got there. We did
like, we only had to do 25 links or something like that between videos. It was a total, totally sponsored
on location type thing. And so me and who was there trying to think, I think Ed was there?
I know we got, we got baked within an hour of being there. It was a fantastic time. Really,
really beautiful, beautiful part of the United States. So today's daily source code comes to you
from a very crisp and extremely bright Guilford. The sun is shining. It's, this morning,
was hovering around, around freezing point, a little bit below it, perhaps. And now it's probably
two or three degrees centigrade above zero. And it's absolutely beautiful. The Christmas lights will
be ignited on Thursday night. So yeah, I kind of get into the Christmas spirit here. There's,
yeah, there's a really good vibe. And the Brits, they, they do it. You know, they do it well.
Of course, they have, it's a little bit confusing because I haven't seen a father crisp. Well,
the father Christmas is Santa Claus. But it seems to me, all of the commercial messaging is
very, um, American centric kind of in, in the way it's being delivered. But still, you get that
little twang of, of real, old traditional feel. Not quite as plastic, which is, yeah, it's really,
it's cool. So I'm glad to be here. I'll be here for a couple more weeks, until I go back, just before the,
just before the Christmas holiday, I'll be going back to San Francisco for some more meetings. And
I think we'll be launching a bunch of stuff in the interim. So, it's where you, there's actually
blood now coming out of my nose. Oh, man. I don't know if you caught it. Um,
America online advertising now on the Daily Source Code. We're getting some interesting feedback
about advertisements and podcasting. Hi, Adam. I just want to leave you an audio comment about
how effective the I dog advertising is. Last weekend, I proposed to my girlfriend, now fiancee,
by giving her an eye dog with the engagement ring tied around its neck. Needless to say,
she's been quite enamored with the eye dog and has played with it every day since she received it.
The pictures on the website don't do it just this. It's really as cute as it looks and even more
amazing than than you, one would tend to think for such an inexpensive gift. Tier advertisers,
this advertising really really does work. Thanks again for the great show, Adam. Here's Adam.
This is Trevor Carpenter from Camario, California. I was listening to Delta Sierra Charlie
272 recently. You talked about Microsoft Office live and all that jazz. You implied that it would
help with compatibility and be all cool in that. Hello, problem there. They'll require internet
explorer and not allow Firefox or Safari or anything else for that matter. This bites. You know
that Microsoft sucks won't be so open-minded to include others. They're like technology
bickets. They hate anything that is not just like them. Oh, man. Don't sugar coat it. Don't
hold back, please. I don't know. When the Windows live, which I think is at www.live.com,
when it first came out and during that big presentation for a whole bunch of bloggers and people,
it actually had a little thing there that said the support for Firefox coming soon. I don't see
how that would make any sense for them to only support Windows Explorer. I don't think they'll
gain any traction. There's a lot of talk about this on the Gilmore gang this past weekend,
which is pretty interesting to listen to and Steve Gilmore did the another episode of Gilmore
Daily. You can find that at Gilmore Daily.podshow.com and also he continues to do all kinds of
interesting reports. A lot of it on this very topic at AttentionTech. AttentionTech.podshow.com.
Oh, man. I feel like absolute crap. For those of you who have been listening to the show for
at least a year, you know that whenever this happens to me and it happens, uh, probably twice a year,
Patricia's always there with her witches brew. She's got the soup with the ginger and she
she gave me a cup last night. I was like, I feel like so much better. And then my 15-year-old
comes in with her girlfriend. They raid the soup pan and they eat it all. No more medicine for the kid.
Hey, what's up, Adam? This is Marcus Kouch from The Seen Zene. No, Ben Podshow music rewind.
Now, a lot of new independent music artists are making their presence known by utilizing the
Podsafe music network as part of their promotional and marketing strategy. Now, I'm happy to say that
I've discovered one particular artist from Atlanta, Georgia who will be adding their music to the
Podsafe music network this week. Now ordinarily, that wouldn't be cause for me to create such a fuss.
But this band has one track that you have to hear. This song not only fits in perfectly with a
mash-up type style, but it illustrates the entire problem that independent musicians have to face
when dealing with mainstream radio. In my opinion, this is the new anthem in Podsafe music.
With that, I'm happy to present heavy mojo with radio.
They say they want radio, they want radio, they want radio, suckers never play beyond the radio.
This is that way too fast and they too slow, but now nobody say they want radio, they want radio.
Hey, I'm sitting at the signal all across the land with my mind real tight with it. My right hand
Start the broadcast on the broadband. My mind sounds nice without the mind stand down. I don't take this hip hop lightly.
What you know speaking in those days tightly, the radio DJs don't like me. They rock it wrong and I rock it so rightly.
They play less, this mind less and smile less. It's safe, safe with sex and some violence, it's fake shit.
It's nonsense, it's hopeless, the whole message.
You're the radio, isn't that me too fast and they too slow, but now nobody say they want radio, they want radio.
My own, I can knock on in the quives home, brother known as stone, up on the microphone.
From the day I was born, I never did nothing wrong, I said rock all night to the bridge, no.
This is the radio, I bet the baby's off, you got to pay to be played. The take is off, if they're the same made.
In the same rage, it's Paul and I swear, I hear the same song all day long. I bought you before, just acting like cool to grab and talk.
Racking ball, packing gants and stuff. You call yourself that radio, I call your blood. When you go, pay something to sound like us.
It's slow, but now nobody say they want radio, they want radio.
I call the same with the label man, the other day, I said down the list and he talked like
a song. Keep on the meet-up, be a lot of some, we're never in a picture, me, selling my soul, I said never.
Showing up my songs, so they don't play long, if we don't nail song, then you put the record on.
I'll sing about a way to your draws and the thoughts, if it creates with some change, wherever it ice on my own.
The best thing, remember your next train, now you're the next king, but it's a wet train,
so you're soul, from my pot of gold, you never hold up the road, you been told, the home,
now you put the stand, my frustration, the need, in fact, it's enough that local station,
follow me as I back to the plantation, walk up to the home or say, we can't shut.
I think you're right, this is an anthem man, that was kicking heavy mojo, radio and I think
I posted on my weblog over the weekend, at the pod save music network, which of course is the
antithesis. Is that the right word? Antithesis? Probably not. It's the antichrist, that's for sure.
For the for the radio business, we played over 10,000 songs, and reported over 10,000 songs,
so those of you who are podcasting using the pod save music network to get your,
your especially licensed music from all these great pod save artists,
don't forget to report, that's pretty, pretty damn important. When we have the metrics,
you know, that's when we can start to change the world. Check in the Gmail, Jefferson Dunton said
me an email about sound advertising in school. Hi, Adam, I've been listening to you show for
five months now, first read about you and why, and I think, well, waiting to see the ultrasound
of my first child. And after coming off the high of seeing my child for the first time, I check
you out, well, of course. I'm now a Delta Sierra Charliata, people of the great work. Now to the
point this email, I'm a teacher in British Columbia, Canada, I teach social studies in English
and show my kids how to use songs in other ways of studying to retain information in their long-term
memory. I wonder how old these kids are. One of the many examples I gave the kids was your
idea of sound advertising. Oh, man, don't need to do that to young children. I told them there
was this podcaster, so of course, they knew what that was, who whenever he burped would say,
ah, senseo, and that would then make the listener associate the burping sound with a coffee maker.
I'm not a big fan of advertising the classroom, but my students have now fallen victim to your
soundvertising. The other day during class presentation, where the students burped and spontaneously,
three or four other students in unison said, ah, senseo, another informed us that he's seen the
commercial for senseo just the other night. Well, I'm not sure I like the idea of soundvertising.
I would hate to have every sound I hear become an ad for crappy product. Hey, wait a minute,
senseo, I was on a crappy product that just not advertising. Okay, Jeff, well, thank you very much
for corrupting the young minds that you're responsible for. I did hear from SLOW sent to me in CC
chapters. One of the things are coming together, Brother Love was in the studio Saturday. This
is for the Christmas song that the podsafe artists are putting together. It's a fly-by-wire type
project. Although I see, so Brother Love was actually in the studio, SLOW's in New York, I think,
completely blew the walls down what a pistol man, bundle of energy. Very cool. Bitties came
in tonight. We worked for a while on the bridge. They were so unbelievably sweet and adorable.
And it could be blast to work with beautiful people, two of them live like a quarter mile from
the studio. Matthew Ebal is sending his stuff in as we speak. Now, that was the cool part about this.
Chances vocals have already been received. Mike Viola is coming in soon. He's from
Candyboardshire is Mitch Alden. I'm sure Mitch Alden is. He has a gig of the bidder on this Friday.
So he's actually coming to the studio. This thing is actually coming together. This is extremely cool.
I can't wait to hear the final result. This is going to be excellent. I can just hear all the voices
on this kind of we are the world type project breaking news feedback. What could this be?
Something important, I'm sure. I'm Robin. And I'm Susanne. We are inside works.com. That's
IMS-YT-W-O-R-K-S.com. Adam, because you are the podfaller, we are giving you the breaking news.
Podcasting history. Podcasting just got some more credibility as a relevant tool in mainstream
academia. Adam, I just got approval from my school Pacific Accreduate Institute in Santa Barbara,
California, to use our podcast as part of my graduate thesis. I expect this is a record event
in the first time ever that someone has been permitted to use their podcast as part of their thesis.
My production thesis is going to be on self-injurious behaviors also known as cutting. And I recognize
this is kind of a morbid topic for some people and maybe consider a narrow issue. But really
cutting is reaching epidemic proportions in the United States and also in Europe and Adam, I'll bet
your daughter knows at least one person in her school that engages in cutting.
This is news you won't hear on CNN only on a podcast, but daily source code.
Thank you Robin and Susanne. Actually you're right, Christina and I and also Patricia have discussed
this a couple of times. She does know some kids who are into cutting and another friend of hers who
lives in the Netherlands and we've talked about this a lot. Now Christina seems to have a pretty
square head on her shoulders and she really doesn't understand why they do that. She's very cognizant
of it. A question I have as a parent is if you hear about this, are you obliged to then talk to
the parents of the child that is cutting? You know, these are really, really tough questions.
But congratulations on the both of you of forgetting podcasting yet a step further and into academia
because as you can tell from what I just told you earlier about soundvertizing in school,
we've got the good end. It's all a part of it. Hey, do you know Roger Smalls? He does the daily,
what is it? The daily small source or something like that? He's kind of, well, no, he is a weird
dude, but I want to make sure that you all heard his latest little podcast update. So many a couple
minutes, but this is an interesting guy. Learn there, Roger. Yeah, I'm quite excited because
I haven't played one of my audio clips on last week's fairly source code. I noticed that he wasn't
last play anymore music because he's anymore. So it's a nice little audio clip to me, he's just
now so like him and he just had to guess what there was and I think he did two out of three.
It made me really happy that he used it, hopefully that'll encourage a professional to make a proper quiz
random show because in our life it's be challenged. But one thing that did upset me was people
call me a stalker on that and show notes. Now don't mind how to have a little joke on his show
because now it doesn't mean it. But I've just done a show note. He's typing in life,
family that aren't true. I'd know that happens doesn't do it don't show notes. The fact
people was me quite a lot because I'm due through reevaluation soon and it's my social work
here's about these accusations then I'll be in trouble. That's the thing about the internet.
Someone can be on the other side of the world and it's really nasty about you about thinking about
consequences. And it's more of a say I'm bothering people that never met yet and I could have
been really big problems and I'm just really worried that leaving none with nobody to look
after it. Well I send a number of three months to talk to the eyeballs on on pills. The thing is
I can't understand that all I've ever said is to say I'm a child minor at them. I've kept
in a few fan drawings. They see masks and they're always shows on to a number of CDs. People
call this stalking and I just think I'm just a regular fan. Erders anyone accusing people behind
the Harry Potter fan podcast. They paid for us because I spend their evening fetching websites
about school children. So the honest, I'm sure he knew a major a list of liberty like Adam,
Liz, Ned, by. Then he'd spend the odd evening with a phone book in a map once or in round.
He wasn't. We sure that Adam would want to speak to his fans and know that he has
people weighing outside. Just say hello to him. I know he's right there, he needs no
ways of outs. So he's more of a stalker. A fan who's just young drawing like me or someone
is this word by word to everything that someone says and then write down time codes on their
show notes. And Liz, I'm making something that's creative. All I can say is that people
should think twice about name calling on the internet because British legal system texting
very seriously and doesn't believe in second chances. Now, I don't know if I should say this
now, actually, because I remember a bit of messages and I don't know if she's just
going to ask her that at the moment. When I can take her to the map she has and I'll say that
at the moment, I was all these accusations flying around and I'm not free at me. I can go
to bed so goodbye. Okay, now apparently Roger lives in Guilford. So hopefully you're feeling
better, Roger. And remember, I've got a alarm system. I've got two dogs and two friends named Smith
and Wesson. Hey, soccer girl got re-incorporated over the weekend. That finally came together.
Purecast media wound up with an enormous bandwidth bill and they had to shut down the service.
I think it was a couple of guys with really good intentions who miscalculated exactly what
podcasting success can mean to your band with cost and they wound up with, I think, $6,000
charge automatically to their credit card and so they had to shut the service down immediately.
And there were a whole bunch of the queue potters were over there and
who worked with the, with Madge Weinstein and soccer girl incorporated and Madge gave me
frantic frantic calls. That was a Thursday, I think. Yeah. And so we got, I know we got soccer girl
up and running. I think one to wisdom and the rest of the folks should be up and running this week.
We're happy to help anybody out. It's a little bit early for us because we weren't quite ready to
present the podcast delivery networks. So we're going to let some of these folks into, at least
the delivery part of it. So then we'll give them, I think we're still giving a standard word
process of show blogs so they can just keep rolling. soccer girl has been diligently
porting everything over. So we're happy to have her and glad that she's back on the air and
glad that we were able to work that situation now because that does it really bites. And I think
probably the worst part besides having to restore all of your, your entries and your files is
your feed, you know, your feed changes. And you know, that, and there's no way to redirect, I guess.
So maybe, maybe because this event passed, you know, with such a bang that people will know about it,
we'll know to look and find the, it's funny because apparently soccer girl had moved previously.
And I had actually wondered why I didn't see any more podcast showing up. I thought she just kind of
given up or knew what happens all the time. And it turns out that I was still subscribed to an old
feed that didn't work anymore. So we got to figure out a way to make that better. That's the,
that's the one Achilles heel of all this stuff is that, you know, still this exporting of feeds and
and redirecting of URLs does not quite work yet, which, which bites. Okay, I'll talk about some
parts of music now in the form of some feedback. Adam, this is Albert Liefis. First of all,
thanks for playing my Skype or someone your daily source go 253. I really appreciate that. Thank you.
I was just calling into bad listening to your daily source go to a zero and I heard the story
about creative comments. And I really want to share my experience from a Dutch perspective.
So I am composing my music. I found my own record label to release my own music. And I became a
member of Buma. Maybe you want to explain to your listeners what Buma is. But, well, okay, since you ask,
Buma is the Dutch version of the ASCAP and or BMI. They basically collect money from broadcasters
and workplaces, bars, hotels, restaurants, anyone who plays music as a performance in front of
some form of audience and how small these guys collected money. Just like ASCAP, BMI, which of course
were not against. When signing a contract with that organization, something strange happens.
So a few weeks ago I started my own podcast and I actually played my own song. But when doing that,
I have to actually pay Buma money to do that. So I called them up this week to ask them whether
there are any exceptions to the rule. And they actually just plainly said to me, no, there are no exceptions.
So even if I play my own song on my own podcast, I have to pay. And I find it very, very weird.
And that actually forces me into looking into alternatives that are more suitable for my situation.
Because what I like about podcasting is that it is a very good media to promote your music.
And so I want to give licensed students to podcasts to say, hey, play my song as often as you like.
But when I'm actually a member of Buma, I can't actually really do that. Well, that's what they say.
But at least this is an information that might be useful for you. I would look in for it to
hear your comments about that. Yeah, thank you, Albert. Yeah, bye. You know, this is pretty
frightening. This is exactly what I said was it was the nightmare that could take place. Now,
I can't believe that this is the actual position that Buma is taking on this. But I said,
wouldn't it be messed up if all of a sudden the law came down and said, you can't play any
music on podcast unless it's licensed through us. Well, now that seems to be exactly what they're
saying, which makes no sense at all. You must have gotten someone on the phone who did know
what they were talking about. I would love to see that in writing. Get an email, get it on a piece of paper.
Because then you can take that up to the highest court. That's bullshit. You know, and I've never
looked at the Buma agreements very closely. But it makes no sense whatsoever that they can do that.
That they can force you to then no longer provide any other type of license to anyone else. You know,
that's thevery. Okay, see if you can get that in writing. I'd love to see that as an official standpoint.
More pod save music now in the form from a rant from our buddy, Munk.
Hey Adam, this is Munk and I just wanted to thank you for spending my new pod safe music
networks on pod people on the daily source code. As an independent artist and someone who makes
100% of his living from music, I've seen a lot of changes happen in my industry,
like digital sound and B3s, the iTunes music store, and now the pod safe music network.
The amazing thing is that each one of these changes has been one more piece of evidence to prove
how antiquated and out of touch the RIA has been with what people want. They spend more than
two decades fighting the technology that makes music better, more available, and more enjoyable.
And I'm convinced they all know their time on this earth is soon coming to an end.
They're out to suck every last time out of our pockets before they go the way of the a track.
While the rest of the world has embraced technology, the entertainment industry gatekeepers have
shunned it, throwing stones at it like cavemen seeing some big animal for the first time.
But honestly, I could not care less what happens to them.
Because of listening to all the great stuff that's out there now, all the amazing shows like
daily source code, accident hash, and Pacific Coast Hellway have shown me, the age of corporate
dominance in the music and entertainment industries is coming to an end, and much much sooner
than those bloated, myopic rat bastards think. You can be damn sure that if pod people are being
spun on as many clear channel FM robot radio stations as the multitude of podcasts, internationally,
that have picked up the song, I'd have record labels knocking my door down at a frenzy to
lay claim to the vision the podcasters and broadcast just demonstrated. Here comes the meth.
Some A&R guy with a polyside agree with it. He's get a seven figure salary, and I'd be left
fighting for the rights to my publishing. Thanks to you and the podsafe music network,
we are driving the last few nails into their coffins. And when we bury those
lethargic, technophobic, motherfuckers face down in a shallow grave, the only thing written on
their teamstones will be one word irrelevant. So happy holidays are I A&A. Enjoy one of your last
free rides on our backs because come 2006. We're gunning for your fat, sorry, asses.
Ah, them's fine words, monk. All right. I'll definitely play the pod people tomorrow.
I'll run it out of time for today. There's something I've been that's been on the agenda to talk
with, not just you about, but the Google guys. Apparently Sergei and Larry and I guess Eric
the CEO have been working on putting together a Google airplane. I happen to know a little bit
about a Google airplane. What they did is they purchased a 767 for 15 million bucks and they're
probably pouring another 40 into it to create. I guess kind of the equivalent Air Force one type
machine. And it will, let's see, hold about 50 passengers. One is refurbishment is complete only 50.
So, you know, they've got some, they'll have two state rooms, a joining laboratories, a shower,
after we'll be a large sitting and dining area, the rear will be 12 to 16 first
classes for guests or employees and a large galley. Apparently, and I read through a number of articles,
the guys did a lot of research and would be the most environmentally friendly. Let me tell you one
thing about aviation. I don't know where you guys are going with the plane, but if you think you're
going to be able to get in anywhere you want with that sucker, then you got another thing coming
in some big disappointments. So, someone there is feeding you information and someone is really
hot and horny on the idea of this plane, but it may not be the most useful business tool you can
think of. Because, you know, you can't just pop this thing down at any general aviation air
field. You got to go to major airports. You have to get a slot time. Now, these things are worth
money. You know, this is what these routes and slots are all about. It's not going to be simple.
And what airport are you going to go to? You can't get into every single airport with that aircraft.
It hurts me to see this. You know, of all the planes you could go by, you know, this is it's
not going to be functional for you. I think you'll find yourself in a lot of secondary planes
trying to get to where you actually want to go and you may find that your time. You don't think
you can just land that Heathrow with this sucker. You know, they're going to say, I don't even
know if you can land a big and hill with this thing or you may have to go to Manson. You know,
it's not going to be that easy. This is another big mistake that people make. You know, they all want
jets. I'll give me a jet. A jet's great, but for little hops, man, once you get a king air,
something with the turbo props, which has jet engines, but it has propellers and it doesn't
may not go quite as fast, but at least you can get into all these great small air fields.
And you can actually maneuver and get some value out of your machine. By the way,
I used to be one of those fuckers that was wrong about that stuff, too. So, you know, don't
take it too hard, but you guys should seriously reconsider the 767. He's a guy. He's a girl. And
we've got a bottle. A guy, a girl, and a bottle is a weekly internet radio show for people
interested in listening to an innovative wine podcast from a pair of novice wine reviewers.
Join us as we visit and review both the wineries and their wines in and around Silicon Valley.
You can find us in the podcast area of iTunes or on the web at www.genb.com.
Hello pod listeners, this is Gabe Mac, and this is Gabe B. And we just wanted to tell you about
our show called solo.tv. That's www.xol.tv. You can also find us in the iTunes music store.
Basically, we have a video podcast with interviews, reviews, and cool filter films about
what's going on in the 3-media blogosphere. So check us out at www.zolo.tv.
Do you guys remember Pump, Pump, Pump, Pump? The first podcast for the French-speaking Mac
community? Well, it's me, Stefan C, and I'm back with a German version. So it's called Pump,
Pump, Pump, Pump, Still. It's just at Pumpcast.com slash DE because I have to re-work the
website at Pumpcast.com to make it in French and also in German, but also in English for the
presentation side, but basically I'm also on iTunes on the for the French part. I'm on the
iTunes music store, French. I'm already, I'm always on the top 20. For the German, it's a little
bit complicated. I'm not in the top 20. You have to search for me. You just search for P.O.M.
basically, Pump. And you're going to see directly Pump, Pump, Pump, Pump. And the variant
in German, Pump, Pump, Pump, The E, which you can listen directly in iTunes, subscribe to it,
listen to me every week. My name is Stefan. I'm also reachable under the email stuff and see
at Pumpcast.com. And that's what I do. I do it in French. I do it in German and I also listen to
the daily source code, for example. Hi everybody, this is Gus Kaveta from a Better Day Media.
I want to invite you to check out our Pot Show card of Better Day.
Where every week I talk about alternative health and fitness and provide tips to help you enhance your
mind, body and soul. Our show is always upbeat and high energy with some great music to help
make sure that you don't fall asleep on the treadmill. So visit us at www.BetterDayMedia.com and
will help you make every day a better day.
Oh yeah, they fucking took the same thumbs off of iTunes. Fuck you. Fuck you.
Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you.
Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you. Fuck you.
My god damnit. Same thumbs up. My tunes. I got to do. Winders last time. And the more you shit,
you did to me, the more I like winders. And I do like a global death step by the way.
The influence is to first wave fast on these bases of garbage. You sell with a god damn,
a little bit of foil on the back. So fuck you. Oh shit. Did I just don't know if I'm actually.
Oh man, I hope you noticed the explicit tag in iTunes before you subscribed and subsequently listened to
this show. Who needs video when you got audio like that? Don't you totally understand what you're
supposed to be saying? Isn't that just the perfect Apple switch commercial? Oh man. And
magic actually did by a Windows machine. It got so pissed off with all the, I think I think she's
still uses all her max, but I saw it, the expo running around with this huge HP. This, you know,
actually one that Ron Bloom has is like a fucking desktop, you know, squeezed into a mini suitcase.
It's just, it's a luggable. It's not a portable or laptop by handing means.
And I just got this horrible craved in my stomach. I'm, we're nearing the end. I think that's probably
good thing. Two more pieces of important feedback. One because it's from a listener.
Hold father. Hello, pod father. I'm Scott. I'm not anybody important to pod casting.
I can't play anything and you really don't want me to sing. But I am a listener.
Can I ask you to use your influence to solve a problem I have?
Now this problem may not relate to all you lucky people with iPods, but I've got a $15 MP3 player,
and it can't cope with every possible bit rate. I really need pod castes to stop sending
their pod cast out in all sorts of funny rates. You may not have the problem, but if I get a
filing code, you'd at say 40, 40, or 56 kilobytes a second, my little player can't play it. It just
shows me a message, bad file format, and skips that track. Now it's not my just, it's not just my
player. These rates don't work in my wife's or my son's one either, except they don't get a message
because they haven't got screens. Now it's easy for me to deal with. I opened the offending file
with a dacity and saved it somewhere as a user group rate. But it might not be so easy for all the
people out there who are not into IT. It's my job, I understand the problem, but I'm too cheeked
to buy iPods. I've got food instead. Now if we want to reach a largest number of people possible,
this needs sorted. iPods are nice, but they're not the only music player. Surely it wouldn't
limit people's creativity if you were to stand up and save. 64, 96 or 128 kilobytes a second,
please people. You've got the influence. Thank you for listening to this request.
Now I think you're really getting it sorted out and I would be pod save music network.
There's a lot in there now that even appears to me, even at my age, which isn't that different from yours.
Thank you.
Welcome to Whisper Pearls. I'm Michelle, I'm Jade, and we're not strippers, porn stars, sex educators,
or trollebs. We're just women. We want to talk about sex.
I hope you enjoy our podcast. Whisper Pearls, I create a filter comp.
I've been listening girls. Very interesting. Very interesting. I love hearing two women talk about
sex the way they do. You should definitely listen to that podcast. It's something different all together.
Todd Peterson says, I thought it saw a little bananas down there in my way to San Francisco. It's
okay Adam, I've peed in the big gulp cup at 10 and a half thousand feet over LAX and my
says no 182. In the old days, there was actually a two built into the floor of plans to pee into.
Yeah, they were leaftube. Absolutely. I've actually tried one of those in the King Air. It has a
suction cup on it, even. A little funnel in the whole deal. My car also shook with the sound of the
bananas that sound seeing two are all the memories. Now I true over 500 knots with wind noise and
turbine wine. Oh yeah, as Todd from the pilot cast, I think cockpit cast. Yeah.
And thanks to everybody who sent in email about that resilience, about the social network that
got basically adopted by Brazilians. That was Orcad, of course. That was Google's social network.
And Mr. Peter said, I had an account but left when too many Brazilians men with oil biceps asked me,
what's up? I think that would make me leave too. Adam. Yeah. What's up? Jason from San Diego.
Jason. What the fuck? You asked us to come up with some new names for your MM50. You give us an
action. We do it. We're sitting here waiting for you to decide which one you like to announce one of
the air. What's going to be the best name for the MM50? You promised some speakers and you don't
produce speaker keys. Speaker keys and don't produce. You can't do that. Well I'm waiting for
nice speakers, some MM50s and you speak a cheese and you don't produce. That ain't right. That's
fucked up. And let's just with don't put the comments in the email when you send it to me. Don't
do that. No time would you do. So I want to send you an email with the comment and you're going to
like and you're going to play it. So yeah, that's about it. Sorry. I guess I forgot all about that.
Maybe I just got no one sending anything in. Send me something then. Give me a name. Then I'll
give away an MM50 and MM50 this week to someone with a great nickname for that product, which I don't
have here, which is in the curry condo. All right, everybody. I'm going to leave it at that for
today. I got to cut another pod find. I got to get that up for tomorrow on iTunes. It's going to be
an interesting week. Lots of stuff to do. Lots of stuff to talk about. Lots of stuff happening
and when I get my voice back hopefully by tomorrow will be doing lots more talking. So take care,
everybody. Bye bye. Another pod show pod cast. Stick it in your ear.