Daily Source Code for February 25th, 2000 films.
Transmeters?
We don't need no stinking transmutes?
Autistic!
It's a food curry!
Hey everybody, thank God, it's Friday!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Last time to come to you from San Francisco, California,
it's the Friday edition of the Daily Source Code.
It is February 25th, 2005.
How you doing everybody?
It's been a long day, been traveling, been up to the northern part of the United States.
North West, that is.
The power of the New York Institute.
That's right.
I made the big trip up to Microsoft today to see my buddy ate a curse.
Now we eat the Dutch pronunciation.
I actually tried that.
It wasn't we arrived at building number.
Wasn't I wrong?
I don't know what building to go to.
Man, that place is too much.
As for to eat a curse.
And of course I have a fault that I had to use the American pronunciation.
Eric Huggers.
Anyway, it's another source code.
With some toxic music, the hit test.
And of course, some mash.
The power of the New York Institute.
I gotta tell you, I really love you guys.
You guys listening right now.
You listening on your iPod.
You sitting in your computer.
Checking it out.
iTunes.
What else is there?
Win-am.
Microsoft Media Player.
I really appreciate it.
But I'm so fried.
I almost contemplated that's where you should go.
But that's true.
And we've got so much real time difference.
It's already 630 in the UK.
That's kind of cool.
Thinking about that, Patricia and Christina are about to go in one minute from now.
And they'll be waking up and I'm about to go to bed.
That's actually been pretty tough.
All the time difference isn't everything.
And talking to the girls.
I miss them.
Can you tell?
I really do.
You know, going through airports today.
Seeing parents with kids and teenage daughters.
I'm like, oh man.
I miss home.
It's time to go home.
It's really been a great trip.
And I want to tell you all about or most about what happened today.
Because I learned a couple of new important words that we'll talk about.
As I said, got young polettes hit test on the way.
It's usual in the show.
Also a pod save tune lined up.
And lots of cool stuff to talk about.
But first, don't you think it's time for another...
Microsoft.
Member Baruch Assault.
Member Yazoo.
Check it out.
Let's go.
February 2005, Ruka Salt, man, that brings about memories. It must have been 1990. Oh, man. I'm gonna take a guess. Five.
My first company on ramp. We had come off doing...
We did a promotion for, actually, we did a cybercast of the Grammys. The Grammy Awards. Oh, that's a story all by itself.
But like half a year, no longer than that. About nine months later, I'm just kind of going by memory here, not by anything I've written down.
We did a promotion for Molson Ice. It was, it was actually a great promotion.
You could win a trip to the North Pole for the Molson Ice Polar Beach Party. And we actually did a cybercast, which was audio. And we also at the time did CUCME.
Remember that, CUCME? From the North Pole, from Tuk-Tyuk-Tuk, in Northwest Territories, that was a several miles inside the, the Pole Circle.
And it was Metallica. It was Varucas Salt and Courtney Love with Hole at the time. And it was a real concert that was put on for like, you know, a couple hundred prize winners.
And one of the prize winners, or a couple of the prize winners came through the internet promotion at the time through Molson Ice.
And we did some cool shit back then. We had this road box that we created, this big flight case, which had, I think, 30 modems in it. At the time, what was it, maybe it was a 9600 modems, probably 9600.
Maybe I can't really remember. I think it was 9600, maybe they were faster at the time. But we had this, this great guy at the time he worked for Digex, who, with the guys who helped me set up MTV.com back in the day.
Robert C. Strum RS, and he had constructed this multiplexer system. So basically, as long as you could get, you know, 20 or 30 or 40 phone lines, we could combine those and create one big fat pipe.
On the other end, of course, at Digex, we had a demultiplexer, or whatever, so that you could essentially create, oh, we had, you know, pipe of like, you know, 350 kilobits per second or something like that. It was very cool.
The road box, I'll never forget. It's somewhere that, that thing's got to be around somewhere. Someone has that. I'm sure I've no fucking clue what happened to it, but it was a beautiful piece of work.
So anyway, so that was my, my memory there of Rooka Salt. Thanks to Sid, the Pimp Daddy from the Netherlands, for sending me always supplying me with a fresh supply of mashups. And I got to say, being out here on the West Coast, also on the East Coast, but more on the West Coast,
more people have come up to me and said, man, what do you get those mashups? You know, I love them. And I always say, again, from Sid, but I think also mix freaks.org is a place you might want to sniff around or email some of the guys there. They seem to be doing a lot of interesting work with mashups. And yeah, do love it. It's totally cool, specifically because, you know, it's stuff that will never ever be able to release, to be released commercially just because of the clearances and we've gone through that.
All the time here on the show.
Some, and I just got back, what time is it now? It's 10.35. We'd left this morning, man.
Got up at five o'clock to leave at quarter six to catch the seven A.M. flight up to Seattle to then grab a cab up to, up to Redmond.
So, you know, and just got back on the whatever the flight gets in at like 8.15, 8.30. And so just back in the hotel scanning through email.
And several comments on my pronunciation issue yesterday of aluminium, pretty much everyone who was emailed me agrees that that is indeed the correct pronunciation.
In fact, some English listeners said, wow, you know, it's like, you're the first yank I've ever heard pronounced it correctly because most Americans say aluminum.
But I did make a mistake, apparently Scott emailed me and said, you know, although aluminium is the correct pronunciation.
It's not an alloy, as I said, he goes on to say, first of all, an alloy is a compound of two or more metals.
Aluminium is a pure element, not an alloy. The metal was named by English chemists, Sir Humphrey Davy.
Who derived the name from the mineral called aluminum.
Sir Humphrey first spelled it.
Now I want to get it right now.
Aluminium in 1807, then change it to aluminum. There you go, in 1807, and finally settled on aluminium in 1812.
English chemists like the latter because it sounds like many other elements whose name and in in like magnesium, potassium, sodium, and whatever ends you can come up with.
Actually, you should check this out. There's more to this history with several great links in the show notes for today's show.
I actually wound up here in this email saying, just started to help out in case some limey brick is trying to make you think that you're perfectly acceptable American pronunciation is inferior.
Next time someone says, it's really aluminium feels, what is this? Ask for it.
I should be reading emails. Should just let you read them okay. Anyway, aluminium, it's our friend, isn't it?
So, this morning we, of course, had a wonderful experience. Do you have any idea what that experience could be?
Well, it's my hot topic, isn't it? Is that goddamn airport security camera?
There's all these grown-up business people taking off their fucking clothes, taking off.
You know, at this case, I guess I'm a business person as well. You know, taking off my bell, taking off my shoes, walking on socks, taking off my coat, taking my laptop out of the bag, put it in a separate tray. Why do we put up with this crap, man?
Email from Sketer Murphy also listed in the show notes for today's podcast.
There's a book called Beyond Fear by Bruce Schneier and he's a security guy and actually agrees that most of what gets implemented in the name of security is pretty bogus.
And there's a link to the book and there's some pretty interesting concepts about the concept of feeling secure.
And I'm all for deterring people of doing nasty shit without a doubt. I just don't think this is very effective.
And I think it's actually, I'm starting to think it's bad for business, bad for the economy.
And, you know, it's just, it's a major pain in the ass. It's degrading. I feel, you know, dehumanized. Again, not against airport security.
Don't want terrorists to do anything, not trying to be un-American. But, you know, I actually, I've made a habit now of studying the security personnel who, I think in, in most cases, are pretty much from private firms who receive government contracts.
And these are the same people that I used to laugh about.
I play that George Carlin bit about airport security. I should look that one up again and play that again for you.
The same people that in the, in the late 80s and 90s were doing airport security. One big freaking joke. They're not catching everything. Certainly not.
You know, if you're really going to make it tight, make it tight. Don't put the burden on me to take off my shoes. That's horseshit. Really do a good job.
You know, I saw people, you know, particularly pay attention to the, to the screeners, people who were watching the monitors.
I paid attention to the one lady who was sitting behind the monitor. And she was looking around, you know, and then stuff is going by.
I saw at least in the five minutes I was watching her three bags passed by the screen when she did not look at the screen. They just went by. And by the way, my bag is, you know, it's full of wires.
It's full of devices. It's full of cylindrical objects. Like I've got my, my eye chat. What is it? I cite camera. I've got transmitters. We don't need no stinking transmitters.
Yeah, I got my wireless transmitters. I got enough shit in there. And I also had my, of course, had my hairspray in there, which I think is illegal to take on the plane.
But no one fucking looks at that. No one opens it up. There's no questions. You know, I think my bag is highly suspect. I'm always ready to have to crack it open and go. I always, I love her.
I a lot ten minutes extra time when I go through airport security, because I think in my bag is pretty much always going to get pulled out.
Anyway, did not happen. So went up to Seattle to go visit my friend, Eric at Microsoft. And he had actually planned for us to meet with a couple other people in the company. He works for the
Winno's media player division. He was just recently brought up. Now he's Dutch guy. I've known him from Holland. He was in Rome.
Not quite sure what he was running for Microsoft in Rome, but he got bummed away up to, you know, he's a big muckity muck now, which is cool. You know, like, yeah, go, Eric.
And so he had he lined up, you know, a little little tour and people meet with and talk with and exchange ideas.
And what happened right off the bat, which was so incredibly sweet as we walked in.
What is it? So building, I think, which building it is. There's a lot of buildings there. I would last time we were there was 10 years ago.
If you believe it, 10 years ago. But that was just as Microsoft was trying to figure out what to do with their browser.
And the Netscape browser was out there and Ron and I were actually doing some consulting for them back then.
And I remember very distinctly, I think, vowing never to go back to that place because we sat in a windowless conference room for three days.
And we actually took turn sleeping and pretending like we were awake. It was just horrendous.
And it was really like, everyone had to stick up their ass and it was, you know, buttoned down shirts and it was, yeah, it was just the culture was not my culture at all.
You know, smart company, of course. But this was 10 years ago. And that's really changed.
It felt much, maybe, you know, the walls, of course, that these buildings are also 10 years older. So it looks a little bit more crudty, a little more lived in, you know, there's some spots on the carpet.
But the people seem, yeah, just, you know, they seem much more with it than then. I don't know what it is, but the culture has definitely been more thing in changing.
All for the, for the better.
Very open culture as well. You know, people talk freely about what they're thinking and what they're working on. It's not this really not the hush hush that that it used to be or, you know,
I remember you had to register your bag at the door and, and, you know, they check your machines and you just, you know, you could even crack a laptop without, you know, people bouncing on you was, it was kind of back in those days, right.
A lot of people who are listening to the daily source code, up in Redmond, which it continues to astound me. Actually, when I call Patricia, I said, you know, I keep forgetting that, you know, this thing is not just, you know, like my, my buddies checking it out.
There's lots of people listening to these podcasts. And, um, they had heard that I had forgotten my eye river or lost my eye river or misplaced it for sure. And there was so kind.
Um, I guess the, well, Microsoft has a deal with the creative labs for the, actually, let me go grab a hold of it one sec.
Uh, for the creative labs and P3 players. Oh, this is the Zen micro. It's the new one you may have seen advertised around.
Uh, and they had one for me and they said, well, you know, uh, we feel so bad that you misplaced your, uh, your non-ipod MP3 player that we want to hook you up with one.
And big caveat, this is so typical for technical for, uh, technical technology geeks.
Like, but don't really use it until we send you the new firmware because you got to install that because the old one sucks and you'll hate it and we don't want you to hate it.
Uh, so that was, that was incredibly nice of them to do. And, uh, so I haven't played with it. I, you know, I'll load the new firmware first before I do that.
Um, that's the kind of interesting. It's, uh, yeah, it's a, it's a cool little device, actually. So I'll give you a full review of it once I've played with it. I'll charge it up and I'll, um,
and I'll see if I can get it to sync up with, uh, with one of the iPod or clients to get it rolling. Um, what is extremely cool about this that I have immediately, uh, gravitated towards is it has a wonderful pair of headsets.
And, you know, don't forget that, uh, the headphones really is a, of course it's the final, you know, it's the final piece in the chain before the sound hits your ears.
And, uh, these, I'm, I'm, I'm using them right now. Clearly, um, they're great. Um, somehow they have a higher output. I actually had to turn down the volume for the first time on the output of my, uh,
my Mac while I was recording because if I turn it up, it's actually so loud that it'll start to, um, produce feedback here.
Hold on. So this, so if I turn it all the way up, you can hear the whoops there. Go. So it's feedback directly from the mic to these headphones.
That's just, that's pretty incredible stuff. So they're really loud, which is good because as a, as an old radio geek, you know, you want to hear yourself nice and loud.
Uh, that's what radio geeks usually want. Um, and, uh, they're good. They're also white, by the way, which is kind of funny.
So it's, uh, it did that. That's some iPod-nish stuff going on there, but I like them. Also, that's one thing I've noticed with headphones.
And I don't know why this is the, so this is the design that I like, which is, um, one wire that splits into two wires of equal length.
And I have had so many different headphones. You know, earbuds headphones were talking about, right? So the little ones that go in your,
you're not in your ears, not something goes over the top of your head. Um, where one side of the wire is really short.
And the other ones really long. And I've never quite understood what the, what the design, what the point of that design is.
You know, I want it, I want it symmetrical. I want it, you know, right down the middle. And, and this one is just like the iPod headphones.
This is a great, and I, like Sony does that. Why do they have one side short in the other side long? You know, I never quite got that.
If you have any ideas why, you know, it's clear to you an industrial design choice that they made, but can't quite figure it out.
So let me know if you, if you have any ideas. Um, so, um, first of all, um,
a lot of response to my comments about San Francisco yesterday. Hey, not everybody is clueless, okay? It was just kind of like pointing out some stuff.
I've learned something really interesting out here and up at, uh, at Microsoft as well.
I'm completely contrary to the East Coast where, uh, I'm not quite sure what it is or why it is.
But on East Coast, you walk in and people like, what's your idea? This is my idea, you know, boom.
What, you know, what are you guys doing? What are you working on? And everyone's just, you know, immediately sharing information and talking a million miles a minute.
And, um, that's kind of like a New York way of doing stuff.
On the West Coast in San Francisco and, uh, and also up north, there's one thing that is just rampant.
It's the concept of an NDA, an NDA, and, uh, I think what the NDA actually stands for is no damage announcements.
Because, you know, you all signed this piece of paper that says, well, we don't talk about anywhere what we talked about today.
I think what they're saying is, you know, no damage announcements. Just don't make no goddamn announcements. It's like the YNDA, no damage announcements.
So that's what everyone's about on the West Coast, no damage announcements. We're not going to say anything.
And there's a lot of heat about podcasting up at Microsoft. I mean, I can tell you that much.
Um, some really smart people have really been thinking about this from, um, all different directions, all angles.
And it was just, it was really nice to see the effort and the amount of thought that went into, um, you know, some of the stuff that they shared with us.
And it was just, it was a really nice day. And they fed us nicely. The heat is really cranking up, uh, particularly out here on the West Coast.
And now, um, people who aren't NDA, who aren't under the no-dam announcements coming out with some announcements. You know, there's so much heat that anyone scrambling to say, oh, we got something going on. You know, come over here. Look quick.
Um, particularly some, uh, some podcasts, uh, I guess hosting and creation services that are popping up.
Remember, um, Evan Williams guy is the kid who started blogger and sold it to Google and, uh, and left like pretty quick after he sold it to Google.
He's not cropped up with, uh, with an offering. Oh, it's not quite an offering. He's, he's made a damn enough.
It's, uh, an audio, uh, audio.com. Um, so, um, that and there's another one.
What I saw some other, um, hosting, uh, creation. Oh, God. I should look that up. It's like it was a weird URL.
Lin, hold on. Let me try, let me see if I can find this for you on Firefox. Hold on a second. Let me, hopefully it'll open up without going nuts. Okay. That worked.
Um, what was it? Oh, wow. Oh, here it is. Oh, I love it when you just type in the L in a meeting.
Libsyn, Libsyn.com. That's another diamond announcement that came out. L, I, B, S, Y, N, or in
Curry Speak, Lima, India, Bravo, Sierra, or Yankee, November. It's the liberated syndication podcasting made easy.
Um, leave your storage and bandwidth concerns to us. And, uh, that looks pretty good. It may not be for someone who has a tremendous amount of traffic that you're pushing,
but the price is certainly seem to be right if you're looking for a place to host your podcast and do that cost effectively.
Um, and I'm actually seeing several of these being created. So, uh, damn announcements all the time. And, uh, you know,
one of these days, I'll see if I can make a damn announcement. Wouldn't that be kind of fun?
Um, let me just see why I just have Firefox up. I'm just looking at, uh, let me see.
What's this, uh, oh, a second. Oh, what's this? Oh, there's actually a story about Odio. Here we go. Let me see.
And the time's cool. As your dam announcement. There's Evan. Cool. Alrighty. So good. So there's, uh,
Oh, audible is also doing something. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. We are really cranking, aren't we? I'm so excited about this. Oh, man.
I can't wait. I can't wait to really get some stuff going. And I think that this, this, uh, this trip has been extremely,
fruitful, extremely fruitful. Okay. Let me see. Um, did that, uh, what are we at? You know, it's, oh,
geez, we're already 24 minutes into it. Well, then, of course, it's, uh,
I'm counting casting with Adam Curry. Well, I'd say I don't get no respect, no respect at all.
At the unpolished guys, shows up in my bathroom the other day with a tape recorder. I started to sing in the show.
And I hear him holler out. He's number one.
Hi, Adam. And of course, hi, all 50,000 subscribers, but they be source code.
A little more. It's not for hit this number fifth. Hold on.
Yon, ever since we started with the hit test, dude, we're moving up close towards 80.
So let's get started right away. This is number one.
Oh, I know it one more time. I know what it is.
I know. I get my five seconds here. I'll say 10 C C Wall Street shuffle.
Number two is a bit longer. Here it is.
And once again, I keep saying tears for fears, but this is, um,
and let us say the page brothers Mr. Mr. with Kiri I lays on.
And the final one, number three.
One more time.
No clue.
That one I don't know, Yon, anywhere to bell.
Time's up. Time for the enters. This is answer number one.
It's 10 C C and Wall Street shuffle.
So that's answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
The Commodore.
Oh, shoot. It's the night shift.
Oh man. Well, there's a mashup to be made. Night shift at Kiri LAZAR.
Hint in.
What's going on?
Evermore, evermore.
Going to be some sweet.
By that was, that was without winery, right?
He was a long gone.
Lion and for the third answer.
What is this?
I really hope you got this one.
I screwed it up.
I'm not saying anything about this song.
Okay.
Oh man.
It's Patricia again.
Of course.
Oh man, I'm in so much fucking trouble again.
Well, Adam, I hope you didn't screw up again.
And this is why it's too late to hard again.
Patricia Pie.
Well, this concludes the hit list for today.
Number 15.
As always, feedback is welcome at hittest.gmail.com.
An information about the hittest and the hittest podcast can be found at www.yumpolet.nl.
That's J-A-N-V-O-L-E-T-D-D-N-L.
See you next time, Adam, for number 16. Bye-bye.
Okay, y'all.
Look.
Now we have some serious issues.
Oh shit.
I'm in so much crap now.
I can't believe it's the second time you've played a song by Patricia that I've missed.
Okay.
Well, that's going to be a really nice homecoming.
I can't wait to be homecoming.
And I'm in trouble.
Damn.
Fod save music now on the source code.
Nicholas Otto from Long Winter.
Here's living on the edge on the David source code.
Woody clips
Same thing, no more but without the fear.
Life double is getting dressed.
Night down in the sky and...
You can judge a wise man by the color of his skin
Dude, what the fuck was that?
That's lame.
I thought there was a whole song.
Oh man.
Okay, well then I totally blew the production for it today.
Didn't I?
Hey listen.
Remember, I'm under no damn announcements, but keep your eye on it.
I put it on the organcurry.com.
Just a thought.
All right, everybody, I'm off.
I'm off the bed.
I'm wiped out.
Time to catch some seeds.
As always, it's adamaccurry.com.
Dailysourcecode.com.
Dailysourcecode.com is we can find all the shares in the pod.
Just power.
If you want to leave a comment on the weblog www.curry.com
And I will probably do an inflight podcast wrapping up the entire week
as I head home tomorrow
from SFO to plan.
Let's get the outline into history.
Oh, what's your mind?
I have to call a card to take me out.
Thank you for reminding me.
And I'll probably be back
to stay inside New York around mid-mart.
So, looking forward to seeing you all again.
Remember, no damn announcements.
Bye bye.
Thank you.