Delta Sierra Charly 2...4...4...
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped my ass...
...than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no thinking, can we?
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
It is Thursday the 22nd of September, good morning from Northern California.
Once again, coming to you from the Curry Condo, how you doing?
Okay, I've got my regime set now.
Here's how it works every single morning.
Eyes awake just before the alarm clock goes off.
Because light streaming into the room.
Do some email on the blackberry, and then get ready for this or else go.
So freaking sad, then.
I swear to God, I wake up and like, let me just check my messages.
I think I'm actually getting better in my email, though.
Oh, let's see, it's 9.
It's about 9 a.m. here in the condo in San Francisco, California.
Three main topics today, which will be about the hate podcast that we discussed yesterday.
A little bit more on the sound-vertising experiments.
I actually may have four different topics.
Let me regroup here.
Yeah, so that's two.
I don't remember what I was going to talk about.
Right now we have, I think several members of the pod show family are roaming around San Francisco.
Doing sound-steens towards Will Smith is in town, doing a movie.
I think that you could try to finagle their way on the sets and do stuff.
So you could get anything sent in, then I'll let definitely put it on.
If it comes in the next few minutes, of course.
So, as I awakened, and your day has probably already started.
Once again, it's very, very foggy outside, and here on the 24th floor and the condo,
the fog just kind of rolls on it, and it's a little bit gloomy, although I do know it will burn off later.
But it made me think of Patricia.
So I thought I'd play one of her songs since I miss her and London too.
A foggy day in London town.
It had me low.
It had me down.
I'll feel the morning with much alone.
The bridges museum had lots to show.
How long I wondered, could this thing last, but the age of miracles?
It hadn't passed, and suddenly I saw you standing right there,
and in foggy London town, the sun was shining shining everywhere.
So I thought I'd play one of her songs since I miss her and London town.
A foggy day in London town.
It had me low.
It had me down.
I'll feel the morning with much alone.
The bridges museum had lots to show.
How long I wondered, could this thing last, but the age of miracles?
It hadn't passed, and suddenly I saw you standing right there,
and in foggy London town, but the sun was shining everywhere.
Girl has some pipes.
Oh, it gives me goosebumps.
Okay, that helped.
Yeah, that woke me up a little bit.
Good to hear my wife.
I only talked to her once a day, because that's why we've talked about time differences being in California.
I got to get up, I got to do my stuff, and by the time I really have,
I'd like to chat for at least half an hour, catch up on what's going on.
It's already 9pm over there, and I'm still in morning, go get a mode,
and she's in winded down decompression mode.
So that's a little bit tough, but only about a week now before I'll be going back,
and we will be, oh, there's another great song.
If I have this song, I'll play it, I'll play a snippet for you, hold on.
Oh, I fixed iTunes, that was my other topic that I was going to talk to you about.
Well, I didn't really fix it, but I figured out how to make it work again.
I didn't fix my subscriptions, those are all lost.
Hold on a second, let me see if I have.
Oh, man.
You'd think I'd have peaches in her with reunited.
Now, I have peaches in her, but I don't have reunited.
What do I have?
I have six.
Yeah, that's a shaky group thing, that doesn't count.
Okay.
Okay, so what should we talk about?
Oh, yeah, iTunes, let's talk about that real quick.
The coffee's brewing in the background, so I mean,
you know, I got to talk about the sound advertising stuff.
So, after installing and reading, re-installing iTunes,
the new version 5.0.1,
still, it wouldn't actually even start up,
and so I figured there must be something completely horrendously wrong
with both the library and probably the XML file that's in the iTunes folder.
So, I trashed both of those, started up again, and of course,
iTunes was fine, and it had to re-index my library,
so I lost my playlist, but that's no big, I don't care about that.
And I'd already lost the subscription, so now I can start over again,
but this time I'm pretty confident that the program is going to be stable.
I guess just for some reason, and I did actually get a couple of emails
saying that folks who were members of the Dutch music store,
and you know, when I signed up for the music store,
actually when I signed up for my whole dot market count,
I did it when I was still living in the Netherlands, actually.
So, never got around to changing that.
It probably isn't even a real simple way,
and it may have something to do with the location specific music stores,
or the XML-associated with that, because I got a couple other reports
that that was happening with folks who were using the Dutch music store.
So, that could be what's going on.
You actually have a meeting over at Apple, was it next week?
I'll bring it up and see.
Yeah, there's some other little features that were fixed here and there.
Let me see, I think I had,
I'm really trying to get all my show notes together here.
Oh shoot, another thing we're supposed to talk about today,
show notes. Oh man, I had some great feedback on the show notes.
Let me see, was this, here we go.
Mike from British Columbia,
Mike Hilderbrand from British Columbia, Canada,
says that it's what was happening here.
He has iTunes that only keep the podcast.
He hasn't listened to, once he's listened to a show,
it gets deleted automatically next time.
Oh man.
I can now I can't figure out what he's saying.
It's okay, they fixed a lot of stuff in five.
Oh shoot, hold on a second.
I haven't done my milk yet, man.
Hold on.
You can hear that.
That's me.
That's the cup of chino maker getting ready to move.
Just blow some steam into it.
Hold on.
Oh my kingdom for a set sail.
Oh man, this is insane.
It's, it's not that the coffee isn't good.
It's just that it's so fricking messy.
There we go.
Once again, we're creating burn milk in a plastic cup.
Oh, there's some reason it's sprawl thing much better today.
How tired do you get up listening to me?
Listen to me do this, huh?
There we go.
Once again, totally not organized.
Hold on one second.
Just let me, just let me grab this sugar.
Don't go away.
Okay.
Here we go.
There we go.
Yes fantastic.
So the reason why I'm not quite as organized
is I have a new system now for my email.
Let me talk to you about this because those of you who are using Gmail
and really like it.
But still want to take advantage of most of the Gmail features
and a lot of the features of the Blackberry.
By the way, I've been getting questions about which Blackberry
I have.
I have the 7290.
It's the plastic one with the, you know,
with the type of multiple keyboard.
I really like this device because, well, a number of reasons.
First of all, the keyboard does not suck.
I can type pretty fast with two thumbs.
Probably not much slower.
It might even be fast.
I should judge it time that I'm not a,
I'm not a blind type this.
I use probably six fingers,
depending on what my mood is.
Never learned to type properly.
And I do have to look at the keyboard once in a while.
But on the Blackberry, it goes pretty fast.
And the keys have good feedback, good response.
So you know when you hit it,
there has lots of shortcuts.
You know, if you want to do a capitalize letter,
you just hold the key down and it turns into a cap real quick.
But more importantly,
I can kind of, you know, take it anywhere.
And, well, you know, why get up in the morning?
The first thing I do is,
oh, just a skin through the mail.
And because there's a limited space on the device,
I think it has 32 megs of memory or something like that.
And also the way these guys set up.
You get like a 25 megabyte email,
a lot meant that can go into your Blackberry,
which makes sense, you know,
10 megs for applications and crap and 25 for email.
And then starts rejecting stuff.
So you kind of get into habit of clearing out the mailbox.
And guess what?
That means you go through it.
I've actually started really reading email lists again.
So let me just tell you how I did it.
Could it might be of interest to you if you're setting that up?
I love Gmail.
There's nothing that beats Gmail when it comes to really search-based email.
I love it.
It works for me.
It's a fantastic idea.
The interface is great.
I never have a problem with SMTP servers or anything like that.
Just give me a web browser.
I can log in all my email addresses are there.
And it's great.
Okay.
We have to besides the fact that I've never seen to be able to keep under 99%.
I'm always at 100% and I find myself deleting things.
But, you know, usually people who still send me MP3 files as attachments.
So what I've done is I've set up a number of rules.
First of all, I set it up so that when I send something from the Blackberry,
it sends a blind carbon copy to my Gmail account.
And of course, I've set up a rule that if something comes in from the Blackberry from me,
then it should not be forwarded back to the Blackberry.
Otherwise, you get this interesting loop.
You just basically read in your own exhaust.
And that's a pain.
So that, that, let me see.
So if it comes in from the Blackberry, then it does not get forwarded.
Everything else does get forwarded.
However, if something comes in from the Blackberry that I've tagged and by tagging meaning that I've forwarded it to myself.
And I put, as an example, DSC in Caps at the end of it.
I shouldn't have told you that, and I should I.
No way, but it only works when it's coming from me.
Okay, right.
And then it will automatically label it as something for the source code.
And it'll file it away.
And of course, it won't send it back to me.
And, and everything else just gets forwarded.
So now, as I, you know, kind of get reused to the a new way of reading email.
And, you know, and being reintroduced to some of the mailing lists,
I'm on that probably just sitting in in folders or our label,
then not in my inbox.
And I rarely have time to go through or, you know, once in a blue moon.
So like the podcasters mailing list.
And I'm reading that again.
And it's, it's really fast, you know, it's, it's, it's actually,
maybe even depending on your connectivity.
It's maybe even be a little bit faster than Gmail itself.
And a great advantage is, even if you run out of space,
because when you hit 100% on your Gmail quota, you can't send email.
You can, of course, still sends something from the blackberry.
And it will actually put the, the blind carbon copy into the Gmail account,
even though you're at 100% because I think you can go up to like 105 or 110%.
But I've got, I mean, if anyone at Google is listening anybody,
Foo bar boy is the account,
F-O-O-B-A-R-B-O-Y.
I'm excuse me, that would be Fox Trot, Oscar,
Bravo, Alpha Romeo, Bravo, Oscar Yankee.
Give me, give me like two more gigs, please.
I won't tell anyone, I'll just, you know,
you would make my life so much better.
It would be so nice.
So that's the, the setup there.
I'm, I'm digging it.
I, I, I never thought I would say it,
but it's a great device.
I like it very, very much.
Y'all, let's send a hint to hit test in,
so we'll definitely be rolling that one out today.
I still have a mashup.
I got this whole CD of like 100 different mashups from,
somebody I met yesterday.
And I'll, I'll tell you about that later.
But first, the, the Sincel stuff.
For some reason, I've gotten a whole slew of emails
about the Sincel sound,
advertising experiment.
So, if you're new,
to the daily source code,
and those of you who who already have done this,
you might want to skip ahead and not listen to it.
Because this is some mind programming that,
that is, it will appears to be reasonably permanent.
So the whole concept is, you're driving right now,
or you're walking, or maybe you're just sitting in the,
on the couch and a living room,
wherever you are, pick a spot right now.
Just look at that spot.
It's an object, probably.
And when I'm going to say Sincel.
So every single time you see that object,
you will not be able to help yourself,
but to think of Sincel.
What's interesting, and I get a lot of emails,
is that it also works in the reverse.
When I talk about Sincel,
someone who might have picked, for instance,
a tree, or a particular road sign,
will actually think of the road sign.
So it seems to be a, a two way street.
It's something about this though,
that it's a little bit disturbing,
because I don't know how to undo it.
It appears to be irreversible.
And, and I'm getting lots of email
of people saying, you know,
and it doesn't bother them that much,
but they cannot stop thinking of the Sincel,
whenever they see their special object.
And I'm like, there's got this,
and where are the psychologists out there?
You know, this has got to be,
some kind of very simple,
and that's a college.
This is like, this is like neural,
neural network programming in some regard.
It's really, it's a really easy way to,
to do it.
And I'm not quite sure what we're going to take this,
but I'm just waiting for the first,
for the first advertiser to think,
this is a really good way to,
to do something to associate their product with,
you know,
anything that people want to associate it with,
but just the message keeps on coming back.
We just run through a couple of,
a couple of emails here about the,
about the Sincel,
the soundvertising experiment.
So we have Brendan Cops,
says I get the reverse.
I don't think of Sincel every time I pass,
the fire hydrant that I picked as my object,
but I do think of the fire hydrant every time I hear Sincel,
and here it comes.
I was listening to Dawn and Drew the other day,
and they mentioned Sincel when Dawn Belts,
which used to be my anchor for the Sincel.
First thing I thought of was the fire hydrant.
Oh, fantastic.
Let's see,
Let's see, what's this next one here?
This is from Sasha.
I was running on Interstate 94 from Minneapolis to St. Paul to attend one of my university
classes while I was listening to your podcast, telling us to look at something outside
or window and things and say, oh, you wanted to see if each time we said the same thing,
do we think St. Sayo? Fuck yes. I happen to look at an overpass. Now every time I see it overpass,
I think St. Sayo whenever I see any overpass, I suddenly want coffee. I just need to get one of
those damn St. Sayo machines. Yeah, they don't, the St. Sayo machines aren't that readily available.
I don't think in the United States. So you can order one through my weblog at www.curry.com.
Same goes for South Africa where the sound advertising experiment is working Paul says the same thing.
Don't have a, don't have a recall ever seeing it St. Sayo machine in South Africa,
but it's working well. He picked a cell phone tower.
It's fantastic. So let me, yeah. I got to get one. I got to have one sent over to you know,
where's Frick and JC pennies? They were supposed to contact me by yes. So that's another thing
I got to put on the list. I need my stuff. I'm still eating off a paper plates. This is ridiculous.
Okay. Yesterday we had a little conversation about the
listing or not listing of a racist podcast in the indie potter.org directory.
And we, you know, I kind of looked at it from all angles. And there's so much response. Thank you all so
much for for sending in your thoughts and your comments. And I would have to say that except for one email
out of easily 60 or 70. And that one email suggested or actually said, hey, look, you know,
indie potter.org is, you know, it's a private organization, it's not a government thing.
You can do it as you like. And that's not, you know, that's your prerogative. Then I agree.
But the other 99.9% of the emails all said, you know, indie potter.org is
such an important resource for all things podcasting that even though the podcast and question
discuss them, even though they, you know, well, just no, no one said, hey, I like that podcast,
right? That would make sense. I guess the no one wants to, it removed. No one wants the listing
removed from the, from the category, from the politics category. No one wants the politics category
altered. And they all feel that free speech is much more important and probably by not trying to
cover it up, it'll, you know, keep it out in the open. Yeah, excuse me. Keep it out in the open.
And leave the issues out there. Don't try to turn your back and look the other way. And that is proved
not a very good idea in, in past history. Interesting idea was to set up a
hate and racism node on the directory and put all, I'm put it in there. I don't know.
But it did, it did really strike me. There goes the jackhammer again outside. It did really strike
me that people view indie potter.org as a really big community resource. And they want everything
listed in there and don't think anything should be pulled out. So how to chat yesterday with a
couple of folks at Pod Show and everyone agrees. That's the way to do it. So we're going to leave
it at that. And probably we should all focus our energy on, you know, trying to stop hate and trying
to stop racism and, and educating our kids and our friends and our neighbors and that that's a
much, much better way than to just say, oh, it doesn't exist. And by the way, you know, really to
the block free speech, we'd have to make it, you know, have to stop them from being from talking.
And, you know, that is, that's, we're not doing that. This is just not publicizing something or
or it is publicizing something. So we're going to leave it in. We're going to leave the
know the way it is. And I really appreciate everyone for sending in all the comments. I did make
a big mistake, though. I said that I had to receive that rather unfriendly email from Podcast
shuffle. Well, let me just get to the, yeah, I haven't gotten so, of course, receive several emails
about that because I totally screwed it up. It was not the, the podcast shuffle. Let's see.
Okay, so I've discovered now that my email system is not working the way I'd like it to
because everything that I forward comes into my daily source code folder as coming from me.
So that's not very handy. Let me go to the comments on curry.com.
Damn, are we already into, are we even like, oh, it's 22 minutes already with the hell of
I've been doing. Okay, here we go. Scrolling down. Oh, man.
Okay, so it was not the podcast shuffle. It was, it doesn't really even matter who it was.
But it was not the podcast shuffle who threatened to call me out if I didn't do anything
about the, the code situation. That doesn't matter. I do apologize now. That was, that was unintended.
That's just another bit of information overload and confusion. But it's even worse, though,
as I did look at the RSS feed for this particular podcast. It was clearly someone who would just
throw an RSS feed together and it copied and pasted someone else's RSS feed to get the right
elements in there, which is, that's a pretty standard, standard way of working, I guess, for newbies
who don't know how to, you know, are doing it with a, with a text or a note pad editor or something.
Unfortunately, in this particular podcast, I, I noticed this, I knew exactly what had happened
when I saw it. It was copied from the podcast for one one podcast and I know Rob has nothing to
do with these guys. And then so you can imagine how freaked out he is about this. He actually sent
an audio comment about this very topic. And this is Rob from podcast for one one. I just want to thank
you for letting me clarify this situation a little bit on your Wednesday, 20th first show. You mentioned
a podcast and you were talking about this podcast with regards to freedom of speech and this was
a white supremacy podcast and I'm not going to mention their name. I don't want to give them any
more PR. Earlier this week, getting of the week, I received an email from one of my listeners who
happened to come across this podcast and to let me know that my email address was listed under
their web manager. I want to let everybody know, I have absolutely nothing to do with this podcast.
I have never talked with them. I have never consulted with them. I have absolutely zero relationship
with this podcast nor would I ever have any relationship with this podcast. Once this was brought
to my attention, I have sent multiple emails to them now asking that my email address be removed
from the web manager. Hopefully, this will be rectified shortly. As you know, Adam, I have
tutorial on my site that teaches you how to create an RSS feed. That tutorial has been accessed
tens of thousands of times. And unfortunately, one of those times apparently was by this podcast
in question, and they copied and pasted out the demo tutorial I have and in doing so copied
out my email address and put that in there. Again, I have absolutely nothing to do with this podcast
nor would I as a point of reference. In my bio picture, I send out is a picture from my visit to Israel
two years ago, which was one of the best visits I've ever had. I love Israel and the people in
Israel. And one of my favorite podcasts is the view from here, which by the way, if you'll as
soon as I haven't checked out, please check out the view from here. Harry and Zeva do a wonderful job.
So again, Adam, thank you for letting me clear the record here. I have nothing and want nothing
to do with that podcast and have asked that my email address be removed from their feed. Thanks, Adam.
Okay, Rob. And thank you for clarifying not that it needed clarification from where I stand,
obviously, but that does really suck. Oh, man, that's horrible. Oh, no, I forgot the turn.
I chatted off. And of course, I immediately, you know, there's too many ways to get to me. There's
too many incoming subspace signals as Rev Tim was say. Okay, and it's definite. I've totally decided
now the studio A to the Audi A8. I'm getting rid of it at the end of the year. Actually, it was a
company least that I from one of my companies in the Netherlands still has Dutch plates on it,
even if you can go figure that. So the least will be up and I'm not renewing it, getting rid of it,
because this car is way overqualified for the mission. I don't care about cars anymore. I've had
every single stupid car you can imagine, except a Ferrari. I've never owned a Ferrari, but I've had
roses, I've had porches, I've had clunkers, I've had, you know, you name it, I've probably had it at
one point in time, even if I couldn't afford it, because I've always loved, you know, wow, we're all
behind the different cars, but I kind of give up on it and I really like the car service, the
cab service that we use in Guilford, which is GM cars. In case you're in Guilford and looking for a
good car service, tell a Mr. Mrs. Curry sent you. You know, they're very trustworthy and those are
just great guys. So we use the car service most of the time, but once in a while, you need to
go somewhere or have your own wheels under your own control, so we do need a car. And I've decided
it's definitely definitely definitely going to be a diesel, and I want, and over the course of the
past four or five weeks, maybe even longer, we'd talk about the concept of biodiesel. This is not
ethanol or anything like that. This is pure oil from different sources that you can make a diesel
engine run on. Garrett was nice enough to send me an email about some article about this guy in the
UK who bought a really kind of like a what a pleasure wasn't it? Yeah, a pleasure to owe five
diesel, and he figured out how to create a biodiesel from on the second, from the chip shop.
Yes, that would be from the, the used up, I guess French right, Greece. And it cost him a total
of 50 cents a liter. So that would be about a buck 50 a gallon, I guess. I'm just doing rough estimates here.
He says it costs about a thousand dollars a year through on his car, which of course depends on,
you know, how far he's, how far he's driving. We made a little processor in this shed from
from an old heating boiler, and he says that the the waste vegetable oil that he gets from the
kebab van. So these are vans that drive from bacon up kebab. They're so happy with him. They actually
drop it off at his house. And I would like to do a project like this because, you know, if I don't
have to use oil from the pump and I can make it, I mean, it's more about the principle of it than
the actual price, but I want to do this. So if you know which car I should get, so I do want to
luxury car, and I want it to be a nice vehicle, you know, that can kind of conceit, well, it has to
have back seats. That's, that's a must. And something that, and now, lots of people send me
different information about that, you know, these newer diesel engines can or can't handle that.
And, you know, there's got to be so many who has the definitive answer. I just want an example.
Give me an example of a car you have that is running on vegetable oil, and I'm going to go get it,
and I'm going to make my own goddamn vegetable oil. I'm going to run it on it, and we'll make
that a project that will, that will be doing together. How does that sound? So yesterday at the
Pod Show offices, I met up with Christina, or actually Christy, as she goes, she's a publicist,
here in San Francisco. We're talking about working together, and she's a big fan of podcasting
and pod safe music, and she handed me a CD, and she said, well, this is a guy who doesn't really
want to be known, and the CD just said boots on it. That's all it said. 113 different mixes and
mash-ups. I kind of like this one as I was spitting them all last night here at the condo.
It's the dreadlock child on the source code, 244.
about this, try to control me when you get this mess, and my own condo, and I pay my own bills,
I always think they've their relationships, shoes on my beat, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it,
I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I wear it, I
wear it, I wear it, I say, you know, no no, no, you don't know, now, talk about this, whatever.
The house that I live in
I want the car I'm driving
I want the car that I live in
The house that I live in
I want the car that I live
I want the car that I live in
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, go get that, like that,IIin, flavorful Scoop bloody
There is no such thing.
Now there is the appeal.
Lindy's blues cast brings in the best blues music in the world.
Is it acoustic or electronic?
Or electronic?
Lindy's blues cast brings in the best blues.
Rightly influenced in RSS feed 50g on top.
Lindy's podcast called Rockspot.com
That's Lindy's blues cast from Germany.
Lindy's blues cast.blogspot.com.
And I play that because I often get emails.
People say, hey, you know, the source code makes it sound like podcasting.
It's a US thing only and there's lots of podcasts all over the place.
A global concept.
Of course it is.
But I rarely play a promo in a different language.
I think you kind of get the gist of that one, right?
That was easy enough if you don't speak German.
But let me tell you, my theory on why podcasting is so incredibly huge in the United States.
And it doesn't seem to be catching on as fast with the same,
a mine, you know, same in scenery speed as in the US.
And that is, and it's my theory only.
But I think it's right is because listening has sucked.
It started to suck in the United States.
The radio is the problem.
This thing, this podcasting that we're all, you know,
freaking out about and having so much fun with is driven by listener demand.
Because the radio in the United States became this,
you know, that's what cruise box is singing about.
It became this homogenized, marketed, playlisted, scripted, you know,
tight, formatted thing.
And no matter where you go anywhere in the United States,
you turn on the radio and you have your formats.
Now the most exciting format is the Jack format,
which is pretty much someone putting their iPod on shuffle
and plugging it into a transmitter.
But then there's the, you know, the WLTW light FM.
You know, there's that station.
There's the rocket flight drone.
See you 100.
And then, of course, there's the news back to you, Bob.
And no matter where you go, it's the same.
And this is one of the things we talked about the very, very beginning of podcasting
before we had the word podcasting,
is that all those voices are fake.
That's, you know, those are all broadcast voices.
And, you know, it's, it's part of a machine.
That's okay.
It's not a problem.
But there's almost no even public radio
doesn't do us justice anymore.
And it's the same.
It's actually, it's the, you have the NPR voices.
So I think that's part of what the excitement is about.
It's just all this fresh new voices, people talking like real people
with all the warts and all the ugliness hanging off of the shows.
It's, it's a human thing.
And maybe we're just, you know, maybe it's just time for it.
Maybe our brains have been overloaded.
Now in many other countries, radio doesn't suck as bad.
The UK, for instance,
was a very nice, you know, community of podcasters.
I believe that the, of course, I missed it because I was here.
It was the podcast con UK.
It was very, very successful.
I know they had well over 100 podcasters come to the convention.
You know, that was, it was a big success.
But it's not, you know, it's not the same rampantness
that we see here in the States.
And that's because the BBC doesn't suck.
They do great stuff.
And even though they, they do have the, you know, the radio voices,
they're just so much more creative in what they're doing with radio.
And it's not all the same.
And also, you know, there are those, of course,
there's the time shifting element that's a part of podcasting,
which is very exciting.
So if there's a show that you like on the radio,
nothing wrong with it.
And it doesn't have to suck.
And now you can listen to it whenever you want to.
So that's all good news.
Germany, same way.
You know, the rate well.
I don't know. I think that some parts of Germany,
I am seeing a little blip of podcasting.
Oh, man, someone sent me a Google map.
I'll have to look for that in Gmail.
Someone sent me a Google map, which listed,
which showed by geography where the podcasters are.
And it really gives you a good idea.
And if you know anything about, about traditional terrestrial broadcast radio,
you'll know that most of those countries, the radio really sucks.
So it's a listener demand thing.
This is different from web logs.
The inherent desire and opportunity to publish for free,
so that everybody can read you and read your opinion.
Yes, of course.
People are opinionated on podcasts and are passionate about topics
that hear nothing about on the radio.
And that's why they're making them.
The reason why people are listening is because it's just bad.
Go ahead, turn on the radio.
Tell me it isn't different.
Any market you go to.
Tell me your radio station is different.
Well, it's there, probably, but it really is in the minority.
And here in the States, we have such wonderful inventions
that we can talk about in podcasting, such as wrestling.
Yes.
Am I on?
Hi Adam, this is wiggly.
Yeah, I am.
No, it's not.
Well, yeah, it is.
It's really wiggly, but I don't really talk like...
Open mind.
Hi Adam and Adam's listeners and me,
because I listen to Adam.
Hi Adam.
This is wiggly.
My buddy, Joe and I might let me start over.
This is going to be terrible to edit.
This is now snow.
This is sweet and sour, Larry.
We need to visit this one for now.
And you're looking at your smart, wrestling fan.com.
Hi Adam, this is wiggly.
My buddy, Joe and I have a little podcast called
smart, wrestling fan, wrestling review show.
For smart, wrestlingfan.com,
now each week we review pro style wrestling,
we see on television, paper views,
or live in in person.
Like the WWE, ECW, TNA, ring of honor,
Chikara, independent wrestling, pro wrestling,
Pupu.
Mud wrestling.
Well, we don't get egg.
Any other type of wrestling?
Found wrestling.
No, we don't.
She listens to his show, because sometimes it's funny.
Now 80% of the people I listen to are show,
have stopped watching wrestling a long time ago,
because they thought the storylines absolutely stunk.
And then people that love wrestling listen to our show,
people that are wrestlers listen to our show,
and people that are necreative for wrestling listen to our show.
And hey, new, with Zach Arnold, Zach Arnold,
from poororesselpower.com.
Runs down his Japan news report.
And all the music that you hear in a show is all original.
Either I've written it, or it's performed by my group, Rep.
Now, I know what you might be thinking.
I'm hungry.
Well, you can always get a sandwich.
You can also listen to our show while you eat your sandwich.
So that's good, you know?
And that's what we try to do.
We try to bring out what's good in this world,
through a weekly, pro, style, wrestling, review show.
I hope you like me, bye-bye.
I like you.
I like that show for the pod-safe music,
some interesting tunes on there.
If you haven't done so already,
definitely check out the pod-safe music network.
It's where podcasters pick up pod-safe music
to play on there on that podcast,
and you can see what the most popular and most played shows are.
Most played, well, also shows with most played songs.
And you welcome there as a podcaster, as an artist, or as a listener.
All on the pod-safe music network at music.pod-show.com.
Now it's going to say something really cool,
but of course I forgot immediately what I was going to talk about.
Oh yes, I know.
It's good to have Yonpalette back in the house.
Oh, I'm counting casting with Adam Curry.
I suppose you think you know everybody was like,
yeah, what do you think you're doing?
The artist.
Yonpalette with Yonpalette.
Hey Adam, I'm back from New York City.
I'm still a bit jet-lect,
but I do have a hit test for you.
Still from the notebook.
I haven't had the time to gear up everything that's here in the studio,
so one last time I guess with the notebook.
Three intros and three answers, and this is number one.
I know that one.
The illustrious in excess need you tonight.
Hope you make it harder for me, Yonpalette.
And number two.
Oh, I love that job.
I think I think that's the raw band with clouds across the moon.
I'm not sure, but big one hit wonder.
And the final one is number three.
I'd recognize that opening for that simply red holding back the years.
I think I've got three for three here in this time.
And times up.
And these are the answers.
This is answer number one in hit test number 59.
Oh yeah.
It's in excess.
This is an idiot tonight.
Cause I'm not sleeping.
There's something about you.
The mix is sweat.
It's a side over there.
And it's clear the involvement.
I've got to let you know.
You want to make it.
And so number one in excess.
And this is answer number two.
Oh, shit.
Now it's wrong.
Same opening.
It's Lisa's dance field.
Oh yeah.
We're around the world tonight.
I can't find my baby.
I don't know when I don't know why.
But he's gonna win.
I don't know where he can be.
My baby.
When I'm gonna find him.
I don't need to know.
Answer number two.
Lisa's dance field.
Oh, around the world.
And this is the third and final answer in today's hit test.
It's simply red holding back the years.
Holding back the years.
Thinking of the real test so long.
I'll keep holding on.
The third answer today's hit test.
It's number 59 holding back the years.
Simply red in today's hit test.
Well, that's it.
I'm gonna try to connect everything to, I guess, cast lasted to record the next one with all the gear and the professional Mike here at help.
As always, feedback is welcome at hittest.gmail.com and you can find info about this hittest.
And hit this podcast.
And of course, all the info on the blog.
Let's come J and P-O-L-E-T.com.
Well, thank you for listening.
See you for hittest number 60 with more higher, bigger, greater production values.
If I do have anything to do with it.
So until then, bye-bye.
Okay, thank you very much.
I kind of like the new format.
It seems like you're playing more of the song.
It's nice.
It's usually, I just, you know, I get right into the song and the hook and the chorus and then you're onto the next answer.
Okay, two for three today.
I could have sworn it was the raw band.
Clouds across the moon.
Do I have that song?
I don't want you to hear what I'm talking about if I have it.
Now that I have iTunes back, I'm actually sometimes able to find my music.
Let me see clouds, search on clouds.
Yes, okay.
Tell me if this, if the first couple of notes here aren't exactly the same as Lisa Stanfield.
Check this out.
Well, you have to get through this piece first, right?
Shit, doesn't sound like it at all, does it?
But I do love this song.
Check out the drum.
Check it out when it kicks in.
Yeah, no, no, no.
I'm trying to reach like among the people.
This is right.
I just want you to hear the drum's cape in.
Check it out.
I kind of reminds me of Patricia and I.
You've got to listen to it song, Rob and Clouds across the moon.
You know, as a final thought for today is we're talking about show notes yesterday.
And I tell you that show notes are very difficult to maintain.
Because invariably, I put in a wrong link or someone sends in a whole bunch of information
about a topic that I discussed that they know much more about.
And, you know, it's hard to maintain that.
It's really, it's a full-time job if you want to do it right.
And I've never really done it right.
You know, so you have kind of the way, you know, you have your prep.
But then you have, which is nice to have it all lined up.
But then really adding all that feedback in there is a complicated task.
I got a whole bunch of suggestions.
A lot of offers of people who wanted to help me do show notes.
But there's really much better way to do it.
And it didn't hit me until a two people emailed me this.
Why not use a wiki?
Now, if you don't know what a wiki is, check out wikipedia.org.
You'll see.
It's basically a collaborative writing environment.
And the thought here is that the show notes are put together by the listeners.
Now, there's several hundred thousand people who listen to the daily source code on a regular basis.
That's a really amazing number.
And, you know, within that audience, clearly there's people who know just shit loads more about what I'm talking about.
And also, I'm skipping over so many different pieces of feedback that come through email on the biodiesel stuff on the sound advertising stuff.
And, you know, and I look at Don and Drew and they have a forum where you can provide feedback.
It's very, very active.
So it makes a lot of sense.
I think, though, that for the source code, I'd like to try this.
I'd like to have a wiki.
And so, basically, with each show, I'll just provide a URL.
They'll say show notes over here, right?
And then, whoever has information about what's been on the show in the rundown.
Well, you know, you'll just figure it out because it's a collaborative environment.
I can go in there myself and actually add some of the information to the show notes.
So, but, you know, it'd be much more kind of a process that would evolve over time,
which will get indexed by great search engines.
And, of course, the question is, you know, how do we fit OPML into all of this?
I haven't quite figured that one out yet.
But then, over time, actually, the richness of the information that's provided with this podcast,
particularly for people who are searching for something,
will, you know, will become available.
There'll be more of it.
So, of course, the first thing I need is a wiki.
I have no wiki expert.
I don't know how to set it up.
I've not looked at it at all.
So, if you're still inclined to set something up, I'll link to it.
And let's give this a try.
Let's test that out for a couple of shows and see how it works and see if people want to collaborate on the show notes.
And this could be lucrative for you, by the way.
For example, with the hit test, by providing the answers, you could put links into iTunes for the tracks to be purchased directly.
And it could be your affiliate link.
So, you know, I'm hoping that I'm, you know, by saying this, I'm not creating a huge spam opportunity.
But let's see, let's see what happens.
So, that's the call to use source code listeners.
I still have some stuff to do for a serious satellite radio,
which we're going to talk about tomorrow because there's some exciting news going on there.
And yeah, I think there's, there's an office here, isn't there?
Yeah, there's, there's an office that I need to go to.
Oh, and a final thought for the day.
My God, I can't believe how long I'm talking.
Final thought for the day is that podcasting has such an extra benefit for me,
because we have a company now.
We're working, probably, we have 20 people who are employed,
yeah, things like 20 people who are employed by us directly.
And most of them have a podcast.
And so, even though I'm not in the office all the time,
I know a hell of a lot about what's going on,
because if you listen to the daily download, Chris Rockwell is talking about lots of pod show,
things that have happened at pod show.
Of course, things he talks about are more cultural to the organization than business.
But it's funny, and it's great.
And yeah, the sue, the super extra heroes,
spider-man action show.
I can never get that one right.
And yes, you really get a vibe of the people that you're working with.
And then I know the much more intimately than I would have,
if they didn't have podcasts.
I was listening to an old podcast by Andrew Grummit,
which before, that was a pre,
we should have a BC, it should be,
because before podcast name, so it would be BP.
Well, maybe BP, we call that BP, before podcast name.
Andrew Grummit was, because he was one of the first developers
that jump on and create, I Potter Lemon,
and built a virtual team around that product,
which just by the way came out with two new releases
for both Mac and Windows.
And we're working with Andrew on stuff,
and just hearing him talk and his thoughts,
then really gave me a whole bunch of insight
as to how we're working together now.
And it's a real family vibe, and it's working,
and it's very, very cool.
And it's not something that every company can do,
but I think a lot of companies could benefit hugely,
hugely if you could just tap into kind of,
thought processes from other people in the organization.
All right, with that said, I got to get out of here.
I'm way over my time.
I hope you stuck through all this,
and I will be back for the thank God,
it's Friday edition of the Source Code.
That'll be tomorrow, bye, bye.
Another pod show pod guest,
stick it in your ear.