Delta's Yeracharly 274
Diagonal secrets
I information you, don't be a liar
Adam Curry
Was $60 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
Done the next generation radio content in my ears
We don't need lost digging trees
I like to think I'm flying you to the future
I guess it is Adam Curry
It is Friday November 4
That means it's time for the Yeracharly 274
Let's get it on!
It's time for the Yeracharly 274
Let's have it on!
Let's get it on!
And five good afternoon from Curry Cottage in the affluent suburb of Gilford, Surrey in the United Kingdom
It's three p.m. even later than yesterday
Probably the latest have done in the last no wait a minute. That's not true when I'm in the West Coast
It's about this time that I actually even haven't even started thinking about the show
So not bad. Hey, I'm ready for a party. I got we got all kinds of great stuff happening today reason to celebrate
I won't tell you exactly why but if you've seen Curry dot com if you've seen the weblog
By the time that this is recorded then you probably have an inkling of an idea and
The lovely Patricia will be by today to join our show so
Everyone who's written in and told me that the show is so much better with her. There you go
It's interactive radio my friends. Lots of stuff going on in the email
First of all I played that Christmas song by slow which is pod safe and my thought was it's to create a kind of like a
We are the world band-aid type of project
Having a different pod safe music artists different members of the network participating and then kind of you know putting that whole thing together
And it seems that slow is now gotten in touch with
Ronald Treiber who's a good friend of mine in the Netherlands, or actually an award-winning sound engineer
And they've got CC Chapman in the loop now as I'm seeing on email
So this is gonna be this is gonna be awesome any the email that slow starts off with it says hey guys
It'll be a Christmas miracle of this thing works out and the the title of that song is a if every day
We're Christmas so we'll see if if we actually get a done but I have a feeling that we can so it's so like a big
Multi-track type of thing. It's more like a
Social experiment to see if we can actually produce a record all
Online without ever having met each other and you know basically sending tracks back and forth and mixing it all together
And if anyone can do it these guys can so I'm really looking forward to that. That's gonna be very very cool
See as a comment on bio diesel
I'll have to talk about that later because that pertains kind of to the celebratory stuff. We have to talk about and of course yesterday
I said BST
stood for British standard time, which of course was incorrect a dream peg
Corrects me saying no, of course you meant British summer time not British standard time
Summer time came to an end last weekend when the clocks went back an hour
So now the time in the United Kingdom is back to GMT Greenwich mean time or
You can also say UTC and then you have then there's also the Zulu part and that's even an hour earlier
But that's really confusing because that's like an aviation thing that even pilots barely barely every use
Let's see oh this is a big news out of the Netherlands. Yes, we're talking about the Netherlands being a
Big test bed for
For basically all kinds of markets because of its extremely western culture although that's that's changing every day
The immigration
Issues have kind of gotten out of hand there
But it's a very western culture very modern great infrastructure
They had at one point. I don't know if it's still that way they had the most densely cable
They were the most densely cableed country in the world so high proliferation of
Cable television also broadband is really big now and
The Dutch version of Ask Cat BMI there she is hey baby come on in. I was just talking about Buma Stemina
Great grab the head fuck I got headphones for you. Oh, yeah. Oh, this is real. Yeah, it's professional
Hey, you're going to pay me for that
Oh
You want to start running through the supermarket
Is it too high? No, it's okay. Yeah, it's okay. It's okay. It's a little
No, it's okay. You got a kind of close mic it. Yeah. This isn't you're not singing a record
I'm interrupting just go ahead
Okay, so what I was saying is the Dutch Buma Stemina. Yeah, I would do my statement
Which is the Dutch Ask Cat BMI they had kind of told podcasters that if they paid 35 euros a month
Then they could use whatever you know, they could play whatever music they wanted on their podcast
You like kind of steam song pass a podcast and listen to so she's doing it under that regulation yeah, but now the end
And I shoot my stool is not right the NIVP the Nadelons Institute for plant the home alone
I would ever do so that's basically the RIA of the Netherlands
They said hey, no way not gonna happen no one has permission to play the songs
You have to clear you know to basically the same thing, you know if you play if you so Buma Stemina will have to come up with a new license and
You'll still you still can't play the song you have to go and clear them through every every record company independently
So that means you guys get really powerful
Who oh the guys who have the podcasts and the beautiful shows and yeah, yeah, exactly
It counts no kidding. Yeah, yeah, no they could totally make in themselves irrelevant so incredibly stupid
Idiots
What you're gonna do about that nothing screw them
You know, we're putting together all right
No, yeah, we're just ignore ignore licensed music it will just play pod save music
That's yeah, we're putting together like a Christmas song. We are the world
Hey, do you want to be on that?
We're doing a Christmas song
Sure, uh, when it it's you want to hear it? Hold on a second. Let me see
Everybody's gonna sing all the podcasts. No, no, please not the podcast. No, no, we actually want to put something professional together
That would sound really good
Hold on, let me see
It's just a podcast Christmas hit
Exactly, but we kind of want to do like a we are the world type thing because that's what the song is kind of like
But then we want to get you know like brother love and chance and you know and all these people from the
Music network and of course there's thousand so it's someone have to make a choice
Hold on everybody adds his voice
Exactly and Rona'll try burn. He's gonna do the whole production. He's gonna do the mix. That's nice. Yeah, hold on a second
Let me I'll play a little bit for you
See I can do this here we go
On sick it's by I don't this guy's name is slow, which is kind of weird
If every day we're Christmas. I'll just play a little bit because I want to talk to you
I don't want to play the music
But tell me this doesn't have like
That's Michael Jackson singing right
And then Bruce Springsteek comes in
This is the hook is pretty good
Exactly, you got to have your headphones on you and hold your headphones like two year
Oh, let me get to the heart
Takes a little while to get to that actually
And everybody
Yeah, it would be
Oh, you can speak yes, never feel blue all our dreams will come true
Every day
Pretty good, huh? Very nice you want to be on it needs a little bit of over push
Well, you know a Ronald Ronald immediately wanted to get the the Dutch metropolitan in our orchestra to play
I'm like now dude, let's just keep it simple
He always wants to and it's and he can get it that's the whole thing as you can definitely get it
No, it would be for free, but it's just I just like let's just keep it pod safe and do it with you know
If someone else wants to add something to it, what does it need like maybe a guitar or something
I need some rhythm and a little I'm pushing do you see how I'm pushing oh yeah
I see it it's a bit slow
Well, we can spin it up
Talk in the mic baby more rhythm so I haven't told anyone yet
About our we have we're celebrating today
Haven't told anybody I'm bleeding today as you're still bleeding. I'm still bleeding. You might have to have stitches
You think no, I'm not interested in seeing it but you should cut her for her pinky on
On the on the vase yeah, there's a piece of the glass the glass falls glass vase yes the vase and you say to my toe
Yeah, and I was cleaning the table and hit hit it with my face and I sliced you sliced and I sliced
You know like a little part of skin and I pushed it back
Really fast and put something around it
All right, and a bandaid, but it doesn't work. It doesn't stop bleeding
Because of your own your medicine you're bleeding to death. I have block thinners and now what I don't know
It's as the stop song stick it in my butt that'll stop it. Oh, there was stop it right away
So
Yesterday was yesterday
Yeah, yesterday we went for a test drive because you know we've been looking for a new car
We found out yesterday by the way from Crystal the PA
Crystal the PA who lives in Geneva and
Was she was in a Miami and couldn't get out because of Wilma
Yeah, she was there for two weeks and I just stay like an extra day or two because she couldn't get out of the age. You couldn't fly out
Yeah, so she found out that the the Audi has to be read is it you know a company lease?
It has to go back December 11. So I've got taxi Eric. I've scheduled him. He's gonna fly over
And he'll drive it back the 23rd okay, 23rd
So we we need a new car and we've been talking about a diesel because of you know my whole hang up on biodiesel
You know who else is a Woody Harrelson is really big into biodiesel. Oh, okay. He was on the
I think it's night show someone told me yeah, he's such a normal guy
Well, he's kind of like me
Yeah, yeah, he is he's bit strange and and he believes in the Oliur baby
Yeah, he's our thinkers. Yeah, exactly
So we test drove a Jaguar
It's not a Jaguar
Jaguar what we said was you know you said what kind of car would you like and I said
I love Jaguar. No, no, I think you said any kind of cars long as it's a Jaguar
No, first I said you mean just a small one. I can do my groceries
You mean you didn't really know you said no you said yeah, but you didn't know you said
Jeep, but you said you ever know, but if I have to drive it, you know, you don't fit in it
You wanted like a little jeep
Yeah, so the pod father cannot drive in a girly jeep. I don't care where I am you didn't want that because yeah, I know it looks very silly
Again, okay, so nothing against gay, but no, that looks so small
Not so expensive nice Jaguars. Yeah, so we went to look for not so expensive nice Jaguars and I said in the back
First of all, the
Sales guy was nice sales guy was funny. Yeah, yeah, and I said in the back and I thought
God, it's a really cheap
Everything sounds cheap. It's for yeah, even the estraise. I don't know what was in there everything was like
Tung Tung Tung Tung Tung
You know, very plastic very Ford. I have to well, it's been that and that was quite the disappointment
Yeah, that was
So then we said okay
We looked at well, no, no, we still looked at if we got the right color and we got the right engine and we got everything and if we got all the things
We wanted which would kind of be dressing up, you know, basically dressing up a piece of shit, yeah, but at least making it bearable by that time
We found out
It was certainly wasn't a cheap car anymore. No, it wasn't
No, it was reasonably expensive and actually it wasn't the right one
No, well, so we looked and because you I drove the car then you drove the car and like yeah drives it drove really well
I'll drove nice and then we both sat in the back on the way to the dealership
We went like this is like like a crap. Yeah
And I said I'm sorry, this is piece of crap. We got to try something
And so they and so then what and then of course you immediately in the show room
But just your jumps into the XK convertible puts on her shades and her scar
This is what I like yeah, but it has no backseat baby. Nobody can sit in the bexie. No no no grandmong grandma coming over no
no
That's so that's a no no and then there was these oh and there was Elton John's car. Oh, that's right
That was interesting the
Elton John basically follows this one mechanic and
Just like a mechanical team or something and he follows them around and they've been at the
H.A. Fox dealer for 10 years and so all of his cars are serviced there and what he had is my Mazurati was there
Yeah, so and we saw on the parking lot beautiful
Beautiful his cell phone was in it. I so wanted to grab it and get his number. Yeah
But we saw nice cars on the parking lot
And we said yeah, that's a good one and that's a nice one. Yeah, but they don't sell Mazurati's
Right so because so what happened there is then we were like then we started look because you know
The Audi is a really nice luxury salute car, you know, we're very spoiled. Yeah, exactly
But we don't want a tank anymore. No, so what we do we we didn't buy a tank we bought a
Anair craft carry
So they had two
What do they call them?
Goreches cars
XJ yeah, and it turns out so that was an XJ that
It's like a year old yeah, and
It has a 24,000 miles on one of the guys who work there. Yeah, it's one of them
Of course they do. Oh, this was a
Board of director he only sat in the back he was driven
So what it smelled good. I always smell the car. Yeah, I'll change that
So I said yet that is a nice car
Oh, man, that is exactly the car. So we actually got it for the same price who would have paid for the
ergonomically friendly
Crap in the earth tank craft car
And we just couldn't resist I went back this morning. I said, let me test drive this thing
It's beautiful. It's gorgeous. It's a supercharged V8
You can just hear and we have to say we are not really in two cars
Not at all. I don't give a shit at all, but sitting in it this morning. I didn't
Man, I put the seat warmer on because you know, I always have to have the seat on high
And then the steering the beautiful wood steering wheel started to heat up in my hands. I was like
And then it talked you can press a button and you'd say like climb the controls 62 degrees
What we actually are are just we are nerdy car users
We just want to have comfy
You know nice comfort of it. We're definitely not greenies baby not with that car
Okay, well, that was here. We're happy. Very happy. Very happy. So now I have to get something in San Francisco
That I could try the biodiesel experiment on
I have to try that. Yeah, I'll just get some I'll get a real one. I'll get a real one. I'll get a real one
Excuse me hurts
You might have had poor vegetable oil in your tank
That's a good idea
That's a very good idea
Okay, it's good to be back, baby
Yeah, you're almost leaving again Thursday
Oh, the
Hover to Rose he's coming to his day, right? He's coming to my grocery shopping. He's coming to his day evening
Even so we'll shoot on Wednesday
Okay, we'll maybe you call him back and fight but I thought it was coming Tuesday because he's coming
Maybe Monday night
Then you have Tuesday to shoot some pictures, right?
And then when talking to the mic please and then Wednesdays leave yeah
How are the headphones as loud as I can see you? I can't see you but then move move the mic over
All right, but instead of yeah, you're not even you're just looking out the window you're not
You keep looking out the window. Why don't you just look out the window?
Yeah, because I couldn't see you. That's why you look at the window. Uh-huh. Mm-hmm. Hey, baby
No, is that better now? You can see me better. Much better. Yeah
Okay, so and and what else
Nothing else, so we're gonna do Christmas song Christmas song. Yeah. No, I don't know. Yeah, I wasn't allowed to prepare anything with you
You said that whenever you'd come up you would just be ready and would be instantaneously great
Okay, now I was looking here comes I heard on the on the radio that there is sort of a nasal spray
That you spraying you nose because you know everybody knows that I get I get cold all the time
I'm I'm now free of it. I feel so good and I stopped kissing the fish guy and I oh
I want to stay like this, but you know, so there's a nasal spray that you spraying you nose and it gives sort of a it sprays a gel
On the inside of your nose. Yeah, and it protects the inside of your nose and you cannot catch cold. Really?
So easy. Well, it was a commercial on the radio where Dr. Under on the morning show this morning on the
Yeah, what Terry woven show
No, it was on TV. Oh, and also Barrow who I just spoke to
Our house cleaning the house
She said yeah, it's it's brilliant. We have to we have to buy it. It's brilliant
Well, but that's I know it can't find it. No, not yet. Remember that guy. Maybe he's brand new
with a doctor
It was it was like we were just in New York. I think in that doctor and David Brenner was one of his patients and he would take these long
Cotton swabs with cocaine on the end and stick him in their nose
It was like some kind of treatment. It was everyone was laughing about it. Do you remember that and then they would they be walking around the office like five or six of these wooden sticks
No, I was David Brenner did that too
No, no, no, but I'm yeah, but I'm talking about that years and years before there was some kind of alternative treatment
Oh, is that? Well, of course not it's for cocaine heads
Naysley and exactly
Okay, okay
Okay, I mentioned that
Well, maybe somebody has an idea
Well, they're definitely respond because I talked about Skype and how I can't hook the Skype phone up to a Mac
Yeah, and everyone is sending me like I have at least a hundred different emails of people saying
We can use this cheap number to call and all these but I just want to use Skype. I like Skype. It's just it's just
We have a cheap number that that we call right, but it's not as cheap as kind of no Skype is it's freaking awesome
And they don't know how long I speak with my mom and with my sister
I used to know I used to know
We have a lot of topics
I'll really what kind of topics. Yeah, everything yeah, everything yeah, so that takes you know it's a long
When did you just want you I could get your wireless headset?
Would you like that is that cheap? Well, no, the thing is like I'm gonna get you a Mac for the kitchen
But I can't get you the Skype handset to connect to the Mac that they don't make it for the Mac. Oh
Okay, that's the problem so I could get you a wireless headset or at least a headset maybe you like walking around with the phone or not
If it's possible, yeah, but I always have an idea. I have to stay you know near near you
It works better if you say this
Skype is gonna disconnect me
Yeah, and it's gone. Yeah, it's like they throw you off
Well, if I give you a headset, then you if you just stay attached to the computer then it'll always work
But you have to kind of stay by the computer. Yeah, but it's not possible when Christina's it
But let's do that when I have my own station in the kitchen your own station Patricia's gonna get a station
The first time
Would you have a leaking you believe no?
When when when when you first came to live with me don't you remember what I said about computers
And the beta will for strad?
While you said keep keep them away from me, but just
Because I'm gonna be addicted to it. It was my Commodore 64. Yeah, and I had it hidden away in a closet and I said what is this?
He said keep it away from me
We fucked that up
Was once you start? He says no going back. There's no going back. No
Okay, what do you want to do you want to hang around or do you want to do a backtrack squeeze with what do we and what do you want to do?
Do a quiz and then actually I want to make some tea
What a cup of yes, I love a cat so I'd look yes, would you play the backplace some music?
But you play the backtricks the backtracks quiz with me. You know it works
The music is played backwards and you have to come on let's do it
Backtracks podcast so you think you know your hits backwards and forwards
Yeah, right
You're listening to the backtracks podcast exclusively on the daily source code without I'm curing and Patricia
Adam
No, let's get right into this week's quiz
Okay, here we go
Number one
No clue is that
Time's up number two
Right here, right now
Time's up number three
Get your booty on the floor tonight make my day
Technotronic I'm feeling like that
Time's up. Okay, here the answer number one
I
Don't know what that is
Oh, if you see
Me and me
No, I was never I guess yeah, I do but it's like an album track
There's number two
Yeah, I heard the tone right
There you go right here right now
Thank you
It's the only herb baby it helps me concentrate number three
So how did you do Adam I like to
One after another some this week's backtracks podcast quiz
You can visit backtracks podcast on the web at jackspotcast.com
Catch you next time
Backtracks podcast spin it back
You're bleeding, so maybe that has something to do with it. It is really hard. I just I cannot
Register, I don't know it's very hard. You do recognize something. Yeah
But it's hard. Yeah, well the second time around it gets much easier. Yeah, yeah, so when he does the answer
That's actually when I the first one I didn't hear today at all. I had no idea that it was anything
You are very good at titles
Not wasn't good today. It was good at the lyrics, but not at the titles to you want to know a disc
Disco yeah, so I have all the Lawrence Welk album. This is so I'm a disc drug
You're gonna go make some tea and then uh, okay, and then uh, you have to do an eye dog commercial for me
Thanks, baby. Now, all right, see you in a bit
Got in a lot of feedback about
Subscribing and unsubscribing and iTunes and luckily
Some audio feedback about the topic. Hey Adam. This is Scott TD in Saskatoon Saskatchewan
And I've just listening to your last podcast on Delz is Cherich early
273 and someone was complaining about they had deleted a file for my tunes and didn't know how to get back
Well, if you just go down and hit unsubscribe
Then hit subscribe, which will pop up right next to the eye to the feed you've just unsubscribed from
It'll go out and check the RSS feed and get any ones that are currently on it
I've done this a couple times before and it's worked out great
I've actually been able to go back about 20 or 30 episodes depending on the podcast
So that should hopefully work for that guy and
Keep on doing what you're doing
All right, dude. Thanks. Much appreciated. A lot of people sent that in
But it's still not a
I still think it's kind of a bug in the way it works. Hold on one second. Let me just have a sip here
Oh, that was fun having the princess here on our Friday extravaganza
So we went through let's see we went through the Dutch stuff
Hi, this was interesting my space.com has created their own record label. That's pretty cool
Although they're kind of doing a packaging thing
Which by the way is commercially. I think very smart
They're putting together see it's the the imprint
Is what's going to be called I think to be manufactured by universal music groups interscope records
I've seen it number 15. So it's just when it drops
It'll be the compilation called my space records volume one and
It'll have mix of tracks by major label independent label and unsigned acts
So sounds like a third will be really
non
non-label pod safe we's there's going to be all there
It's going to be on there all American rejects fall out boy
Okay, so I think that's very cool
That's not exactly what we're planning with the unlabel concept
But it definitely is a start get more more music out there
And I presume that that those independent songs will be pod safe that'll actually be interesting to see
When those come out if they're licensed by as cab BMI and they haven't been entered into the
Excuse me
No, I'm not going to say it they haven't been entered entered into the pod set music network
Then we won't even be able to to play them so be cool if they could actually mention if they're pod safe or not
Okay, uh, man Patricia's gonna be back with a T in a second and she's gonna
To some advertising so let's do some promos in the meantime. This is the sound of 25 cents
On every college campus in America. This sound can be heard every second of every day
This is the sound of $31 billion
The amount of money each year that families need in financial aid that they don't get
You can avoid being one of the families by listening to the financial aid podcast every day
We cover financial aid news how you can get more money to pay for college and what the politicians are doing to you
Behind your back and Washington
tune in today at www.financialaidpodcast.com and start putting this
In your pocket instead. That's what I call a great promo
Do you know now? I really want to go listen to the show
Of course, I'm actually subscribed
It's gonna get to me see more Gmail
High QD remember me high haven't talked to you in a while remember me we met on the personals not too long ago
I could a lot of these
Thought you might want to get together maybe sometime this weekend since I moved here
I haven't haven't haven't met too many people you still live here don't you hope you're open-minded
I like to get a little freaky sometimes have a camera set up now we can talk if you want to
I'm usually online if I'm not at work so get in touch
I'll probably be on when you get this here some picks if you don't remember
Amanda
sexy
Wait there was a I know that there was a
There was something here about some other podsake music then we talk about reggae from Germany yesterday
Yeah, that a lot of podsake reggae music seems to come from Germany and a dub art from mashuptown.com was
As always he was right on the ball. He said
Who's you talking about Jamaica man, but you like distract by dejecting fish
That's far away from Jamaica
He lives in the wrongs
Oh
Isso
See
Not
Yes
Yeah oh
Oh
You need it for a treat, yeah
And you're the one, and I am on the side
You need it for a treat
You need it too
You need it
You need it for a treat
We're still not being able to get them
Stop them! Darling!
Think about something
D estoyinki.
do
what
no
Take the heart, we'll come in back in
Shoot catch it, and be there with you
Light reed, past the moon's power, it's you
Yeah, I'll dance y'all, damn my name, damn my mind
Yeah, dance y'all, damn my name, damn my mind
Yeah, damn y'all, damn my name, damn my mind
Yeah, damn my mind, damn my mind
I'll dance y'all, damn my mind
Yeah, I'll게요, moon a lizard wohin me
Me, hold tight Jesus, you better go
Boy I can't be the first time I run around in it
Whisk shotgun is fast enough for ages
I know I cannt have I got closed
Let's go land for this
Just boom, yeah, yere, switch Call me if I want to
We found a big problem, his was long
shipment will be for you, it's you
Yeah, followed by a test call, why didn't you
I thought you didn't, did you, just call him
Dead, dumped out the moan, damn my mind
Yeah, dance, y'all, damn my name, damn my mind
Shout them, shout them, I end them up high
Shout them, shout them, shout them, I end them up high
I hope that's Pod Safe, I'm just gonna suppose it is.
I have no idea who DJ Kingfish is, but totally, totally rocked like that.
A bit you drew from Dawn and Drew is rocking away to that too.
He's a big reggae head and major.
All right, but I don't want to make the show too long, so hopefully, hopefully,
there's my Dutch slipping in again.
Hopefully, but you should be back with the tea just in time for the end of the show.
Let me see.
I'll go call her and you listen to...
Once again, for me to swallow my pride.
Because it is that time in the month again.
That time of the month where I asked for you to go over to Podcast Halley and vote for Podcast 4-1-1.
Is that time of the month where I asked for you to go over to Podcast Pickle and pick me as one of your favorites.
Show number 97 on the pickle.
Time to go over to Odio and subscribe to Podcast 4-1-1.
And let's not forget iTunes.
Subscribe for Podcast 4-1-1 there.
And then there's Podcast.yahoo.com.
Is that so much to ask?
Well, actually, yes.
That's not too many places.
I had this, she is.
Thank you, dear.
Tea.
Magic.
Remember, Magic was pissed off that there were no queer potters featured in iTunes.
Remember, I told you that?
I told you that, right?
I'm sorry.
I don't have your mic on.
Oops.
There we go.
And also that there's been no queer podcast.
Don't let Steve hear it.
Then he won't put me on the home page.
There's also been no queer castor apparently on the podcast 4-1, which is kind of like an industry magazine type show.
Are you still bleeding?
Yes.
What are we going to do?
I don't know.
Look at that later.
You're so hardcore, baby.
Thank you for the tea.
Okay.
So, for you, I was just thinking for your Skype.
We have a Logitech, one of our sponsors.
Makes a Bluetooth wireless headset.
Oh.
Yeah.
So, I just had to figure out what to do with the microphone, but at least the headphone part can be.
But you want mine wearing headphones?
Is that okay?
It does mess up the hair.
No.
You can wear them like Abba underneath your chin.
How lame was that?
No one did that?
No one did that.
It's very uncrew.
I don't want to mess up my hair.
So, I'll, I remember I used to go to radio stations when he had it.
He's singing back to back.
Knowing me.
Knowing you.
There is nothing we can do.
It's a good radio station.
When I had the big hair.
Yeah, yeah.
And they'd be amazed when I put the headphones on over the big hair.
Wow.
We thought you wouldn't want to mess up your hair.
Well, and if anybody doesn't care about his hair.
That would be me.
That's you.
Except when I didn't have it.
Yeah.
But when with all of that.
When Sam.
Shh.
Just add them.
That's right.
Just add.
Well, it's made me the man that I am, baby.
It's true.
Yeah.
That's true.
Remember?
You said, you said, can I change your hair?
So, as long as you take care of, you do it.
You've been doing my hair for 19 years now.
Yeah.
Well, it's not so important anymore.
But then, I mean, you just looked like anybody else.
Right.
You didn't have the expected.
The expected.
I didn't have the expected.
You added hair factor to me.
Yeah.
You know, Chris Rockwell, daily download, poopcaster.
So he actually shaved his ass hair.
But he shaved it.
Yeah.
It's almost stupid experiments.
But he shaved it.
And then like a day later, it really started to, to shave and get red and scratchy.
Or then he didn't do it right, didn't he?
Well, so, but I was thinking, I mean, does anyone still actually shave?
I mean, there's not what would nare and veet are for.
Isn't that much easier?
No.
But I don't know if you did it with a lady shave or, but if you put baby powder on the first.
Baby powder.
And then with a lady shave, or have a very nice soft shaving cream.
Mm-hmm.
And powder it after.
He probably didn't even know how to do it.
We ladies do it for years.
Would you do it for years?
You didn't even know we had it.
That's right.
I didn't even grew there until I got married.
No.
That's not.
I'm kidding.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
So I brought home the eye dog.
Yeah.
It's cute.
You have not been paid to say this.
No.
It's a commercial.
So tell me about the eye dog.
Only moves and it reacts on people's voices and sounds.
And what else does it actually do?
It doesn't.
Well, you know, it's something.
It's nice to put it down.
You don't feel lonely when you have a little dog.
What have you been doing with the eye dog, huh?
When I'm not there, I know what else.
It moves it's ears.
It wiggles it.
Wiggles it's down.
Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
No, you don't like that.
What?
No.
Oh.
Um.
Sex toys.
Yeah.
I hate that sound.
That turns me off.
No.
Doesn't it sound?
You know?
I don't know if you haven't been listening.
Maybe you should put your ear closer to it.
I don't.
No.
Maybe you're like the sound.
No, that is kind of a turn off.
It's such a turn.
Mm-hmm.
So back to the other.
Desperate.
Sounds so desperate.
It is kind of a...
I've never been desperate.
It's always been there.
Mm-hmm.
So anyway, it's like a $30.
I don't miss a pretty cool gift.
Yeah.
The eye dog.
Should we give an eye dog to someone for Christmas?
Who would also like that?
Roxy would probably like that?
Yeah, I think so.
She would love that.
I bet she would like that.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's a great stocking stuffer.
But it's sweet.
It looks sweet.
Yeah.
Yeah, it does.
Some guys want to hack it.
They want to see if they can program it.
Which I think is totally cool.
Yeah, I bet they can hack it.
I bet it's hackable.
Like what?
I don't know.
Who knows?
I mean, it does learn.
It does have some like nano pet type stuff in there.
So it does do more things.
And it learns from when you interact with it.
When you rub it's head or have it's tail wiggle somewhere.
Yeah.
And it learns.
Ah.
Okay.
Um.
It's our Friday show on.
So we always have to do something special.
Friday.
We want to sing along.
I mean, the New York state of life.
Alright, where's your life on?
Everything is so fucked up.
Oh yeah.
Hey, baby, what's up?
I can't play jazz in a singer.
Hold on a second.
Hold on.
Christina?
Yeah.
What, can you hear me?
Wait a minute.
What is it on?
Go ahead, say it.
I said the time is not here yet.
Oh, man, do those guys suck or what?
What time is quarter to four?
Can they just get it right?
Well, come on.
You call him Christina?
Yeah, call him.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Yeah, you call him.
Just call him and say, would you want to say?
Okay.
We pay for it.
And they need to be on time.
Do you hear that?
Christina.
I can hear you.
Mom says, will you please call them and say,
Hey, yo, I'm waiting for my cab.
Okay.
It's Aaron Call.
No, I'm sorry, baby.
Okay.
Call the cab and call me back and let me know what they said.
All right.
Love you.
Bye.
She wants it.
We had tickets for the day.
We had tickets for my chemical romance last night.
We didn't hear until like 7 p.m.
Way too late to go to Brickson Academy.
And then we couldn't get him for tonight.
So she's she's like the Aaron Call.
Aaron's very disappointed.
Yeah.
But you know, I'm not going to go to Brickson Academy.
When we're just eating at 7 p.m.
You know, it's an hour and a half.
What?
Old fashioned.
What's that?
Is that your phone now?
No.
Man, what's going on here?
Okay.
Well, let's see if that.
I hate music.
That's Hall Westerberg.
You think it's fun to be 31 and have ambition.
Not the bullets for the gun.
Everything is so fucked up.
My fingers just ran.
Hello.
There you go.
I love it.
That is so fucked up.
Exactly.
So I got an email.
William Durfei,
which is,
Hold on.
What's his email address here?
It's,
W.
Okay. He's at apple.com.
I'm not going to give his email address out.
Hi Adam.
We received several complaints about offensive content
in your daily source code podcast.
You.
Yeah.
Well, how about that?
Everything's so fucked up.
That would be,
Please mark your podcast.
Explicit.
I have attached to a spec document that will explain how to do that.
You will not have to resummit your podcast.
It will be automatically updated about 24 hours after you make the change.
How that said.
There's such a need person.
So much.
Well, and you have magic.
When you have magic,
yelling at Steve Jobs to stop pulling his pants up to his vagina.
I think, you know,
that some people just take offense to that.
Wow.
These are the right words.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
But it's not done.
But it's just, just put the text.
It'll say explicit.
Nothing else happens.
It's just, it's a warning.
It's a warning so that people know that bad language could occur.
It doesn't feel, you know, I have a vagina.
I don't feel offensive for any.
Can I tell you something?
Yeah.
You have a wonderful vagina.
Thank you very much.
God.
Yeah.
But I, you know, I don't feel.
You don't feel insulted.
Exactly.
No, okay.
Well, you also didn't report to iTunes.
So.
Okay.
Alrighty.
I think you want to say to anybody.
Uh, no.
Thank you for listening.
Yes.
Shout out.
And, uh, you love me.
You really love me.
It's true.
Oh, you spilled on my carpet.
No.
I think a little bit.
Yeah.
You mean, blood?
Yes, be careful.
All right, everybody.
Have a great weekend.
I'll be back here on Monday.
Take care of yourself.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.