POTCHO, the coolest podcast on ice.
Delta Sierra Charming 2-9 or 5.
It's Friday!
Merry Christmas, Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
You need me a lot of his treat.
Merry Christmas, you need a lot of this tree, love from by the way Christmas was meant to be
meant to be, so fill up your cup, raise it all up, don't shine up, now that I've found you
because you haven't finished Christmas and you've allowed us a tree, love from Christmas
then to your wish and then Christmas and I'll say it's one year, it's a home, forever to you for so, ever long, Merry Christmas
Merry Christmas, Merry Christmas, to you
Merry Christmas at the start of a Friday's edition of the Daily Source Code, hey everybody, how are you doing?
There's my phone's going off already, that's PW Fenton saying, dude, we need the show for serious, the while you're already hearing it, so apparently that I'll work out, didn't let me just see what he says
Hope everything's going well where you are, hope you've had a great week and wait, maybe I was wrong, oh wait, here we go, Friday, it's amazing, I just sent him a text message
and then he sends me on back asking what the status is, that's weird, there must be something wrong with text messaging, I gotta look into that
All right, everybody, hey, that by the way, it's from the pod save music network, if you've been logging in as a producer and wondering where the holiday category was, something was broken, Chris Rockwell
went ahead and fixed that, so now you can go any consort, excuse me, sort by genre and if you select holiday, up it comes, we'll have more holiday music
coming up in the source code, including subhonic music, another fix I saw which is cool is now when you're going to build your playlist, it shows up with the most recently submitted items, so that's the default now of the list view, which is also cool, it's amazing how many songs come in every single day
So the reason why PW is frantically texting me is because I am a little bit late on recording the show today, getting ready to the this morning after I took Christina to school
And oh man, does she hate going on Fridays for her first period on Fridays is math or let's say here maths maths
It's you know, just let me ask you for a second for a country that is so incredibly proud of its language and you ask any bread here, they'll say hey look you know you guys in America, you speak a different language, the original language, the English language we invented it, how come
That everywhere and it may be very much a London area, but I see it on television a lot and I hear people even Carol Thatcher, she you know, she may actually have a she won't have a speech impediment, I don't know, but the it always seems like the R is replaced with a W
Oh, blah, oh, great
And sometimes the TH is also replaced by different sounds and of course it's slang, but you can't help but but recognize that the bridge definitely are mispronouncing
You know words based upon this it seems like a national thing and of course the more national it becomes the more people started adopting it
We've seen this in the states with with acts no longer do you ask anyone something you pretty much acts can acts I can't even do it you pretty much acts in for that
And it's rampant anyway, that's just a side note with the hell was I talking about okay so
Right took a Christina school came back because it was time before I leave for San Francisco to go and get our Christmas tree
Which of course they don't deliver Christmas trees you got to go by when they put it in this bag, so I went to our local Saintsbury's which is you know the huge shopping market type thing super market
We got we got all kinds of stuff we got all kinds of stuff to make it nice and cozy for the holiday season
Of course, I've only helped participate in bringing everything here next week. Well, I'm gone Patricia and Christina probably Patricia primarily, but I'm sure Christina will help and I'm going to decorate everything then we get back it's going to be a great week
And I have worked it out now. I'm going to be able to go see my mom on the 21st so yeah things are vibrant we're going to wind down the year with a lot of good
Friends family hanging out and good cheer
I got in a couple of emails here that I want to talk to you about today
Andplifico who you've heard on the source code another
Band I guess that is available through the Podsick music network for podcasters to play have their own email list and Donna from Amplifico
San such a a wonderful update
Let me just see if I can pull a couple of pieces about this so she kind of says what is the title of this it was like podcasting it really works with podsake music
So here's what Donna says anyway a couple of months ago we said a few songs in email to mark hunter the tartan pod cast
I didn't know what a podcast was then on recommendation from a friend mark like your music played as a few times on his shows
Praise their music highly on the show more importantly introduce us wisely to the ins and outs of podcasting and getting exposure
We sold numerous CDs on his recommendation. We put our music on the podcast music network and watch our tunes get played on almost 70 podcasts across the globe over coming weeks with wonderful feedback
We sold more CDs mark then recommended us to Adam Curry of the daily source code who played our track
The practice MP mix on his show immediately upon receiving marks email. That's right anything Mark will send me. I definitely that's a huge recommendation
See how the social network works
Our site hits rocketed as did our music sales. Well, they rocketed in comparison to what we normally sold via our site. It was very exciting
Let's see and then it just goes on and on and on and I just want to bring that up
Because that's that's really what the intent was. It's working. You know, we the only other thing we can do is help artists sell
The actual you know the actual mechanics of it on the pod sake music now work what you know we're working on Chris Rockwell working hard trying to get all kinds of shops and payment systems whatever integrated
Hmm
Oh, man, I'm nice cup of sensio
The trick by the way to the sensio
Madge because Madge says she hates it. She likes the convenience of it, but the trick is first you put in your sugar
I don't take a lot of sugar just a small spoonful then you pour some semi-skim milk in and then you put it underneath the
Sensio machine and then you get a nice frothy rich
Coffee with a nice flavor it goes down smooth. It's not too bitter. I use the medium roast pods by the way
And also what's nice about it is it kind of gives you something to do while the machines warming up
You know you hit that that center button to get it rolling then you get your cup you get your sugar. You get your milk in the by time you're done with that is ready to the buttons ready to be hit
That on the side
See what else that I have here
I asked some questions about ask cap BMI asked if you joined ask cap or BMI could you still collect royalties from overseas?
There by circumventing all these and we'll talk more about another country that showed up on the radar
That has these very restrictive agreements with their local versions of ask cap BMI as it turns out and I'll just be a little repetitive here if you sign up with ask cap BMI in a number of European countries and
You know look at the show notes through daily source code.com or show notes that info
To see all these different countries that we've discussed apparently you're signing over your rights and that's it. You know if you want you can't give podcasts
There's the right to play your music. So I said can you circumvent it
And let's see this
Why don't I have his name here shit. Oh Michael. Okay, you know Michael says that's him
I'm more familiar with how BMI works, but I assume ask cap is similar basically as a BMI writer BMI has a reciprocal agreement with most other international performing rights organizations
So that you get performance royalties from other countries sent to you
So there you go as a BMI publisher BMI can collect royalties for you as long as you're not affiliated with a publisher in a particular foreign country
So I think that is maybe a way to get around this horrible horrible
Situation. In fact, let me see do I have
I thought I had to always have it in feedback. Don't wait. Okay, now we'll get to that in a second because it's actually Israel that has a similar
A similar set up for their version of ask cap BMI or wait a minute. Was it this one was I so brilliant as the schedule at here
Okay, yeah, the Jacob's of the rock and roll Jew show. Oh, yeah. Well, you can add Israel to the list of countries where music oppression is happening
You got an email from a band called RBS music with a really interesting lecture that was done by their leader Nimrod love
And we'll read the little pretext that really set that up before the translation is translated into English
Think on us so the rest of the world can read it says Nimrod love a prominent Israeli musician and leader of RBS music participated in a panel on online music
Organized by the Hifah Center of law and technology which took place at the faculty of law
University of Hifah Israel on November 16th, 2004
Several days before the panel, the Israeli music Federation announced its intention to sue users who download music for copyright infringement
As far as August 2005, this is not happened. On the cards also is a bill promoted by the government to impose a levy on blank media and use the money to compensate artists
And I think that's something that's happening currently in the United States and has been for quite a while
But this is a really really good read all about the music industry and it's very specifically in Israel how it works and there's some just all kinds of really interesting things of how it goes down there
Good read, take a look, I will provide the link for you for your website, the law, so be linked up on my blog
www.rockandrolljew.com where you can also find the best part safe rock and roll out of Israel. That's it. Thanks a lot
And I will see you later. Oops, I got to fix that. Why is it doing me fix that right now because it keeps doing that there must be a setting so that you can set it to playback
and fade out, no fade out, fade in, auto sag, shoot. Maybe we just do, oh, you can't do a zero. Oh, that's interesting. You can't do zero fade out on this. I must be able to. There we go. Okay, hopefully it's fixed now.
I remember that something I fixed a long time ago before my drive crashed. Update on that. The community computer Patricia set up, broken, beyond repair. I have Norton's utilities
But I can't get this titanium to boot up from from the disk because that's supposed to be your final
Savior. If you have OS 10, I'm actually saying properly now. The OS 10 disk goes in. It eats that.
But the drive smart status is verified, but it won't mount because the B tree catalog is all hose. But I can't get it to start up from the, from the Norton disk. I don't know why.
And of course, and now you've got to hold down sea and all that stuff. And I've done it before, but it just keeps spitting it out. It does not want to recognize it for some reason, which is
bummer because now what I'm going to do is tonight, I'm going to take the G5 here or the I Mac and create a new account, create
Patricia's environment on it and then install it somewhere else instead of the podcast complex so that she can use it so we can do our
email. She can do our email and our I cheat conversations between San Francisco and between the condo and the cottage. Yes.
So I want to thank David very much for his first feedback there. I appreciate it. If if you know what's going on in your country, let us know. It seems pretty much outside the US so far, every country that's reported in
has these very stringent laws. And the only unfortunate thing is that I got to take, you know, Dave sincerity there with little grain assault based upon some of his podcast pickle postings. He's not very friendly.
Let's see, pod show. They already drained AMP once. I hope they aren't coming back for more. That's not true.
Anyway, maybe we should form an unpod show company. Come on, David. Don't be like that. That's not necessary. I guess it was all in fun.
But it just didn't come across as very funny to me.
Oh, yeah. I've told you about hood hype, right? This is as far as I know, one of the few, it's the only one I've really found that that sounded like a real urban hip hop podcast with pod safe
R&B urban hip hop music. Jay Mac produces and hosts the show. And I love listening to the show. This amazing, amazing music happening there.
He's working, I think, with Michael Butler now on getting some of these artists also to upload some songs to the pod safe music network for you on podcast.
But not only do I learn a lot from the stuff he plays, he learns a lot from the stuff that I'm playing. Check out this comment he sent in.
Okay, for you win, you caught me, man, off guard. These guys are here.
Check, you know, it's not too often that I hear a music. So it just makes it here on the back of my next stand up and the music is a talent in the song.
Like, man, you know what? I'm buying a copy of the CD for myself. I'm buying a copy of the CD for my brother and probably both my sister. Man, this track is just freaking nuts, man. You know.
Well, I tell you where I love podcast, but I'm now more motivated than ever. When you hear music like this and people are underground, man, oh my god, you just want everybody to hear about them. This is just insane.
Well, with that, I wouldn't get back to playing this track in my car. Thank you for playing it, man. I appreciate it. Don't forget to be like, you know, you know, I would have got calm.
Damn, I want to play this. I think it is.
Hey, buddy, no problem, man. You know, that's what the pod safe music network is about.
Just registers a podcast and you can play it. Here's the track he was talking about. I played it just the other day, but I don't mind playing it again. You know.
Hey, people, let's stop.
People, people are in music in your hand.
There's music playing in your head. So listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen.
So listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen.
So listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen,
listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen
listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen listen, listen, listen, listen listen, listen listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen, listen listen listen, listen, listen , listen listen, listen, listen, listen listen, listen listen, listen listen listen, listen listen listen listen, listen listen listen listen listen, listen, listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen listen
which was held in Paris, a lot of what are called the A-list bloggers met up there,
and there's a video and a lot of conversations circulating the internet
or the blogger sphere, particularly, which I guess is almost the internet these days,
about the speech that Mina Trot gave, Mina is one of the co-founders of six apart.
I believe that's Typad, the web logging system, and Type Key,
but it is weblog software, and Mina's topic was about civility,
and it was funny because I recognized a lot of what she was talking about,
and I knew from almost the minute she started talking,
that it was headed for a collision course,
and at a certain point she just, you know,
they have an iris, this is something I really don't understand.
I've never done this, but I've witnessed it,
where you have an IRC, basically a command line chat,
going on during a speech by someone,
and that's actually projected behind the person,
or next to him on the screens,
so everyone can read along with what they call the back channel,
and at a certain point someone came in and said something,
and I don't want to go into the details,
because I really don't know,
I'm not familiar with all the all sides of it,
but she just lashed out at some guy,
and then they had a public conversation.
And I was witnessing all this, and of course,
I've been the subject of a lot of public flame wars myself,
and I thought to myself, oh man, you know what?
You can't call for civility, it just doesn't work that way.
I think that we're building up systems here,
particularly online, where, you know,
everyone just, it's, we're almost interconnected into the brain, I guess.
I think that's what I'm seeing,
most of the time I'm seeing things that are,
that people might not even say out loud,
because it would go through so many filters in their process,
before speech was actually formed,
but for some reason we're communicating straight from our brain waves,
and all kinds of thoughts and emotions that are taking place there,
and it's going straight out through the finger to the keyboard,
and then nothing but net, and the perception of it
is equally as messed up, where we're reading tons of stuff,
lots of information, lots of banners and stuff
all over and words and things fly in,
and our brain immediately starts the process,
and they go the fingers again, and before you know,
you have full-fledged flame war.
I was very happy the other day to see that I'm podcast alley,
some of the people who were most vocal,
you know, all of a sudden the real discussion started
about Pod Show and what we're doing, and what our plans are.
And once I saw that, I of course immediately took advantage
of the opportunity to hop in and start providing some answers.
And although I don't think I use the word civil,
I just want to be focused, you know.
It's okay, bulletin boards and forums,
it's great to spout off and have that direct brain
to fingers and eyes to brain communications to loop going on,
but I just have to pass by most of that.
But when there's some serious conversation going on,
it really starts to work.
And man, I hope we can make Pod Castile
like the place we can have some of these conversations.
And you know, when people fly off the handle,
you know, let's, you know.
There you have it.
Then it happens.
I'll draw it back for a little bit
and then maybe start to do thread, but it's clear to me
that I have to be able to participate somehow
in the online ongoing conversation,
because there's so much good information
that gets lost.
You know, that's the signal to noise ratio I talk about.
It just gets lost in there, you know.
And I won't even look at certain threads,
because I know what most of it or what I'm going to find.
And of course, then you lose some of the gem.
So anyway, I don't think there's any way to stop,
but I think it's only going to get, quote, worse.
And I don't know if it's worse.
Maybe things have to get a whole lot worse
until they get better.
But this is human nature.
I don't think that, look,
as humans in the, in the non-ciber world can't fucking get along,
we're bashing each other's brains
with hot lead and fucking deserts.
You know, this is, so it's not foreign to me
that this kind of thing happens online,
particularly when people are very protected
and there's no real bullets flying.
So people are passionate.
People believe what they think is true.
They are the center of their own universe, and that's okay.
I'm 41 now.
I think I'm finally starting to realize it.
It doesn't make it any easier to get something done,
but understanding it and,
you know, the pipe people say,
oh, don't take it personally, but I just did
with David, didn't I?
See, there you go.
It's fucking, it's human.
It's, oh, but I hate it that sometimes
that I'm human.
Right on.
So as I said, it's Friday.
Tomorrow 830, I'll be hopping on,
I'll be hopping on a virgin for my shuttle flight to the oil rig.
Just a short week.
So we got a board meeting coming up.
We got lots of people want to meet with.
We have, oh, just a lot of stuff going on.
You know, we're figuring out how back office
processes work and, you know,
with a commercial media network,
which is going to be different from anything
that has ever existed for sure.
Yes, indeed.
You know, the only, I've told you this, right?
When I say Senseo, I figured it out.
Because every time you burp,
you're going to think of me,
but every time you see Senseo,
you're going to think of me.
It's the ultimate marketing program.
I encourage you to use that yourself.
A couple days ago,
we were talking about,
can't remember how we got to the topic of,
oh, yes, mtv.com.
That's right.
This existed before the World Wide Web existed.
I didn't know about until Mark Andrews
and sent me a link to the HTTP,
the NCSA HTTP server.
I think it was version 1.2 or 1.3
that I set up on that,
on that headless Sun 3 card at DJX and Virginia.
Before that, though,
and I had done it myself.
I can figure it out for sure.
Actually, I built the client,
you know, with like CC and all that crap.
I don't know if I could still do it,
you know, command line builds,
but I could figure it out.
So I was able to compile it and install it
and was using that in the University of Minnesota.
Came back and he said,
hey man, mtv.com.
That sounds commercial and you've got to pay
a $5,000 license.
Obviously, that wasn't workable.
And we struck a deal.
And I was sent to lovely link by
BNP shit.
I wish I knew who BNP was.
Let me just go to that link right now.
You'll get a kick out of this.
So that's actually at the University of Minnesota.
Let me see.
If you follow the cookie trail,
the breadcrum trail home,
Mark P. McAhill,
MCCA, H-I-L-L,
projects,
and then go for t on mtv.
circa 1993,
a seven second quick time of Adam Curry
fulfilling the terms of his commercial use of in it.
So, well, that's not entirely true,
but okay, we'll let it slide.
Fulfilling the terms of his commercial use of
internet go for server software license.
Adam's license terms required him to wear.
It's funny.
A go for t shared on mtv.
We called this gorilla marketing since
we had zero budget for real marketing.
And it worked.
Okay, yeah, I'm going to play it.
Adam Curry introduction to a Nirvana song
on the mtv top 20 video count.
Okay, you can't see it,
but I'll play it for it,
because it's just,
it's kind of cool.
Let's see if it'll load here.
Here we go.
Oh my god, look at me.
It's in the top 20 video countdown.
When we come back,
we'll have the latest video from the gentleman who puts
Seattle on the musical map.
Keep it here.
And I had a huge black and white go for t shared on.
Very cool.
Thank you very much for sending me that.
Excellent.
And the saga continues.
I had to listen to this next piece of audio feedback twice
to just hear all of the information that was coming out of it.
This is that the podcast or Roger Smalls
who lives in Guilford.
Of course, you know the cottage is also in Guilford.
And he's somewhat confused.
I think he's probably really sweet,
but he's confused and sometimes very angry person.
But I just, let's listen to how his mind works.
Listen to this piece of feedback he sent me.
Hello, I've been Roger here.
Now, you don't have to play this if you don't want to say that it's quite alarming.
Now, you're talking about how I just came on your show.
And I've just heard that someone's copied one of your pubs was.
I'm not sure what you know, but I heard that there's actually a pair of
Gapsuic 606 Road Letters, being cool, imagine I changed.
I found out today that the elderly has been Madonna
has started her own podcast,
well, it's the gay audience, son of her.
And a formula, certainly, that much wine steam has been done for about a year now.
She's even called herself much for having a sake.
The nice thing is, real much has gone and got taken out by a change.
And the imposter is now getting all the credit.
I mean, you're much bigger and older star than she is at them.
And you managed to age gracefully,
without resorting to stillness, people's work,
and very hardcore bras.
I think something is being done about the Charleston.
If you can ask your daily source code listeners
to become that report concerned,
then in the iTunes directly,
some Madonna's podcast.
Well, we can do it.
We'll get kicked out for copyright reasons.
But in that, I think the more direct approach might,
you know, I'm assuming you know where she lives from your NPD date.
Now, I don't actually own the pub,
and not sure where you got the impression that I'd drive a mini from either,
but I actually don't drive at all.
But I was wondering, if you want to tell you a little how the culture
over some Madonna's house,
and that we can show things out with a once and for all,
I think it's the plummeted house.
You can always bring along some muscle,
but your church is quite handy, which is past.
Anyway, you take care, and talk to me,
just to sort all this mess out.
And it's not really much happening with me at the moment.
I've got a bunch of nails,
but after that it's,
see, see, have a try to skin it,
so let me see others.
Bye-bye.
Okay.
If you couldn't hear what that was all about,
now would be the time to hit your little rewind button,
and listen to it again.
That's what I had to do.
Okay, here's what I think Roger is saying.
He's angry because he feels that Madonna,
known in the UK as Madge,
has stolen Madge Weinstein's idea,
or whatever he thinks the copyright is.
He's calling it copyright,
and that, I don't know if this is true,
I don't think Madge Weinstein,
I think East Radio has been kicked off of iTunes,
but I'm saying that I should go and take care of the imposter,
which apparently Madonna would be the imposter.
Roger, it's okay.
Don't worry about it,
and stay away from Madonna.
And she's not known as Madge anywhere,
but here, so Madge can be the US Madge,
Madge Weinstein,
and Madonna can be the British Madge.
And that'll solve it.
Okay, hopefully that works for you, Roger.
And I'm kind of happy you don't have a car.
Really?
Hey, I know I'm sure you're going to be this a sledge.
Very many of the exposed sledge,
from the I love kitty, it's podcast.
That's very, very, very, very, very, that I love night's dot com.
And we spot like the night on the horse for the lens.
Yeah, can I teach you a start com?
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Welcome to me on academically.
Oh, you, get out.
Oh.
Hey, everybody.
Hi.
What do you call this isestone
right now?
Sometimes I panic about it.
I can't take that little while,
because definitely it happened.
one song every show and the audience decides whether it's a good song or bad song.
Songs like these is the Hanukkah overtures by the Nishama Orchestra.
Also, we have commissioned the artist themselves to play these songs, so it's completely
hard to say it for us to guess what we're saying.
Anyway, I'm hoping to play this, so thank you for playing it, and everyone out there
in Hebrew, Kaga, Hanukkah, Samayah, I'd be happy to come up with.
For a Merry Christmas, Happy Kwanza, Happy New Year, and keep on listening to WWE WWE
that I love makes that come, let's do it WWE that I owe you, and I teach yes.com.
Happy Holidays, everybody.
I need to make the back stop the beat, and that's all I'm saying about it.
Hey!
I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to
make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back
stops the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the backstock the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, disable the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to make the back stop the beat, I need to
Thank you so much for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video, thanks for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I
I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in
I'll see you in the next video.
Fantastic.
Ladies and gentlemen there's somemore Castro under direction of tonight's conductor Steve
Bill.
That was live, crap.
Thank you very much, I really appreciate of that.
It's been so hard to find a Hanukkah music that I like that sound up and up and
like a little, a little more modern,
like we've been finding all over the,
the Pods and Music Network in the holiday section.
And you actually said,
you know, you can fade the music out whenever you want to.
I'm like, no, but that's the beauty of podcasting
because I can just let that play.
If someone doesn't like it,
they can shuttle past it.
They can fade it out.
The listeners and control.
I love that.
And if you have more Hanukkah songs,
please let me know about them.
And if you know anyone who has them and artist
and they're asking if they wanna submit it
for the Pods and Music Network,
I know I sound like a broken record,
but I'm so excited about it.
Oh yeah, yes, that I do my typical scan
of all the new podcast and video podcasts.
There was Daily Planet TV and Lusion.
And that is spelled Lima Uniform Shira,
India, Alpha, November.
I spelled it incorrectly previously in this show notes,
I believe, responded to my request about information
about how he puts his show together.
And indeed, he is using the wire screen software.
And he actually showed us, he has two cameras hooked up
to his Mac, it's amazing, he's got a regular camera.
I think probably camcorder through what must be Firewire.
And then he has an eyesight cam hooked up
and he actually showed his entire screen as layout.
He's a one-man band and I love it.
And I wanna congratulate him, it was beautiful man.
He played a sound, which was so, you know what,
let me play the sound for you.
It was so beautiful.
Hold on, I gotta fire this up in a quick time.
Okay, so this is the actual video,
let me see if we fast forward,
it was somewhere around here.
Resilient prostitutes.
The fashion show, that wasn't the one, obviously,
here comes first, too, you know, the two Adam Currys.
Well, here's the third.
Here's the, okay, listen to this.
That sounds you hear, it's my baby's heartbeat.
You can just hear lures, heart beat in the background,
lures in my life.
In that beautiful, so he got an ultrasound of his unborn child
of, it's heart beating, and any, any dad, any parent,
but that, or mom, was ever heard that,
knows what a beautiful sound that is,
was really cool the way he shared that on the show.
DailyPlanet TV, dot net, fantastic video podcast.
I'm subscribed, and I love it.
Okay, DailySourceCode.com is where you can find the,
the podcast feed for the DailySourceCode,
where you can always find updated episodes.
Of course, I crosspost it to curry.com,
my weblog, where all kinds of other crap gets written down
and documented.
If you want to submit a promo for the show,
and I still could use some more holiday greetings
for xmus.podshow.com.
I'm still releasing two songs every single day,
mixing them together.
So we adhere to the, the license that we have with artists
who upload to the podcast and music network.
But it's really a cool way to fill up your MP3 player
with holiday tunes.
I don't just want to be Christmas, by the way.
And, you know, so if you've got Hanukkah tunes
or Kwanza or whatever, you know, send it in.
It's all about the whole festive spirit.
Then it's right, I said promo.podshow.com.
I got that one, right?
That's where you can upload your promos.
It's a great way to, for me, at least,
to keep a track of where everything is,
instead of people sending it into my Gmail.
Gmail, fullness count today.
Let's see.
What are we seeing?
I've got to go back here.
Where's my Gmail screen?
Shiza.
Hold on.
I'll tell you, we were 92% yesterday.
And what are we at today?
That's 92% of four gigs.
93%.
So does that mean I'll only have seven more days
if it's rising at 1% a day?
And then I have to go start deleting stuff again.
I certainly hope not.
Okay, wine that I've done with one more song
from the podcast music network.
Even though it's a summer song,
it has a kind of holiday feel to it.
Yeah, that's the point I know it's always cool.
Relax.
Yeah.
For the lovers out there,
just turn your ring and get one band.
It's fine, that it's cool.
Yeah.
Instead of some a feeling,
yeah, I'm chillin' with a friend's party in the morning.
Trains around the way bend these days.
It's been in the old days, been in superb.
Remaining it's in the old days.
Women don't check it for a thug to take home.
They don't roam around the two in the mall.
Everybody look at things for us.
We got some grub on the grill, so I'm eating.
I think my split love in the middle.
You can get them.
Children in the middle with street dancing.
As per ladies, the chef and ladies smokey with Samsung blowing
on wood, showing on wood.
It's so good.
It don't matter when you hang on, slang is understood.
How the time is, you'd like to eat and roll baby.
It's like you don't die to say it's cool.
Maybe having your ability to celebrate like the late high
Saturday pop club.
High sweat if you cut in the room.
Free back with a green bottle.
Z's taking a look.
The music never stops in my city.
Hotel is packed with habdiparties by $78.
You The Lost Half the Body,
To LPM, the party's starting over
Yeah, folks, I'll have naked in the blazes
It's on for the time we wasted waiting
No days to come, we got the motorcycle blazing
But ain't nobody hating, you're just strictly hospitality
And I realize it, because it's even green bills are large accounts
The theory you banked, the heart of you bounce
No doubt, ain't nothing like the summertime playing in the sand
Layout and give blazes to your favorite jam
You can spend a path for the riddle, let the good times roll
With no worries, you get wide open and no worries
Yeah, I'm just feeling what I'm saying
I've paid the yield blind for work-up used to Side
The brands I rise sometimes are
Oh, yeah, focused to wax W-ade up
Sris, weather, Tommy, you're good
Who's on the field?
You're here, you show mine with an cyan
Look at me, andveis make you mind
That's the same. Make you feel like I'm falling
Nice Carl, you said Oh you can afford a few
1900ols on the field. I like that
I like you
She loves you
I'm living through yuh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uhuh-uhuh-uhuhuhuhuhuhuhuhuhuhuhuhuhuh
uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh
on the feet-in- that's the playing.
I know the way I know it was so-Blanc thing.
Yeah.
Oh.
I'm recommended by Sourcecoida listener.
With the link to the Potter & P dependent on Rota I was here very cool.
His hith chiker is Sarmir Fiela.
I'm not quite sure what it was like, if it made the track,
track, or was my setup, but it felt like on some of the bass tones, it was kind of like
the track was stuttering a little bit, sorry about that, not quite sure it was going on.
Okay, how cool is that?
We went from Christmas song to people, which is totally funk, R&B, then we went to some
Hanukkah music and ended up with a summer song.
I love that.
And by the way, listeners are more than welcome at the Podsafe Music Network.
You can register as a listener, and you can listen to all of the tracks there.
If you find something, you know, let your podcast know about it, send them the link, you
know, tell them that you're digging the song, so that we can share it with other people.
If you like something you heard on today's show, you can go check out the show notes, or
you can go to the Podsafe Music Network and look up the Daily Source Code and see all the songs
that I've played.
If you'd like one or two, there may be a couple more on the list there that you're digging,
there's always a link to the artist's website, and two other shows that I've played, which
will, of course, lead you to probably other music that you like.
We thought about that shit.
Okay, so as I said, I'm off tomorrow morning, right, and early, maybe I'll do an update
from the condo on Sunday.
I know when I get in Saturday afternoon, I know that I immediately have to start mopping
the floor because I kind of left it a mess, herid exit a couple of weeks ago when I left.
So some vacuuming and mopping is an order, everything else should be, and maybe
all change the sheets on the bed, they've just been sitting there rotting away for three
weeks, and yeah, we'll have another week of stuff from the condo information about what
we're up to.
We've got the Christmas party on the way, and I hope that you have a fantastic Friday
or weekend whenever you're hearing this.
Take care, everybody.
Have a good one.
Pot show.
Nothing says love and light, pot show from the oven.