Hey everybody, it is Friday, May 6, 2005.
Coming to you from Curry Cottage, a special Friday edition of the Daily Source Code, with a...
I don't know where my guest go, my guest has removed himself from the studio chair.
Oh yeah, we've set it up as a studio, it almost looks like one and makes me sound better than the guest.
Oh yeah, look, I have one good microphone and then I have the other one, which is a radio
shack, Mike, you know.
And guests who get the microphone.
This is my special guest, Steve Leeds, we've talked about him lots before on the Daily Source
Code and certainly several times during the MTV Chronicles that I do with Ken Clark.
And Steve is in town visiting and I was able to convince him to hop on a train and come
down to Lovely Gilford to the cottage to see the wife, kiss the baby who'll be here after school,
and to talk about, I don't know, radio, records, stuff like that.
So now it's going to be really hard, Steve, because this is your first podcast, I think.
With a crummy microphone.
Oh come on, let me boost the volume a little bit there, say something.
I noticed the resonance on the host's microphone as opposed to the guest,
usually the guest is supposed to be treated better than the host.
Yeah, but that's not the way.
Why have you ever watched the Letterman or Lennon, don't you see that they get like the microphone
on the desk and they get the chair that's a little bit hot, well, Letterman doesn't need that,
but Lennon gets his chairs a little higher and stuff like that, you never noticed that.
I mean, this microphone is really weird because it got, uh, maybe that's just the headphones you're wearing.
Doesn't sound that bad here.
I mean, the microphone has these faults in it because they're so often, oh, really?
Oh, I don't feel that.
I'm, hey.
Yeah, that's just you mucking around, stop doing that.
So, Steve is actually in the, almost like, my position myself a little bit,
or Steve is in the big green thing today, and uh, I'm over by the controls.
I've got the sensei of standing by, Steve, okay, I know you're going to be silly for like the
first 10 minutes because, you know, it's just because you're not used to it.
Oh, I like the green thing.
So, uh, Steve is, um, without a, without a doubt, a legend in New York,
radio and music, and probably far beyond, but, you know, New York is like,
anywhere you go, anyone you speak to, everybody knows Steve leads.
Now, you can just post a cough into the mic on the podcast.
Actually, yeah, thank you.
What was that?
What happened?
I took control.
You just blew the mic out. Did you hear that?
No. Yeah, no, it sounds much better.
I'm telling you, the microphone cleared its throat.
It's like the, wait, but not on here myself. Hold on, where am I?
I'm over here, now you say something.
I'm over here.
I'm telling you, the mic, what's, did you hear that, the difference?
It cleared its throat.
That's amazing.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you very much. See, I was wondering, I thought that radio shack might really
sounds like shit. I'm embarrassed about it, but,
yeah, but you get the windscreen.
No, you got a windscreen. There we go. Now, see, this is much better.
Okay, hold on.
Let me just turn you down a bit there.
Perfect. Okay. Thank you.
No, thank you. Thank you.
That's much appreciated. Okay.
So, I first heard of Steve Leads in,
I'm going to say it was about this time. No, no, no, no, it was,
when was it, Steve? It was, uh, back in the,
it was 1987, I think. 87.
Yeah, but it was, you were at Radio Veronica.
Yeah, and I got a call at the desk downstairs.
Actually, I was walking up to my desk in the reception and I said, oh,
there's a call for you.
And, uh, so I took it and it was this guy, Steve Leads.
And I think we had a, like, a five-minute conversation.
Yes. You said, hey, you want to come and work for us at MTV in America?
Would you be interested in coming to New York and working for MTV?
And what did I say? Actually, I'm an American,
I'm transplanted over here in Holland. That would be
not such a terrible thing. Yeah.
And you were interested. Yeah, that's right.
And we had the deal done in, like, two weeks?
Yeah, it was fast. And that your, your representative did a fine job,
but he was talking to the time with Lee Masters.
Oh, that's right. Lee Masters. Yeah.
A-K-A-Y-R-O-Mone. Who?
His real name is Y-R-O-Mone. No way.
Lee Masters isn't his real name? I didn't know that.
Well, is Adam Curry real name? Yes, that's my real name.
That's not a stage name? No, you know, come on. You know that.
You know, that's my real name. Okay. Yeah, you know, you know, I thought your last name was Bloom.
Yeah, right. Oh, how you doing? Y'all?
Y'all? Shalom? Shalom? It's Adam Bloom here.
And so that's the way we first met. Now, how did that work, Steve?
I don't think it would actually ask you how that came here there.
Lots of people claim claim that they brought me to MTV,
but I know you're the guy that called me, so.
Um, Steve Lieber of the famous Lieber Krebs.
Lieber Krebs? Aerosmith Management.
ACDC, Bellamy Brothers, Def Leopard.
Steve Lieber had shown me a video tape of Adam and said,
here's your next VJ.
And I said, okay, that's nice, but my relationship with Steve had always been very
one-sided. And so I kind of didn't follow through.
And then I was reading Media Week, which was an international music trade,
and there was a picture in Media Week? Yes, a view with doing some interview on Radio Veronica.
Really? And there was the in the American Media Week?
No, no, no, no, no, no. It was the, it was the European sort of billboard.
Oh, no, that was music and media. Music and media?
That's it. That's it, that's it.
T-O-Rose, who owns all the Genesis publishing. That's guy.
Ah, really? I owe him a thanks then.
Yeah, so there was your picture, and it had Radio Veronica.
And I went, you know what? I just want to call this guy out.
And so somehow I fomphered my way through the international codes,
the directory assistance, got the phone number for Radio Veronica.
And I think the first time I left the message for you with the switchboard.
Yeah, that's possible. And then the second time I got the switch,
that switchboard when the call came in. Right.
So that's how that happened. Is that you were me feeding back? I can't quite tell.
Well, I've lowered my cans. Okay. He just used me.
You're such a professional baby. I love it.
That's probably me. So yeah, and that started.
By the way, his cans today are white.
Very sexy. All of the iPod cans. What yours are mine? Yours. Yeah, well, these are actually my,
I can't stand. There's no atom. His very sexy cans.
My creative labs headphones. You know, can you buy replacement iPod headphones at the Apple
store? Have you tried that? That's a good question. I'm sure you can. I mean, you should be able to.
One would think. Yeah, because they probably wouldn't allow that because then people could have other MP3 players.
I have an iPod. I don't like having headphones.
So you actually have the the white ones, which are the creative labs. So they kind of look like iPod
headphones, but they aren't really. And I don't use them on my iPod. Now they're using them on the
I River. Now they are telling people in New York City if you take the subway, do not use your iPod
headphones. They were just saying that last week when we were there. Cellphones and iPods, right?
That's what gets ripped off the most. But the dead giveaway is white, wired earphones.
You hear Patricia Latham? Yes, things are really rocking here today to carry out your boyfriend finally showed up.
So Steve, tell us just one. Tell us a little bit about your background. And then I want to talk
about, you know, because you were here for the cream concert. I was talking about it. I was talking about it.
Small. I had a roommate in college and we shared a room in the dormitory and he preferred to have
his girlfriend come over and spend Friday nights with him rather than me. And I wonder why that is.
So I had no place to go. You know, the old tie was hung on the door knob. Oh, that was the signal.
That was the signal like we're getting busy. So I wandered over to the campus radio station
and no one else was stupid enough on a Friday night to want to rip and read news. Back then,
you had a news tell a type. Right. Right. I came off the wall. Back in the old. Back in the old.
That's the wire, baby. That's right. The wire. As opposed to the source. To what school was this?
That was a American University in Washington, D.C. in Asia's capital.
Okay. So that's how you got, so you got to Friday night shift on the...
Well, that eventually was said way into becoming a disjockey there.
And eventually worn my way up from music director to station manager in my senior year.
On the same time, I produced foreign language broadcast in Arabic and in Vietnamese and Cambodian
for the U.S. Information Agency. So I had a low level government. You're like a spook man?
Yes. I was. Cool. I was. And then I applied for a job as a golfer production assistant for
New York legendary radio district. He Murray the K. Murray the K. He broke thousands of
acts. Didn't he wasn't he the the man to go to back in the day? Yes. He was the end of his heyday then.
This was when he moved down to D.C. and decided to sort of go into a slower lifestyle.
He worked at a adult contemporary station in Silver Spring, Maryland. And he wanted somebody to help him
program the Bobby Gullsboro records. What do you mean program the Bobby Gullsboro records? What does that mean?
Well, he was allowed to program his show within the constraints of the format. So he needed somebody to
put together the playlists. Oh, you're just saying Bobby Gullsboro is an example of the whole station.
Yes, that would be yes. That's really cool because that's a talent that that fewer people have
because it's all relegated down to automated systems like selector and profit and it comes off of playlists.
It's kind of a science consultants tell you what to what to play and when to play it, right?
Right. And at the time there was a program director there and a music director.
But Marie they said, you know, you're going to do after noon drive. And okay, you got this guy here and he can
help you out. And of course, we opened up with the obligatory Frank Sinatra record every day.
And Marie taught me a lot. He taught me a lot about the business. I mean, he was he was the guy and
he was the man and he brought me to with him to New York at the time. He was doing syndicated radio
on weekends for the NBC radio network was called Monde. Oh, I remember that. Sure.
And then that's segue into a special weekend.
Marie the K's New York on WNB WNB and NBC and that eventually led to a full-time gig. And so
summer after my senior year, I was working with him there.
And that was Marie the K on drugs and strung out like a typical DJ and it's no, I like no, he was it was
funny. I probably in responsible for turning on to his first marriage of Anna. No, Steve, you
don't say you don't you don't smoke the holy herb. No, I don't. But I anymore. And no, it was funny.
He was on President Nixon's anti drug council. So, and he was smoking, though.
Yeah, that's great. Yeah, it was it was it was wild. He was with a moved in to DC with his
hot young woman model down there who was much younger than he and he was was the tie on the door
knob there too. Oh, I'm sure it was. And he left WWDCA and bought afternoons drives at WHFS.
Let me bought. They sold in the four-hour block. Really? Yes. Oh, that sounds like an atom curry move.
And he was allowed to do it every one that four hours and sold his own advertising.
Excellent. Excellent. And I became then his real full-time producer and my roommate at the time
became his board engineer. Okay. And we had a lot of fun. We started up a bit. It was a little
incongruous with the rest of the station sound because Marie would play hits. Now, this was early,
this must have been early 80s or even 70s. This is early 70s. Early 70s. Oh, this is 71.
How old are you now, Steve? 48? Um, you know, oh no, no, it's actually maybe 51 something like that.
I'm a child of the 50s. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Later.
Child of the 50s. Yeah. Patricia's 49. So, you got your younger than she. Number nine. Yeah. Number nine.
Number nine. So, the time it must have been crazy in the record business because this was the
beginning of really FM radio. Right. And what was the vibe about FM radio when it just started?
What were people saying about it? Because I've heard stories, but was it really analogous to what
we're, you know, what we've seen. It was, it was called free form progressive radio. And you could be
as loose or as open as you wanted to. And you do things. I remember I then did the overnight
CWHFS. And I remember one night, station broadcast in stereo. Actually, WHFS brought it.
That was, it was a quad. That was, oh, quad sure. Yeah. So, you had to read your own transmitter
engineers. You had to have your third class license and all that. Yeah. And there was a red button
you pushed. If you were going to play music more than a certain length, it was in mono.
Because you weren't allowed to have the stereo generator on. If you were broadcasting a mono, it was
as an FCC regulation. It's just like that. So I'd go, okay. Now, I'm inside your receiver right now.
Right. Left speaker. Okay. Now, watch this. That little red dot on your stereo system.
It's about to come on. It's going to go off. Oh, my god. I can troll you radio.
What used to do stupid messed up stuff like that? You know, and if you didn't feel like,
you know, segueing records, then it was records. Put on the side of Bob Dylan, you know,
sad-eyed lady of the low land, which went on for low land. 14 minutes. It was more like 20. Really.
Or play a side of John Lennon and the mother's invention at the film more. You know, doing scumbag,
which went on for, wasn't it, Frank's app on the mother's invention? No, but it was John Lennon
from live piece in New York. Oh, okay. So that's before my time, man. That's okay. That's okay.
So, you know, you could anything went? You know, what was AM radio doing?
Were they tightly formatted? Were they doing news and music as well? Well, still the bigger stations were
in DC at the time the big station was weamed 1390. The weamed team red coats, the big 1390.
Everybody. Good afternoon. So still, it was a transition. Don't we hear a team?
If you were an audio file, you had this great Mac daddy stereo system with the gold, gold plugs,
gold connectors. No, those, no, that was pre-gold. Yeah, it was just one one. Yeah,
if you're KLH speakers. Oh, that was the shit. That was the state of the art. You know, your thorns
turn table perhaps. Yeah. Yeah. And, and, you know, you listen to that. Oh, baby. Like the headphones on,
too. Oh, we used to do, oh, we just had to have said an hour every night, music for headphones.
And you'd find that the trippiest records, whether it was Pink Floyd or Jimmy Hendricks,
racing that phased back and forth. Back and forth. Wow. Wow. Okay. So it was, so you could totally
do whatever, what was the ratio of talk and music? Was it like WKRP kind of like Dr. Johnny fever?
You could do whatever you want it. I mean, we, we did a lot, we're there a lot, there was a lot of talk as
well. It could be. It was like, hey, brother Dave, it's not feeling too well today. So we're going to play some
tunes in the key of D next hour. And you play an hours worth of music in the key of D all segue
together. And you come out and I have to do, you know, 10 minutes of commercials. And of course,
I would love breaking them up with like little vignettes from the fire sign theater just to mess
with people. You're Steve Gilmore used to produce some of the fire sign theater stuff.
You know, they have a wonderful podcast, uh, site too. Yeah. Yeah. The fire sign. Yeah. After,
they were on the Gilmore gang. And after that, then they started up the whole podcast, uh,
stuff that they're doing. Yeah. Yeah. Totally. So so anyway, so that all went fine except,
you know, I was doing overnight. It's a WHFS and making $60 a week, sleeping all day, eating
Roy Rogers hamburgers, ruining my health. And I said this sucks. So I got accepted at grad school,
at Syracuse Newhouse School of Communications and went there, got my master's degree. And then I
came back and I needed a job. Okay. So, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so this new
fangled thing, cable TV. So, I go to the Warner Communications Building, learning a suit.
Now, this was, this was what year was this? This is going to be 73. Had you gotten laid
about that point? Um, maybe once. Okay. All right. Just checking. And so, um, I ran to a promotion
person who said, what do you don't want to wear in his suit? That's time I saw you. You were like,
a bowl of fur, smoking a big fatty with cactus. And I was like, yeah, well, I got to find a
job. So, we might have one for you. And lo and behold, I found myself Columbus Day 73
employed at $250 a week as the local New York City rep for Atlantic Records. Really? Which was
really cool because back then Atlantic had the wrong stones. And they have the left one. Yeah, let's
take a little longer. I'm spinners, a wreath of Franklin, et cetera, et cetera. Oh my god, that's awesome.
So, I didn't know what I was doing. So, you had to promote the local radio stations. So,
is my job to suck up to the air talent because then, for example, WNWFM, which was a big
Macdaddy station in New York City, the jocks had told discretion to play or not play whatever
they wanted. So, this was, this is really important to know this history because this is where a lot
of stuff, you know, it's important what we're doing right now with pod save music. Yes, it is.
Um, so was this in the payload days, or pre the scandals, or that was after the pills. No,
man, there was nobody know that people wasn't about, like, getting the stuff. It was like
appealing to a higher authority. Like, this was the cool shit to play. So, it's like, if you wanted
to play that track from, yes, you'd play it. Or if you didn't like, yes, and you preferred midler,
you'd play that. Right. Or I'm just trying to set the timeline history, pay all the scandals that
already happened, I think, right? Yeah, I mean, and that was almost, that was a different kind of music
and a format where rotation and repetition mattered. And FM was like, you want to play the same song.
That was my point. So, we had a revolution really. People were tired of the repetition and all the
crap on AM radio. FM radio came along. It was basically loser like you and me who had perfect
faces for radio sitting up there talking shit, right? You should be so self deprivating about that.
No, this is our time. This is the geeks and nerds are winning now. That's the geeks. But you were
on television. So, you did it all hair and makeup on. You come on. You know how that works.
So, it was a great, and it was a fun time, and, you know, people would play things and do things
because they liked it. And it was about the music and the passion. And I excelled in that and got promoted
and clawed my way up the corporate ladder until I exceeded my own expectations and found myself on
employed. Well, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a minute, first of all. So, you're promoting
all these bands. You got to take these bands up to the station sometimes if they were in town?
Yeah, okay. So, here, all right, one here. Brian Ferrie, rock scene music. Okay, Brian Ferrie's first
U.S. solo album. I drive, I'm driving around in a 1968 yellow Volkswagen convertible. Yeah.
And we go up to the radio station, W R and W and Breyer Cliff Manor in New York. And this is the
station where Howard Stern started? No. Yes, yes. But he wasn't there at the time. This was before Howard.
All right. And the honor of talent is a guy named Jeff Beck. And Jeff Beck's going to interview Brian Ferrie.
Now you have to understand rock scene music and Brian Ferrie are huge act overseas. And the states
they mean absolutely nothing. I mean, here's this good looking guy with his slick back hair doing
a version of it's my party. No way. Yeah. So, it's like it's strange. Yeah, work this one too.
Love is a drug. Yeah. I'm just going to play a little background. Okay. So, we're driving up the
Henry Hudson where Westchester and I put the top down and it's, all right. So, he gets up there
and the interview sucks. The guy on the air has no idea who rock scene music is. It has no idea
Brian Ferrie's. But we model through it. And then drive Brian back. Well, Brian goes storming
it to omit Irrigan's office and says, you're putting a damn convertible. My hair's blown up. The guy
doesn't even know who I am. Oh, no way. If you were to fold a whole attitude trip. Yes. Because he was a big star.
Not in England in the UK, right? All right. Or the time Mick Jagger delivered the tumbling dice record
to Atlantic. And I scurry over to WNW and give it to Scott Muni, the late great Scott Muni. Who plays
it on the air? And then Mick Jagger swagger's into omits office. How's it sound on the radio?
He says, well, I like to hear it on the radio. Get leads on the phone. Leeds,
mix and he wants to hear the song. He just played it 10 minutes ago. I don't care.
Got it. So, you had to call up Scott Muni. So, I call, I hotline Scott Muni. Listen,
fats, I know you just played this. But Mick Jagger's listening to the radio right now and he
wants you to play it again. And he did, of course, right? Because Scott was that kind of guy.
Now, the payback was, Scott would read live radio, come up spots. At the time, the big retailer
in New York City discount, retailer for records, was E.J. Corfets. So, they'd give him live copy.
And it'd be this week, he's exciting Atlantic albums on sale at E.J. Corfets. Emerson Lake and
Palmer. Batman, the spinners, the Rolling Stones, Led Zeppelin, Blubber, and Heathrow in
your name. And you say Steve Leeds? Right. And if you didn't call him,
you wouldn't listen and you got into deep doo doo. Oh, my god. What a power trip. Oh, no.
That was bad. But I would, I would be a good boy and I usually catch him.
But yeah, but lots of, this Jockey Scott Shannon would do that too. And, you know, when he knew
people were in town, he'd, he'd mentioned them on the radio. That's right. Yeah, he said,
well, I have everybody who has a good morning there. I think they'd be DJ Adam Curry.
And they'd be the DJ. Yeah. I did kind of like those days. They were kind of cool. Yes.
But then I guess, I mean, it kind of went away. Steve, what was the turning point when it
turned to the consultants? Is that the, is that what did it? The consultants really? The consultants
came in and commercialized and made a business out of the format and would come in with their
catalog on index cards, right, with a second set of index cards that had all the liners,
where like more of the music you want to hear or more music from dead guys, you know, 13 dead
guys in hour. And so, but why did the consultants get brought in? That's because there were a lot of
me. They were stations in markets where the owners wanted to try this newfangled format
playing that music that for them, though, young kids was the long hair. But they didn't
have to do it. And they were scared of their license and they needed a comfort zone. So if a guy
came in with a suit and a box of records within index cards, well, he must know because look at his
track record. So we bring him in. And so it, it bred this new breed of people who knew how to read
cards. Yeah. G. No time references ever allowed. No date. No weather. It was this vacuum where
you were so never supposed to leave. And if you told people 10 minutes on the uphill side of
eight o'clock, it's like, oh, well, people are going to leave it eight o'clock because they got to go
somewhere. Right. Which is kind of what your front on the radio should be to helping you do. I had this
horrible nightmarish fantasy and it happened to me. I was somewhere in the Carolinas and I woke up and
put the radio on and I didn't know where I was. I didn't have a clock in the room. I forgot my clock.
Right. Right. And the radio is not telling you the day. It's just a generic,
could-top 40-session. Where how am I? I had to open the window and look out and see that there was
sun. But that was what radio was supposed to be doing back then according to the concerns.
And who were these independent consultants? What were their backgrounds? How, how did the
someone must have gotten started with something? Must have been some seminal station that got
it all going. Well, funny enough, the guy who's the head of programming at XM,
guy named Lea Abrams. Yeah. And he really was the guy who, he was the young,
wonderful, wonderful, who had had some success in the Midwest in Chicago and he partnered up with
the guy named Kent Burkhard out of Atlanta and Kent was the sales guy who had much success in the
world of top 40 CHR and he brought this young kid in and they were just rolling because it was
the format was called Superstars. Hey, everybody, Superstars, Superstars. And it, you know,
really for a while was the thing. That was the format. It was almost like a national playlist almost.
Right. Was that, was that time that radio and records became important as the-
later, the play- because that's really- so if we shuttle forward, and this is just fascinating.
So in podcasting, I'm just trying to draw analogies that you can well understand.
The commercialization came with the consultant. So it was really fucking with the content.
But then big business became involved because the music and the record industries could generate
huge amounts of sales. If all these Superstar stations started playing tracks from albums,
there was this massive, you know, effort of sales that would be- we'd come out of the exposure.
And then the concert business would, you know, follow with that because they would begin the
roots of the dreaded radio concerts. And so you could break a band on that format,
bring the band in and so you develop the following. So like, always honky Dorian, everybody's
having a lot of fun making a lot of money. But it was, again, short-term thinking.
Because it all came crashing down, you know, and then it was like, we've developed nothing.
We've built no careers or bands. We've got a bunch of faceless songs. We've mentored no air talent.
And there's no training ground. You know, then you can go to the broadcasting school.
But no one knows how to pick a grade. I've had all these guys who had great sounding voices,
great sounding names, and they could read better than anybody.
But they had the personality of a dish rag.
Well, there was no personality.
Yeah. You know, I- I'm a graduate of the Connecticut School of Broadcasting.
Did you know that?
I have certificate.
Well, you could always go back there and be a faculty member now.
That's always plan B. Oh, no. That's why you moved to the curry cottage to Guildford.
Well, I want to start my new, my Guildford School of Broadcasting School of Broadcasting.
That'll be perfect, wouldn't it? So it has a nice ring to it.
So what do we have to do this time? There are some key differences. One is,
you know, we don't have to try and ram 13 songs into an hour because we have no defined time.
And we have infinite number of frequencies. The spectrum is infinite.
Compared to fragmentation, opportunities, or for immense playgrounds, audio playgrounds for people
to develop their craft. And expose new unfamiliar things. There's no stinking playlist. There's no stinking consultant.
All there is is this wide open pallet. And each one of you an artist with a paintbrush, and you can just, you know,
it's not about moving things around. It's like taking something brand new and opening and exposing it.
And it's basically where underground FM free form radio was back in the late 60s, early 70s.
Podcasting offers that amazing opportunity. Freedom. Right on.
Now there's a lot of talk about the commercialization of podcasting. Well, I think we all are
capitalists. At the end of the day, we all have to have a roof over our head and food in our
tummies, low fat foods, cholesterol free. No cheese. She's not listening. Okay. This is not brought to you
by the American area association. No, not this time. Not this time. But so, yes. So, you know what?
So, we can all stay in that cool ethos of non commercial world and fantasy. But, you know what?
We all are maturing. We have families. We have personal needs. We all want to have the new iPod.
We all want to have super fast computers and connections in that cost money. So, you know what?
We have to deal with that. And there are people who want to reach this audience. And you know what?
So, it's not about playing eight minutes of gibberish every hour. There may be somewhere in there
a few minutes of information that you might find useful and helpful in your world. Or you could choose
to fast forward, you know, or not listen or go away. I mean, the beauty of the media today is no one's
forcing you to do anything. If you don't like what you hear, do something else. Go change the channel.
Switch the frequency. How up to another playlist. It's all about, you know, choices and freedom.
And so, if something isn't your cup of tea, move on. But there's nothing wrong with bring some
Monet into it and monetizing it because you guys need to be monetizing it rather than big
brother coming down and saying, okay, here's what we're going to monetize it. Right. Right on.
Right on. Well, I'm really excited about the the music angle of it, the pod safe music angle.
Because I think we're building our own music industry. In many ways, very analogous to what you just
spoke about, only again, you know, the the amount of choice and the amount of freedom that the
artists have, particularly to do their own sales. I mean, that's what I think is really cool.
And their own distribution. However, it's still limited online. You know, it's still just
is a limitation compared to what you can do with the distribution Starbucks. You know, I mean,
Jesus, those guys sell some fucking records. You know, like that puts some of the majors to shame
these days how well they're doing. So there's going to be alternative forms of distribution that
will also tap into. Maybe it will be the next Starbucks. You know, it could be maybe the next time
you go to Starbucks, it's an iPod filling station wireless or something like that. You know,
stuff like that could happen. So I think we just have to kind of grow into it. I think that's
what I feel is all these opportunities are here. And we have to figure out what the new ways
are going to be. You know, we still have to be developed. Personally, what I find interesting would be
the critical mass of music exposure of pod safe music. That is stuff that is not
put out by any international music company, but is receiving a lot of airplane exposure through
the world of podcasting and the challenge I raise is I wonder if someone can put together a pod safe
airplane chart of the most spun spun terrible work. Well, most played pod safe music. It's
interesting. You say that because that's exactly what part of the pod safe music network is going to
be unbelievable. Did I tell you that? I don't know. No, because I mean, this is, I'm not saying
you well, thank you anyway. That's exactly what we're doing. You know, it's going to be
you come on to the site and there's a place for artists to set up their sales to put up their
demo material to make whatever they want available to podcasters and or regular listeners.
You know, some licensing options. You know, basically creative comments. You can say how it can
be used, but the point would be you let it, you let your songs be played on podcasts. And then
there's a place where podcasters to log in. And there's a whole bunch of statistics there, obviously
most downloaded, you know, all kinds of charts. But one of those charts, of course, is going to be
most played. You know, that's going to be really interesting because then we, I mean, then you basically
close the loop, right? Totally, totally awesome, dude. No, it's all the way. We never finished. We're
like, wait, we're not, let's play some music for a second. Let's play, uh, what do we play?
I'm going to play that mashup that I played earlier for you. Oh, this is awesome. Yeah,
this is, uh, this came into the mashup at podshow.com email address for the series show
exclusive on the source. The goes that feeds Ray Parker Jr.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah,ha, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah
We'll get you one teller, we'll get you
Can you get out of your knees?
So many, I can hold it down to it
I won't be, I'll be soon, I won't be falling down, I'll be down
I won't be, I won't be, I won't be
Baby, I love you, we'll stay down, I'll be soon
We'll fight, we'll be soon, we'll stay down, I'll be soon
We'll fight, we'll get you one, I'll be soon
We'll stay down, I'll be soon, we'll stay down, I'll be soon
Ray Parker, Jr. versus nine inch nails on the daily source code sent to us by Craig Maloney says he
don't know who the original person is who mixed it. He's just a carrier. Good enough for me. I love that. Awesome.
So, you know Steve, we can have to do another one of these because it is just no way we can ever get to all the
all the cool stuff, all the history. You got a lot of knowledge about just how things work and you
work with some amazing people. Just give me a couple of the names of the people that you work with
that you've either through promotion or just working with them and you're some of your favorites.
You really hung out with that you really met. Like Joan Jet, I mean, you really were
closely with Joan. She was at my wedding. Oh, there you go. Before I forget. Yes, sir.
Do you know who is the hugest Joan Jet fan and would really want to interview her
just like the most fucking enormous, huge fan? No, who rock and roll geek, Michael Butler.
So, we should hook that up. Can you hook them up with a phone or something like that? I think he'll be
required to play the eyeliner CD and exchange for that. Well, as long as she gives him the rights to do it.
Well, I think it's on black hard records. I think I can do that, right? Yeah, I think I believe so.
Yeah, could you hook that up, sir? Yes, you'll give me his contact information. I will call Lenny Kuhuna.
Michael Butler will freak out. But he'll be good. And he said he only want, you know, it'll just be
what happens when a geek freaks out. He's the rock and roll geek, man. He's not just a geek. He's
rock and roll geek, man. Okay, thank you. So, Joan, he's what I'm feeling. I'm feeling yeah.
Well, I've been blessed and privileged to work with a lot of people on both sides of the fence,
super executives, you know, like Chris Blackwell and Doug Morris. So, you know, those are people who,
you know, you feel blessed to work with. And then the artists, you know, George Thurgood,
when I was on my own, the first album on round of records was something important and going out
with the stones and their 78 to or same thing with Emerson Lake and Palmer in their heyday
Robert Plant, like convinced him to do his first interview in the, you know, in the Led Zeppelin's
heyday back in the 75 with New York legend Allison Steele, the night bird, right? And he'd never ever
done, you know, an interview like that, you know, or, let's see, you two have been over the
years so kind to me, really. I actually work the octane baby. So those guys are including
Bono, they're all really nice. Yeah, I mean Bono pulled a little out of two on the ones. That's
why. Maybe I just, I don't know, maybe I pissed him off and was unaware of it, but
well, they, you know, they were very cognizant of what a record promotion person does. And when
their record was knocked out of number one at the radio airplane chart by Blind Millen for one week.
It pissed me off because capital records pulled a fast one at the time and what is that being?
They actually paid a station to play the song like a million times in the overnight. But that's
illegal. No, it's not as long as it's disclosed. Wait a minute. So it's legal to pay a station to have
that station to play a song as long as you disclose that information. If you disclose it on the air,
yeah, and, and you have no personal gain and the station's getting paid. Well, first of
personal gain. No, no, no, no, no. The station is selling advertising. The following version of
Blind Millen is brought to you by capital records is perfectly legal, really. Yes. Well, why don't
they just do that then? Well, there's a lot of stations that do do that in overnight. They offer
rather than selling a four minute block of four different commercials to sell a four minute hitting
me. No, I don't know. That goes on all the time. Oh, really? Well, that's stuff won't happen in
podcasts. Can they just do their own? Well, why is it? Well, okay. There you go. Do your own. Do
you want to thank him. But when you hear someone talking passionately about record, that's something
else. But anyway, that's pretty amazing. So, so they saw the record back to number one. Wait,
wait, hold on a second. I'm sorry. I'm not even understands how this works. Sorry. So, you buy the
time that plays the record and then multiple times. Multiple times. So, they got enough additional
airplay. It jumped over, chemically. The number of spins. You too, Dr. Justin. Just so you understand
because the top 40 charts that compiled partially. Well, this was the modern rock chart. Okay.
So, but all charts, I think, are still compiled partially through cumulative number of
impressions, aka spins. How many times it's played in a given time period? Interesting. You
use the word impressions because that's something that shows up in the banner world as well.
That's pretty interesting. So, okay. So, that's basically buying your spot in the chart. Right.
So, I was, but I thought, but now that they do sound scan isn't that the way that the chart's
compiled now, or that's still no sound scan is the sales sales. Right. What we're talking about
is either media base or BDS. What the fuck does that mean? There's two competing services that
record companies and radio guys look at. There's BDS, which is broadcast data systems, which is
owned by the fine Dutch company, VNU, Yahoo, who owned Nielsen. They own Nielsen correct. And they
have computers that are hooked up to all major market radio stations and secondary markets
and monitor 24 hours, day seven days with every single frigging song they're playing. And that's
tabulated into million different subsets depending on what information you're looking for. Media base
is owned by premier networks, which is owned by clear channel. Right. And they have a similar
service, except there's up until several months ago was human monitored. And there would be a
skimmer tape developed fed down your internet connection. And then somebody's sitting there
and going through the songs. And there are people actually out there in radio and who can
listen to a five second snippet and know what that is. And they type up a playlist. It's called
the hit test. By the way, obviously, you would never be able to be employed by media base
given on your averages on that. Sorry. But he's still a guy. He's still a good guy. So okay. So
those are the two monitoring services that the industry is used to reflect what's going on in
radio land. Interesting. All right. So those guys should be fucking frightened of us because,
you know, that's what DRM, what that actually does is they, you know, within, I know it's within
every Microsoft player, probably within every, or Microsoft base, you know, like all the other MP3
players. But also probably on the iPod is they can track when you play, you know, when you press
play and when you stop, they can track exactly the device can track exactly, you know, what you
listen to. And we're not feeding it back. I guess. I mean, who knows what what Apple and my,
well, you know about grace note, right? No. Okay. When you put a song in your computer,
that was CD in your computer. Yeah. And it pops up. It tells you what the, what it is. It identifies.
It's already sent that to home base. No. When you start listening to that, it sends it to grace note.
And they actually, if you go to gracenote.com, publish, not publish. It's wrong word. They make
available international charts of the most listen to songs. Sorry, correction. Most listen to CDs
or albums by artists internationally. Really. They don't, they, they do have the availability
and the technology to drill it down to. Here's the most listen to music and gilfirding one. Right.
They could do that. But they have to be incentivized to be able to do that. But that database is already
evolved and they're fabulous. So those are the guys that bought CDDB, I think. They are.
Yeah. They are. You know that I was one week late of buying that. I wanted to buy it and I,
and I, and I called the guy said we just sold it to someone else. Like a ridiculous amount. Like,
you know, 75 grand or something. I knew it was, I knew that was going to be fabulous.
Interesting. So are they using that data? Are they selling that to anyone yet?
They haven't figured out how to monetize it. Oh, man. What have some ideas?
Well, they know they know, but they haven't found people who want to pay for it. And they have no
idea with the economic where it'll be. And I'm derelict in my responsibilities because somebody
there has offered that research information on trial basis to me to share with folks up at one
of my clients. Yeah. We should look at that. We should look at that. Yes. So you just said clients.
Because now interestingly enough, Steve, you're a consultant. I, I'm an consultant. That. Okay.
I'll take that. And we should talk about your MTV years and stuff. But let's do that on the,
on the next time in New York. Oh, because we're like 44 minutes. I still want to get your
cream review. Oh, yes. Yes. Well, the reason, the reason I'm here. Yeah. So that's not a
kill for it. Did you, I mean, did you see if you weasel these tickets? How do you hook up with all this?
Sure. I have a very good friend in London who has been involved in the music industry for
the last 20 some odd years. And when I'd heard that there was a possibility that cream
we're going to reunion constant royal Albert Hall. I called him up and I said, listen, if this
happens, can you cop a pair of tickets for us? And he said, yeah, that's no big deal. Who's this? You
want to tell us who this? No, it's my friend Peter Price. Peter Price, Peter Price, the pick of Pickle
Pipper Puppers. I can pop my piece. I'm very careful. Yeah, it's perfect. Yes, it's perfectly
really. Radio, shack. Everybody. It's a handy mic. Not handy, but handy. Really. I'm Peter. Peter,
I met Peter when he was managing musical youth and passed the dog. He asked the Dutchy by the
left. And so I bet you. That's not hard safe. Can't do that. I bet you haven't no matter what.
By the mighty diamonds. No. No, you got the, the, the, I bet you. I bet you that I have the musical
youth first. And Peter had done promotion at Virgin Records UK. He had done international.
He was the managing director of W. E. A. Ireland. He came back to work.
Yep. That was a big hit. Remember the huge hit. All right. So all these pop radio stations
are playing this song and they don't really know what's a Dutchy. What back of the time you
mean? Yeah. Yeah. I think most people understood it's Steve.
I don't think so. No. Okay. So anyway, so Peter, that's how I met Peter.
Over that song. And over the years, he's worked for Stockhaken and Waterman. Now he's doing some
international work for Universal. And he's just a friend and a guy who I've worked with over the
years. We've known each other. And you know, in fact, I'm staying with him in this trip in London.
Yeah. All done. We have an intermission. Hello, dear. Hello. Yeah. Good. We're just winding up. Steve's
going to do his cream review. Cream, something very filled with rich, fat, dairy product. Very unhealthy.
Finally some cream today. Cream. By the way, in England, they have this thing called
clotted cream. Yeah. You might as well just like inject fat into your arteries. It's the most unhealthy
thing. Yeah. It's a heart attack. Get in front of the mic, huh? If you're going to talk it's
sort of a heart attack on A. What is it? It's sort of a heart attack on a bone. Yeah. Right.
Heart attack on a bone. Heart attack on a bone. But it's good. Sounds like a recipe. This is what
we didn't talk about this because Steve, do you know what August 5th is? Is that someone's
anniversary? Yeah. That's right. Because Patricia and I decided to get married in New York.
Yeah. And was it kind of like a 988? 88. Yeah. We said, uh, how about Friday, right? Did we?
Was it something like that? How about Friday? Yeah. It's okay. It's good. We had to go to
down the city hall and we needed a witness. Can't I get a witness? Yeah. You remember Steve?
Yes, I do recall that moment in city hall where the act was committed. Yeah. That was cool.
It does. How many years ago? It'll be 18. 18 years folks and they haven't fought a day.
18 blessed years. No one's drawn blood. Let's put it that way. And by the way, they both look as
happy as youthful and young and fresh as the day you married us, Steve. Actually, the only difference
is Adam's hair is differently clothed. That's true. Maybe there was a couple in front of us,
like some punk rock and they were getting married and they needed a witness and I was there
witness. Yeah. Oh, yeah. And I don't have that thing you may be growing the back of my hair.
What? Appreciate you kept telling me I needed to have a ponytail? No.
Hair on your shoulders? No. What do you? A little braid? No, I had that. But no, you kept telling me,
let the hair grow in the back. It should go down in the back longer. Oh, okay. She was my stylist.
That was my stylist. She did Adams hair. Adam went on the roadie. We had to send a hair stylist
with him. No, no one, the MTV never paid for a freaking hair. No, they didn't pay for it. They had
to have one. And let's see, we tried getting him corporate endorsements for hair products.
Just never worked. I wish someone had done that. No one ever approached me about a hair endorsement.
You could have been the first pearl guy. Oh, no. I think they went for the short cut gay guy. Look.
That's true. Pearl. They call you the big hair guy. Yeah. They still call me for so many years.
You don't have any big hair. No. No. No. No. But it's just like the bluffed one and the material girl.
Yeah. Exactly. Exactly. That's right. That's right. Madonna, Michael and Nate.
He's a good company. Yeah. A really good company. It was. And that's how he can walk around.
Michael Jackson now didn't do anything. Michael Jackson. I think he didn't do this. I think he's
being fucking. He's being fucked. Did you do this? There was an article on the New York Post. It showed
his, he has a hair weave in the front. Yeah. I wonder. And it was like, can you imagine
with all the plastic surgery? And now he, like, has hair implants? I don't know. I've never had
a contemplate that. We see just. I thought he was a whole week. But answer the question.
Michael Jackson, did he do it or not? Is he guilty? What is it? Child malestation?
But what does that mean? What is, when you see child malestation, he's slept. It's it's clear.
He slept with no, that's not child malestation. No. No. So you're talking touch.
You did. You graved robbed. Every man. No, no, no. That's not what you got me.
That's great, great, really.
Never's feelings, what I did.
And you can't edit on podcast,
wait, no, I don't even think that's the same trouble
when I got it in the Realize of Nicor Filiac.
Yes, what are you doing?
Yeah, wait, how old is he when you stole his heart?
But you've met Michael Jackson.
I've met him.
You've met Michael.
I've never had touched the glove one.
I've never touched him.
Wasn't there a story about him and Tommy Matola and Alimo?
Oh, that's, no, that wasn't Tommy Matola that was,
that's for another episode.
In fact, you'll have to interview Harvey Leeds for that.
Will he tell the story?
Is he going to chicken shit like you just didn't?
No, no, he don't.
He'll tell the story.
Yeah, he has the specifics much more graphically than I do.
I would love to hear that.
Yeah.
Well, he got our Harvey's trip to Neverland,
tune in for that particular episode.
Okay.
What I'm in New York.
Are you good looking?
Is that, you'll have to ask him.
Just check out, both all the Leeds boys are good looking.
Yeah, all two of them.
Yeah, they are, they are.
She said as we stare at the Star Sisters photo outside the door.
No.
Um, all right, so anyway, so Peter Price.
Oh, so he got us tickets.
We're almost done, huh?
All right, we'll be down in a bit.
All right.
Okay.
Good bye.
And then could you turn the red light back on again over the studio door?
So people know not to just come in.
No, just come in.
So we got tickets for Royal Albert Hall for the third night of four.
Right on.
And got very good seats.
Not ever been to Royal Albert Hall.
Not knowing what a nice place it is to enjoy music.
Do you know how many holes it takes to fill the Albert Hall?
No one really knows.
But it's surprising to you that.
I could.
So how was it, dude?
So is Ginger Baker like ancient now?
He's only 65.
But he looks ancient, doesn't he?
Well, he looked ancient back in 60.
That's like Charlie Watts, like his drummers man.
They always look old when they get going.
They do.
But the audience last night was amazing for me.
It was the audience.
Because there was nobody there under 40.
Right.
And the merchandising booths where they're selling, you know, 20 pound t-shirts and eight pound
coffee mugs and $60 jackets if you want to go that way or a $35 loan.
A little bit of the ground pound.
Yeah.
So for us dollar guys.
That's right.
But then.
Okay.
So, you know, the audience was.
So how many t-shirts did you buy?
Well, funny enough they're having, they have a website wwwcream2005.com.
But they're not selling anything there yet because.
And of course, brother Harvey had to have a t-shirt.
So I got a t-shirt.
A t-shirt.
And only one for you for your bro, not one for yourself.
I'm not.
I have enough t-shirts and that's true.
And I asked you where your CDs are or my t-shirts.
Yeah.
Exactly.
So, okay.
So, we're allowed with a haul.
They don't dim the lights.
They keep the lights on the whole time.
Really?
Yes.
And the audience was a trip.
Why is that?
That's funky.
It was cool.
It worked.
It felt much more intimate that way.
Like chandelier lighting.
Is that kind of the deal?
Or is it just really house lights?
House lights.
So, some of your friends from MTV were there.
I saw Tom Freston.
Yeah.
I mean, now like the co-head mother fucking hauncho of Iacom.
Yes.
Unbelievable.
Van Toffler.
Who's president of MTV?
Right.
He used to be the lawyer who sued me.
Ah.
Okay.
So, the weather here in Guilford today is cloudy.
Very nice.
No.
I had respect for Van.
No problem.
Juan Sikes was there.
I said Gary Gursch.
There.
I don't know who that is.
He's a president of Strummer Records.
They put out the Mars Volta album.
I saw what the fuck that is.
I had no idea what the Mars Volta records.
Well, so you were living in America?
No.
Okay.
Living in America.
James Brown written by Dan Hartman and Q.
And what's his name?
Charlie Midnight.
Wow.
There's a reference.
And so sitting right next to me is this young kid.
And sitting next to him is somebody looks really familiar.
Look over.
It's Steve Windwood.
Now, how bizarre is that.
Steve Windwood watching Eric Clapton.
Jack Bruce and Ginger Baker.
I mean, if you substitute Rick Gretch, you had blind faith.
Unbelievable.
By the way, Steve was actually bought merch.
Frisk.
Yeah.
I was shot.
So his kid must be like 20.
No, no.
I was kidding.
I'm very young.
Oh, he has a really young new wife.
I don't know.
Yeah, whatever.
So that was.
So that was a lot of.
A lot of fun.
That's cool.
Actually, I introduced him because he had just met my brother last week,
because he's looks like he's going to sign with epic.
Yeah.
Really?
Yes.
Based upon his newfound transit.
Well, I think that records the shit, by the way.
Well, that's a great record.
His last album came out on the same label,
The Jam Band String Cheese.
I forgot the name of the label.
It came out.
But he decided he wanted to, you know,
to the corporate, you know, universe of records.
Yeah.
Fuck, man.
So, you know, it was cool watching Steve Windwood, you know, there.
And so, the, you know, I was lucky.
Here's the Murray, the K connection again.
When I was a, we,
uh, led back in 1967.
Cream played their first show ever in New York City.
Excuse me.
First shows.
For nine days straight,
they played five shows a day at the RKO theater.
For the Murray, the K Easter review.
No way.
And who else was on the bill?
Because they were probably were forced onto the bill
by one of the agents saying,
well, if you want such and such,
you have to take this new band.
Five shows a day.
Five shows.
And if you got there before,
and you got a free album.
So, the who were on the show,
the cream,
and the headliner was Wilson Pickett and Mitch Ryder.
No way.
So, this is amazing.
This is amazing.
It was probably four or five bucks or something.
It was amazing.
And when people saw a cream,
they were like,
it was arrested the band.
Because there were only three guys.
Right.
And I remember the marquee outside.
So vividly,
it's three little mountains of cream.
I said,
debut cream.
I was like,
what the heck is that?
Yeah.
And they did two songs.
They did,
um,
I feel free.
And I'm so glad.
Which, by the way,
is the song they opened up with last night.
I'm so glad.
Interesting opener.
Yes.
Yeah.
So the show was really,
um,
interesting.
Because the rumors around are that they,
the only reason this is going on,
is Eric Clapton wants to help out Jack and Ginger
and put some money in their pocket.
Is that, well,
you know what?
That would probably make a lot of sense.
I even see Ringo Star doing,
infomercials for time,
life records.
So I guess the,
the might of the last forever.
You know,
rumor has it that Ginger is not in the best of health.
Yeah.
Well, I think he's been sick for a while, hasn't he?
I don't know.
I remember these rumors from 20 years ago, even.
So Eric certainly doesn't need the money,
nor the exposure at this point in his career.
So he agreed to do these four shows with a DVD committed
to coming out this fall.
That's really sweet.
Yes.
That's really sweet of him.
And there's talk that if the music is approved,
that they will allow a CD to be made from it as well.
Does that mean there might be a tour to fall along?
No.
Because Ron Delzner,
the people's promoter in New York City.
Is that, do I, do I know the hint of sarcasm there,
Mr. Leads?
Not at all.
Uh, has offered them a boatload of money to play
Madison Square Garden, and they've turned it down.
And then I heard that,
well, then it can't be about money.
Why did turn it down?
Well, then I heard that it's driving the price up.
No, no, no.
A, Eric has some tour plans,
and B, equally, or more important,
probably in the reality world,
is that Ginger has some issues
and can't come back into the states.
Oh, man.
No, that's a rumor.
I want to clarify.
That's probably a taxation rumor.
No, no, no.
I don't think it's something like that.
Really?
Is it drugged there?
I don't know.
Come on.
Not from 100,000 years ago.
The US government has a long memory.
By the way, folks,
in the Curry Broadcast studios here in Gilford,
there's a photo of Adam and W on the wall.
It's a good one, isn't it?
Yes.
I know what he's doing all those years in Holland.
Oh, I just want, not equal, equal opportunity.
If you haven't listened to it,
check out that John Kerry podcast.
Oh, yeah, that was cool.
Well, can I just, I just want to, I just want to play one,
one snippet.
Just listen to this part, Steve.
I didn't play this for you.
Listen to this.
By the way, we are podcasting today on top of
Jack's blanket.
Listen to me.
And we're having to be really careful because
Elizabeth has her dot coat sitting on this.
This is great stuff.
I like it.
I have my dad.
Listen to what she said.
Zero sitting on Jack's blanket, which, by the way,
is really important because she has a great,
I'm not drinking that coat anymore.
And it is like a huge change for me.
First, how long has it been there?
Cold turkey for like three months?
Yeah.
Three months?
You're still drinking it there.
I am.
But I'm finding out that I'm not drinking quite a lot.
It's not quite as much as I thought it was.
That you were drinking mussels.
It's like John and Drew.
It's one of those things to death.
I don't even waste the blood on the blanket.
I don't think it's the worst thing that I've ever gotten on this blanket.
That's it.
Didn't need to know that.
Was that the line of the, of the whole podcast?
No, is that product placement for Diet Coke?
No, for sprite zero, whatever it is.
No, but that's, you know, this is, if I, if I listen to this guy talking,
instead of that long-head jackass, you know,
I would have had different feelings about,
about the outcome of, of the election.
This is really good.
And she's talking about her life and the radiation that she's going through.
It's interesting shit.
Well, podcasting will change the politics of the world soon.
Did better.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Back to the, back to the, back to the cream reunion.
Okay.
So they opened up with, I'm so glad.
I didn't need it.
It's spoonful.
Then clapped and sang outside woman blues.
Then changed her.
Did pressed rat and wart ag.
It was remind me of like an eanduri thing.
It's almost like a rap thing.
It was pretty wild.
Did you do a drum solo?
Did you?
Well, we'll get to that.
Okay.
Then we did sleepy time.
NSU.
Erica did badge.
You know, singing on that.
And of course now, today is the morning after the British election.
Right.
And Tony Blair won.
He won.
But he got his ass woke, because everybody expressed their
displeasure with him being W Junior.
Well, and, and in this parliament, you know, and I figured out how it works.
Now, it's, it's, it's number of seats in the house.
So, um, labor still has a majority, but only by 66 votes.
Or that's projected, I think, at this time.
But it's almost over.
So that's pretty much what's going to be.
So, how ironic the day of the British election.
Cream do politician.
Yeah, of course.
Of course.
Sweet wine, Roland and Tumblin.
Uh, we're, we're Jack didn't play base.
He just, like, jammed on the harmonic of the whole time.
Uh, now they did one non cream song, Stormy Monday, which is, like, a
Clapton, you know, Evergreen.
So that was interesting.
They did deserted cities.
One under bed sign.
We're going wrong.
Eric did it.
You know, jammed up version of Crossroads.
And this little girl, one of the youngsters in the audience, go.
Screams.
You're my hero.
Don't you crossroads?
Yeah.
So that was cool.
It's in on top.
White room.
And then the piece that exists.
They opened up.
And then Jack and ginger.
Sorry.
Jack and Eric walk off stage and let ginger just go wild for about 10 minutes.
Oh, really?
Hold.
Now, here's, here's the culpa.
As soon as he breaks in drum solo, people start rushing the stage.
Really?
See, he's, like, 40 year old.
Oh, push it up to this stage with his no security guard.
No.
And adult concert elite event.
Right.
So it was, it was pretty funny.
Oh, and why were people dressed?
Oh, you know, lots of denim.
But there were, you know, it was a very subdued crowd.
There wasn't a lot of body piercings.
Let's put it that.
How about dope smoking?
Must have been some pleased.
Didn't see any of it.
Didn't see it.
I think that went on before.
I think people arrived with that.
And, oh, so the, sort of the, the,
with the stage is covered by this white psych.
And projected on it is a light show.
I love the old film more.
But it's not with the liquids and stuff.
Yeah.
It's just, right.
It's like an orange.
It's an animated, an animated.
I was like, okay.
And he's going off on to it.
I mean, it's just like, it's out.
Was it was the animated stuff, okay?
Or was it kind of lame?
It worked.
But if you saw, if you lived to that, it was lame.
The house lights on too.
That was an infunky.
It was weird.
But you won't be able to see it in DVD coming out this fall on.
One over home video.
I don't know.
Yeah.
It definitely will.
And so that was it.
And told and they come back and finish the few notes.
And I'm sorry.
I'm boring.
Go.
It's just, it's a long, it's a long podcast.
Like a box of gin.
No, no, no.
Take no note of that.
This is fascinating, Steve.
I wish we could play some of these songs, which we can't.
Yeah.
That's the bummer here.
It's not pot safe.
Yeah.
Fucking bummer.
So, towed finishes.
Grand finale.
Boom.
Everybody's screaming.
They walk off stage.
And the three of them joined together for the first time
or leading in bow.
Because to me, they started off like a house on fire.
It was almost like going through the mechanical motions.
Eric just didn't seem.
He was like Mr. Cash will out there with his sneakers.
And his, you know, turquoise blue shirt.
And he was just like, he was like doing it.
Because he was just doing it.
Right.
And so it kind of was at the end.
I felt it was lackluster.
And they came back.
And they're not going right.
Well, white room.
I've heard Clapton do as a solo performance.
But you said they already played that.
Right.
But it was, it was great live.
But last night it was just like so mechanical.
You know.
Anyway, so toad.
That's the end.
People rush off.
And then they come back for an encore.
And what do you think their encore would be?
White room again.
Sunshine of your love.
Ah, that's pretty cool.
And of course, that, you know.
Again, I was like hoping for the heavens to open.
It didn't happen.
But you know what?
These guys were in their 60s.
It was a fantasy.
It was fun.
They did.
Sorry about that.
We're just going to go a little background ambience.
And this was the finale last night.
And it will be the finale tonight as the fourth consecutive night of Cremes reunion.
Royal Albert Hall.
You're talking it up Steve.
You're talking up the record.
Hey, we got 10 on the uphill side of wherever you are.
Whatever time you're listening.
This is ever coming.
Did you break a jack bruise?
On the ancorate.
See, I need the digital clocks.
I can tell.
Yeah.
Hard for sure.
That liner reader card for sure.
No, that would be somebody else.
Oh, and Sean Penn was in the audience last night too.
So it was, he's right.
He was a festive evening from start to finish.
You know, I Sean Penn story.
I told you my Sean Penn story, didn't I?
No, but you must know Michael Penn.
No, him too.
But it was Sean Penn.
Where is that?
It was, that was his musical brother.
But Chris Penn.
Chris.
That was the, the tubby one.
Come on man.
Don't you remember he got in all kinds of fights and shit.
He was like the Billy Carter of the Penn Brothers.
Wow.
I didn't know the Penn Brothers.
And he did a little bit of acting.
Yeah.
It was obnoxious.
So I remember the MGM grand.
Yes.
MGM grand was the airline between Los Angeles and JFK.
And it was all first class, like 737 with state rooms.
The preferred airliner of the Jays.
Yeah.
Of course.
Well, it was still around and it was golden toilets.
And it was just fucking great.
And it was all movie stars and record execs and celebrities.
And it was like our private little airline.
And how many seats were?
How many people?
The whole plane was maybe like 50 or something like that.
And that was it.
And so I was flying out by myself.
And I had a state room.
So it was, you know, just like in a train.
We closed and there's three on each side.
And the table can levitate up in the middle.
So you can have your meals facing each other.
And I was there with Sean Penn.
Chris Penn.
And his mom.
And we're sitting there the four of us in the state room for like five and a half hours.
And you know, it was really uncomfortable because, you know, it's like dude.
You know, this is like Sean Penn.
And at the time he just, you know, the big messy divorce from Madonna and everything.
So first Chris Penn is there.
You know, taking off his shirt, he's walking around with, you know, with a bear.
He's a bear chest drinking beer.
You know, burping and farting all over the place about the whole plane.
So he's just an embarrassment by himself.
And then, you know, finally, so Sean Penn says,
Yeah, how you doing?
Are you the guy from VH1, right?
So of course immediately, I'm shattered.
It's just fucking shattered.
And say, uh, wrong channel.
So I said, hey, dude.
Uh, what was it like?
I don't know.
He says,
Hell have no fury, my friend.
That's what his response was.
Hell have no fury.
And we didn't talk about anything.
And he's got issues, right?
I think I like him.
He's a fucking bitch.
What do you say at the Academy of Worts?
He was trashing that I didn't see the Academy of Worts.
I like Sean Penn.
He's a great actor.
Who was the male actor in Alphi?
I don't know.
I haven't seen Alphi.
Oh, he keeps, he can't make nasty references.
So.
No.
Don't know.
Well, he always has some issues.
Oh, whatever.
Yes.
Whatever.
Hey, Steve, was any more you want to say about the cream stuff?
Um, no.
Did it, did it fulfill your fantasy?
Listen, I went to the first show in America.
I have some, you know, in your life,
you don't get too many chances to have closure.
Yeah, because you went to the first one and kind of the last one.
That's closure.
So in the final days of my life, I can look up and go, okay.
I spent enough time doing the things I needed to do.
And one of those was, I got to see cream.
The entire career from beginning to end.
That's true.
Oh, my God.
That's so beautiful.
Oh, that's a rock and roll lifestyle.
And I'm not a rock and roll geek.
And now what you hate, man?
Hook that up for my boy.
No, hold on.
Right on time.
This is almost ready, isn't it?
Whatever.
Oh, you know what?
That's Jeremy.
Hello.
Okay.
Well, Adam is having this conversation.
And boring you to hear listening to that conversation.
Even I just doing a podcast.
So we're going to close out this special edition.
What give you a call?
From the curry cottage.
Okay.
In Guilford, England.
The Saturn Curry was Jeremy.
He was finishing his cell phone call, which he has now terminated.
Yeah.
All right.
You know what?
I need one more bit from you.
Because what we didn't talk about is that you.
The Adam.
You.
Yes.
This is the Adam.
I hope people listen to this because that was a lesson.
You had some great stories, man.
I love listening to that.
This would be good for people over the weekend.
They can carry it through like an hour and nine minutes already.
So let's.
It's a lot of treadmill time to be listening.
Yeah, no shit.
Well, maybe they already checked out who knows.
You hooked up the serious deal.
Yeah.
You're to blame.
I'm to blame.
Okay.
Go ahead and tell us what's the ability.
Tell us what happened, man.
Well, it's not.
It's not.
You know, it's not very exciting.
It's not as enticing as.
No, I know.
MTV story.
That's what.
Well, man.
It's almost as right.
But to me to bring closure Steve, we started with the MTV story.
But there's no closure.
This is a continuing epoch.
That's right.
So Adam is.
You know, on the front page of the New York friggin times.
This was a couple weeks ago.
And he's everywhere.
And I hear his podcast.
He's going to be in New York.
See the power of podcasts.
Yeah.
You know what?
I got to look him up.
I haven't seen his post since the days at MTV.
I kind of missed his whole dot com.
That chapter of the book sort of fell out of my.
Per view because I was immersed in my own.
Misha Goss.
So, um, I said, you know, I got to find him tracking down and I tracked him down.
And I said, you, uh, being in New York.
Yeah.
Hey, why don't you come up to serious.
Since you're a toy geek and a technology geek, you might like this.
And of course, I at the time mentioned it to Scott Greenstein, who's president of serious
music sports and entertainment.
And he said, oh, we got to get him here.
We got to get him here.
I said, no, no, he'll be here.
Oh, we got to get this podcasting thing going here.
And I said, you know, that's exactly what everyone envisioned.
So, we love their go.
I'm going to get him here.
I said, oh, well, you know, I'll feel be here.
You can talk to him.
Oh, great.
So, um, that's not fair.
He doesn't talk like that.
But anyways, he does talk like a radio guy kind of.
He's absolutely no radio.
He's a, he's a, he's a, he's a, he's a, he's a, he's a, he's a, he's a film
and an attorney.
He's a lawyer.
Oh yeah, low but low is there.
Yes, but he, if you ask him a legal question, I don't know.
I don't know.
Yeah, that's done great so invited Adam up and showed him all the toys because it's a pretty
interesting place when 50 fucking full-blown studios is like the entire podcast universe could fit in there
and happily live for the next 10 years cranking out great shit. Mind you it's in Midtown Manhattan
in a sexy location all the studios are all glass because the guy who designed this this Canadian
guy David Margolis had this vision and that's how he did it and back then in those days apparently
there was the resources to do it. Oh yeah that was dot com money to build that shit right and
I wasn't there I assumed so but you know in this in this day in age it would be you know
somewhere else and not a high rent district and it wouldn't be a sexy looking. Yeah
But all the toys and bells and whistles and tools and digital studios and work stations
and this people buzzing all over the place there's a positive
I emphasize that because in the entertainment business and a lot of not a lot of positive
there's a lot of positive young energy running around much probably like MTV was prior to Adam and I
you know art tour of duty through there but there's also a lot of old radio guys run I mean not old but you know
guys are doing radio shows who harking back and and are looking for the holy grail and want to be able
play things and talk about things and not be confined by because liner cuts that's right because it's
totally open format right or not or is it totally or did not totally open or does it depend on the channel
you know there there it is a commercial money making entity so there is that need the money making
part maybe not yet perhaps so you know there need to be successful in in that way and so
there is a desire need to find out what what response and feedback is the good part is there's no
parent company there's no you know big brother you know looking down upon you and say
via com on MTV you mean or any any big it's you know it's a publicly traded stock it's
yeah it's yeah it's you know you make your own bed you lay in it right so they're on their strategy
and they're moving it along so it was it was a moment where Scott had wanted to meet Adam and Adam came
up and I brought him into the office and the two of them started talking and you know Scott made
a podcasting overture that I guess Adam felt had some value to it and he and the gentleman you've
heard on on this show before or this podcast rather Ron struck a deal and I said well you know
I fucked up your life twice now yep so what are we going to do Steve on this show so there's
going to be a daily show on no what I fucked that what what that's the press release what are we going
to do what are we going to do what should we do I mean I I'm saying just sending your shit I'll put it on
well yeah I mean I think if anyone out there who's listening has something that is compelling
interesting left of center different unique tasty flavorful that's basically anything that is
an on regular radio they need to let Adam at the source code know about that and that's but there's
a special email drop where you could yeah well there's a couple and that that's for the daily
source code as well it's like that you know like the mashup today I got off with the so that's
mashup at podcast dot pod show dot com we have pod safe at pod show dot com and submit
so let's be a promo as your shows whatever you know like the newspaper USA today or some of you
might recall in school my weekly reader or even go back to readers digest not everybody has or
readers digest condensed books not everybody has the discretionary time to go to the source and
feel and and participate but they hear about it we want to be part of it and how do you do that
in this day of electronic choices where you're over mediated from all sides so there's this
going to be a daily for our program that satellite subscribers we have listened to where
Adam will act as the editor the filter of of turning you want to interesting things
that rather than you if you don't have the discretionary downtime which some people don't believe
or not of surfing and finding things out he'll be able to turn you on and be like the
canary in the coal mine the early adapter detector I like that I'll be the canary in the coal mine
because you know that when the carbon dioxide levels too high that's what the canaries for right
yes if he kills over so it would be great after that I guess it's time to say bye bye
hey you should have you should put us a bit of podcast for the show we'll see I need somebody
like you to help produce help no no not help produce but help me figure out the technical
way of putting it this 50 fucking studios there oh no no I would do this from from from from home
from the Chickaway studios in in suburban northern New Jersey you can you can sit on
John Elizabeth carries blanket there and talk about what other scum stains are like so with that
go into the museum with Monica Lewinsky's dress make it make a play stained records
all right Steve thank you very much man that was great let's do this again sure let's tell
it now but there's so many more stories three minutes on the train from Waterloo station
from the curry cottage an hour and 16 minutes on your MP3 player so we've overstayed our welcome
I'm sure sorry oops all right feedback Adam at curry dot com you can get the podcast feed
at daily source code dot com as we can find the latest episode of the archives remember this
weekend Patricia and I are hijacking the daily source code feed for a special Dutch addition from
the cottage and we'll be back Monday with more daily source code take care y'all bye bye