Dota Shara Charley 2-3-1
You're DJs!
Are you the next player?
Your DJ has only just begun
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
In the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into the future
You're fantastic
And it is the 30th of August 2005
Welcome to the daily source code
Another beautiful day in the UK
Here at Curry Cottage
We've got the Conveyor role in the high speed
The air cooled fan
Because of course air conditioners
It's not excessive
Homes built in the 1930s
In affluent residential areas of Surrey
It's quite unbelievable
It's unbelievable
Okay, okay
Well, they start off a little bit slower than normal
Right now it's 434pm
It's a little bit later than usual
Patricia definitely needed to go to the doctor this morning
Looks like
What I had in New York
The full on full blown bronchial infection
That she kind of skated through
Oh, she's got it
And so I had to go get some penicillin
Oh, you know, she's a danger to society
With all that cough medicine you can't drive
So I gladly took over the driving duties
Okay, so I'm a little confused by all the reports that have come in
About Hurricane Katrina
Some say, oh, wasn't all that bad
Some say it's horrible
I don't know, I'm hearing reports of 20 feet of water
That sounds pretty bad to me
And 50 people died
Man
Of course with such a huge evacuation
Something's always bound to happen
But that is extremely sad
So I guess we wait for some other water to drain
And the cleanup to begin is going to be quite
Quite a big job
And last night the MTV Video Music Awards
Rolled out here in the UK, of course
One day after the fact
But I'll have some comments on that
My favorite definitely from the entire show
Had to be Gwen Stefani just the way she looks
She acts the video
The whole Gwen vibe is fantastic
So how about this smash up just for her?
She's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's like she's
she's like we're all ready.
yeah
I love it pretty much, I love it
You and me, when they're open, they'll call them
I'm in the camera, but it's all
The lack of justice has less to pass, less to pass, less
I don't know if I pass, crack, ladies, don't use that track
It's my talker, little touch
It's the love, it's the name, it's the real beer
It's the name, it's the real beer, it's the real beer
Watch me as a grab, take a sip, hop, hop, hop, hop
We got a ghost town, there's no town, it's so sad
You win, bling, don't fight with us, stay fight with us
Which no sad, you kill ain't so don't stop
Lily, yeah, until it's mise this shit, Luna
Watch me react to every pass, less to Jahren
What the shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit
Don't you just… don't you just know what's the shit, shit, shit
Whatever they're on the internet,
Don't you just know what the shit, shit, shit, shit
I feel like I'm not in a hurry, man
What the shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit
Thank you, одну, Riversome and Beatmen
Man, hero, same as life and death
You know I'm no father, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother,
no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, no brother, he, no brother, oh brother,
So now they're already fuf gonna extravaganza, Gwen Stefani versus Gorilla's Hall of
Backgirls feel good on your daily source code for August 30th, 2005.
It's nice and hot today, it's great outside, it's really beautiful, so I feel kind of like
a schmuck for sitting inside you hear the con bear blowing away in the background.
So we've discussed this over the past three shows about mashups and hit test and backtrack
podcast, all driving sales of back catalog, and I think I just wanted to read a couple
more pieces of email that came in, it really seems to be working, this is just a fraction
to people who actually feel like sending off an email to send off their comment, and
we really are driving sales with all this stuff.
Patrick Seaman says I listen to daily source code on my commute, which means that even when
I like the music from mashups and hit test, I can't buy it right away, back at home,
I usually don't know the title artists anymore, don't have time to listen to daily
source code either.
Would it be possible to list the songs used in mashups and hit test directly in the
show notes?
Well, you know, I've been investigating that, and I've signed up to become an affiliate
of the iTunes Music Store, and also talked to Jan Polet about it.
Jan said that he'd actually been doing that for a little while on JanPolet.com, and
he says it's such a hassle because you have to find the right versions, and he says,
you know, it would take him about 45 minutes to an hour every time he had to go into the
iTunes Music Store to actually, you know, get the links, and he said, all of that for
60 cents, didn't feel those words that I, that was his commission, I guess.
And also, that seems to be some problem with the Windows version, if you use an iTunes
link, but I'm not quite sure what the deal is on that.
Jason Hallowd says he actually, when he heard, was it, the data source code 230, so I
have the Windwood album back in the Highlight from iTunes already, it was inspired to listen
to it again after nearly a year away from me, still amazed how incredible Steve Windwood's
voice sounds.
I just want to thank for the podcast, blah, blah, oh man, I got to look at so many different
podcasts, people are sending all these links.
Okay, in Australia, it's not working too well as Craig Russell says, we're pissed off about
it.
There's no iTunes down under, next time you're talking to jobs, tell them to put a rocket
under the record company, because until then it's limewire for Aussies where no one makes
a penny.
Okay, good point.
John Knell, just bought fantasy off of iTunes that I remember how cool it's Groove and
Boogie Wonderland.
Whereas I got them as well, that's after hearing the hit test, I think number 51.
In Neri or Relaana, Adam can begin to tell you how many tunes I've bought after hearing
mashups and hit test, I think I've spent in total to date since iTunes launched in
Canada, just over $3,000 on albums and audio books, oh man, of course that's Canadian,
so it's not all that much, right?
Here's a familiar name, Doug K, from IT conversations, Adam I should be embarrassed to tell
you this.
Wait, I am embarrassed to tell you, but after listening to the toxic shack mashup on
the daily source code last week, I went to iTunes and bought Britney Spears toxic, just
wanted to hear the bass line and it's original context, really trust me, it was just
the bass line.
I'll probably never buy another Britney Spears song again, but it's more evidence
that mashups do sell music, yes, how about John who says, I've bought at least 10 CDs
as a result of the daily source code, podcasts and also be great marketing tools if you're
on a Friday to put in the effort, if anyone needs an example, look at Rob Costlow, I gave
him his first Amazon.com review after hearing him on the show and his Amazon sales have surely
gone up.
Yeah, he's doing great.
I think Rob is hooked up with a movie company now, and then this is all in the show notes
by the way, Craig Myers sent in this huge idea of a mashup generator and regenerator
with the idea, I think we've come up with something similar to this, but he really went
into a spec and he has an XML spec that he put in this email, you got to take a look at it.
The idea is basically, you have the tracks already, so you buy the tracks, but then you
have this piece of software that can regenerate the actual mix, the actual mashup.
I don't know, well, I mean, it would have to be a pretty sophisticated piece of software,
but definitely an interesting idea and something to think about for the developers out
there.
And here's one that I, you know, I've looked up licensing, I think I thought I'd looked
it up, licensing of MP3 because it's not free, it turns out.
Now they don't really have a podcast license, but if you want to use the MP3 standard,
I guess it's just a standard, not even the code or the codec or anything, it's just using
MP3 itself.
For instance, if you're making players, then you definitely have to pay a royalty, you have
to pay a license.
And from what I've been able to read and all the links to MP3 licensing.com and everything
is on the show notes, if you make over $100,000, then the licensing kicks in.
I think it's, I think it's 2% of all applicable revenue.
Now it also states that you have to pay this if you make money streaming using MP3.
And even though it doesn't say it explicitly, I'm pretty sure, and any lawyers out there,
I'm sure we'll be happy to check it out.
We'll note that there is enough description there to cover podcasting.
So the question is, how does this work?
Is that ad revenue, does it include barter?
I mean, is this just like a music license?
I think that there's something we have to look into there because there will be money made
with podcasting.
In fact, I wonder how Disney and ABC, radio.com and those guys do it, who are all getting
the big push through iTunes.
I wonder if they're paying their license.
So it might be time to bring them into the conversation because we want to make sure
that we're doing at least that part legally.
I mean, the music stuff is hard enough to figure it out.
And by the way, the new show notes, yeah, they suck so bad, they swallow.
Thank you.
Everyone was very, very clear about that.
So I won't be using the eye frame today.
I do like the dynamic nodes of the outline.
So I'll make sure there's a link to that.
And we'll just put top line nodes straight into the show notes, into the actual post because
of course, what everybody got was basically an eye frame with a URL, nothing else instead
of showing notes.
So apologies there.
And now, back to your regularly scheduled promos.
All right, well, John, we got to do a promo.
You know, we've been doing this show for three months and we've got to do a promo.
So can you think you could spare a minute of your time to join with me?
I'm hungry.
Oh, come on, man.
We just got to do this.
Adam Curry.
I listened to his show.
I was in Austin all last week.
He did a show a night day.
Yeah.
And he was begging for promos every day.
He did one every day last week.
We only do one a week.
Well, he's committed.
He is.
Every day.
I guess if we do a promo, we got to tell people what we do, right?
So let's get the list together.
We're Mac Geeks.
And we share our gap.
We give.
So that's why we call it the Mac Geeks.
We share our knowledge with them, right?
And they share their knowledge with us in the form of usually audio feedback.
And Chris, we send that right up to the show because it makes the show easier to do when
we don't have to talk the whole way through, right?
Yeah.
And then when you get talking and you confuse the heck out of them, I'm there to help
kind of translate, right?
For everybody.
I agree with you, the only part of that.
We've got to refine it.
It is that sometimes you really get, I mean, I don't know what language you're speaking.
And I really got to help people out.
They write me a thank me, but I know share those with you because you'll get all
great.
You don't want to like to hear that.
So anyway, we are from the Mac Geeks, yes, come visit us at macabserver.com slash podcast
where you can search for Mac Geek Gab in iTunes and come join us because every week
we have a lot of fun sharing information and good geeking.
Thanks.
Hot Joe, content that will make you walk the dog and kiss your mother.
You're listening to KZFO.
Do you ever get the feeling that you're not in charge of your government anymore?
This or a dictatorship, it'd be a heck a lot easier, just so long as I'm the dictator.
Do you ever sit back and think, hmm, I could do better job.
It's hard work.
Well, now's your chance to find out.
Join us at KZFO as we explore the micro-national world, discussing the day's news and
you can interview the top news and it goes to the day.
You've done nothing, you have no idea, because that's too busy to defend myself.
What you've got is plenty of the option, and your goal now is to get bored about it.
Yes!
And the point is, you're not losing nearly enough, you're not doing that.
You're not losing nearly enough, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not
doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not
doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're
not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that,
you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not
doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're
not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're
not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing that, you're not doing this,
you're not doing that, you're not doing this, you are not doing that, you're not doing
that, you're not, we're not doing that, we're not doing that, you're not in that, you
know the way I do anything about what I, and you, you, you know the way that I
was doing that, I even went up there, really.
Because I honestly don't know what I'm doing, so they're exactly how you do that.
I'm feeling it, you know, you know, they're being pretty funny.
You factor in the energy input into the entire production process, it takes considerably
more fossil fuel energy to produce the fuels than you get out of them.
And that, as a according to a Cornell University and a University Berkeley study, 29% more
fossil energy to turn corn into ethanol, ethanol, but I don't think that's the same as
biodiesel.
I think that's just like, it's an ethanol, a step before ethanol, something like that.
I don't know, I really don't know, but I guess if, you know, why would you have to use
fossil fuel if you can make the ethanol fuel?
I don't know, maybe I thought there was some kind of perpetual motion you could get in there.
James Berghoud says,
make magazine did a 30 minute interview about biodiesel, then of course, forgot to put a link to it.
According to the make magazine podcast, the diesel burning vehicles made today are better
suited for biodiesel than those made back in the 80s, and apparently biodiesel smells like
french fries.
Eric says, I want to come time to rebuild or replace the engine in that 182 RG.
That's my plane.
You might want to consider a Delta Hawk diesel engine, which may affect you as a diesel
motor for the aircraft industry.
Awesome, awesome.
It's just such a weird idea to have a diesel engine in the air.
Oh, and he says, by the way, you need something cooler than the SESNO 182 RG, like a
CRS SR22, where a land care column be a 400.
Yeah, I don't know about the CRS SR22s.
You know, I don't know if you've seen them, you might may have heard that there are these airplanes
now, private planes that have a parachute, you should go to the website, it's fantastic.
You actually see that, you know, someone's pulled the shoot in this plane, it's just kind of
drifting down.
By the way, the plane is pretty much destroyed on impact, because you still come that, you know,
it's like basically landing a space capsule, only you're not landing in water, probably.
I don't like the the the CRS planes, and yeah, it does, I don't know, something,
something about them that just doesn't sit nice with me, but they look nice though, that's
sure, that's for sure. Andy White says, since you're interested in biodiesel,
I might find this link of interest shows how to make biodiesel use from cooking oil.
Now, that's when I'm looking for, so that's a freedom for freedomfuelusa.com, of course,
all of those links are in the show notes, and finally, Steph and C graves goes into great detail about
the thing we talked about this peak oil, that basically the oil reserves are gone, but now they're
different ways to get oil from from coal, for instance, so there's a lot going on with this
biodiesel, and I definitely want to keep my eye on it. Talked about teenagers as well, as well,
about them listening to the source code and responding, and about the relationship between
teenagers and parents, and Cabrin writes in Adam, heard the source code today, and heard the
feedback from an actual teenager, I'm a teenager, actually turning 16 soon, so around the same age group,
as with a lot of parents, I'm an only child, as is Christina, by the way, and my parents have never
experienced a child grow up, let alone a teenager growing up. Well, hold on a second, we actually
all were teenagers once, believe it or not. My parents seem to have a hard time letting go, at least
my mom, I guess it's different since this is feedback from a male teenager, but being a teenager is
hard enough with high school and friends, especially being the big geek I am, we don't need any
more trouble from parents, hope this will add to your experience with a teenager. All right, Cabrin,
a cabrin, I'm sorry, I'm mispronounced at Cabrin, thank you very much. So it sounds like there's
no discrimination there between guys and girls, you get the same treatment as the teenage girls who
are written in, and fra from Belfast, Francis actually, 15 years old from Belfast,
heard you talk about Mark the Surgeon. Last September, I was diagnosed with
hypertrophic cardiomyopathy, I think that's it, HCM, currently to keep my heart under control,
I take 15 milligrams of the beta blocker pill a day, and I've done the 24 heart monitor thing,
since I always keep on forgetting to ask my doctor, are there any side effects I should expect
sometime or in the future from the beta blockers? That is a good question for the heart surgeon Mark,
let's see if he, if he replies, it's a good information to have in our household as well, since
Patricia also takes beta blockers every day for her heart condition. I'm not sure, I don't think it's
15 milligrams, I think she takes much less than that, I thought it was only five. Jeffrey
Snedden says I'm a 13 year old boy, my relationship with my dad is minimal, mainly because he's
either dealing with work stuff or with political stuff. He used to be head of the north east
five district council for which he received an OBE, that's an award here in the UK, this means
he's rarely in the house and not busy. When he is in the house, he's often dealing with his
2500 plus video collection. All right, we're kind of videos with, he should be podcasting.
All right Jeffrey, yeah, that does kind of suck. But at least you got a dad, I mean,
there's something to be said for that. I'm sure that if you really analyze it, it probably looks
well, and he probably is it, he's probably a good guy. And he should maybe figure out what he's
gotten that video collection, send something over. Ben Collins says last week and introduced
my son, Nick, who's 13 to the concept of a podcast. We listen to a few that I subscribe to,
spend some time talking about what he could do on one. He's pretty typical into what most
13 year old boys are into, but he worked on for four hours straight and he came up with his
own podcast, the game's snafu. I can't wait to hear a promo for that. He says as every teenager
will tell you, they're smart and insightful. We just heard that. And as any parent will tell you,
they need focus guidance and the creative outlet, podcasting fits the bill brilliantly.
It can't be simple or technically sophisticated, meaningful or silly. Whatever they want,
and it gives them something to do. It is active, not passive at a time in life when that's
really important. I agree, Ben. And that reminds me, the minute I'm done with today's source
code, I'm marching downstairs, and I'm going to get Christina to do her podcast, damn it.
All right, check this one out. This is kind of a match.
And in this album, I'm saying, I remember what it's all about now, you fuckers,
fuck you all. Thank you, John. So I'm saying, fuck you all. Imagine this.
Thank you all very much. Thanks for the warm welcome man. Let's roll one, two, three,
four, imagine. There's no heaven heaven. It's easy. If you try, try, try, try.
No hell, below us, us, us, us, us. And above us, only sky, sky, sky, sky,
sky, sky, earth, imagine. All the people, all the people living, living, for today.
Imagine, there's no country, it's country, it's, it's not hard to do, hard to do,
nothing to kill or die for. And no religion, too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too,
so good I need to imagine all the people, all the people living side by side,
peace, peace, peace. You could say, I'm a dreamer, but I'm not the only one, and I hope someday,
you'll join me in the world. We'll live as one, two, three, four, imagine, no possessions.
I wonder, wonder, if you can't, nobody's afraid, we're hungry, we're hungry, we're
under the man, imagine, all the people, ensuring all the world, imagine, thank you very much, peace.
We strive for peace, let's come together, on to a deep home, imagine.
All I'm saying is good peace, a chance, let's come together, let's come together,
all I'm saying is good peace, a chance, let's get these a chance, imagine,
We see this.
Unless there's no place to rush, unless there's no end.
Yeah, they will be full of water, and water will be full of water.
And now it's killed.
All of us want peace.
Wax audio does it again.
Imagine this.
Wax audio dots.
It was an AU.
I linked to that in the show notes.
That is your present.
And so just what?
Once you stand over there, huh?
I have a microphone set up for you.
I love it.
And I heard you.
Here's stand over there.
I have a...
No.
This big thing?
Oh!
It looks like a microphone.
Yeah.
I'm talking to that.
I see it.
Can I hear you?
I said I loved it.
You sound like shit there.
Hold on a second.
Why is that?
That's not good.
Hold on.
Say something.
Talk to you too.
Yeah.
I give you a little bit of low end.
Hold on a second.
Say something else.
Go ahead.
You got a talk.
Well, you were talking about the beta blockers.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
It sounds like shit.
Let me turn this on.
You've gone.
Shall I just go on that?
Yeah.
You've gone.
Yes, they told me that they're going to stop people in traffic.
Not only to check their alcohol level.
And also a medicine.
And a bit of beta blockers.
Because they find out that people on beta blockers are really stone.
No.
Actually, the reaction is too slow.
Really?
Yeah.
And if people take a high dose of beta blockers, then they shouldn't drive.
Isn't it ridiculous?
Well, do you feel different when you use the beta blockers?
A little bit.
But that's good because I'm a little bit hyper.
No.
You don't say.
I'm a bit hyper.
So that's why probably people are hyper.
Get hard problems.
I think.
Right.
So this is running to fast.
So this.
The boy that sent in the email says he takes 15 milligrams of beta blocker a day.
How much is he taking?
15.
Oh, that's not much.
Well, he's 13 years old.
Oh, that's sad.
Yeah.
He needs to take that already.
Oh.
Yeah.
He has.
You know, what is it?
Uh.
Let's see if I can find it.
Oh, here it is.
Yes, it's started.
He has.
I just started.
He's so novice.
That hyper traffic cardiomyopathy.
Oh.
What is the HCM?
You ever heard of him?
I think it's seen.
Yeah.
That's what I think it is, too.
That's like what Bob has.
I think.
Are you a regular?
You think?
I don't know.
Probably.
So besides the beta blocker, what else do you take?
By the way.
So we took Patricia to the doctor this morning because she has bronchitis.
So I'm myself.
You are not yourself.
But you look beautiful.
You look gorgeous.
I don't feel anything.
And I don't like to be sick.
No.
You don't get me in bed.
I don't like it.
Excuse me?
I don't get you.
You know, like laying down and.
And.
Oh.
Okay.
Because if you will feel better after a couple of days, I'm going to do that.
No.
You're not a take.
I can't stand on my feet anymore.
Yeah.
But you have to be careful of your lungs because you've had two cases of pneumonia.
Okay.
No.
Yeah.
I'm just sensitive.
You know, when I was a little girl, you have those kids that always cough.
Yeah.
And that was you.
It was me.
Oh.
Is that the fun?
And I think later in my.
You get these sort of things that if you get it cold.
It's just lingers on a little bit longer than yeah.
You got to be careful, man.
I know.
Okay.
So we had a.
A moxacillin.
I was that what you have a moxacillin.
That's my favorite.
Yeah.
What flavor?
So that's good.
No.
No flavor.
I see crap flavor.
I've seen every member and she was little.
Yeah.
She had that pinky milky stuff.
That looks like a milkshake.
Kids love that.
You have to really hide it from them.
Which happens.
Some kids.
Lay off the tennis ceiling kid.
All right.
So yeah.
Isn't it something get people stopped because.
Because they might be on beta blockers.
Yeah.
And then what?
And drive in.
I don't know.
You know, they're going to outlaw pornography on the internet in the UK.
Yeah.
Violent pornography.
Violent.
But okay.
So, but how about violent war pictures?
Is that okay?
I mean, where do we draw the line with that shit?
Yeah.
So, well, I must say in the UK that they definitely don't.
They don't.
They, you know, it's about the sexual thing.
I just.
I'm just.
I'm fine.
I'm fine with that because I don't.
I don't want, you know.
I'm fine with them trying to to make up that law.
But I'd like.
I'd like to know the definition.
When is it violently sexual?
And when isn't it?
What's the line?
First and probably.
Yeah.
So what's the line?
That's just I'm wondering how they're.
Forget about how they're going to enforce it.
Just something that's very sexy.
Right.
If I, if I, if I have a picture of.
Not that I have one.
But if I have a picture of someone in a leather outfit and.
And someone whipping them with a writing crop is that.
That's pretty sexual.
But it's that violently sexual.
Do you like it?
Maybe.
Let's get arrested.
All right.
Get out of my studio.
I got to play some magic.
Okay.
Yeah.
Stay as long as you want.
Bye.
Hi.
This is PW Phantom.
Create a radio for your radio's digital flotsom.
And I'm here to tell you.
I am a big fan of Mad Weinstein's yeast radio.
I am also here to make a confession.
Anyone who is listened to digital flotsom knows that I often tell personal stories from my life.
But I think that you should know that there are still some things I haven't talked about.
One of those things is that for my whole adult life.
I have secretly felt that I was a lesbian trapped in a man's body.
I just can't help it.
Ever since puberty, I've just been attracted to women.
Oh, I'm so glad I got that off my chest.
You rock my world.
And I'm not ashamed to say it.
Hi Adam.
Just a quick audio comment from myself.
Mark Hunter, a host and producer of the Titan podcast.
One of the seven music podcasts.
Over at the Podsafe music network as I'm sure you know.
And it's just that a little mention about the podcast called UK.
I've sent you a link to where you can download a promo that I've made.
The organizers of Podcast called PodcastCon UK are hopeful that you'd be able to play in the daily source code.
Just to increase the exposure for the event.
There's been a lot of hard work put into it.
And as it's Europe's first podcast convention.
It's certainly as a milestone and it's a landmark in the history of Podcaston.
I believe there's this well over 100 attendees in place already.
The BBC are sending representatives as are the times of London.
The garden, times magazine, virgin radio and several media and advertising companies are sending representatives along.
I've been asked to do a speech about music podcasting.
And obviously I'll be heavily featuring the Podsafe music network.
And how that is the number one resource for music podcasters.
Or for anyone that wants to have a music in their podcast.
But it's hopeful.
Or it's hoped that perhaps you can play the promo on the daily source code or make some mention of PodcastCon UK on the daily source code.
Just to keep everyone in the United Kingdom that's involved with this event.
Feeling good about it.
And I think they just would really appreciate.
And just a little saying of support from the podfather himself Adam Curry.
Thanks for listening to this Adam.
And I look forward to meeting up with you at the Podcast Expo in November over in California.
I'll be there. Cheers.
Yeah, I was there.
And of course I want to go as well to podcastCon UK September 17th.
The problem is, and I just can't commit to anything these days.
Because, you know, there's just so much going on.
In fact, Monday I'm flying to New York for two days.
Then I'll come back on Thursday Friday Patricia and Christina.
They going off in the trip for the weekend.
They'll be back on Monday I believe.
And then either Monday or Tuesday or sometime in that week.
I'm scheduled to go either back to New York or the San Francisco, probably San Francisco.
I just don't know yet.
So I really hope I can make it.
And I'm of course very supportive of this.
And it sounds like this is going to be a lot of great press covered.
It sounds like all the right people are going to be there.
And a hundred plus podcasts.
So definitely be on the lookout for more information about that.
And I have the promo as well.
So I'll be sure to roll that out either either in tomorrow or the day after source code.
And now.
The Pod Save Music portion of the show.
I was listening to other promo and I heard cruise bucks come by again.
Like, man, I haven't played that in a couple of days.
I heard it on a podcast.
Tell the FCC to stick and kick in its cruise box on your dead source code.
Do you remember?
We back last summer.
When me, she made you a such a fucking mama.
No ending music.
Nothing to funny.
Cleared channel motherfuckers.
He had a problem on it.
But somebody heard it wrong.
Now you can't have it all.
I heard it on a podcast.
Rockin' fucking radio you wanted.
Got it?
Just downloaded a part it on a podcast.
No one's gonna stop you telling FCC to stick and kick in the revisions.
Do you remember?
Your first computer.
That piece of shit was like a freaking router.
Now we've got Wi-Fi.
Downloading files fast.
Listenin' to everyone.
Save a dumb podcast.
It's his duty.
Now you see each and every nation.
Radio is gouged into its armmancipation.
Me that song sing a loud mash it up.
Mix it.
Real fucking logic.
I'm girl mixed in.
You're somebody heard of it all.
Now you can't have it all.
I heard it on a podcast.
Rockin' fucking radio you wanted.
Got it?
Just downloaded a part it on a podcast.
No one's gonna stop you telling FCC to stick and kick in the revisions.
On a podcast.
Rockin' fucking radio you wanted.
Got it?
Just downloaded a part it on a podcast.
No one's gonna stop you telling FCC to stick and kick in the revisions.
I from junior attention to more.
Don't ever shine.
It's always nice to drive you on a dac.
No matter what you say.
Crews box the revolutions on heard it on podcast. Tell the FCC to stick it kick it and tell
Yon Polette to come on in with the hit-tales
Oh, yes, I do
Hey Adam this is hit-tales number 53 not recorded on a train this time but in my room in
Apple Dore and just finishing the last two weeks here on my rehabilitation program so
the hit-tales again three intros and three answers and this is intro number one
She's always a woman to me
I don't know I think this is number two
ABC the look of love
Think it's the look of love if it is then it's ABC and the final one is always is number three
No, yeah, okay
That was the golden hearing twilight zone our Dutch buddies come on and time's up. It's time for the answer
Hit me this is a song from 1978. Let's begin slow. This is Billy Joel. She's always a woman.
Yeah, you go she can kill with a smile she can run with a ride. I get a reward
Faith with her casual life and she only reveals what she wants you to see
She hides like a child but she's always a woman to me
Just don't take the wheel, Billy
That is a great song yeah good choice
Okay, it's low start of this hit-tales and now let's pick up the tempo bits with a song from what is it 19 82
And it's also answer number two in today's hit-tales. It's ABC this is poison arrow
We were the right combination. Who wrote my heart? You
And I'll sound the same
Always narrow look of love
See
Number two poison arrow ABC and this is answer number three
The golden hearing from 83 to twilight zone
Oh, yeah
Okay, all together now. We're the bloodiest of all. Hey y'all for a great quartet. We're the bullet hits at a ball
Also a really great song to finish up this hit-test a Dutch band by the name of the golden earring and the song is titled the twilight zone
Okay, well Adam this
Concludes the hit-test port today. Oh, by the way, this is a different fill-on using just just plugging something
It has a fixed end, so it's not faded out at the end, so don't start talking until it's finished the game
Well, I don't know as always, there are two at least hit-test and Gmail that's come for feedback and
Y'all put that scumb Jay and PLLAT.com for info about the hit-test and the hit-test box kept
See you for number 54. So until then bye-bye
The Veronica radio school. I told you y'all was up to no good with those guys fantastic y'all and I think I'm gonna run over to my iTunes right now
and pick up a couple of tracks of some great stuff that I want to get. I got to listen to some earring, man
Last two shows have been a little long, but there's been so much feedback that I just want to be able to get to all of it
So what are we at now?
Shoot 46 minutes. This is definitely over my past my time and longer than your commute time probably. So I'll try and bring it back to 30-40 minutes by tomorrow
for the hump day edition of the source code
Power
As always, your feedback is welcome. Adam at curie.com please stick it up on a server somewhere
Make sure you got your ID three tags. So I know what it is. Don't call it promo.mp3
And email me the link, you know mine still skirt around 98% on the GPU
If you have a promo that you'd like to send to the entire middle here
Then you can send that to submit at podshow.com
So we can put it on the pod show on serious satellite the pod find our nine tunes and of course here on the daily source code five days a week
Sometimes
Excuse me daily source code.com is where you can find the podcast feed for the show
If you don't know what that is look for little orange on white XML icon
Do you want to copy that address and that's what you're going to put into your pod catcher if you want to work
That's all about headed over to podcastallie.com or indie potter.org or
Apple.com download iTunes and just search for daily source code rather I'm curious to find it one way the other and just click the subscribe button
It couldn't be any easier. There's almost no step three in the process. You got to love it
And of course comments at www.curie.com
I'll make sure the show notes work out a little better today. Thanks for listening. Stay subscribed. I'll talk to you tomorrow on the source code. Bye bye
Another podshow podcast stick it in your ear