Delta Shira Charley, 2-7-0.
Potcho has been shown to be an effective decay-preventing
unit.
When used as part of a regularly applied program of oral hygiene and regular provisional care,
you don't yet have.
Delta Shira Charley, 2-7-0.
Delta Shira Charley, 2-7.
Perhaps someone like a globe-trotting podcasting entrepreneur, but for the locals of Sydney,
if you want to know what's really going on in your real estate market, subscribe to Real
Sydney via iTunes or directly from realsidney.lipsim.com.
Secure a day, secure a day, attention to cast messages, and be three divers, media
downloads.
On Jokecoza, Pod Diberatium, the skin cast, and your data deeper into podcasts, and
carry out the podcast on Delta Shira Charley.
This week, the travel commons podcast turns number 20, and that's right.
The 20th travel commons podcast talks this week about the airline experience.
Travel.
It's a people business.
Though there have been many advances in technology.
I'll tell you, I'd be at to receive a heartfelt apology from a website.
The rise of the virtual airline, outsourcing flight attendants, and what's next?
Then the pilots?
I mean, these are the people who deliver the service on buying.
Well, after you do that, what's left?
You know, a logo, some gates, a frequent flyer program, and the boundaries and the rules
of personal space at 35,000 feet.
The seat that I'm in is mine.
The back of my seat, to the back of the seat in front of me, from the floor, up to
the ceiling in the outer armrest.
Oh, my, all this and listen your feedback at the travel commons podcast, www.travelcomons.com,
our Mark Peacock, and I hope to see you there.
Take care.
Oh, Mark, thank you very much.
That marks the guy who poops in toilets around the world and tells you about it.
Closely, closely related, yet not affiliated with Chris Rockwell's Daily Download.
It's an interesting thought there about airlines, basically outsourcing everything.
I, of course, I took Virgin back from San Francisco to London on the upper class flight
of course.
And they've now, I knew that this was happening.
They've changed the ground crew.
They outsource that now.
They were there before that they had full-time employees who were working for Virgin.
And I must say that, you know, I could tell the difference that they had outsource that,
because, well, I don't know, you could just, I mean, first of all, there were different
faces.
That was kind of a tip off.
I actually had a brief conversation with the flight attend to the ground stewardess who
checked me and she said, yeah, you know, we're, we're from the outsource.
We're from a different company.
But this is my only account.
So, I, that works too, I guess.
That makes sense.
It's a, from a business perspective, but you got to be careful with this stuff.
Because, yeah, you know, when you say outsourcing pilots, it's kind of freaky, but it
does already happen.
Many, certainly, I think holiday airlines.
I don't know what the regulations are about that either.
That's kind of interesting.
But there's, sure, are a lot of pilots out there who feel very much members of their
family.
Goldis and the Joe D on fly with me podcast.
He really feels that he's a member of his airline, a member of the airline family.
And he's interviewed flight attendants about, you hear that?
That's the crackberry, not dim it.
Unbelievable.
The technology is kind of failing me today, although it was, I snapped the mixer right
back in.
Everything worked again.
Perfectly the way I wanted it.
So, you know, Windows is being very rude wanting to continuously reboot on me, don't
you can't do that, not during the Delta share at Charlie.
And before that, real Australia, that sounds like a very interesting podcast.
You know, it's not, first of all, I told you, I'd love to live in Australia.
It's just too damn far from, from family, I guess, that's, that's the biggest problem.
If, if Patricia didn't have any family, yeah, we would have been gone by now without
a doubt.
Probably the might have happened, it definitely could have happened.
You can't just move to Australia, you know, you've got to have something unique.
You know, it doesn't matter how much money you have either.
There's really all kinds of rules and regulations when it comes to immigrating into Australia.
You can't just show up and say, all right, here I am.
Oh, I've got plenty of money.
Yep, they're not interested in that.
It really does take more.
You got to have some, you got to be like a rocket scientist or something.
Now, the makes sense, I think that's pretty good, actually.
I got to, I should see if I can drag Patricia in, have her on the show, talk.
Huh?
See if she's around.
No.
Okay.
Uh, let's see what's going to say, yes, man, I've so many other things to talk about.
It's just, it's, I've got to say, it's just so good to be back.
It's good to be ahead of the times because I know that by the time you're listening to
this, it, actually, you're going to get up in the morning, hopefully, and this will
be the first thing you download.
Um, it's so nice to be ahead of the United States, you know, time-wise, it just makes
all the difference in the world.
Of course, it does bring me back to my 16 hour days because around 4 p.m. is when we kick
off the West Coast day, and that's always interesting, but, yeah, whatever.
Speaking of my, my blackberry, this is pretty interesting that came in, you know, this
thing has got me completely hooked.
I, by the way, I didn't take it to bed with me, so I didn't read any emails this morning
when I, when I woke up, I thought that would be rather rude to my bed partner.
But I had it in my pocket, and I'd drop Christine off at school on the way back, and
there was always a shitload of traffic, I was, of course, scams, skimming through all
the emails.
It's still a beautiful device.
I am totally hooked, and I am not alone in that.
Do you do it every day?
Yes, all day?
Yes, all night.
Yes.
Weekends.
In the shower.
At work.
At birthday parties.
Weddings.
Our Memphis.
Work your dog.
Yes, they got the garbage.
Yes, paint the house.
Yes.
Then you're one of the millions who suffer from blackberry titus.
Huh?
The people at BBA, blackberry anonymous, can help.
Here's founder Bob Sharfleys.
I, I was at a control, and I knew others were as well.
Colt turkey was hard, but I had to do it.
I went back to my black rotary phone.
After the night sweats and diarrhea stopped, the flashback started, but I made it through.
This is one of our clients.
The Beast.
Him.
I knew I hit rock bottom during the birth of my first son, Charlie.
While she was pushing, I was hitting send.
For some reason, she was really, really upset that during the miracle of childbirth,
I was there on my blackberry.
Click, click, click in a way.
Treatment begins with counseling and medication.
Then we remove both thumbs and replace them with tiny drink umbrellas.
At first, it was very difficult getting used to having drink umbrellas.
But, eventually, I got used to it.
And now, when it rains, I just hold up my two former thumbs up in the air, and they're
drinking umbrellas, so they kinda keep me dry.
All those severe.
The people at BBA, blackberry anonymous, believe they can help.
You may experience withdrawal like symptoms, dry mouth, tightness of the chest, nosebleeds,
uncontrollable crying, and of course prolonged bleeding from the thumb holes, where there
are now two drink umbrellas.
My thumb holes have been bleeding for about a year and a half.
Not after some gauze and some scotch tape, and eventually stops, but very anonymous,
because who needs thumbs up?
American, that's a good stuff.
I was working in the West Wing late one night when I heard the gurgle of a water pack,
so I turned it to cheating in the counter-smoking, we said, we stuffed the chronic here.
Have a talk.
We smoked some monster hash.
He was his personal stance.
We got completely trashed.
We smoked some monster hash, recording in the White House, living dead, mouse red,
and house red, young Republicans, strict and screened.
Want somebody please, pass the vasine, they smoked some monster hash, who changed
his personal stance, they were all smashed, they smoked some monster hash, the conduits
choking on a bamboo fall, as Kroth said, don't over there, pass the lawn, roughing
with his belly, shaking too fast, it would have a hoppin to the block that I twisted.
The scene was rocking as chicken hogs moved, the undead marching bands, dancing all
grooves, backing the kitchen, muck a brown baked, some heck of a job rannys, cookies and
cakes, we ate some monster hash, we had the White House smash, we had the White House
we all got trashed, we ate some monster hash, party with a gun on to we all passed down,
just then we heard a blood curdling shout, watch out, beware, cover your knees, roasts
got the munchies and he's totally red, he smoked some monster hash, he was completely
trashed, that's been Dr. Smash, he smoked some monster hash, now every net the Democrats
rushed from the grave, to our taking our happening, T.H.C.R.A. for you, the Liberals, this
hash was meant to, when you get to my door, tell him, but it's too sexy, we'll smoke some
monster hash, we'll all get trashed, from my personal stance, we'll smoke some monster
hash, this is a good step, it's just how I can't crowded, we'll sum up in Bobby, now my
joint, how to divide it, give me a cup, I can barely give my legs, it's just a set of
that way, let me know, we had worse America, the lands, monster hash, if only that smoke
some monster hash there, maybe we have some, oh my goodness, scared in the Gmail as the
crap will keep wanting to reboot here, Lorna Dune, hey Adam, so I'm walking around China,
Chinatown in downtown LA on the Saturday morning, catching up on my podcast, listening
to DSC 267 on my iPod, see what I'm standing next to me, but there's a girl talking
furtively, furtively into an eye river doing a sound seeing tour of Chinatown, too
cool, I think this podcast thing is catching on, best regards from LA, I'm Lorna Dune,
cool Lorna, send wirelessly by a blackberry from T mobile, another, this is a cool email
that I got, hey Adam, as you've been talking much about all the all things porn on the
DSC, what does that mean, I thought you might find this video cast I found by accident,
no really, so basically it's this lovely chick called Miss Kitka, she goes running to
be doing people and talking about porn, they also talk about what I think you've been calling
personal porn, as always you're right on the money, really well cut together, very funny
and sexy at the same time, yeah, I'd actually check that out and I subscribe to it,
at least I'm subscribed in the condo, my private porn palace, misskitka.com, Mike
Sierra, Kilo, India, Tango, Kilo, Alpha.com, it is, you know, I really still don't know
where this is all kind of fitting all these video cast other than some of them, I really, really
enjoy, but you definitely have to take time for it, hey I got in touch with the Tiki Bar crew too,
I love what they're doing, that's just the more great ways to communicate your message, whatever it is,
let me see how to sense sale message here, I've been receiving a lot of feedback on that, let's see,
this is about that free sense sale offer, you mentioned the free sense sale offer,
I looked it up and sent them a picture of my trash coffee pot to get a free sense sale, plus shipping
and on the form they say, how did you find out about sense sale, and this is from Chris,
and you said, from Adam Curry's podcast, that's sourcecode.com,
I must say, I really should get a sense sale at the condo because I do miss it,
particularly now that this morning, our cattle went on the Fritz, our hot water boiler,
because we drink a lot of tea around, around the cottage, so I resorted back to the sense sale,
it was really nice, oh man, as much as I wish they would advertise, and then I got the message
by the way, because I think my disappointment got through to the agency and turns out that
they're definitely not going to be doing anything in podcast, we just kind of weird, you know,
what an obvious place to start, you know, and they're going to be doing some more mainstream advertising.
Geez, geez, I mean, listen to this, listen what you could be a part of.
Adam, my name's Graham, I just thought I sent a sale, so I thought I'd send you a bit of audio feedback,
I didn't want to send a sale, I don't need one, but suddenly, you know, with all your
in-sacent marketing, I found myself drawn to them in supermarkets and constantly looking
up on the internet, trying to do some price, so I bought one, it's arrived today, so I'm going to
have a crack with it now, and let you know what I think, and it better be good for you also.
Okay, so I've unpacked it and flushed it, and it's heating up at the moment, I think I'm going to
be talking about some new cups, and I think it's a big of a moment, because I'm really fit under
there a lot while. Smells pretty good, I've got the medium roast pops, so so far, I don't know,
you know, things are looking pretty good, we didn't go off in a very good start as a delivery guy
delivered it while I was in the shower, it's always the way, isn't it? But I think our future together
could be pretty good, I mean, it's unsafe. Okay, I'm just trying to calculate whether
the dam pot goes in, pots, pot is in position, lid is on, press in the button,
yeah, I have a half cup of it, I've been seeing a nice creme of air thawing, this is
you know, so far, I'm fairly impressed. Okay, I think he's done.
Sensei, yeah, it tastes pretty good out of, I think I say it from this one, so thanks very much for
the recommendation. Hey, now, I was listening to that, Graham's Graham Sensei machine has like a
second gear, maybe I have an old model, mine does not, and he, his went like,
three gears actually, shoot man, let me get that back for a second, hold on, let me see if I can
say what I do that, yeah, hold on, let me just, my name's Graham, I'm hot guy. Hey, listen to it,
I'm okay. Hey, listen to that second gear, it is on, he hits the first gear, right, that's what
mine sounds like, and then it goes a little softer, right, exactly the way mine sounds. Now,
listen, listen to what happens now, I have coffee, here comes, yeah, oh, oh my god, it's turbocharged.
The hell is that? Oh, man, they've done some kind of improvements without telling me.
Interesting. Of course, the sad thing is, is that when Sensei will finally
gets around advertising and actually sending me money for doing this, everyone's going to hate it.
It's so funny. I've gotten so many, so many comments about advertising. Hey, yeah, it's real
simple, you know, it's real simple. We have to figure out ways to make it interesting and entertaining
and it has to pertain to the podcast that you're listening to. That seems like a no-brainer. And by the
way, that's, I was thinking about, I've been thinking about a lot of things. I gotta tell you about the
items thing, too. Unlike web logs and other types of internet advertising, the power that you can
have. Let me see, so we have, for instance, an advertiser who has this, no, man, I don't even
know if I can talk about it. No, I'm going to, it's not going to be advertising on my show,
and I don't know the name of the product, but it's basically like a low jack for dogs and
crackberry. And, you know, so what do we do? Is we, what is that? We actually, I got to see what the hell
is going on. There's something here. There's a message from somebody who's sending me a message.
Oh, PW. Oh, cool. Yeah, PW is using, uh, he's doing a disaster run today. So he's, um, he's doing an
entire, what if, uh, power, what if a hurricane hits and power goes out, then how do we get stuff, uh,
to serious? He's doing the only, uh, you know, uh, complete mobile setup. Anyway, uh, where was I?
Okay, um, so the low jack for dogs, right? Uh, so that will be advertised on podcasts about,
guess what, dogs, and uh, and animal podcasts. So that makes a lot of sense. You know, it comes to
the broader stuff. That's where people get a little, um, little flaky, and, you know, how does
senseo pertain to you? Maybe you didn't know about it. Do you want it? You know, even,
well, Jarred George Carlin said it, you know, um, he's sick and tired of, oh, they're going to
make a Windows computer again, wanting to restart. He says he's a sick and tired of, I should look
up that. Where's the, just a George Carlin quote, hold on. Why am I even trying to,
Carlin, George Carlin? Let's see if this is it. Uh, hold on. Let me put it up here.
Let's listen, see if this is, I don't want to paraphrase the man, you know. Please,
save me from people who've been told what to like and then like. There you go, that's it.
In my opinion, if you're over six years of age and you're still getting your music from the
radio, something is desperately wrong with you. I can only hope that somehow MP3 players and
file sharing will destroy FM radio the way they're destroying record companies. Then, even though
the air will probably never be safe to breathe again, maybe it will be safer to listen to.
Right. So somehow that also, that pertains to music in, in that context, but somehow it also
pertains to advertising. So still a lot to work on, still a lot to think about. And also,
we have, now it's necessary if we want, if we wanted to work the way I envision it, then there's
got to be some kind of money flowing somehow. Okay, uh, remind me iTunes, got to talk about that.
First, let's go back. Backtracks podcast. So you think you know you're hit backwards and forwards?
Yeah, by now. You know what? Yeah, right. You're listening to the backtracks podcast exclusively
on the daily source code with Adam Curry. Hey, Adam. Hey, how you doing? Let's get right into
this week's quiz. Okay, here we go. Number one.
Politics of dancing. Politics of dancing. Thanks. Thank you.
Times out. Number two. Number three.
Eight. Something. Michael Jackson. Dirty Diana.
Definitely Michael Jackson. Okay, here are the answers. Number one.
Yeah. Got it. The politics of dancing.
I'm here's number two.
That was entirely too easy this year.
Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
Number three.
Okay. Oh, no, it's, uh, yeah, it's Michael Jackson.
Rockwell.
Somebody's watching me.
So how did you do Adam? Well, like to an add about a three. Thanks for joining us on this week's
backtracks podcast quiz. You can visit backtracks podcast on the web at
backtrackspodcast.com. Catch you next time. Backtracks podcast.
That is so well produced. Every single time I hear it, it's got, um, love it, fantastic.
And once again, I'm just enjoying the valve processor. God, I got to get another one of those.
Oh, I even got email. Someone sent me, you know, said, you know, the show just doesn't sound
to snappy as it usually do. It's not, not the, not the content, but somehow there's something
that just isn't snappy. Yeah, that's right. You, whoo, boy, do I miss that? Uh,
makes such a difference. This is the conversation I continuously have with Casplaster Mike.
It's so important to be able to hear the compression to hear what you're doing for me at least.
And this is only for me as just, you know, and I think, but I think a lot of, no, you know what,
you have to listen to what the listener is going to hear. That's why you have to hear the final
and recorded signal as it's going to come back through these little ear buds into someone's
noggin. You know, that's really what you have to hear. Because that's how you can only then
can you really create the med scientist. Okay. What do I have here? 17 minutes. Okay. I tunes.
I finally figured something out. This is also for Matt at Pod Show, who does all our insertion orders
and the tracking, et cetera. I figured out there's been something really weird going on. Where
one day we saw thousands of downloads just disappear from the daily source code. And
the subscriptions didn't diminish. That was the crazy thing is that the subscription number was still
the same. Only there were thousands less downloads. I'm like, how is this possible? And, you know,
we're like looking at our log files, we're trying to figure it out. And it hit me this morning.
All of a sudden, I figured it out. In iTunes, if you subscribe to Podcast, but you don't listen to,
I think it's five episodes, then it will automatically stop downloading and give you a little
explanation mark next to the podcast. Haha. So that would be it. Because of course, you know,
when daily source code is featured or when, you know, for some reason people hear about it,
particularly through iTunes, then, you know, thousands of people subscribe on the same day.
And if they stop listening to it, then it won't, well, it doesn't unsubscribe now because it still
goes and checks the feed. And through our relationship, I know how many subscribers I have through
iTunes, which, by the way, is not a service. They, you know, it should be a service. You should be
able to log in and find out how many subscribers you have. But it's not a service that's opened
everybody, which is a whole nother topic of conversation. But that's really interesting because
that really does keep the whole model very fair. So that you don't have advertisements going out
that are just sitting around the someone's iTunes and not being listened to. So actually,
although it sucks because, you know, like, wow, man, all of a sudden what happened to my
listenership, you know, there's like a percent dropage or something. Now I think I figured it out.
So the key is, is to, well, it's to keep marketing because that's what it is. It'd be, and of
course, iPod or lemon, I think, doesn't do that. You can probably set that as a default. I wonder,
I wonder how that's going to be. But it does seem like a very fair way to do it. You know,
if you're just so that you're, and it's also, it's not just fair for reporting purposes,
but also fair for for bandwidth purposes. I mean, shit, if you're not listening to the show,
stop downloading it, please, you know, that, that actually costs money. Although, you know,
since it sends teams per download, it's still costs money. So I just wanted to, she had that
brain fart with you. That's all. Hey Adam, this is PD Love, Everett Lovehouse Radio, and you mentioned
your show last week about not having heard a DJ speak about a song, whether they liked it or not
for the past 15 or 20 years. And it made me think back to a specific occurrence,
that was exactly 15 years ago, back in the summer of 1990. One of my favorite artists is
Jude Colt. I don't know if you've ever heard of Jude, but I was really turned on to him back in
that summer, and it was actually because of a local DJ here named Lisa McKay on the local
pop station. She worked the three to six shift. I guess the evening drive shift. And when she
first started her show, and when she ended her show every day for about a month that seemed,
she would mention how much she liked that song and liked that artist, Jude Colt, and the song was
Baby It's Tonight. And she'd play it, and then just kind of started sticking to me, and eventually
I bought the CD, listened to it every day through my senior year of college, as well as forcing
our roommates to listen to it, and it became kind of our anthem. We've spread the Jude as I put
it to a lot of people, but just wanted to give you that. That was about kind of a specific that,
yeah, it has been that long since I've heard a DJ really turned me on to music.
Until, of course, now with the podcasting and Brother Love and all the great artists on the
PMN, but just wanted to share that with you if you get a chance to listen to it, and check out Jude,
Jude Colt.com. He's got a recording studio out with Keith for Sutherland out in LA, so maybe they
can help out a little bit with the unlabel and some of these groups you're putting together,
or whatever's going on with that. So, again, just wanted to share that with you, keep your real
talk to you later. Peter Love. Thank you very much, my friend. Yeah. Well,
there you go. It's all this, this PMN is we're calling it the Podsafe Music Network.
So many suggestions. Even comic strip blogger offered his version of suggestions on the comments
for the Daily Source Code entry for last Friday. Of course, it didn't the typical comic strip blogger
way, which is completely rude in your face, but improvements definitely coming, and you know,
I think we have a real good idea now of how this thing is finally being used. I am,
well, it's kind of like the site that is almost now my default homepage, and I was looking for
Christmas use music, and I found some.
People are shopping for the loved ones, and making plans for Christmas Feast,
but it all goes by in the blink of an eye, and then we have to wait another year.
But what if every day would Christmas? What a wonderful world this would be?
We would never feel blue. We may call our dreams come true if Christmas or every day.
This time brings out the good in people. Just look around now and you'll see.
Everybody is nice and full of life and they give to those who are in need.
But if every day would Christmas? What a wonderful world this would be?
We would never feel blue. We may call our dreams come true if Christmas or every day.
So throughout the year, from the summer to the spring, I'll take you, time cheered, until then it's Christmas again.
But what if every day would Christmas? What a wonderful world this would be?
We would never feel blue. We may call our dreams come true if Christmas or every day.
Oh man, I just had another one of those big haired fact, the brainfarts. That was slow.
Every day we're Christmas from the pod save music network. I love this song.
And as I was listening to it, I was thinking to myself, this is the perfect song. This is like
We are the world. Do they know it's Christmas time by bandaid? Here's a thought. Here's something
we could, it would be very, very cool to do. Not trivial. But what if we got a whole bunch of
pod save music artists to cut, you know, just like a USA for Africa, we are the world in
like bandaid. And I can almost hear, brother love doing a bit. I can hear. I can't even come
up with the name of the list. There's so many different pod save music artists. Wouldn't it be
cool if we did that? So I'm thinking maybe Slow can release the tracks or, yeah, I don't know what
he's recorded it on. And then maybe we can have someone who is like the producer and then
everyone record their own version and then send it into one central spot and then the producer
could mix it out and could turn it into this huge, beautiful pod save music Christmas song
with just tons of pod save music artists. Anyone, basically wants to participate. Shit, we could
have 15 different versions of this. Think about how powerful that would be. And then we could even
go so far as to register it with ASCAP BMI with ASCAP or whatever or BMI. And whenever it's played
on the in the traditional media, which it will, I really truly believe if we make a great
ass song, we can get it distributed by a record label and we could give away the proceeds
to whatever charity we decide on. Perhaps Hurricane victims would be an interesting one. Of course
that's not a global issue. Well, in a way it is. Anyway, it doesn't matter. Think about
how cool that would be. So I'm just thinking maybe you'll do that. Oh my god, that would be
so cool. Okay, staying on the PMN for a second. What's up Adam? How's it going? My name's Jay Mac.
I've been a listener for a few months and you inspired me to start my own podcast, Hip Hop Podcast,
which I produce. We got a host for and everything. And then what we ended up doing was because
the Hip Hop, it's really hard to reach people simply on the internet. We do get a lot, but it's
not enough. So what we did is we hit the streets with, you know, flyers. We started our own little
street team with people just in Michigan right now. We got people into Troy Lansing and Flint,
Michigan and then we're spreading out to the Chicago area. And it's working really well. We're
getting a lot of artists, submissions, and stuff. But the problem we're having is, you know, a lot
of artists don't necessarily have internet access or, you know, they don't, they don't mess with the
internet much. So what we want to do is, you know, they can't submit themselves into the pod safe
music network, but we want to get them in there for the extra exposure. Anybody who are bringing
in is definitely unsigned and an underground artist. So I guess my question is, is there,
is there a way to bulk some artists to the pod safe music network? Because we have several artists
to put in there into the database, but, you know, it's, it's cumbersome to create an account for
each and every artist that we bring in because we're talking, you know, I mean, we bring in new artists
every week. So I'm hoping there's some way that we can streamline the process for us to be able
to put artists into the pod safe music network system without necessarily having to create an
account on their behalf, you know, under us. So anyway, I'd like to hear what you have to say about it,
get some feedback. And, you know, if there's anything we can do to make that work, let me know,
appreciate your time. Thanks. Yeah, Jim Mac for hoodhyped.com. Yeah, actually, that's a very good point.
And I think particularly in hip hop, you'll see that it's difficult to motivate the artist to get
there. You know, there's a traditional way of getting hip hop out there. And that's basically
by playing a really loud in your car and then getting picked up for distribution deal, you know,
through some sub-label, like a PDD or something like that, or, you know, Russell Simmons, or any
just countless of small Indies who have big label distribution deals. That's kind of the path that
you take, which, of course, is very limited. So we've done something to address this because
not only does this happen in hip hop, it happens. I guess artists in general across the board are,
and this is not from, you know, I've heard this from our performers themselves, that lazy.
So that's not my opinion, but it does seem to kind of ring true. And what we've done,
you know, we've enabled a number of podcasters to quit their day job, drew from Dawn and Drew.
Well, we're kind of with Mad Schweins, you know, though, she still manages the girl band.
There's just a number of them, which were very proud of by the way. It's very cool to be able to offer
people that. So one of the people who have, who's quit their day job is Michael Butler,
the Rock and Roll Geek of the Rock and Roll Geek Show, Rock and Roll Geek.com.
And he'll be coming into, I think it's, I don't know if he starts this week or next week,
but he'll, he's actually not just going to continue doing the Rock and Roll Geek Show,
he's also going to be working at the pod show headquarters. And his primary job will be
getting artists into the pod safe music network, which is fantastic. So I'll make sure that he
reaches out to you and there's a, you know, connect there so that you can, you guys can figure it out
away to facilitate that. That's just going to be very, very cool. And that's exactly what is needed, I think,
to really build up our, our database of, of pod safe songs. And in the future, I think that it
really is true that artists and bands will become, you know, one-man companies. It's already happening
that way. You know, you have to have your website. You've got to, you've got to get your merchandise,
which you get either through Zazzle or Cafe Press or, you know, with any other number of websites,
you've got, you do your, you, in many cases, you accept bookings through, for example, my space
and there were a lot of, a lot of pod safe music artists get, get bookings through my space.com,
uploading stuff into different places, such as the pod safe music network. There's a lot of work that
goes along with that. I know, I see what the listivious biddies do, man. It's like a full-time gig
and they still work. All kinds of tempting jobs to, you know, basic, hey, biddies, you know,
speaking of speaking of such, since you guys are on the road roaming around, why don't we hook
up with a biodiesel or something that's cheaper? You know, you're always renting vans. Maybe we
can get a bit of bitty mobile together. Hey, and all you have to do is just take some of the
vegetable oil from wherever you play and, you know, pour it in the tank and you're good to go.
Which reminds me, I think we've decided on the car. Because like, when I came home yesterday,
we were talking about it, because, well, you know, basically I saw our old car. So, oh shit,
yeah, I got to take care of that by the end of the end of the year. I promised to get rid of it.
And fucking windows. No, don't restart now and don't ask me again.
So, I was talking to Patricia and I said, well, there's so many different cars,
make some models and types. And, you know, what do you want to get? I don't think we should
get such a big car because we're really not going to use it. She said, that can be any car.
You know, I like all kinds of cars. As long as it's a Jaguar,
there what? Yeah, as long as it's a Jaguar. And notice my
correct pronunciation, not Jaguar. Jaguar Jaguar is a Jaguar.
Okay. So, we looked at a couple of Jags online at Jaguar.co.uk. And apparently,
this, you've got a, the S type, which is not the, it's not really super sexy, but the, the S,
the Jag S type has a 2.7 liter diesel engine. So, if anyone has any experience with the Jag,
and, and, and diesel, bio diesel, let me know because that's definitely a candidate.
That said, my friends, we've done it once again. Another daily source code. I'll be here all week.
Thank you very much. And I hope you have a very enjoyable day and a good start of the week.
And I'll talk to you tomorrow and Tuesday's Tuesday's edition of the daily source code.
Hey, W. Yeah. So, I'm super, you ready?