Delta Sierra Charlie 2-7-3
I don't see threats.
I'm sorry, information you don't get out of it.
Now I'm Korean.
I was 16 million dollars worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm signing you to the future.
Well, good afternoon from Curry Cottage.
It is Thursday.
It is the third of November 2005 from a very rainy wet and dark gilfer.
It's time for your daily source code.
Kick it off with a mellow mashup for the day.
Every day, every day, every day, every day.
Every day, every day, every day.
It is a wonderful,
inside of me so I'm too good.
Now I'm there, I get in the phone.
I'm all alone, I'm so blessed.
But I am beautiful.
No matter what they say or what they say or what they say or what they say.
Now, for no more.
So I am beautiful.
When we're single, we're here.
First can bring me down, for no more.
So don't you bring me down, for no more.
No matter what they say or what they say or what they say or what they say or what they say or what they say or what they say.
Now, for no more.
So don't you bring me down, for no more.
It's kind of pretty.
So Christina Aguilera, mash it up with Bob James.
Beautiful versus in the garden.
Good use of ID three tags there by ad of mashuptown.com, saying in the album title, making Adam a happy clam.
A lot of response to yesterday's show.
Oh, man.
Most of you thought it was pretty funny, particularly the Mads rant and Patricia's Pickles and all that crap.
Literally that crap.
Cast Blaster Mike was not happy at all with my windows rant.
Man, I really threw him off.
And, you know, he's developing in Windows.
And he had a really bad day.
I apologize.
Mike, nothing personal, obviously.
I've just been assimilated, dude.
That's my entire problem.
I've been assimilated by the art.
So a little bit later, the normal today.
Right now it's two when I started 135 British Standard Time.
So I'll be 12.
Oh, I don't want to get near that UTC code.
I don't want to mess it up for Zulu time.
A little late because well, two things happened actually.
One is Gmail had an outage this morning, which was, yeah, I was actually, it was pretty significant.
I kept getting the friendly messages like,
Ooh, the system couldn't handle your request right now.
And stuff was breaking all over the place.
And it kind of gave me like, like, you know, like a little chill there thinking,
Oh my god, if I think how much of my information is stored with the Google,
well, particularly in Gmail, how much of my life is in there and that I really depend on.
And it's like, well, yeah, of course, I could make all kinds of local backups and pop the nail out and all that stuff.
But that's kind of not the point.
And I guess I've never really read their terms.
What happens over, you know, how, how, well, actually, I think their whole business should be securing and protecting my data.
So I'm just going to assume that they will and that they do, but might not be a bad idea to,
to grab a copy of everything of all the, God, it must be at least 30,000 messages in there right now.
We know the size of it, so that's not a big deal.
What is it now? We're up to, I'm almost all, like, I'm like, at three gigs.
So, you know, I have that special gigazoid four gig limit.
I love it. I wonder if that's going to start growing once they start hitting that limitation.
So anyway, so that did lay everything because everything that I have is always stored in Gmail.
And, you know, I got to download all the different promos and stuff that people have sent me.
And I've forward a lot of stuff to myself to, you know, with special rules so that it's tagged and labeled in a certain way.
So that I kind of, it's kind of a live organization system, which works quite well, actually.
Could do, we could do it even better, but yeah, I'd have to get into it.
Let's say Springsteen Chase out of Fort Lauderdale by Wilma.
Hold on, this is just one of those, I never look at those web clips on Gmail. What does this say?
And does it write at the top of my email? It had this message.
It's a guess it's an AP report sending me over to news.yahoo.com and what does it say?
With much of Florida still recovering from Hurricane Wilma, Bruce Springsteen has been forced to cancel as November 3rd,
solo acoustic show near Fort Lauderdale because of officials' concerns over public safety.
Wow. The rocker, I love how they say that. The rocker, the loved one, the material girl.
We'll now play the seminal hard rock live arena in Hollywood, Florida on the 19th, according to a message on his website,
Springsteen.net.
Okay. Coolio.
It's the first time I've ever clicked on one of those at the top of Gmail.
And there was also a message here that said, Google Mail in the UK, right at the top of my Gmail.
I think we went over this before that there's a trademark dispute over the name Gmail.
And so as of October 19th, I'm reading here, Google Mail in the UK will start handing out Google Mail.com addresses.
Why the name chains? We've been involved in a dispute regarding the Gmail trademark in the UK.
Another company is claimed right to the Gmail name.
We have tried to resolve this dispute through negotiations, but our efforts have failed.
You didn't want to pay the prices what that means.
Still working with the courts and trademark office to protect our ability to use the Gmail name,
but in the meantime, we want you to have an email address that you can rely on.
Okay. So the address is good.
And more importantly, please, please take care of my data.
This is, you know, with that Windows live stuff, this is going to be a big deal, I think.
You know, because now, what is it live office, I guess, and you'll be,
yeah, was it someone sent me an email, and I actually tried to fire this thing up.
It's, oh, God, I can't remember the name of it now, but it's, it's,
think office, think free, think free, I think it is office.
And I tried to run it on my Mac. It looks cool because you can create word documents,
Excel documents, and PowerPoint documents in a web browser.
And then, of course, it said, hey, you don't have the latest JRE, you know, 9,000 or whatever,
with a link to a page on the Apple site, which was non-existent,
God hate that.
And then my Mac popped up saying, you have 97 megs worth of update to download for the OSX update.
So I did that and I'll go back to think free thing and see if that works.
I remember those guys around quite a while ago, but I didn't know that they now had kind of this,
the browser and the service metaphor, which is very interesting.
We're seeing some really interesting things happening, particularly what Microsoft is doing,
very interesting to see where this is going to take us.
So far, the demo that they have at live.com doesn't really work in Firefox.
It works somewhat, but I tried it out on the, on the craplet and got definitely different results.
So we'll wait until they fix that, until I can really comment on it.
So today we have a couple of pod save tunes, obviously.
I think only two promos and lots of feedback, as I said, the feedback about yesterday's show,
and it's very obvious, there's only one real star here in the cottage, and that will be my wife.
So I talked to her last night and I said, could you come in more often during this show?
I don't care what you say, just come in more often, please.
She said she would.
We'll see.
Hello Adam, this is Andy from the Skinny on Sports or T-Sauce as we like to call it pod show.
I was listening to your show yesterday and I wanted to point out a few things.
So let's see if I can queue it up.
Okay, here's the beginning of your show.
Geltis, here are Charlie, two, seven, two.
Now let me jump ahead here a bit.
Oh yeah, here it is.
Where is the voice of the fan in mass media?
You know, it's always some idiot with blue and white paint on his face holding up a sign
or standing next to his mates with a, with a big letter on his belly, you know?
Or it's the epitentiary here, shouted from the stands at the, at the rough, or the, or other, or opposing team players.
But where is the voice of the fan?
You don't really hear it.
You really don't.
So it makes a hell of a lot of sense at that's happening.
Cool to see it because there's no outlet whatsoever for him.
Alright, so I got to this point and thought, what is Adam thinking?
No voice for the fans?
No outlet for them to be heard?
Adam, you just have to look to family.
Your pod show family.
At the skinny and sports, we give that outlet for the fan.
So whether you're wanting to talk about your favorite sport, team, athlete, or the game last night,
the skinny and sports can give you that voice.
You can email us your comments at skinny and sports at gmail.com.
You can record audio comments and send them our way as well.
And the newest way is to call the t-sauce hotline.
At 206-350-ts-o-s.
That's t-s-o-s for the skinny and sports.
Then you can look for your voice to be seen and heard at www.s skinny and sports.com.
Alright Adam, now that we've got that out of the way, you can go back to your show,
knowing that your pod show family is looking out for you.
Have a good day.
Hey buddy, thanks.
We got to figure out how to get you in both speakers.
Both earbuds at the same time.
Yeah, absolutely.
Of course.
What I meant was a little bit different.
Because of course, skinny on sports, the fastest 10 minutes on your iPod,
gives the fan a voice.
I was thinking more along the lines of fans creating their own podcast.
And I think that's not that you guys aren't fans.
But I think there's places for all kinds of podcasts.
And dude, I'm definitely going to call you guys up.
We should talk about that.
What we can do, how we can facilitate even more fan interaction.
A lot of the problems seem to be that whenever the fans get together
and build great websites and fan-zene websites and do podcasts,
is that the clubs usually come down really hard on them for using their logos
and trademarks and stuff like that.
It's kind of like the music business in a way.
You know, where it's all about the players,
it's all about the sponsors, the television rights,
and somewhere, oh yeah, yeah, there's the people who pay for it all.
That would be us, the fans, right?
So I think we're going to see some meltdowns all across the board.
And the more I think about it, in position I would talk about that last night,
there is such a meltdown on the way across the board.
It's, who was saying that to this guy, a friend of mine, Rob,
who lives in the Netherlands.
He used to be used to write for gossip magazines.
It was like the one chill I had on the inside.
He always worked at shitty rags that had no circulation,
but at least like it gets some room or debunked a little bit.
And he's now heavily into all kinds of online activities
that involve SMSing, that's basically text messages
that you send for a fee.
And he has real valuable propositions for people.
I'm not going to get in digs.
And it's okay, okay, he's doing porn, all right?
So anyway, we talked about cross-promotion from television,
promoting URLs and how that would work and radio.
And he said interestingly enough, he says that advertising on television
really doesn't give him a lot of traffic.
He says because people who are inclined to go online
or to do something of that interactive nature,
basically aren't watching television.
I thought that was, and this is a very small country,
but it's a good country for testbed of how things will work,
because it's his own eco culture, it's own language and all that stuff.
So I thought that was pretty interesting.
He said radio still does seem to work, but of course,
it's so ubiquitous, and they have such horrible traffic problems
in the Netherlands.
Everyone spends at least two hours in their car every day,
if not more, sitting in traffic,
so they listen to a lot of radio.
And obviously he thinks that iPods are the next place
to advertise.
He feels that online advertising works much better.
So if that's the vacuum that's being created in traditional media,
you know, there's a lot to be afraid of,
or a lot of opportunities,
just a matter of how you take a look at it.
See a couple of emails here, Michael Grosch.
Let's see, as a former headbanging bedbanger's ball addict,
I was surprised to hear about you from Steve Jobs
and one of his keynotes.
And I've been a happy subscriber to Delta Sierra Charlie since.
Tonight I've run into a little problem.
After syncing my subscriptions and iTunes,
I found a repot of yesterday's episode and deleted it,
because I thought it would be the same as the regular episode,
what a fatal mistake.
Unfortunately, I have no idea how to recover deleted episodes on iTunes.
Re-syncing doesn't work,
hopefully you could point me to a solution,
which would probably be useful for other listeners of the DSC.
Michael from Germany.
Okay, first of all, excuse M.W.
Shapo, no, that's not what I'm looking for.
Excuse M.W.
My French sucks.
I have like four things I know, I just say,
and I pronounce them well, so I can get away with it.
Mia Culpa, let's use that, not French, but it'll work.
I don't know how it happened, but I basically am still,
I have the oldest crappiest upload production system in the world,
and I'm keeping it that way for a specific reason,
because the team that is now working on the Pod Show PDN,
the Pod Cast delivery network,
and everything that's going to be associated with that.
I have to basically convince me to use their system.
And until I do, it won't be good enough,
and they have lots of issues to deal with with me,
because there's migration, my feed,
my iTunes feed, where to stuff live.
I mean, right now I'm uploading to three load balance servers,
and I post a link on curry.com,
and then I post the same thing again,
and in radio, user land,
just to make it a little more complicated.
And that's the actual feed that activates the iTunes feeds,
and somehow, on copying, I copied a wrong link,
and I had everything in there right,
it's just I copied the wrong enclosure link
into the user land upload interface,
and it's crazy.
Of course, that also kind of does show you
that iTunes, as an aggregator, is technically broken,
because it should never download the same piece of content twice,
and it did, it actually created two files.
With the same name, one with an appended,
was like a dash wand or something.
That should basically never happen,
particularly if the bite sizes are the same,
which they were, so that doesn't seem to be working right.
Now about deleting stuff in iTunes,
yeah, that's very dangerous.
If you delete one episode,
it basically deletes your entire subscription,
and where it does something funky,
really the only way I found to do it
is to completely delete the whole daily source code,
then re-subscribe to it,
and you may want to subscribe
by using the link on dailysourcecode.com,
the XML, the orange on white XML icon.
If you copy that link,
and you can go to, what is it on iTunes?
I think it's a bit just check.
I think it's advanced, yeah,
and then subscribe to podcast,
and then paste that URL in there,
and then you're still going to get fucked up shit
if I do it wrong,
but it does remove one step from the loop,
which is the iTunes system,
which essentially scans all of the feeds periodically.
I don't know if they've actually changed
to looking at a ping service,
and now we talk to them about that a lot.
And they may be looking at,
I don't know,
when wintersoldweblogs.com,
you also sold audio.weblogs.com,
and I think that the short changes XML,
that's basically the file that shows you what changes
have been made in the past X amount of time,
and it always pops up empty for me,
so I guess they're not supporting that anymore,
which is for obvious commercial reasons,
but I don't know.
So now I don't,
they may be pulling it from ping.indepotter.com,
or ping.indepotter.org.
That's could be where they're getting it from.
If they're doing pings,
but again, I don't know.
Now I'll find out.
They got some cool guys over there now,
who are dedicated to working on the podcasting
and the iTunes music store,
so they'll definitely let me know.
Let me see a couple of sincere things.
Oops, hold on a second.
The blackberry's going off.
I'm going to check and see what that is.
I have an extremely busy day today.
Ah, okay, so we're late for this.
It's 12 to two.
Today, Patricia and I are going to test drive,
the Jaguar, the S-Type.
V6, turbohunker thing.
Turbo dieselhunker thing.
Okay, so we're going to be late for that.
I was contemplating a sound seeing tour,
but I think I'm going to wait.
They don't have the really the car that we want.
They have the car with the same engine and suspension,
and all that stuff.
But I think that when we go back and test drive,
the car that we're really interested in,
which has all the toys and all the cool bits in it.
You know, probably at that point,
we might do a sound seeing tour.
I'm pretty jazzed about it actually.
Now, we won't be able to take the delivery of a car
for almost two months,
so we still have to see whether we're going to take one out of stock,
out of the showroom,
or if we're going to order one custom order it.
I've gotten some pros and cons,
email wise and feedback from people about the Jaguar,
saying that the typical stuff about English cars,
and some other suggestions.
But I think I'm still pretty high on this,
and depending on if it's not a total dog to drive,
I think we'll just get it,
because I don't drive here at all anyway.
So, except to maybe go to the Farrowx Airport,
when I'm flying the 182.
So, still looking for people who might have had some experience
with the Jaguar Diesel, Turbo Diesel,
regarding Bio Diesel, otherwise,
we're just all going to experiment together,
then aren't we?
More feedback.
Hiya, this is from Brian Deamer.
From the Comic Geek Speed Podcast.
They're Brian.
This is Brian Deamer from the Comic Geek Speed Podcast.
I wanted to take this opportunity to thank you
for inspiring me and my friends to do a podcast.
Your daily dose of all things podcasting keeps me informed,
and motivated to make our show better each day.
And I want to let your listeners know
that it is possible to be successful in the world of podcasting.
Our show started out in March,
just a small show with a few listeners.
But by filling it with our passion for comic books,
and trying our best to make it the best show we know how,
we now have more than 2,000 downloads every day.
We are selling advertising that targets our audience,
since I owe.
We are traveling around the US to comic conventions far and wide
to meet our listeners.
Hell, we've never owned t-shirts.
So if you really want to,
and if you're willing to put in a lot of hard work,
you too can have a successful podcast.
We owe it all to you, Adam.
If not for your constant energy about this exciting new medium,
we wouldn't be where we are today.
So have a great day and thanks so much.
And by the way, if you're a fan of comic books,
or you're even curious about the joys of superheroes,
check us out at ComicGeekSpeak.com.
Hey, Brian. Thanks, buddy.
I cannot accept all the credit you gave there.
It sounds like you guys have been working really hard.
And there you go.
So you see what a couple of thousand subscribers can do
if you're, well, essentially,
if you're certainly if you're targeting some kind of nature,
basically whatever the frick you have passion about,
right, that's really, wow.
I hate saying right after sentences.
Oh, that's so Silicon Valley.
I'll get to that in a second.
So you can see how it works.
You know, if you're passionate about a topic,
and I like the wrestling promo from yesterday as well,
you know, these are very targeted audiences.
I mean, think of all, you know,
the, oh, man, any extreme sport,
anything that's narrower than the Daily Source Code, basically.
I think you can be very successful in because the audience is going to be so well known.
Advertisers will, will hone you out.
They will seek you out.
I'm telling you, they're going after this because they realize it's a great place
to reach the audience.
They just have no way of reaching because,
that's what they're not really watching television anymore.
They're not really listening to the radio.
And if they are, it's not quite working as well as it used to.
So congratulations, guys.
That's fantastic.
That is just fantastic.
I love it.
About the right thing.
Throughout Silicon Valley, I've noticed.
Whenever you talk to a technologist,
someone who really knows this stuff usually will do this,
there's this, this habit of people saying,
well, you know, I'll give an example.
Well, the RSS feed, of course,
will update through the dynamically generated court, right?
And they always end the sentence with the right,
which is,
it gives a non-technical people a very easy way to say,
oh, yeah, right.
But I find it highly annoying.
And I do find myself often saying,
no, I don't think that's right.
But that's incorrect.
But the danger is you start taking that shit
over yourself and you start saying,
oh, God, I hate doing that.
I'm the chameleon of talk when it comes to that.
I always, you know,
I'm still still struggling,
very hard not to slip into the magic vibe over here.
The Madonna vibe of talking with the English accent,
which is not fake, it's not,
her accent is not fake.
It's so easy if you live here to slip into it.
It's just,
it's a fascinating way of using the English language.
It really is so much nicer than,
then what I grew up with,
so much richer in description to be honest.
Gabrielle Moreno,
this is the email I was waiting for.
Adam, been a fan for several months.
Thanks for playing some country.
I would not complain if you play more of it.
I am a jazz in the country fan.
He he he.
Anyone wants to know if,
there's a way to buy pot-sake music other than through iTunes?
Well, yeah, of course.
Most of the artists have sales mechanisms or deals with places like CDB
be set up on their own websites,
which you can get to from the pot-sake music network.
And, well,
they're,
there possibly could be something in the very near future
in the form of an unlabel that might,
might answer your question a little more,
so,
this one's for you,
another country song,
this is Amy Dallas.
It's just a long-label,
quite a tragedy.
Same time,
same channel,
and you're hosting down,
and watch the show.
It's a revix,
it's running out with a broken heart,
and I'm afraid,
making it time away.
It's trapped in myself from the flame,
oh,
hey,
it's gonna be kidding,
there's gonna be tears,
and I'm not trying to drown
and I'm in a couple of fears,
but you don't want to meet
us up the shows,
just starting,
running out with a broken heart,
and I'm in a couple of fears,
and I'm in a couple fears,
Looking hard,
Running out with the broken heart.
Yeah.
Right now.
Amy Dally.
I presume it's Dally,
D-A-L-L-E-Y Friday night.
From the Podsate Music Network,
a little bit of country for you, Robotta.
Uh...
Music.podshow.com.
Now, so here we are.
And the Patricia Knight talked about her coming on the show more just last night.
And I said, I'm going to go to the show.
And then I just saw her drive off in the car.
Did you just post it?
Hold on.
Let me just call her.
Let's see if she has her mobile honor.
I'll see if I can do this.
I think that's it.
Let's see if I've got everything hooked up right.
If so, it will function.
Come on Skype.
Do your thing, baby.
Right.
So far, pretty disappointing.
Come on.
Why isn't that working?
Connecting?
That was wrong here.
I'm on the right network.
See if I have the right number in there.
Let me see.
Hmm.
Well, this is not working out the way I plan.
Let me try one more time.
Why isn't Skype out just working?
Man, I'm going to go off on another tire.
I can feel it.
I guess not.
All right.
Told you leave it for what it is.
Another thing that I got a lot of quite a lot of feedback and comments on.
And in fact, over the past couple of weeks, it seemed to seem so intensified.
Is the naming convention and I wasn't understanding what the problem was.
People are saying, hey, however you name your show.
Please change it so that I can actually see which episode is going to play on my iPod.
Because the iPod essentially takes this whole title and you got it.
It abbreviates it or it gives you a dot dot dot dot dot.
I think sometimes it'll scroll if you put your if you mouse wheel over to the episode.
It'll scroll so you can see what it is.
But of course, my episode numbers come at the very end.
And I'm thinking, that doesn't sound right.
My episode.
In fact, I name my my shows.
D.S.C. Dash episode number dash year dash month dash day.
And I couldn't figure it out until finally I had a closing.
I don't usually look at my own.
My own pod.
I'm subscribed to it and I looked at it.
And it doesn't represent the ID three tags.
The actual file itself.
It represents the post that that was made.
So the podcast is basically named or I guess.
Let me see.
This is an interesting question.
Anyway, so what shows up in iTunes on the iPod is from what I post on the website.
Not what I put in the ID three tags.
That was pretty surprising because yeah, right there.
I say daily source code for day.
You know, it was like, we guess they would have been for Wednesday,
November 2nd, 2005, 2007 too.
So basically all you see on the iPod is daily source code for dot dot dot.
Well, that of course sucks.
Let me see if it.
I mean, look at the original file here for a second.
I think we can do it like this.
Wow.
Yeah, they actually name the file.
Oh, that's interesting.
iTunes renames the file.
Now, let's see what's in the ID three tags.
Don't have that didn't change, please.
That's let me see the ID three tags say.
I have to open up in quick time, I guess.
Hold on one second.
This is kind of interesting.
Okay.
Let's look at the ID three tags for it.
Read my God.
Wow.
I had no idea.
Okay.
So that's really interesting.
And at the same time, I don't know if I like that.
So when you get a podcast from a through iTunes,
and then it sucks it into iTunes,
it basically repopulates all of the ID three tags in your font.
That is not right.
I mean, so yeah, I know how to work around it,
but that's basically changing my content.
Okay.
So what I'll do today is you've probably already noticed.
I'll post it differently so that you can actually see it on your iPod.
And of course, I'll get all kinds of people angry at me
because I changed the name convention.
But this is pretty important stuff.
I had no idea that iTunes did that,
and I'm just finding this out.
Okay.
So basically, I have to put, I have to change the way I name them
in the posts to the weblog and to the podcast feed,
which I'll do.
Pretty interesting stuff.
Something else that happened.
Oh, Skype out is working, I think.
What's working?
Hello?
No, I don't hear anything.
Hey, baby.
There you go.
Don't let yourself go.
Oh, I couldn't hear you.
I wanted to call you on the show.
Oh, I mean, I'm in the car.
In the car.
Yeah.
For some reason, I can't get you on the mixing board, either.
Whatever.
Um, I mean, the car has to put things to it.
Do you know that?
Yeah, I know it's dangerous, dear.
Please be very careful.
We're driving off the left side.
Well, I, I, I want to say that we've missed you on the show
and you drove off.
Yeah, I have to get new, do I?
Okay.
There's a peanut here, someone.
We have the teenagers hungry here.
Okay.
Well, see you later, then we'll go test drive.
I'll be back in five minutes.
Okay.
Well, yeah.
If you're back in five, then we can still talk.
Okay.
Love you.
Hmm.
I don't know.
For some reason, the mixer didn't work.
All right.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
CC Chapman had something pretty cool to say about the upcoming podcast
Expo.
Yeah, I'm curious.
This is Scott from Anchorage, Alaska.
Listen.
Wait a minute.
That's not CC.
That's Scott.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Here we go.
I was thinking about all the great artists and talent that's over there at the pod safe
Music Network and I was thinking, hmm.
You know, all this needs to be packaged up.
Maybe Showcase.
How about a pod show polusa?
That's right.
I think it would be a fantastic idea.
Not only would it support and pump up the independent music artists that are out there.
But it also demonstrated the music industry.
How many people are listening to podcasts and listening to independent artists that are
on most podcasts?
So I'm all for you trying to make that happen.
Let me know what I can do.
And look forward to going to a pod show polusa this summer.
Take care of yourself and keep podcasting from Anchorage, Alaska.
This has got Sloan at the Alaska pod show.
Right on Scott.
Okay.
So that was a pretty good point.
Although, you know, the problem there is if you want to package up a concert tour.
It has a lot of money involved in that to get that going.
And who knows what kind of ticket sales we'd have.
I guess it would really had a great way of promoting it across the network.
Well, actually, I think it might actually work.
I have to think about it.
But we are taking small, small, tiny little steps.
And one of them is what CC is going to tell you about.
The podcasters are coming.
Hey, Adam.
It's CC from accidenthash.com.
How's it going, Matt?
Haven't talked to you in a while.
And I want to talk to you listeners for just a minute to let them know about something very, very cool.
The podcasters exposed next week.
We all know that Friday and Saturday.
Well, everybody's getting in on Thursday, right?
And we need something to get everyone together to kick off the whole expo right.
And what's that going to be?
It's going to be an unofficial kickoff party.
And we're calling it give love a chance.
We're doing a little acoustic party.
Everybody is welcome.
And we're going to have two of the hottest podsafe artists out there.
We're going to have chance playing an acoustic set.
And then the number one pod played artist out there.
Brother loves flying all the way in from New York City to rock the place down.
I can't wait.
It's going to be a nice cool upbeat set, but acoustic set.
Brother love.
I know we're going to pull him back and make him rock the house a little acoustic.
So I'm encouraging everybody.
We're going to have a sign-up form very soon because we know we're going to pack this thing out.
Nine o'clock at the Marriott details to follow.
There will be posters.
There will be flyers.
You can't miss it.
So when you get into town on Thursday, look up around the Marriott.
You know, they're going to have the little screens everywhere.
And I'll swing on by and add them.
We'll make sure you're on the guest list.
So if I when you parachute in and you get all your your hos and your limos and everybody else and your whole
archeological coming in, we'll make sure this room free at the door.
Details to follow.
If anyone has any questions from my accent at hash.com, I will have the latest information.
I appreciate it.
And I appreciate this.
Show being put on by the podshow podcast network and the podsafe music network.
Helping me make this a reality.
So peace man, play some songs.
And I'll talk to you soon.
But it's all good home fries.
Absolutely.
Very cool.
That's Thursday night, which kind of bones me out because I was planning on arriving Thursday afternoon.
I wasn't actually planning on going up until Friday.
If I can get the bitches, the hose and the limos all set up, you know.
I'm afraid to go now.
I really am because inevitably I'm going to piss somebody off by not having time to talk to.
Because everybody is sending me messages.
Hey, you know, I'll catch up with you at the expo.
Man, I don't want to like, you know, hold court and talk to people.
That's sucks.
You know, I just want to, maybe I should go and disguise.
There you go.
I did check it coming for the great disguise.
Well, five foot 17 of me.
CC just sent an email, internal email here at podshow.
Songs reported played on the podsafe music network.
8,060.
My god.
Fantastic.
Over 8,000 songs played from the podsafe music network.
That's a lot of airtime.
That's a lot of songs played, man.
That is fantastic.
See, we have,
Oh, yeah.
Oh, man.
We have 1,000.
Just thousands of podcasters registered thousands of artists.
Thousands of songs uploaded.
This is fantastic.
That's really, really cool.
That's great.
Paul, to UCC, and of course, the podshow podsafe music podcasters.
You can find out more about them all at music.podshow.com or podsafe music network.com.
And it's funny.
Because CC actually says, you'll dig this in one of his email subjects.
And that reminded me that someone,
Actually, a couple people pointed out to me that I'm on dig.com.
And yesterday, apparently, someone was incredibly brilliant.
And went to one of our investor's websites.
A quiet capital and found the podshow address and telephone number,
which is no problem.
It's like a phone listing.
And then, and here's Adam Curry's personal phone number.
And so people were sending me message like, wow, man,
you must be really bummed out.
And that really sucks.
I'm like, what are they talking about?
And I looked at the number.
And it is one of my phone numbers.
And it probably picks up with an answering machine
that has my voice on it.
But it's like, it's a prepaid, tea mobile from a couple months ago.
I don't even have to, I'm pissed off about it.
Because I don't have the sim card.
You know, I really wanted to play some of the messages
that folks had left on it for me.
But what was interesting is that people see,
you know, that's like that some kind of intrusion.
I'm like, no, you know, it's like,
I think everyone can have my phone number.
As long as I have your phone number,
have you in my address book,
and you have your caller ID switched on.
Because my phone actually doesn't ring.
If you don't have caller ID,
if you're not recognized in my phone book,
and then you just go to voice mail,
and I'll catch up with you later.
You know, it's funny how that's flipped around,
where the real personal contact happens through email.
It doesn't happen through the telephone anymore.
In fact, my phone barely rings at all.
If only for a prior agreed to time to talk with someone.
It's all email instant message.
It's, uh, it's changing my friends.
It really is a changing.
All right.
Here are the couple promos.
I promise you that I had lined up.
Hey Adam, it's Aaron Chapman here from Vancouver BC.
I love the daily source code,
and I listen all the time.
Listen, I've got a promo here.
It would be awesome if you give it a spin for me.
Check it out.
Send me, me, send me.
Recte, alvi.
Tent, podcast, text, look, again, again, again.
Radio, right now.
The other side of my guy, Tentzoi,
Interess I'm a long guy,
I often change my program.
Orvi, Kai Devi.
Esperadding, where are you from?
Radio Verda.
Lavocho, the Esperanto.
Radio Verda.com.
Did you get all that?
That was in the International Language Esperanto.
In case you haven't heard of Esperanto,
it's a constructed language that's extremely easy to learn.
It was designed to bridge people's cultures around the world,
and it's been around since the 1800s,
so there's a small but vibrant community out there.
Radio Verda, which means green radio or green ray or beam,
was launched in 98 and was the first independent international
radio program entirely in Esperanto entirely on the internet.
Since then, it's been a small, on again, off again project,
but it's recently been relaunched as a podcast,
which you could find at Radio Verda.com
in large part from inspiration from you, my friend.
So thanks very much for that, and all your great work.
I'll keep on listening, especially on my new iPod,
if it ever gets here.
Cheers Adam, take care.
Hot show should only be enjoyed under the supervision
of a podcasting professional,
warning, do not attempt this at home.
Yeah!
Adam Curry, got a couple of quick questions for you
to short plug for my show.
It's kindergarten.
The groggy job is show.
That's available at groggyjovith.tv.
Yeah, what's up with German raygays?
It just made it as a scene like a lot of the raygays.
It's available online today on the podcast,
if you're sitting at work another similar network's like it.
Now they all can seem to come from Germany.
Maybe there's something going on there,
I don't know about.
Maybe there's something you know about it.
I'm not really sure.
Anyways, I would like to see if you could put out a casting call
for more raygays just in general.
I'm for the podcast music network.
I haven't taken out jam and incorporated power,
step for his back-to-luncher.
I've been spinning them.
I've been really digging it.
I'd like to see if we can get some more up in there.
Also, it was interesting for Cisco to be before the last one.
I noticed how very similar there are two
and an answer down the place
that really feels warm in the sun,
cool in the breeze.
Columbus and Grant Boy,
that's about a red light district up around there,
isn't it?
Anyway, is this an SSH department
on my show from a longer winded form
out of Gavin and John,
and having it all in?
Into the more of the morning coffee talks show
with music and me,
and having some fun with guests and stuff like that.
Perhaps some of you,
this is one more stuff by groggyjava.tv
for a cup of Joe.
Anyways, got to run.
You will do.
Thanks for the time,
and have a good one, dude.
You will.
Right.
Let me see Columbus and Grant,
and I have to do a sound scene tour of that.
And today, the source code for Thursday,
to more, of course,
to be the thank God,
is Friday, and we'll have our regular party schedule
and I'm looking forward to that.
Another bit of music I picked up off
of the Pot set music network this morning,
just going to the home page,
and I was listening to the first five songs that come up.
Kind of like this one.
And Lynn.
This is from Renalbo.
The way Loves meant to be,
actually it's an EP as part of the scene
of a daily source code.
It turns everybody on.
While I try to cheat my distance,
everything is the same for everyone.
It's about the door,
the competition has begun.
I'm looking out the window for a sign,
you'll never pick me up all the time.
The queen insisting by their past relationships.
They were broken.
But it keeps you on the ground.
It just keeps you hanging on.
You just can't let go.
It's just leaving it alone.
It tracks us all around.
I'm not going to go out on a limb here,
and suggest that the artist's name is the scene
and the title of the song is Anne Lynn.
Not the other way around.
The wonders of ID3 tags.
Sorry for being such an idiot.
PWB just sent me an email.
He was listening to yesterday's source code.
He said that I was trying to hear
that I was trying to track down a ground loop home,
and he goes through, this typical PWB.
He'll go through all the different steps
until he narrows it down to one thing.
It turns out that the real solution
is to make sure your computer that you're recording on
is plugged into the same power circuit
that your outboard gear is.
That's pretty interesting.
I have no desire to rewire this thing.
I got no desire to rewire.
Definitely not.
Okay. I think I've stalled enough.
I can't get Patricia on the show today, so I'll have to do it tomorrow.
But I'll trapper.
So she can't leave the house.
She had to leave the house today early at 10.
She went to see her new cardiologist here in the UK,
and I'm happy to report that we have a very healthy
bouncy baby girl.
She's doing great, so that was great news.
Okay, dailysourcecode.com is where you can find this podcast.
We can always download directly from the website
or even better. You might want to subscribe to the show
in iPod or Lemon, which by the way
is going to change its name pretty soon.
Maybe I'll tell you more about that tomorrow.
And also there's iTunes links
so you can subscribe to it with iTunes just by clicking on the link.
And for feedback, fired off to Adam at Curried.com.
I can't say it enough.
I'd really, really, really appreciate it.
If you could add the appropriate ID3 tags
and stick it up on a server somewhere and just send me the link.
So I don't get too filled up here on the Gmail.
And that's it, really.
Okay.
If you got anything cool for tomorrow's weekend kickoff celebration,
send it off to me.
I definitely love playing the crazy stuff.
You know that.
And I will be back tomorrow on the thank god it's edition.
Thank god it's Friday edition of the Daily Source Code.
Take care y'all.
Another pod show podcast.
Stick it in your ear.