Okay, everybody, I'm on British Airways flight 284 traveling from San Francisco to London.
I go to London. At the moment, I am completely flat on my back.
Now, that's because I am in the club world class of British Airways service, which
I guess in quite a couple of years, they have a sleeper class service, which means that in the first class,
and then I guess this would be a business class where they call a club world, your seat can actually extend pretty much horizontally,
so that you can sleep. Well, of course, I can't sleep.
Because, well, for a number of reasons, hold on.
One.
I'm going to see this for a very long time.
I'm recording now.
Number one, the seat.
It's probably about six feet long, I guess, from head to toe and I'm six four.
So, kind of have to scrunch up, and it's not really, well, the first class is much better.
There you could a little mattress, and you could a little pajamas, and they tuck you in.
And it costs $8,000.
So, what that?
Normally, I wouldn't even book myself in the club world, I'd book myself in the, what I call it,
they call it, the traveler plus class, which is coach, but with a little bit more room,
and it also gives you more flexibility if you want to rebook your flight, you can, you know, you can change stuff around.
But also, if you're in the traveler plus class, then you, it happened to me last time I was in San Francisco,
which was, well, it was watercolon, you know, member.
Is there a room?
Was I?
I just can't remember.
When the last time was that I was flying around.
Anyway, then you have a good chance that if the flight is oversold, then you get bumped up to,
uh, the club class.
Another benefit, and this is something that is very specific to, uh, London to Heathrow,
is they, the concept of fast track.
So, you have customs, end to end airports security, by the way, on the way out,
but you have customs on the way in, basically, in the UK, the class system is alive and well,
because you could just bite by yourself, a faster way through customs.
And so, they give you a little pass, a pass track pass, looks like a boarding card.
And when you could off the plane, you go into the, really short line.
You don't have to stand in any long line.
Oh, stupid.
You go right through, you kind of blow through customs.
And it wouldn't be surprised if my bag even comes off in a separate carousel.
So, I'm doing, I'm recording this on the creative labs, send micro that was given to me by folks
of Microsoft.
I talked about that on yesterday's source code.
I'm not even going to call this a source code.
I'm just going to throw it up there.
Um, so they want to talk about a couple things.
First of all, what I want to talk about is this little device.
I'm pretty impressed.
Um, wait, don't go away.
I'm going to check and see how this sounds.
And if it's recording, okay.
So, stay right where you are.
It'll take a nanosecond.
Okay, cool.
It actually works.
And not bad.
I have to say I'm just talking right into the top of this thing where the microphone is located.
And I have to say the quality is pretty good.
I'm pretty sure it's not an MP3 that it's recording to.
But I found, I was pointed to some max software for the Zen micro.
Got that three email after talking about it, which I was very thankful for because, of course,
when I plugged it into my USB port, nothing showed up.
Nothing happened in the mountains drive.
And so now I have kind of the the manager of the iTunes, if you will,
of the Zen micro so that I can manage the files.
And it plays, you know, all the usual suspects.
The Zen micro XMP3 wave windows media.
And it's kind of funny.
It's the interfaces.
And you can see that they've tried to emulate a lot of the iPod.
Sort of the click wheel you've got a thumb slide, I guess.
But they have been some things.
I think better just, you know, more thought out as to how you actually
find tracks.
They're still talking about music and artists and all that.
You know, she's unfortunate.
Not the whole MP3 ID3 tag thing that will just be stuck with for generations of devices to come.
I'm sure.
Don't know how the battery holds out what the charge is.
So far so good.
It's really, it's pretty stylish.
Although I got in the really ugly color.
I like a yellowish green.
But the back of it is white.
Very much iPod white.
In fact, the same kind of high gloss.
Very chic kind of expensive feel to it.
Really like the fact there's an on-off button on that you can actually turn it on, turn it off.
And yeah, some of the menuing is is very interesting.
And upon recommendation from several people, I have not upgraded the firmware.
I don't know if I can upgrade the firmware with the Mac management software that I was given.
But as a matter, so far so good.
I'm liking it.
And I'm quite impressed with the voice recorder.
There's no settings.
I can't set it to the quality or the bit rate.
I have no idea what the sample rate is.
But it sounds pretty good.
And again, these headphones are a little up and up.
That reminds me.
Thank you all so much for sending me.
And I must have received 50 or 60 emails about my question about headphones,
about the asymmetrical headphone wires on my Sony headphones.
Well, it turns out I must be pretty dense.
I never even thought about what that was really intended for.
It's so that you could put the wire to your other ear behind your neck.
So you have the wire running down one side of your head.
I guess the left-hand side of this case.
So that's the short end of the wire with a short wire with the earbud.
And then the long one goes from the back ear neck in the other ear.
And I guess that would be the secret security kind of look.
And the reason why I never thought about it is because headphones for me
have always been a tool.
It's something that I've used on while recording or while doing radio shows.
And I've always had the symmetrical ones that kind of run right down the center of your chest
and up to each ear.
And it's kind of like it's a tool for me and it's my armor.
It's my uniform when you're doing a radio show.
So I never thought the height that because you don't.
And in fact, why would you?
Anyway, but now I also understand how to use my head set that came with my Sony phone.
Because it has the same asymmetrical headset.
It's funny how you think you're pretty smart and you just can't figure that out.
And then you would have to do with, I figured it had to do with different lengths.
You know, or do it.
And I couldn't figure it out.
There you go.
I don't know, I know, thank you.
It's kind of weird the lights are out in the plane.
Everyone's asleep or they're pretending to be asleep.
And the way it's set up, I don't know if you ever seen one of these.
These sleepers seat classes.
So I'm actually traveling backwards.
My head is towards the nose of the plane.
My feet are pointing towards the tail.
On the way ahead, actually I'm traveling in the right direction.
But if I sit up, then I'm sitting with my back to the nose of the plane.
Actually sitting down or lying down doesn't really all that strange.
Next to me, with the screen in between, which I can pull down if I want.
That would be if I was traveling with the nice lady next to me.
But I'm not so the screen is up.
And she is, as you heard, it's over feet.
Basically, if I could see them are where my head is.
And of course, she has the joy of my feet where her head is.
So it's dark.
The shades are down because let me see right now.
It's 625 AM UK time.
So we probably have about 4 or more hours to fly.
And of course, we're flying towards the light.
So all the window shades are down.
So that might actually I can check it for a second.
No. Oh wow.
The moon is beautiful.
Wow, a couple of stars.
That's actually really nice.
I'm all going to get my glasses.
Because it's blurry.
I want to take a look at the moon.
Oh, man.
It's not really comfortable.
Just turn around.
Look at glasses.
By the way, many people who met me, of course,
the past 10 days have been traveling.
Some of them seem to not only impression that the rose-coloured glass
as I wear are a fashion statement.
While that may be true, they are glasses that I need to see better with.
We are just a beautiful.
I've actually never paid any attention to this.
It's up in this stratosphere.
Of course, there are probably 40, I'd say 42,000 feet.
Just in space, man.
The moon is so bright.
It's beautiful.
Absolutely beautiful.
Okay. You know, pull the shade down now.
There we go.
The rose-coloured glass is where Patricia's idea.
She said, you know, it was actually an inappropriate.
We were still in Belgium.
And there was all kinds of crap going on in my professional life or business life,
I guess, with lawsuits and bogus partnerships and stuff like that.
And yeah, I get depressed pretty easily, I guess.
But I'm not like pros act depressed or anything like that.
Just bummed out.
She said, well, why don't you try some rose-coloured glasses
because the world will look that much nicer.
And you know what?
She's right.
The world does look nice to these glasses.
But at the same time, I really do need them to see it.
And I stop wearing contact lenses.
I used to wear contacts all the time.
And even though they're painted in the ass,
it's pretty easy just to have.
You know, not have to worry about not seeing stuff.
You can't find her glasses, but contacts are painted in the ass.
You know, keeping him in, taking him out,
you have the extended wear, the throwaway kind.
But it wasn't until I was offered a new pair of glasses.
And I tried them out.
And I went flying with them that I said, well, wait a minute.
I'm pretty sure that I see everything just a little bit better
with the glasses as opposed to contact lenses.
And when you're flying, it's pretty important.
So I started to pay attention to the difference.
And it's a big difference reading from computer screens.
It's just contact lenses. It's cool.
You know, the whole idea is all right.
But the technology is, in my mind, it's still not there.
It is absolutely not on par with glasses.
Now, that being said, I would love to have my eyes laser.
Because that seems to be a pretty good fix.
But there's still an issue with FAA pilots license.
If you have your eyes laser, I think there's,
it's either two or five years that they hassle you about your medical
requirements in your license.
Instead of really getting into all that shit and trying to figure it out.
And by the way, in aviation regulations.
No, it's hard for someone to give you a fucking straight answer sometimes.
Because it could be, yes, it could work that way.
In the US on your FAA license, but maybe in other countries,
you'd have to adhere to the joint aviation regulations,
which have different set of rules and standards through that.
I'm wearing the glasses.
And I'm wearing the rose-colored ones to do.
Where was I?
Oh, yeah.
So I watched the movie Kinsey with Liam Neeson on the Inflite Entertainment.
Oh, since we've got that, that was so stupid.
And I don't know if you've heard about this movie,
or if you know what it's about.
I, of course, in my life, had heard about the infamous,
or the famous really Kinsey report.
I had about it for my mom and my dad.
I remember them talking about it, or I'd quared them about it.
And I'd read about it, or heard about it.
And it was this series of studies, and it turns out,
the books that came out in the 50s, about human sexuality.
And it's by this guy named Kinsey, who was a biologist,
who studied insects, and, you know, in a time where,
actually, you know, if the times of change are not really,
I mean, you think about it.
In a time where sexuality was not discussed at all,
you know, there was no sex education in schools.
In fact, sex with or without,
another human being was discouraged, was deemed bad,
could make you go blind.
And what I like about this movie is they certainly did not pin these,
these thoughts that, that were the thought of the day.
They didn't pin them on the church or religion,
although I'm sure that has probably had a lot to do with it.
And it, kind of say, was kind of confusing because
you're looking at this movie, and I'm aware that it's a movie,
and it's a story, right?
It's a bio picture, it's about a real story, a real guy,
and real events that took place that were very well documented.
But it doesn't really translate to movie,
because although this is kind of the perverse part about it,
the movie was, of course, sanitized for my protection,
probably to get it be our rating that it needed to make any money back.
So, yeah, you see, like, you know, some,
some incredibly shocking pictures, and not suitable for children of
human body parts, like penises and vaginas,
and men kissing other men and adultery and debauchery.
But it was done very tastefully, and it was interesting how the
colors of the movie kind of went in and out from black and white to
color again, and I'd have to see it again to see it.
I think that some of the scenes of people having sex,
might have gone black and white at some parts.
I'm not quite sure, but the photography was actually very well done.
It just, like, really, well, I guess the point of the movie,
or the story, if anything, about Dr. Kinsey,
is that no two human beings are alike.
There is no normal when it comes to sexual,
desire, acts, thoughts,
because everyone has different feelings.
Everyone wants different things.
And there was a sub-tone to the movie,
and I would say, let's see if I can articulate this,
basically that if you have a sexual desire,
which more than likely, if it's not straight up
down missionary with your wife or husband sex to procreate,
then that's going to be suppressed,
and it will become an obsession, which, of course,
is what makes people go fucking crazy.
And in thinking about that,
I'd just start to reflect on how weird society really is.
You know, when we think about, you know,
are you really gay or are you straight,
or are you bisexual, or, you know,
if they're a sliding scale, you put a number on it,
where does love come into play in sex?
Can you measure love?
Can you measure sexuality?
Can you measure where you are on that scale?
Very deep stuff to think about,
and then the hypocrisy of how you can,
and this was very well done in the movie,
of showing male breasts and nipples
is completely accepted by society.
But, you know, do I have to mention the Janet Jackson controversy?
You know, Marky Mark can,
I don't know why I came up with Marky Mark.
Maybe because he has nice nipples.
Marky Mark can do that.
What the hell?
Mark will work.
Okay, let's the bread pit, okay?
Let's take bread pit.
But, you know, Janet Jackson
bearing a nipple for a nanosecond,
actually in a performance of art,
it's not only a huge issue,
but punishable by law,
and cost a lot of people a lot of money.
So, somehow all of this ties into what we're doing with this podcasting,
and I feel that there's another, you know,
it's got to be cyclical.
I mean, I think Patricia tells me often about the late 60s and the 70s,
and all the free love and just the vibe
that was going around back in the day.
She said, oh man, you would have loved it.
She says it was so much fun because, you know,
you could hang out with someone and say, hey,
I want to fuck you out.
Okay.
No problem.
Mail, female, whatever.
It was, and it was good.
It was accepted and people liked it.
And then it didn't necessarily have anything to do with drugs,
but that probably made it even that much nicer.
You know, a little bit of wine or a little bit of weed,
whatever.
And I have a feeling that because we've broken through this imaginary boundary
of what you can and can't say on the radio,
because let's face it folks.
This is radio.
It's just, you know, it's just not what we're used to calling radio,
but it is the, the actual,
it is the same act of transmitting sound from one person to the other.
So it's, let's call it radio communications,
even though there's no real radio waves involved,
but the broadcasting part is broadcasting.
And we're now able to do,
to communicate thoughts much better and use words that,
and feelings, and even even just this conversation that we're having now,
although it's kind of one way, but don't worry,
you'll all get back to me.
Either the email or MP3, your feedback or whatever.
You know, this, this is something that just wouldn't have been possible.
Not that long ago.
So I think that we're going to see a lot,
and so as I was listening to Don and Drew,
with their, the last show from San Francisco.
And even though, you know, they kind of joke,
I mean, these are two people who love each other.
You can hear it.
And then they jokes sexual nature to each other all the time.
And it's just really beautiful somehow.
And then Madge, who is, I don't know if Madge is coming or going,
or what she is, but I don't care.
It was, it got caught off, unfortunately,
which was interviewing transsexual hores.
It didn't, in Miami.
And then there's,
Michael Butler, who in his own way.
Of course, you know, he's either rock or roll star.
He's an, he's an American hard break.
And he's got all his little groupy girls talking about that they love him.
And their boobs are, are, are the best boobs.
And they want to show him to him.
And, and then all of a sudden, one girl says,
but I'm a virgin.
I mean, it's just, it's crazy.
And then the list of these biddies.
And the, well, there you go, even the title of their,
of their van, the Sivias, go look it up.
Lute in the Sivias.
It's probably in the, in the, in the law books somewhere.
It's great.
It's great to, and even though it's not about talking about sex or sexuality,
you can tell the, just the liberated feeling of everyone not having to worry about it.
And when it's audio,
you don't feel so conscious about, you know,
when you're saying something or talking about something,
how you look or where people, you know, when,
when, you know, when someone's looking at you basically.
What was that?
Some thought that someone rolled out a bed here.
It was kind of cool.
I can see the lady next to me sleeping.
All right.
She's not that cute.
Let me see how many minutes it's been recording here.
There we are.
Wow, 20 minutes away.
Holy moly, that's pretty cool.
So, I don't, there's not really a point.
So what I'm saying here, but I,
I was just, I couldn't, I couldn't get back to sleep after seeing that movie.
It was just, wow, you know, what happened to us?
And of course, it's more, you know,
did we ever really get out of this,
this thing about, you know, body parts and,
and, and, yeah, just nature.
And how, how twisted it all is that, you know,
now I think many of you were podcasting,
understand why, well, maybe, maybe,
I hope it's as liberating for you as it is for me.
Have you been a broadcaster for half my life,
and, you know, not being able to ever, ever express
myself fully because, you know,
that would be too real, if you, if you're real,
you're going to be indecent.
That's just no two ways about it.
You know, I get email from people saying,
you know, could you please stop with all the afterwards and the asswords?
And, you know, I point, point taken, you know,
sometimes to go overboard, but I just forget, you know,
and, in fact, I find myself catching myself in public places,
you know, so used to being free to be able to talk on the podcast
anyway, I want to, that I'm in restaurants and, you know,
saying shit, fuck, piss, whatever,
and I forget that, not everyone really digs that.
And of course, my voice is sometimes loud,
so I get some interesting looks.
I don't want to, you know, I don't want anyone to get mad at me.
Can you tell it six a.m.?
And I'm kind of rambling.
I'll shut up in a minute.
So anyway, interesting movie,
if you can catch it, do,
but maybe look up the Kinsey report
and look up the history of Dr. Kinsey
and look at some of the results of that report
and see, you know,
maybe draw some conclusions about society.
I certainly need to be a little bit less fucked up.
That's for sure, because it's just weird.
Things that are permissible,
of things that aren't permissible,
and I think that women totally get an unfair shake in this deal.
Certainly in the United States, certainly, certainly.
Okay.
So that was all really.
At a great time in the States,
really enjoyed
hooking up with old friends,
acquaintances,
new friends, possibly with new business partners
and people who are doing exciting things.
And I think that there will be some fun stuff
to report in the coming weeks.
Some fun things that will be happening.
I heard a lot of interesting projects
from many different people.
Remember, no damn announcements out of me.
Thanks, everybody.
I'll talk to you on probably on Monday
with a regular daily source code.
So, from 42,000 feet
with my feet extended out,
it's Adam Curry saying bye-bye.
I'm telling you, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm telling you, I'm sorry.