Delta Sierra Charlie 2-5-5.
We saved!
We've been told what to like and then like it.
In my opinion, if you're over six years of age and you're still getting your music from the radio,
something is desperately wrong with you.
I can only hope that somehow MP3 players and file sharing will destroy FM radio
the way they're destroying record companies.
Then, even though the air will probably never be safe to breathe again,
maybe it will be safer to listen to it.
There are no secrets.
I'll be information you don't even have.
Now I'm Korean.
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying you to the future.
And it's Thursday, my friends October 6, 2005, crisis in the cottage.
Oh yeah, it's been one of those days.
Everything has been gone wrong.
And I'll tell you all about it, of course.
Because in that way you tune in to find out about how even my life can mess up.
Well, of course you do.
And for some of the pod save too.
Which of course today I will get to.
Yes, they was kind of a rant that I went on.
It certainly made me feel good.
And this morning, it kind of happened all over again.
I woke up.
Actually, I could barely get to sleep.
I was so excited about the evolution of the original idea.
We had here yesterday about the pod safe music network and about rights organizations.
Did my homework?
Looked at a couple of things.
Actually, I dreamt a lot last night.
All about Armageddon and pod save music was very, very Jewish to scenario.
It's a little bit later than normal.
I apologize.
It's 10 after two local time here in Gilford, Surrey in the United Kingdom,
where we bring you the daily source code.
When I'm over on this side of the big puddle, I got to kind of keep my eye on the door.
Of the window, actually, to see if the DHL guy is arrived.
And I cannot miss it.
He has a very important package.
He has to transport to Paris.
Curious?
Now, I'll satisfy that in this show.
And hopefully, of course, the Mac will hang in there.
Just another one of the minor crisis you've had today.
Looked at all of that in just a few minutes.
First up, Art Adub, Art from mashuptown.com, gave me a couple of different files to check out today.
His mashups.
He had three options.
And for me, there was really only one.
It was also his first choice.
If you like the who and the Beastie boys, you'll love front and on the route down.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
We're gonna kick it from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death
from death, from death, from death,, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from death, from off which one.
Until came from death, because one died and he survived, he died, he died.
It's not like that.
Turned up loud in the studios on the speakers, you know, that's something that I forgot to talk to you about
back in the day, and remember we talked about how the turn table were started with the relays and Big SLIPMATS.
fader on all of our mixers back in the pirate radio station days and
Funny the Microsoft which would actually run 220 volts through it, which was fucking stupid because you know if you press down too hard on the the metal casing of the
Of the mixer there was a real potential shock hazard and many of this jockey has spilled the beer in the in the console and been electrocuted
No one with horrible results, but we'd have a micro switch in there and when you
Pull the fader up for the microphone a red light. Yeah, a real on-air light would go on outside the studio door and the speakers would cut off
Boy, that's something we got to get back to that again. Oh, there's so many things that we're remembering
So you heard the little hiccups here and there that was crisis number one today
I came in my Mac I'd never turn my machine's off by the way, which I guess there's two schools of thought on that
It's not about the power consumption which by the way
They you know, I got like three machines in the tube amp and the mixer and that all stays on all the time
So it sucks some real power, of course
But I walked in and I could hear my hard drive going
And that's usually a bad sign and
So I
Rebooted and it gave me that little can't find the system can't find the system icon
I was finally able to start it in single user mode and you know went through all the typical things
Man, it took like an hour to boot up after that and I went through some of the things that I would normally do
You know repair file permissions and such and it actually was kind of handy because while it was booting up
I was looking through the Gmail looking at some of the
Some of the comments that had come in and low and behold Bob was there was some ready advice
Mac heads pay attention. I add them. This is Bob host of the never published bomb cast
They'll have been figured out my format which so I haven't started but we've got some good things coming up
This mini cast is to address some of the issues that you discussed with your power book and thinking about getting a new one
Couple of things maybe four items to cover and less than two minutes if possible
And they should hold you over for a while now
I'm not sure which 12 inch power book you have
But I have a 12 inch 1.33 gigahertz hold on hold on Bob
I have a
month 17 inches baby your hurts with 768 megs around now since I bought that about a year ago
They have upgraded the power book 12 inch
One time it's very soft upgrade because it's a 1.5 gigahertz and it has 512 standard mine had 256
Mears is probably older than that. I would guess by what you've said on your show
So I'm assuming that you get something around a one gigahertz
Are you gonna upgrade? Yeah, you should upgrade you probably want to do one and here's what we know
We know that there's going to be a new version of power books staying in a G4 line
They were never able to get the G5 small enough and cool enough to put it into a power book
But moving right along we also know that apples ramping up to put Intel machines out and where they're slow
Where they've been slow to release the the performing machines has been in the power book line
We don't expect dibooks to get a G5 what you expect the power books to have something similar
So my guess is the first Intel release will be power books
And that means that if you buy that if you wait for that then it is sure probably we're getting it next
Then you're signing up to be apples beta tester
Dude, I have been beta testing for apples since since the what was that luggable thing the apple portable
100 was that it I had one of those I had the one
40 series the one 70 series the one 80 or 190 the duo docked to 30 C
The apple to the apple to x the top of the apple to fx
The Mac
Mac plus Mac ED
Mac 512k
You know floppy disk based I've had
Remember the black power books. I've had every single one I am a lifetime beta tester
There's going to be a bunch of applications that don't quite work and and you know the ones are going to take the hardest hit or always the fringe guys guys
Like audio hijack pro. They're not mainstream and you know we hope that there's stuff works
But we rely on it and so it sucks when you get an image seen it just doesn't work
All on let me just say something. I'm pretty sure it won't
I'm pretty sure audio hijack pro won't work in
Future versions at least it won't work the way it's working today because it's way too easy to copy
To directly copy music from your iTunes and if you play an iTunes
If you hijack your iTunes and you play it and you record it you can record
Basically music that you purchase on the iTunes music store. I have a feeling that functionality is not going to be available pretty soon
Which is a major freaking bummer
And hopefully only that stream will be cut off because I use audio hijack pro on the other machine here to actually
Actually record in addition to that
You become their beta tester and you can't afford to do that with your main stream machine the machine that you're living on so
We do know that there are new power books coming in the G4 line
It'll probably be another pretty wimpy upgrade, but I would wait for that upgrade before you buy your new power book
And then I'd snap one up and expect to ride the storm out until the second generation Intel pieces come out
a couple of other things mac and end.com says that the Apple is planning a special media event on October 12
It's an invite only event
It's one day after the announced their financial results for the fourth quarter. It's 10 a.m. October 12 the California theater in San Jose
And it's right after another special event in the very same theater where they introduced iPod nano
iTunes 5 in the Motorola rocker phone
Early last month and according to one report the invitation shows close theater curtains with the words one more thing
written on top so they're definitely going to release something. I wouldn't be surprised if
The new line of power books is in that list. So well now the the jury's kind of odd on that. I've received several messages of
Who sent me that email
Oh, that's second. I got an email from
a couple of people forwarded me a Yahoo email
Paul
About this special event some people think it's going to be
New line of power books and
Some people think it's going to be the video iPod. I got to tell you. I don't believe in it
I don't think Steve Jobs is going to do a video. I could be wrong of course, but I
Had this conversation with him and someone brought up the video iPod and and just to look on his face
He went like
Video iPod he said makes no sense. You know, what's the earphones of a video
When he said that
I was pretty sure that wasn't going to happen. So I'm I'm betting on the new power books. So you may want to wait for that
In addition to that you were talking about moving everything over
Well believe it or not 10.4 in the utilities folder has a set up slash migration assistant
And basically if you're running tiger
The set up assistant runs immediately after you install the macOS
So when you boot the machine you do have the option to use this migration assistant
Just connect both computers on your network or by firewire
And you'll be able to transfer all your data and it'll act like it had always been on that new machine
Before you do that though you want to clean up your hard drive and here's where you're having some problems
One rule of thumb on your boot drive is to make sure that you keep 10% of that drive free for
Disco operations if you've got a 40 gigabyte hard drive and you've got 39 gigabytes on it
You're asking for trouble and you know, I'm I'm going to stop
I'm going to stop does not that it is an interesting but
Feeling that none mac users will not be digging. It's up. I'll put the file up up
That's DHL Christ I got to explain to you why DHL is here. I'm going to pause this for two seconds. I'll be right back
Right I think the word for today is discombobulated
I'll come back to Bob in a second with his mac fix it to cast oh, man
So remember I told you that I had arranged for a special weekend for Patricia and her sister in Paris
where they would be invited to go watch the
Fall Chanel fashion show. Well, that's this weekend actually it's tomorrow
Tomorrow is the show and then they're gonna stay Saturday and hang out in Paris and then come back Sunday
So she left this morning. She left the house at 10 o'clock and really there's only a couple you know when I go on a trip
The only things I need are my phone my my power book increasingly less need the power book
Credit card passport, you know, that's pretty much all you need everything else is just baggage
So for Patricia it's her phone it's a credit card you know some cash of course for taking the cab from charred to go
To the hotel and and her heart medication and so she was off at 10 o'clock
After I took Christina to school and then I got a frantic text message SMS from the plane
I forgot my medication oh, man
I'm like okay, well, of course, you know my wheel started churning. Well, this is possible
I knew that she'd taken her medication this morning so she really doesn't need anything until tomorrow morning
But first I was a little worried you know if she's on the plane and she you know how you can just like
You know get a start-up. Oh my god, you know that feeling when you forgot something that goes through your whole chest and your whole body and your shoulders and your neck
He just feel horrible and you can even start to
Perspire
So I had these horrible visions of that happening to her and her not having her emergency pill over there
So I immediately called DHL
Actually, I normally would use FedEx, but FedEx doesn't have the same type of FedEx really isn't as good
I don't think for international European international delivery and they have a next morning next day before 9 a.m. guaranteed service
So got a great great person to DHL in the line
Explain the situation she said well we can get it there before 9 a.m. She said would you like a quote on that and I said yeah
Well, yeah, you know 102 pounds. I said oh let me think for a second if it's worth it
So that's why you know as waiting for the DHL guy and at the same time hoping that Patricia wasn't too freaked out on the flight
She's fine
And so now it's also all the medication. It's on its way with my hero the DHL man
So that was one of the crises that was that has delayed the show today and as I said the other one was the power book and you hear it's still skipping
Bob really put together a great cast. I'll have to get the full audio of this up online still another two and a half minutes of it
um
And he has you know, there's all kinds of tips that he has and I went through everything meticulously
I think my drive is just shot and I have like 20% of free space and I don't know what's going on and also this this
The book is just had it, you know
I've said this before you know the life of a power book. It's a couple of years and whenever there's problems you close it
Treat it like an etchisket shake it a little bit open it up it works and then at a certain point, you know
Who knows and then it it becomes a
video server for your television in the living
Something else about the skipping because of course
Lots of people are sending in comments
Hadn't spoken to cast blaster Mike for a couple of weeks and he came back
He was out he spent a couple of days in like a log cabin and
Completely reprogrammed cast blaster. I mean completely
And he's working on several versions at the same time one which of course will be for me because
I really want to use the product, but what what's exciting is he is now
And I'm still not he did did it down at the actual frame level of the MP3 players because the problem one of the big problems is the way that quick time buffers
The audio and Windows media player also has issues with that
Sorry
So he went down to the frame level of the MP3 files and and he is now created recreated cast blaster with the mix
Happening entirely in software
Zero latency
Zero freaking latency so you can use this thing and the sound is
Just phenomenal
Now doesn't it still doesn't have all the the control bits that I need to be effectively be able to use it
Just in the way I work that's my problem not the not the software's problem
So I'm very very excited about about what I saw and there is also no no delay on
And no
No delay in no skipping
Using the the new cast blaster so it's still I think it's beta beta or alpha beta alpha beta
I don't think it's been released to the beta group yet, but it's called a beta and was given to me
And I love it and hopefully we're gonna be able to talk about that a bit more in the very near future. What are we at now? Oh my goodness
Special job cast coming up in the daily source code today if you're looking to work with the with us and you got some skills stay tuned
Stay tuned hey, what a handsome speckfick reviews
Yeah, you do for reviews of speculative fiction that science fiction fantasy and horror
Check out the rev up review at
www.revupreview.co.uk
Thanks the rev up review covers books magazines films TV and audio and anything else that takes the rev master's fancy rev master
Who's this rev master? Oh, he's just this bloke, you know anyway
Probably some frustrating writer, I expect well he does read an episode of a short story on each show
See what did I say just check it out will you?
www.revupreview.co.uk
The world's first Marilyn Monroe podcast join me for my bi-weekly show where I discuss Marilyn collectibles her life career
I even play Marilyn inspired music that I bet you've never heard
And if she did I see mine be alive
Yeah
I've been a Maryland fan and collector for over 15 years and I'll try to answer any questions
that listeners may have about this incredible woman.
More than 40 years after her death, she is arguably more popular today than during her
own lifetime.
So come and find out why at www.mymeralyn.ca or look for me in iTunes.
But don't just take my word for it, what do you think of the show?
I've been subscribed to that for quite a while and I'm going to make some
I think it is sent off a new promo.
Prohomers are welcome.
Always submit at podshow.com, send them in feedback, adamantcurry.com, please if you can, put
an MP3 up on a server and just send me the link to it and try to do some work on those
ID3 tags.
It really makes it a lot easier for me.
Got a lot of feedback, of course, based on yesterday's discussion and now I've had at least
three people email me saying, hey, you know,
this note on inepotter.org hasn't been updated since August, you know, can I take over
the note and as I might my standard response, please email the note manager, copy me, ask
him, you know, what is it, his or her intentions are and we'll take it from there.
And that's pretty cool because the conversation and I've seen it in the stats too, really
did send people searching, I guess everyone's perusing through the entire director to
see if they can find any horrible podcast that I don't listed and I got a great email
yesterday from the Netherlands, people have listened to the daily source code, what are we
episode, 255, 255 episodes, 255, probably somewhere around episode 30, I think I introduced
mode zones, banned from the Netherlands who independent, they produce all their stuff in their
attic, I think it's two brothers, they produce it on a Mac with Pro Tools and just it's
something about the vibe these guys have, it's something about, you know, just the song,
I just really like them, they also played at the North Sea Jazz Festival, by the way,
LeCivies, Bitties are applying to to perform there, of course, going to use as many
back channels as possible to try and get them in. So I got an email from your from the Netherlands
and you said, hey Adam, skinny, that's the, uh, one half of my Jones sent off, uh, hold on a second.
Have no one, that's not. I went too fast for me.
Skinny, uh, uh, Mo Jones has a new record coming out, it's titled My World and Skinny wanted you to have
the premiere of the first track off of the record, always the same, Mo Jones on the source code.
Everything notices in the school, everything's sacred, it's will, everything's safe,
and it's will, everything's life.
Everything's rich, it's will, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's
buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's
buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's
buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buy
everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyingable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's buyable, everything's boughtable, everything's buyable, everything's
It's not the ever-changes, it's always the same
It's always the story
Nothing ever changed
People who don't worry about things
They don't worry about things
Yunzie!
From the new CD My World
Always the same
It'sפit
It's their own label
their own songs and permission to play it loving it and got to get these guys listed on the
pod safe music network. I know I'm gonna have to plug it again music.podshow.com, really, really
like that. Did I see Steve Gilmour's head poppin along? He's a big fan of Mod Jones. So, um, oh man,
I hope I can hook up with these guys pretty soon. They are so good live. They bring like a
rhumba box and a couple of the oil drums and a guitar and an armonica and they're and
they're good to go. Another crisis that happened today, uh, as they say, when it rains it pours,
so I was already late with the source code. As you know, uh, we are a simulcasting, uh, the pod squad
on uh, serious channel 103, which is right next to Howard Stern's channel. So, he's not there yet.
Welcome those of you, uh, just channel surfing. Um, and so the way that works is, uh, pww fenton from
digital flots and fine podcast. Uh, he manages all of that and uh, and this, it's quite a bit
actually just collecting all the pieces because they're all sent in the evening before such as my
show the day of, but I get up a little bit earlier because I mean, the UK. And, um, and so I emailed
them saying, you know, dude, here's what's going on, the power book Patricia's Heart Medicine,
I'm a little bit late, so don't freak out, it's coming. And in here back from them, I get a
a text message and he was in a car crash last night. Now, in nothing serious, he's okay. He's a
little bit sore, um, he got rear-ended, which normally is really nice. And, uh, I said to my
immediately, the pw, two words, man, whip, lash. Maybe that's one word. I said, we're sitting on a
cold mind by brother, but now his car won't function and wouldn't start and his ISP, which is
a roadrunner, so that's a pretty respectable ISP. And he's one of the super duper accounts,
was completely down. Uh, and so, you know, we're late and just, you know, I was like,
what are we going to do? And so I came up with a genius solution. I said, look, you got a
power book there, right? Because, you know, yes, to put all the shows together and then has to be
converted to the satellite MP2 file, whatever, and then uploaded to their server. I said, you got a
Wi-Fi power book and you got one of those thumb drive, one of those USB one, you know, like 500
megabyte drives, he says, yeah, so, well, off you go, in a cab, to Starbucks, and uh, download the shows,
come back, stick the drive into your system at home, do the stuff, and then go back and upload it.
So, thank God for Starbucks. Remember those days when I used to stand here,
bitching and moaning about Starbucks, and then have to go to Starbucks and upload it before
there was a bandwidth in the cottage? Oh my goodness. Lots of great comments coming in from
people about podcasting and pod safe music. Next, five or six minutes or so, I want to talk
about it and want to tell you a little bit more about my idea for, um, for the pod safe music network.
I think, uh, think you're going to enjoy it. Oh, man. Christo, mighty. There you go. I think that
today is the day that I buy a new power book. Uh, I now have the spinning beach ball of death.
After I asked it to advance to the next file. Oh, man. It sucks so bad.
Piece of shit. Sorry about that. Try to take my composure there.
One to comment on a couple of things that's been going on lately. One is, thank you very much.
Um, getting up early in the morning and getting your, uh, your pod cast, the daily source code before
I go to work. I'm on the road all the time. It's been great. So thank you for that. Uh, it's one
less time I need to think up during the day. You might say, uh, the other thing is I wanted to kind of
voice a just a listeners kind of point of view for, uh, for, um, this whole idea of the music industry and
what's happening. You know, I kind of gave up with music. Um, and I just subscribe to Yahoo,
make music for, you know, a yearly account for what 50, 60 bucks a year plus Rhapsody. I had that for a while.
And I just kind of gave up with it. And, um, I have X and satellite and that was kind of nice.
But, uh, pod casting is done for me. Something that I think a lot of other people that
listen to pod cast, um, it's given me kind of an appreciation again for music. And I'll give you an
example, uh, Rob Costlow. I guess it was this name. I'm, I hope I got it right.
One of the, that was just beautiful piano playing. Now, I'm kind of conservative in my mother-in-law's
very conservative. And she heard that. And right away, she said, who is this? Who is this? And boy,
it is so refreshing. I mean, I, I hate to use these words because it is a paradigm shift. It really
is a thinking because a lot of the stuff that's going on right now isn't so much the monetization
right now. But it's building a relationship. I mean, pretty soon, these artists are going to have
a following. And, um, I'm going to want to give them money because I want to know what they're doing.
And where they're going. And I feel like as a, as somebody who's just in the very beginning stages
of this, that as they grow as an artist, they're going to, yeah, I get to be important in their life.
And, um, I think that's what's going on with podcasting. It's, it's, there's a, you know, a thousand
podcasters out there. But what is doing is it's raising the level of, um, what's the, what's
the best way of saying it? Um, it's transforming a relationship that you can have with the, with the, with
the artist. I mean, you can really talk to an artist in a way that you couldn't talk to. Even if you
don't, you know, it just by sitting in email to somebody or just knowing how, how cool it was to,
to get somebody into the beginning stages and be recognized. And you were there for them.
I mean, I think this is the greatest thing going on right now. And pretty soon, you know, this
way, I don't, I don't care anymore about the old stuff. I just don't care. It's not that important to
me anymore because there's so many good people out there that all they have to do is start.
And, um, man, I'm looking for the, for the next beetles out there. I'm looking for the next guy
that's just going to say, hey, you know, this is how I got started. And, uh, me, Mark, I was listening
to him in the beginning and, uh, follow their career. And, uh, you know, at old radios dead,
old old radio, uh, CD, the record company said, got to change and get with the program here,
because I'm just Joe average, but Joe average is starting to get a little tired of the old way of doing
things. And I'll find this stuff I want to listen to. And, uh, so, so that's my two cents. It's just,
um, you know, you don't have to broadcast or anything. I just want to tell you how I feel because
this has made a change in my life, uh, not just the music, but all the, the smart people out there
that are podcasting and the funny stuff. I mean, uh, if once people get in the habit of it,
I can never see going back to, to old, old media again. So, uh, that's it. I'll talk
you later. Thanks again for putting your podcast early in the morning. It's, it's, uh, it's, uh,
it really is cool getting on that damn freeway. And it's, uh, parking lot out there and, and L.A.
and being able to, you know, listen to some fun stuff, you know, with no commercials. Man, that's great.
So, thanks. Mark, right on, man. Uh, I really wanted to broadcast this because that's exactly
the voice that, that I love hearing is when, um, Joe average, as you say, and, uh, look at this,
look what happened, man. You're listening to my show on your commute, and then I don't know
exactly what you recorded this on, uh, doesn't really matter. Um, it came in as a wave file.
Uh, so probably some, maybe it was on your, um, none of your iPod, obviously, but on, um,
on some portable device, maybe your phone or something like that. If this is fantastic. You're
absolutely right. Absolutely right. I'm loving it. It was worth all the hassle to get to that
wasn't it? So, I had some more thoughts about, uh, the pod safe music network, and how,
remember we talked about, um, um, about the, the performers and the people who make a song,
which is the author composer, this is what I feel by the way, author composer, uh, producer,
and then the musicians. And, um, ask a BMI, if you're a member of either, and I went through
these sites, I've done a lot of research. I got another beach ball on my Mac by the way. Steve,
Steve Jobs sent me a new Mac. Now, please, please, crying. It's a hand-pring my work, man.
Um, what was I saying? Okay. Um, so of course it would be great as we start to monetize, not all,
but, you know, some pod casserole monetize, and I think it's only, we discussed this. I think it's
only fair that if you use someone's music, and that is a part of your product, um, that they should
be compensated for that. Now, the, here's, is what's, and here's what I found out was very interesting
about, uh, the way Ask Cap and BMI work. They, uh, talk about a, uh, basically a defined or a finite,
pool of money that can be brought in because, and that's it really hit me, there's only a certain
number of radio stations. There's only X amount of frequencies. There is no growth. The only growth
can be in more listeners, more revenue. Well, if we know anything, we know that it's exactly
the opposite. Radio revenue is going down. Listener ship is going down. Now, let's look at pod
casting. Pod casting is unlimited. So, maybe we have 9,000 podcasters today. Why wouldn't
that be 90,000 in a few years from now? And if every single one of them is donating just a little bit,
just a little piece, not like Ask Cap and BMI have or actually BMI has, uh, has a specific podcast
license. And it's so complicated. It's like a minimum of $288 a year. And then you have to,
you know, you have to track everything. And then they'll come at audit you. And then you have to,
say, okay, how, you know, what percentage of, it's like 1.75% of your growth revenue,
you know, but then you can subtract 15% for agency commission. It's just, it's, oh, man. And,
and if you get played on the real radio quote, real radio, there's a whole, the, the distribution
of money is even fuzzy. You know, it's like you get, if you have a hit record, then you get a
super hit bonus and you get extra payout, you know, because they can't, they do have one system that,
that most, most people are not subscribing to, called BDS and BDS listens. It's a computer
program that listens to radio stations and can detect based upon waveform, basically what's
song is being played. So I'm not going to lay the whole thing out right now, but first of all,
I have a name for it's called the Podsafe Music Rights Organization or a nice acronym Pro. I kind of
like that. Podsafe Music Rights Organization. And it would of course be a nonprofit. And I have a
way, and I don't want to delve into all that right now, but I have come up with a way that anyone
who is podcasting can use Podsafe Music. We can do that already through the Podsafe Music
Network, but also each time you use a Podsafe song, the artist will get paid, not just the
artist, but those four categories, right? And I'm seeing it as kind of like an equal four-way split
with the, the, the, the vocalist and musicians, they're divving up their split. And that may not
be the right way to do it yet, but I'm, I'm pretty confident that it's, the fairest thing is
author composer producer and performers because there are organizations throughout the world for
every single one of those groups. So if we could have it all in one and the Podsafe Music Network,
and let's just say that I haven't figured out, I haven't figured, and you wouldn't even have to
report back anymore. You wouldn't have to report into the system because the BDS sound system,
well, you know, that's easy. We know how to analyze wave files. We deal with it every single day.
And we can do a much more accurate count. So we can actually distribute the money, like I almost
aren't like a certainly a monthly, probably a weekly, even a daily basis. And of course,
it all do it through PayPal and, you know, we'd be very, very online about it. And here comes the
kicker. This is the part I love. No, wait a minute. No, no, no, I'm going to tell you about the
part I love in a second. First, let's talk about reporting for a second because another faux
pot has taken place in my friends. Now, let's see if we can get, uh, of course not. Of course,
it's not going to play. It's just going to sit there and give me a spinning beach ball. Hold on. I need to
kick something! Hey Adam, it's Derek Miller from the Penn Machine Podcast in Vancouver, Canada
at podcast.pen machine.com. I was listening to your Delta CR Charlie number 253,
where you were talking about podcasters, about 95% of the mom and pod save music network,
giving credit to the pod save music they're using. I hate to be a nag, but Adam, you're in the
5% because back on daily source code number 235, September 5th, where you did the job cast from
podshow headquarters. Well, the only had one song on that pod cast. It was mine. It's called
Cold Cloud that a nice pack. Well, you didn't list it on this pod save music network and you didn't
put it in your show notes. So, you know, it could hurt a little. You did, but I'm okay now. You know,
it's been a month that I've recovered. Anyway, just so you know, my pod cast is original pod save
instrumentals that podcasters can use them have for theme songs and background music and
well, and people that just listen to it if they like. So, once again, it's at podcast.pen machine.com.
Give it a listen. You can also get it searching for Derek D.E.R. E.K. on the pod save music network.
Grab some of the music. Use it on your show. I'd love that. Anyway, go ahead to listen to the source
code and I'll check you later. Derek, man, I'm so sorry. I suck. But now there you go. It just shows
how hard it is. I reported it today, put in episode 235 and you're probably receiving an automatic
email from the pod save music network that I played it. I'm sorry, man. I really do. I love the tunes,
obviously, but it was because of the job cast. Oh, maybe I should do that now. We've had so many
interruptions. Again, the word is discombobulated. Let me play one more thing about the pod save music
network. Then I'll do the job cast at the very end of the show. Hello, Adam. This is Franklin
McMahon from MediaArtist Secrets. The pod cast for the creator professional at mediaartist.com.
And I have a pod safe music question for you. I just launched podmodel.com. It's an enhanced
pod cast for iTunes and the nano and iPod photo. Basically, it's pictures of my model and fashion
photography. And as I was developing, I was thinking, what a perfect place to put in pod safe music,
you know, for the background while viewing the images. And the problem is I didn't know all the
places yet where my shows are going to go. For example, my MediaArtist Secrets, that show is available
on CD and computer arts magazine. Now there's a special page on the CD interface and all. And now
that's something I didn't envision when I started the show early this year. It's a commercial
venture and you know, they're selling magazines. So, I know the thing I might want to do down the
road is sell a CD of podcasts, perhaps episodes that are no longer available or, you know,
things like that. Anyway, one of the thoughts, I look at anything I do as content and content
goes many different places over time. Places I haven't even thought of yet and places we all haven't
thought of yet. And I just think we need to start looking beyond iTunes and iPods to see, you know,
what the next step is, it would suck to have to go back and edit out pod safe music from these
things this content or, or is it safe? I don't know. This is just something I'm thinking about
over the next several years. We'll be able to download a received podcast in many, many, many new ways
and I'm just wondering if pod safe music can legally come along for the ride. So, we may not have
all the answers now, but I want to write. Of course. Of course, it stops right in the middle.
So, very good point there. So, that's what Pro would do. The pod safe music writes organization
would do exactly that. We would help you license for CD ROMs, for CD's, for any other type of
distribution. And if the radio industry wants to play any pod safe music, by the way, they're doing
it already. Just so you know, I mean, I know for a fact that some radio stations have definitely
played pod safe music because they dig it obviously and there's nothing against that, but hey,
hold on a second. Just like we have to play by your rules, you have to play by our rules. And I
predict that because the growth potential of pod casting is unlimited by frequency or by time
that the total number of, let's just call them spins, right? We agreed on that previously.
The total number of spins of a pod safe song will far outweigh what is being played on the radio.
Think about it. Think about how incredibly powerful that is. And guess what? That's when
everybody comes knocking on our door and when we get to turn the tables and where we get to
basically call the shots. So I'm really excited. And you know what? We don't need, go to Manhattan,
go to BMI's, they have the BMI has beautiful offices, beautiful building. I don't think I've been
I think I've been asked cap one, same deal. Lots of people work there and that's all in the,
because it's a non-profit, but they got really nice company cars and they may even have a company
jet for all I know. And they've got full time people sitting down the basement speculating with the cash
and would be very simple for us. Every week, we look at the money that's to be distributed.
And that's the part that I just want to hold back on before. I'm not quite ready to
talk about that yet. We'll say a no-dam announcements rule on that for the, for the time being.
And then we look at the number of spins and then everybody gets a percentage done.
It just, it all clicked into my head. It was completely clear to me.
So I'm really excited. We could run it with two people. Two people could run it. Everything else is
online. You do the same thing you do with those guys. You have to send off 30 bucks to the
copyright office. But you know, by the way, by the minute you lift your pen from paper,
you already own the copyright just so you know. Anyway, all that stuff to come, I'm going to go
throw this piece of shit out the window this Mac. I'm so angry about that today. I can't even
play the closing, the closing tune. I'm just sitting here looking at the goddamn beach ball. And I
tune to keep's popping up. I don't know what's going on. All right, everybody. I'll be back tomorrow.
We'll do a thank God it's Friday. It shouldn't take care now. Bye.