This is the daily source code, episode 186.
This is the daily source code coming from San Francisco.
Oh boy, lots of new stuff in the setup here.
First of all, I have new headphones.
Not like in the headphones, that much has to do with the setup there.
And I'm messing around with Audio Hygiene Pro.
Can you tell?
The power of the audio is coming.
Today is Sunday.
It is the 20 or the 29th of May 2005 actually according to my watch.
You know what?
It will actually sound better if I have the microphone clip done.
What do you say?
Oh yes.
This is what happens when you do podcasts at quarter to 12, almost midnight.
That's okay.
Got some promos, got some pod save music, got a mashup and some stuff to talk about.
Line up on the day's source code.
Okay, to start right off, I'm having a real time monitoring what I'm doing.
Went to the Apple Store in Los Angeles, which is, I forget even what the address is.
They're just giving that shit away at the Apple Store unbelievable.
The lines.
There's so many people buying stuff.
It's just outrageous.
And I needed new iPod headphones for my iPod obviously, which I also use in the eye river.
And I decided to go for what they call the in-ear phone.
And the in-ear stuff.
I don't know.
But it's like, unless you really jam it into your ear, it just doesn't sound right.
It sounds like really light and kind of tinny.
Maybe just don't have the right ears for this stuff.
Maybe, that's the problem.
I'm not liking it too much.
I'm almost ready to find different set of headphones to use.
Never, never you matter.
Welcome everybody.
This is the daily source code.
My name is Adam Curry.
I am at the Hotel Vitale, which is a brand new hotel.
They opened up, I think, just two months ago.
Vitale is spilled, spilled Victor, India, Tango, Alpha, Lima, Echo.
It's another one of those wood and metal and glass kind of,
It's kind of a, it's obviously contemporary.
It's a rather modern hotel.
Not bad though.
I like it.
We just spent the past three days in the Beverly Hills hotel
in Beverly Hills obviously in California.
And let me say something.
I'm not staying there again.
Memo to self.
No more staying at the Beverly Hills hotel.
Now, is it a beautifully decorated, you know,
there's my wires or scraping against my microphone.
I'm on the live microphone as you can tell.
I don't have the big mic with me.
Is it a beautiful hotel that has impeccable service?
Does it have great food?
Yes, yes, yes, to all of the above.
Does it have consistent internet connectivity?
No.
It seemed like every evening.
And it usually kicked in around,
I'd have to say around 9 p.m.
The bandwidth was just fucking crushed.
There was nothing left.
Nothing worked.
It was dripping in at like 1 or 2k a second and forget uploads.
It was just, it was shit.
And so I called around engineering.
And of course, the outsourced all of this.
So it couldn't get anyone on the phone.
No, it could help.
And it was every single day.
It was the same thing.
It was almost as if someone had like some huge, you know,
install of limewire or or kaza or god knows what.
And it was just turning on the porn pipe.
And just leaving it for hours and hours and hours.
And I tried to explain to them.
I said, look, this is the same.
It's actually worse.
But let me just give you an analogy.
The same as if you had no hot water.
You know, can I live without it?
Yeah, I can live without hot water.
But do I want to live without hot water?
No.
That's one of the basic essentials of a hotel.
So, you know, until they can absolutely guarantee me that it's going to work.
And by the way, there's no real danger.
I'm going to go back to the Beverly Hills hotel.
The reason we checked in is because we've been on the road.
And we've been in real douchebag, fleebag, dives of hotels.
Which just isn't entirely true.
Because the network connection was good.
And that's really all I want.
I just want a television.
And that's really just for background for loneliness.
Please make sure it has spanked television.
And I want my internet connection.
You know, that's all I want.
And so, if the vitale hotel, it's nice.
They have a wired connection.
They give you a nice ethernet jack.
And on every other floor, they also have a wireless connection.
Which I haven't tried yet.
And see, they have one.
Let me just check.
I'll take a look at my thing here.
Hotel vitale 7 floor access.
Okay.
So, they have one on my floor, actually.
And it's great.
It's given me great throughput.
And, you know, I could really care less about the hotel to be quite honest.
Oh, and hey, go heat.
You know, now that my kind of my second home is South Beach,
where we're on less, we're on a vacation.
And the Miami Heat are in the playoffs.
And this is the playoffs.
I guess the playoffs.
Or is this the Eastern Conference?
Whatever it is.
The kick-and-ass.
10 points.
They won today.
And I'm not a big sports fan.
And really, I get my sports from the skinny on sports.
And I live it vicariously through season ticket holders on Bloom.
And let's roll out a mashup right now.
This is a pretty cool one that I found.
Yeah, you recognize that.
You recognize that the Kira song anywhere, right?
This is a little different though, it's from DJ Tripp.
Dr. Dre versus the champs.
Then the next to P-Li.
And I'll get everybody.
You know the way to come back, ball, you beat the ball.
Lock the ball.
The foot's up in the air.
What an air.
Yeah.
Got no time to fight them all.
You're burning me dumb.
Deep deep deep.
Deep deep.
Deep deep dead.
Break off the kill and release a C.P.G.
Pick up the beach right door and get ready
Who's the real rolling on door?
Are you crazy looking?
What?
Brains who didn't come to sin the night
We're docking the back sip and don't ya?
Cliping all the ants to fit through the water
Calm then you don't be king or woman
Sops and slops to the website
Gotta pour your love
Scallop on your butt
Gotta pour your king or pro
I'm gonna ruin the might better
Than the city glow
With my jeans on
And my jeans roll
Get my drink on
And my smoke on
And go home with
Some of the folks on
They're like a stone
But it's too short for long
Come to real
The next episode of the song
Play
We gon' break it till the wheels fall
Roll
Hold up
Play
We're my secret
I can't control
Take up
C.P.
I'll be ready for the next episode
Hey
That's won't be long
For tea
The next episode of the song
A person who ineschin Logan
to put like exhaust corrosion on it.
So it really looked like something
that somebody wrote around like a hot rod.
If you look at Han Solo, he's a bootlegger.
You know, he is the band.
And the Death Star is a biggest smokey cruiser of the mall.
Sports editor Josh Barnett on where fans are with the Phillies.
We sort of passed the in the stages of grief, if you will.
We're really into the anger stage in a significant way right now.
And Ronnie Polleneski on her radical idea for Mother's Day fundraising.
I am all for racing for a cure.
I'll walk for a cure.
I'll do anything for a cure, but not on Mother's Day.
Unless it's nothing for a cure.
You'll also hear music you've never heard before by local bands and artists come in the town.
What you'll never hear on Philly feed is podcasting from an elevator
and sound seen from a cockpit of a small plane.
We think you have those areas completely covered.
So we're going to stick to what we do best.
A fun, informative, entertaining podcast.
This shockfully attitude.
To download Philly feed, go to www.phillyfeed.com.
Philly feed.
It's the People Paper Podcast.
Very cool.
Philly.
I've been to Philly before when I was going to school in West Virginia.
It was, oh, what was her name?
She's a great girl.
She was really sweet.
E.D.
E.D. was her name.
And she was from Philadelphia.
And one point, she got me so nuts.
She said, you know what?
Let's drive from West Virginia to Philadelphia and back.
And one night, we did this.
To go see the Flyers play.
That was the one and only hockey game I've ever seen in my life.
And quite honestly, I was so tired from driving
at a Chevy Nova at the time.
Two doors Chevy.
No, wait.
Four doors Chevy Nova.
I'm sorry.
Straight six Chevy Nova.
And I was like an E.D. too.
So probably that's why I didn't pay much attention to the, to the game.
Never got anything going on with her though.
But Philadelphia.
Yeah, nice time.
Definitely.
Thanks for the promo guys.
Really appreciate it.
See what else to have on my notes here.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, I went to the Apple Store because I needed to edit some video.
And my drive, I've been basically nursing and nurturing my G4 along
on about anywhere from one to two gigs left of drive space.
And I've tried to delete stuff.
You know, and really, it's my iTunes musical libraries.
Really what it is.
And then you just take into account all the applications and stuff.
And what is the, what's the total drive size of this puppy?
It's probably what like 50, 60 gigs I think is what,
what this G4 has built in.
So I said, you know, since I'm going to do some editing.
I need do some importing, which would take me well over the gig I had.
Left, I bought myself a little fire wire drive.
This is the fire light smart disk.
It's really thin.
It looks like it looks.
It's probably about the size that the communicators are on Star Trek.
And it has actually some similar lights.
Really nice power through the fire wire cord itself.
And it's got a hundred gigabytes on it.
So that's just perfect.
And I'm storing shit on that.
And it's actually something I'm just carry with me.
And it's not really a real chore to plug that in.
You know, so I can basically use some space.
We'll keep the space available for podcasts.
I was able to free up some space because while I was at it,
I bought Tiger, which is the new version of OS 10,
which is what is it.
I guess I should take a look at that here.
I'll say about this Mac.
It'll tell me I guess.
Oops.
There we go.
10.4.
Okay.
That's what it is.
Nice.
Very interesting.
It seems a little snappier than 10.3.
So that's good.
I like these.
Was it a call?
It's Spotlight.
Searchlight.
What does it call?
Here.
What was this thing called?
Hold on.
Let me just check.
Spotlight.
So you basically, you type in a couple words.
And it, I don't know if it's free.
It must do some pre-indexing.
But then it goes through your entire drive through your email through PDFs.
Into any file.
And it brings up a list of options categorized by file type that you can then select.
So it's a hell of a lot better than navigating through file folder structures.
I like that.
Also the Automator.
Man.
The Automator is.
It's kind of like an abstraction of Apple script.
So if, of course, I know a little bit about Apple script having,
use it to create the iPod or the original iPod or.
Um, it basically has all the commands that you could script in Apple script for applications,
kind of as a set and ready to go block.
And you can build up a workflow.
So within five minutes.
And this impressed the shit out of me.
Within five minutes, I was able to create an application.
We double click on it.
It starts recording.
It brings up a dialogue box that says, click stop when you're done.
So when you're done talking and I just did practice.
This for this test application did it into the built-in microphone on the G4 power book.
You hit stop.
It then saves it.
Renames it.
So of course, I did like daily source code test.
And then it will put a date stamp behind it.
Turns it into an MP3 and FTP did right up to the server.
It was like a built it like a five minutes.
I created a podcast application.
It was really fucking cool.
So I'm going to delve into that a little bit more like that.
The widgets are okay.
I mean, I've been using widgets.
Ever since widgets first came out, which were not done by Apple.
So yeah.
All right.
I don't know if I find great use for them.
It's kind of like a dashboard.
It's an overlay that flies over.
What do you have?
What do we have?
Open on your desktop currently.
And you know, and I have like the calculator and the weather and a couple other things.
So that's, that's all right.
Of course, I got I like 05.
So I got the new I movie.
The upgraded iTunes already came with it.
The new iPhone.
Oh, it's looking good.
It's I'm quite happy.
I'm quite happy.
And I think I've actually convinced Ron to move our to a Mac now.
He's been struggling so much lately with his windows machine.
It's just.
Sometimes it's a little bit tiring.
Okay.
I think that's what we do now.
I want to hear some music.
Of course we do.
Let's do another promo because this is a pot.
This is like this was synchronicity man.
I was looking through some some categories in the directory.
Someone actually said to me, well, what kind of podcast I listen to?
And I said, well, what do you interested in?
What are your interests?
And she said, well, I have a three month old baby.
And so I went into the family note of the iPod.org directory and came across the
Mommy cast.
And one day later, I kid you not without me having said anyone to anything.
This promo shows up.
The online community radio show dedicated to moms in every country who are holding the
world together one child at a time at www.mommycast.com.
She moves like she don't care.
Smooth that till.
Cool you out there.
I had him this is page and Gretchen from Mommycast.com.
Our podcast is four moms by mom.
We've got tips and advice and some really cool interviews.
Adam, we've got seven kids between us.
Oh, yeah.
We're talking about.
We love your show and we think other moms will love podcasting too.
It's convenient and mobile for moms on the run.
So give us a listen and thanks for introducing us to your audience.
Hey, guys.
Tell your wives about Mommycast.com.
The most recent episode.
They interviewed the mom of the year and it's fun.
They got some great topics on there like sibling rivalry and kids hitting each other.
It's funny because I was talking to some people and say, well, what do moms talk about?
And I say, well, I've stood at the playground.
I've been the designated mom more than once.
And we talk about kids, you know, talk about kids, whether they're doing.
And of course, you talk about your husband, right?
I would expect some of that on the Mommycast as well.
A mention here, the iPod or developers have been working very hard.
There's a, who is my battery running low here?
Hold on.
I thought I heard my crap out for a second.
I just checked.
No, we're good.
iPod or lemon has a new release out with some very cool features.
And iPod Rex has released their 3.0 version of the application, getting a lot of great feedback on the new iPod Rex.
Those guys, I think, are doing something very interesting.
They're moving much more towards really becoming an aggregator for RSS feeds with enclosure.
So it's not just for MP3s, but they can handle PDFs and, well, basically, almost anything you throw at it.
And they're really seeing a world where there's going to be a subscription to all types of media content.
And I think that's very smart that they're looking at that.
And, you know, next, of course, they should do Windows release and then can really clean up the market when it comes to RSS.
They've also become more of an RSS text news reader and something very interesting.
I'm sure that's only going to be on the Macintosh for a while is they can, you can create a newscast.
So you can subscribe to a weblog and it'll bring in the most recent post and it will use the internal Apple speech synthesis text the speech to actually create a voice version of the new updates of those weblogs.
Now, I use Bruce and we're using that voice is actually it's doable, you know.
I'm not a big text to speech fan because I think sometimes I just can't understand what the hell is being said.
Particularly if slang is used, et cetera, but very cool.
So congratulations to the iPod and developers for all the great work that they're doing.
All right, now I want to play some pod save music.
This is something really good.
You're going to like it.
It's called push.
It's on the daily source code.
Push.
To walk away, let me stay, let me reach out.
Search me.
So slowly.
I get years.
Yeah, I'm thinking now.
I'm running out.
I get in there.
You're logging out.
You're making so hard.
Yeah, tell me now.
I have to go.
Yeah.
You're pushing my hands down in my lips.
I can't take care of you.
Yeah.
You're so afraid.
I'm afraid.
I'm playing you.
I'm the better.
Who's always messing with your heads and now.
Push.
Let me stay.
You want to play.
You want to be with you.
But you're behaving.
Yeah.
Push.
Don't walk away, let me stay, let me reach out.
Don't let it in this way.
I have a body roof for the girl.
Who will they walk away?
Play.
What about the better, girl?
I don't think they'll hide your words.
I used to go.
Right now I know you.
Yeah.
We get so sexy when we make it dance and snow.
I'm going to stay.
Yeah.
I'm not playing you.
You're just not used to.
Guys, not messing with your heads and now.
Push.
Let me stay.
You want to play.
You want to be with you.
You're behaving.
Don't let it in this way.
Don't walk away, let me stay, let me reach out.
I think you wish I was a different person.
All together.
I do believe I am the right one.
You're running down.
If you don't know what I put up with.
Which I'm crazy.
Yeah.
You're going to regret that day.
You let me get away.
Yeah.
You're just not used to.
You want to play.
You want to be with you.
You're all a thing here for you.
Yeah.
You're just not used to.
I ever stayed.
You want to play.
You want to be with you.
And be with you.
You're behaving.
Don't walk away.
You're just not used to.
I don't want to play.
Brother Love, push on the Daily Source Code.
Sentiment by CC Chapman of course of the accident has pod.
Cass, man.
He knows how to find it.
Doesn't he.
at BrotherLoveRox.com, push by BrotherLove.
And of course you can find all of that info in the show notes
to today's Daily Source Code.
We're recorded at Studio483.
We're listening to Urban Family and I am a leader.
Are you sick and tired of listening to the radio station?
Listen to the U.F.N. show, first content delivered weekly.
Listen to a straight couple, a gay couple, and the British homo,
as we discuss life, liberty, and the pursuit of horniness.
You can listen to our show that U.F.N. show.com.
And remember, gay or straight, all men want low jobs.
If the company didn't arrive, we'll set up a lot.
We'll wait a minute.
We'll just rewind that a little bit.
Oh, no second.
Wait a minute, what was wrong?
You can listen to our show that U.F.N. show.com.
And remember, gay or straight, all men want low jobs.
If the company didn't arrive, we'll set up a lot.
Okay, U.F.N. podcast.
All righty.
Let's see.
Oh, it seems like so long ago, but it really was only a week ago that I was in San Diego.
And got the iTunes demo from Steve Jobs.
And, of course, he announced that the D conference that iTunes is going to be supporting podcasts.
So, I call home twice a day.
I went on the West Coast.
It's kind of tough because sometimes I'll call like 11 at night and then it's basically
7 a.m.
at the cottage.
And Christine had school last week.
She's off this week.
So, I'm not calling this week.
We're not calling tonight.
And then, you know, I usually call around 11 or 12 noon, which is around 8 p.m.
Or sometimes a little bit later, just before they all go to bed.
So, and I talked to Patricia.
You know, she tells me about her day.
And I tell her about how I slept for the past six hours or whatever.
But with Christina, she's always online.
She's on the computer.
She's on a lot.
You know, and so I can see her.
She's got Skype and she's got to MSN.
So, we chat back and forth, just aimlessly.
And so, she heard about the Steve Jobs thing.
And she said, that's really cool, Dad.
But when you get to meet Bill Gates, because I got some shit here that ain't working
that he's got to fix.
And I was like, yeah, you go, bro.
He's fantastic with Adam Curry.
He's back.
It's time for the hit to go.
With Yarn Pollet.
Hey Yarn.
Hey Adam, I'm back.
I'm connected to the internet again.
I hope to be creating hit tests and hit test podcasts in the coming week.
So, be ready for them.
This is number 39, and this is intro number one.
Pure energy.
And this is number two.
Okay.
Well, Steve leads with kill me if I didn't know that one.
That's a white room by Creen.
And the final one for today, this is number three.
Oh, I pointed it.
We're probably all clapping songs.
Okay.
That's, uh, cocaine.
Then the first one isn't pure energy.
And times up, these are the answers.
This is number one.
It's the Despant.
Oh, right.
This is let it all blow.
Oh, good one.
How did great video, too.
Oh, good one, good one.
Oh, good one.
Sounds a bit like pure energy.
The Despant from vinyl is answer number one.
And this is answer number two.
It's an only from 1968.
It's Creen with a song titled White Room.
In the white room with black curtains in the station.
And white room with answer number two in today's hip test.
And this is answer number three.
It's J.J.K.
It's all J.J.K.
Oh, and the song is titled Cocaine.
What the hell?
You got to take a round, cocaine.
She know lies, she know lies in her life.
Cocaine.
The third and final answer in today's hip test.
J.J.K. Oh, and Cocaine.
Well, that's it for today's hip test.
Adam, there is also a new hip test podcast.
Number 10 is finally released.
Oh, cool.
So check it out.
Let me warn you that it's different.
It's more personal than the others.
It's much longer than the others.
And it's also a bit scary for me.
So please let me know what you think about that.
So check it out at young polette.nl.
Feedback as well.
Use your address.
It's hittest at gmail.com.
And well, the web address is young polette.nl.or.com.
That's J.A.N. B-O-L-E-T.
.nl or dot com.
Well, please expect more of the hittest in the coming weeks.
Thank you for listening.
See you next time.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much.
Young polette.
Good to have you back, buddy.
And I'm downloading your long personal podcast as we speak.
Young's been going through some health issues right now.
And I suggest you check out his podcast.
It's a great podcast.
It really is.
Because if you want to get to know the guy behind the format that is sweeping the nation.
And that's going to do it for me.
I am going to upload and hit the head.
Yeah.
Tomorrow will be Monday, of course.
The actuality is Monday.
It's Memorial Day.
So everyone is kind of hanging out.
Hope you actually have time to listen to the show.
And on Tuesday, one last meeting then it's home to the cottage.
I have to tell you, I miss my girls, something fierce.
Really good.
You know, even though we get to talk on Skype, email, and some message.
I miss it.
I really do.
So these damn hotel rooms.
Talk into the walls with microphones, strap to my book.
Maybe it's the hardships that make the best art in.
Alright, as always, we'll be back with a podcast.
Almost every day this week.
We're probably doing on the flight back home Tuesday night to Wednesday.
That will might be posted a little bit later.
I'll probably report me the report when I'm on the plane or whatever happens.
We're safe.
See you back out of the curry.com.
If you want to send in a promo, please send it to submit at podshow.com.
If you got pod save tombs, podsafe and podshow.com,
and please mashups.
We'll need more mashups.
Where are you guys?
Mashup at podshow.com.
Alright, everybody.
I'm out of here.
Take care.
DailySourceCode.com is where you can find this feed and all the latest shirts.
Bye-bye.
Thanks for watching.