The Lays there began as you reach Web Chapel.
There were tons of hits shut out of your text.
This is Ranger's final score last night at 9.
Really?
First on 6.35.
We did it.
It's Adam Curry.
Adam Curry.
It's the first source code of the year.
How are you doing?
Hey everybody, how are you doing?
It's Monday.
Well actually it's not.
But with a bit of luck you're hearing this Monday morning.
January 3rd, 2005.
This is the first daily source code of 2005.
I'm really excited because I'm leaving in the morning.
This is actually Sunday night.
And if all went according to plan, then I was able to upload the show at the airport.
Within the time window of my team oval membership experience.
Membership expiring, which expires I think Monday.
It's the 3 in the afternoon.
I had one week pass for Starbucks.
But I'm traveling towards Ben with my friends.
It's waiting there for me in Miami.
I can see it now.
How are you doing?
So packed up the bag.
So right now it's a quarter to eleven.
Sunday night.
So it might as well be Monday.
I got my bag packed up because I'm going to be in Miami for a full week.
Patricia helped me out.
And it's just been so busy.
I haven't had time to get my hair cut or really any personal grooming.
It hasn't really been one of those months.
So Patricia cut my hair.
She's really good at it actually.
She does the total package.
She trimmed my hair.
Why am I telling you this?
Anyway, she did my hair.
I love it when Patricia does my hair because it just looks so good.
And what I try to do then is if I go on a trip, I'll say,
could you please do my hair and then wash it.
And then as I said, she cut it up a little bit.
And she did it just perfectly just the way I love it.
And now I got to be real careful with it because I want to get up tomorrow.
I'm more after get up at six.
The cab is coming to pick me up at seven.
You know, so if I don't roll around and bend too much, then it'll be good.
And so I said, I'm going to cut the source code for tomorrow.
She said, well, wait a minute.
I just did your hair.
Now you're going to, don't tell me you're going to put the headphones on.
And I'm like, oh, yeah, that's a real bummer.
So I'm doing an ABBA.
Those of you who are, I think, probably at least 30 years old,
you'll know immediately what I'm talking about.
But remember when I'm afraid in a new year,
where a singing was it?
So dancing queen?
Well, there's a studio shot.
So it's not to mess up the hair.
They have the headphones across the forehead.
And actually, I'll add the across the forehead right now.
And now you do it underneath the chin.
That's also a very big ABBA move.
So the hair will be beautiful.
Drop, drop, drop, drop...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This one comes from the NIU Huskies.
Ace.
Oh, that was over much, sorry about that, so that's a great example of asking
that was shall receive. I was only asking, why just last year, wouldn't it be great if there
was a drum cadence of the day podcast and boom, there is a showed up on openpodcast.org,
which is a great service, by the way. You should check that out. It's a great way to, you
really want to do a full podcast, just want to promote your podcast. That's probably the best,
it's really what it's really good at. And if you have an idea that you just want to shoot
into an interesting community, or what I hear someone put on openpodcast.org, voice
mails that came into his voice mailbox by accident. Sorry, very, very eclectic bunch of files
that come through openpodcast.org, including this drum cadence of the day. And if it really
does show up daily, let's get it, it's own site, it's own podcast feed. I love it. It thinks
the absolutely excellent idea. And so what you can tell, of course, is that I sat outside
the neighbor's house for, well, pretty much, pretty much every single day, been during
the weekend. It was great. All of a sudden, there was this Wi-Fi that showed up, just
boom, just it appeared. I talked about this last week. So instead of going to Starbucks for
the past couple of days, I just been driving out, like 15 feet into the road, I still have
no idea which house it came from. But that's really not because the easy-and-guys are
coming in with British telecom this week, while I'm away. Hopefully everything will go
smoothly, Patricia and Christina are briefed. So anyway, I did get a chance to re-acquaint
myself with openpodcast.org, particularly after I had plugged it on a previous source code
and boom wall, so the stuff just came flying through, not just the drum cadence of
the day, but look who else came back.
When the alleged rape victim withdrew, what a civil suit would mean another ring for
his wife or a few. The tap dancer of the year award goes to Dan Rather, who stuck up
for his news when the source proved fake. And his retired money will have plenty of time
to gather, investigations of stories that still employ dangerous break. And you went
up officials at Welding Country's or Stacey Bush that were not at all with step-up
donations for the tsunami at top levels and put out a call to Americans to give
what they can, whether woman or man, or a kid with a plan, will all help put in a
need you together again, stay tuned for like breaking up day. That's the 2004 tap dancer
of the year. Happy New Year to you too. Good to have the podcast and tap dancer news
back. I missed it. It was gone or just wasn't showing up or I don't know, but hopefully
we'll get a brand new one for 2005 that was the wrap up for 2004 and it came right through
openpodcast.org. And at BloggerCon, was that October and November? That was the beginning
of November. Yeah, so it's been two months since BloggerCon. We had one of the thought
dinners and at my table, I sat next to Michael Eman, a very interesting guy. I thought
his hobby. I didn't quite realize how serious he was about his music, although he had
told me quite a lot about the recording of music he'd done. And I know that he's
consultant. He just works all kinds of interesting jobs and does, well, he also does podcast.
And I ran into a couple different projects, a couple different audio files and Michael is
out there and they just popped up in my iPod. It started off with this one. This is Michael
Eman from www.softwareland.org. And there's a new episode of in my life now available at
www.inmikeslife.org. Please stop by and check it out, everybody. Like the reverb, Mike. He's
more cowbell. So then, and I actually subscribe, I think I subscribed to this podcast, Mike's
manic minute. This is basically Mike's life on the flip side of the coin.
Stop, you just shouldn't miss. Almost alive, from Mountain View, California, it's 2005, everybody.
And I'll be the first one in it. I was wrong. At least about how fast podcasting would grow.
I predicted two months ago at the water continent. We reached 1000 podcasts by today.
At the iPod or X-Directory now lists over 2,000. But we expect from Microsoft in 2,000,
five. It's blame or I worked for Microsoft, it's a consultant. I was a product developer.
I wonder if he records this all in one go, or if it's edited together and if he speeds it up,
it's great. It's studio 2005, team system 2005, sequel server 2005 and other stuff I can't talk about.
Was that a commercial? Yeah. Speaking of this ruptured change,
Craigslist.org is now being cited as the direct cause of millions of dollars of last revenue
for local newspaper advertising. By the journey Microsoft, I got my last two consulting gigs
via Craigslist and I hired four amazing good people from job posting by found there.
Anyone want to start a video Craigslist to be by podcasting to sell junk in their garage?
New podcast from the iPod or that extra directory, video game, news radio,
lex tech, paying bare video 2004. They're changing that name today. A TV guide podcast,
godcast network, 10 new feeds, first watch radio, track source, cyberjans radio show,
in over your head radio and rock a boom. And that's your manic minute for January 1, 2005.
Yeah. Oh, man. Beautiful. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. It's perfect.
That's one of the podcasts that I love it. It's great. If I could actually understand,
I'd probably love it even more. So now some might comes out with a song that he did himself call. Good.
It's the podcasting song. And it's actually great. Good.
If I need you sexy, self opponent, I must watch to succeed.
You're chosen HDTB on your flat screen LCD and you've been at your brand.
And I feel that we're never so. You've used your commercial thinking.
I will sing along. And the perfect life you think I need. But I'd rather be happy.
I'd rather feel good. I'd rather hear my casting. The listen to the crap from Hollywood.
If you think it's fantastic, wouldn't mind that shit. Even if I could,
I'd rather be happy. But rather feel good.
The ostrich eating chronic placements, which are a trade box, they're for me.
On everything, the breath means to the apples on your trees. To reach my damn and crappy.
You brought my optimal life ham. But where am I stopped in traffic?
When I'd take a bath, you wish I'd see your ego in my sleep.
But a drowser behind me, rather feel good. I'd rather hear my casting.
Listen to the crap from Hollywood. You think it's fantastic.
Wouldn't mind that shit. Even if I could, I'd rather be happy.
I grew up in the teenage generation. Still I used to think you thought I had a mind.
Now it's clear if you just want my attention. You convinced me I'm no good.
When I'd show precious brother to life. I'd rather be happy. But rather feel good.
But rather hear my casting. Listen to the crap from Hollywood. You think it's fantastic.
Wouldn't mind that shit. Even if I could, rather be happy.
I'd rather feel good. I'd rather feel good.
Yeah, come on, that is awesome. It's good. The podcasting song, Michael Leeman on the Daily
Source code. And of course from the show notes, you can pick up the MP3. I suggest that if you
got a podcast and you'd like it, you give it a whirl. It's awesome. Michael, fantastic. I mean,
I'm actually blown away. We need to get bono to sing it.
Uh-huh. Yeah, that'll happen. What the hell you've been just laughing? Who can't beat?
Oh, sorry about that. Oh, God, that was bad. I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'll leave it to you later. Oh, radio.
Reality, bitch, laughter, radio is on the air. We'll see. See you, jammer.
I got an email from Joseph. Of course, as usual in the production show notes.
Thanks for the podcast. He says, it's actually something pretty weird. I don't know.
He sent me a really nice email. He's been clearly listening to the source code.
He says, I wonder if you would remind the podcast community to be courteous to its supporters.
I've tried to email the podcasters. I enjoyed to show my support. No one except for Nicole Simone
of useful sounds and the iPod Lounge Guy. Father to say, uh, at least say thanks.
Oh, this is interesting. And he goes, this is why I kept this. Of course, podcasting has to compete
for my time. Since I enjoy both XM and Syria satellite radio, medium wave band scanning,
ham, and shortwave radio, I was attracted to podcasts because it felt like a community with some
level of camaraderie. But now it feels disinterested. I think it's just, it's growing, you know,
and I have to be honest, it's email. When you do a podcast, what happens is, um, I think even
Dave mentioned this, there's a delay in the comments that, uh, that show up and it actually flows
out over, over time, over a number of days. So there's just so much more that is spread out over
so much more time. Once again, my email box keeps filling up. And that's also mainly because
of attachments are being sent to me. But I just have no, I have no time to manage it. And that is
also partly a bandwidth issue. But still, it's, um, I don't know, email is so broken. It is
so fucking useless to me. It really is. And Skype is kind of the same way now, you know, it's like,
I'm in the Skype directory. So if I turn Skype on immediately, this 5,000, please authorize me
requests. And I don't even know what happens if I cancel or that, or if I say, I mean, no, I know what
happens if I say, yes, but because, you know, then people can Skype me. And it's not like I
don't want to be accessible or available. But the application Skype has actually just become useless
to me at this point because I'm always getting instant messages all the time from people just say,
hey, or hi, you know, whatever. It's like, it just doesn't work. And I guess the only thing I can then
do is it's basically, you know, get another alias and start over and, uh, only use it with a
select group of friends or people that it doesn't, it doesn't work. Is this maybe where it comes
down to what Dave was talking about? Or, I mean, some of it's got to be that, um, about identity
and who, I don't know. I don't know anyone who is Skypeing me, really. I think the biggest problem
of these things is, this is what I like about my cell phone. When my cell phone rings, um, and I
don't always have it on me. In fact, oftentimes it says sitting on the charger, you know, connect
hooked up to the charger, sitting on my desk. But, uh, so it, it is always on. So it'll ring and eventually
goes to voice mail, I've like five or six rings. But sometimes, if someone calls and caller ID really
works very well in Europe and certainly on GSM phones and that, uh, that does work pretty well in,
uh, in the States as well, I believe now. But I think it's more, uh, a function of GSM technology
working better with caller ID or just, it seems to work better there. So I always know if it's someone
who's in my address book and I'm pretty meticulous about saving numbers and I sync it up with my,
address book on my Mac and all that works. Um, and but if it's someone I don't want to talk to
or if it's a number I don't recognize, then I can just basically silence the ringer and I just let it
go and it, you know, and it goes to, uh, voice mail. Therefore, not giving the caller any clue if it
was just sitting on my desk or if I was ignoring them or whatever. Uh, I just didn't answer the
phone and it went to voice mail. You can also reject the call, right? So if it comes in and it rings,
you say, I fucking won't talk to this person. You click it, it goes to voice mail. Well, of course,
that's a dead giveaway if it rings more than one, so it doesn't go to voice mail automatically,
you know, the minute you call the number because that's what happens when the phone is off.
Then basically you've rejected the person and they know it, which can have its benefits, but
I don't want to piss anyone off. I just want to have the option of deciding when people know
if I'm, this is it. If I'm, it's the presence thing. I think that's it. I don't want everyone to know
that I'm online. I want a couple of people to know that's what I'm looking for. Uh,
took me a second there. I don't want everybody to know what I'm online. In fact, I want a different
status of my presence in Skype for different types of people or different categories of people.
That would actually work for me. That would be pretty cool. If, you know, you know, like my friends,
if Dave can see that I'm online and available for Skypeing, but other people won't see me at all,
or I guess that's part of the authorization thing. Fuck, the authorization thing is it's not the
way to do it. It's very annoying. It makes me not want to use Skype. It really, it doesn't just
annoys the hell out of me. Um, oh, by the way, I want to thank Dave Winner so much for
basically podcasting directly to me. It was so cool to hear his comments about my show notes.
And, um, this is where our communications, it's sometimes just hard, you know. We're, we're talking
a lot these days communicating partially through email all of, as I pointed out, that's not always
the best for anyone to communicate with me through email. Um, but usually on cell phone calls,
which is good. The, the quality of the phones of the phone calls and basically the connections
not being drops ever since Dave got his GSM phone on its AT&T wireless. That's been very good.
And, of course, we, I did think every single time the caller ID has worked, I'm both ends.
But, you know, when he calls me, he's probably on the road. He's been driving for an hour or two.
Maybe he just had lunch or before lunch. He's driving through Texas. I'm in the UK. It's different
time, you know. So, you talk about stuff. And, and I'm, we were talking about the show notes.
And, um, at a certain point, uh, I think this is what it is. Where, uh, I sometimes, and I think
it's common that people do this. Where you confuse, uh, talking about what you would do or as an
example, if I were a, fill in the blanks. So, if I am a punter or if I'm, uh, that's what they say here
in the UK. So, if, you know, if I'm someone who's, if I'm a source code listener, uh, then I want
my show notes up front. And, so sometimes it gets confusing where there were, uh, you know, thinking
about, is this, uh, someone who's listening is this you or this me. And, uh, I never, for a second,
doubted that you weren't loyal to the source code Dave, not for a second. But, um, well, forget all that.
What this whole conversation led to is such a boring moment, like damn, of course, that the show
notes need to follow after. And there is a timing factor after the show. And it should indeed
show up into the, um, uh, into your aggregator when you're in link browsing mode. That was what
really hit me as what Dave said in, uh, in his response to, you know, the, the whole concept of show notes
and will people judge the show by looking at the, the show notes before actually listening to it.
And I got comments from other people, um, you know, drew from Don and drew lovely. He said,
he sent an email and said, you know, dude, I said here and, and, and, and listen to the show with
this show notes in hand, I'm like, what's in your other hand, big boy. Oh, tell me about it.
And so, um, and then, and then, that's when Dave said it. He said, um, I want the show notes
after. And I wanted to show up when I'm in link browsing mode. Because of course, when you're listening
to the show, you're not really in, in link browsing mode. You're in listening mode. You're in, uh,
driving to work mode or exercising mode. And yeah, you may want to hit a button and, you know,
bookmark, I'd like, oh, y'all go back and check that later. But probably it's just better to figure
that, well, the next aggregator scan after you've received it, uh, I'm just guessing, or maybe it's
half a day later. Maybe that's the way to look at it. You know, then all of a sudden, these links
will fly by and these will be links that you've, you know, you've already heard about, um, and you
say, oh, yeah, that's right. I want to, I want to check that out. And I think that's actually brilliant
because that's, that's what always bothered me about interactive television or the concept of interactive
television. You have to respond immediately. But when I'm watching television, I'm in laid back
chill out drinking a beer or smoking something else kind of mode. You know, I'm just chilling. And
I don't want to be link browsing. Think about that though. Think about that. Uh, um, big broadcasts
could really benefit from that theory. Right now, this very moment, they really could benefit from it.
You know, it's like, how do you get the information about the show that you want people to have
at the right moment? How do you time that? That's the, that's the kind of stuff that Ron
Bloom loves thinking about and comes up with great matrix matrices. Right. That's right. We got a big
meeting, um, or meetings or hang out or it almost feels like a jambory. It's an on-air jambory.
As we're going to, uh, to Miami, good choice by Dave, uh, at first it was going to be New York,
New York, of course, being, you know, a great place for energy, great place for business.
But I have to agree. I like the idea of 75, 76, 77 degrees,
particularly now because it's getting pretty hold and pretty cold and good old
gilford in, uh, in Surrey. Okay. Um, and there was a couple other things that Dave also spoke about.
Um, about the Surinami and, you know, I'm, I'm too tired. I want to talk about that now.
But I will come back to that. In fact, I'm copying this node from today's show notes
almost a second. I'm going to put it in for tomorrow because I do want to come back to that
because it really gave me an interesting or a new perspective on just a couple of different things
and on life as well. Uh, but it's 10, 10 past 11. I got to get it early. I'm too tired and I have
all kinds of easy, uh, pre-packaged comedy bits just waiting here for you. So why bore you with
the salilically when you have this? Hello. This is Eric Jeffcoat, and I want you to see the
this is just a short teaser for technology instructional technology tips for today's teachers
preparing students for tomorrow. I'm preparing some podcasts for using technology as instructional
tool in the classroom. So, pot in it's teach knowledge with Eric Jeffcoat. The poetic
literations are just some of the many benefits you'll receive from listening.
So, of course, you couldn't check that out in the, uh, in the directory at ipodder.org.
Um, that's where all the podcasts eventually flow through. Um, everything that's new
comes through, uh, oh, man. I almost forgot. You got to check out the IT conversation
node in the ipodder.org directory. Uh, Dick Doug K. did such an awesome, awesome job of collecting
all of the different feeds categorizing them, putting them into two main categories, one for MP3's,
one for AAC's, which, of course, are, uh, apples. I'm not, sorry, not necessarily apple,
but they, iPod plays. I'm, oh, I'm really butchering this. It's a fucking different format
that's bookmarkable, okay? I've been hacking my eye river. I've been trying to get the new
firmware on that that makes it mount as a, as a USB drive. Uh, and it's not working. I keep getting
an error. Uh, actually I should have written down the arrows, a error number, and a negative error number,
uh, but something was wrong with the firmware upgrade, whatever, but I've really found that I like it.
I like this. It's the IFP 799, we talked about it before. I'm still using the I river manager,
but basically what I'm doing is I'm just dragging my entire, um, iPodder download folder
into the I river manager, and I just, and I'll just say, yeah, you know, um, replace everything
that you, that you hit up against. It does, I don't, I don't, I don't mind if it takes a little bit
longer to, to re-copy stuff on. Although, of course, it's foolish in, in an efficiency sense of,
of doing things, but I like it because you can basically select a folder and it'll play through the
entire folder or, uh, it's just, you get to do your own file management. You can delete stuff from,
from the, from the device itself. The sound is exceptional, battery life, phenomenal,
like in it very much. It's small. It's, uh, of course, it doesn't play my, uh, audio books that
I download from audible, but otherwise it's one gigabyte fits right on it, you know, so that's,
uh, there's no way I can listen to more than one gigabyte in a day. It's just, it physically
impossible unless it's the highest of high-fi quality, which I don't even think you can encode in
most cases. I like it. I'm really digging the I river. Uh, but if anyone can help me out with exactly
what's going on with, with the, with the firm work I've created and how come I'm not be able to do that
on my Mac, uh, that would be highly appreciated. And I bumped against the, uh, this podcast, uh,
from the podcast brothers, uh, who apparently are setting up the podcast expo, uh, podcast expo.com.
I just want to play a little bit of this podcast because I think these guys are pretty interesting.
They've got a very interesting take on stuff. And they actually are doing a podcast about podcasting,
you know, we need more of those.
Welcome back to podcast brothers, our second podcast in so many months. So now we're,
right after Christmas here, so we're going to be doing a podcast for the week about a podcast
about podcast. And I guess I'll show about nothing if you will refer to the same film season one
into DVDs that I got for Christmas. Anyway, there were a couple of issues I wanted to air out today,
a couple of things bothering me in podcast world, but I think need to be said, not for the, uh,
your controversy of it all, but, um, I think there's, uh, you know, I refer to a lot of the
butt kissing going on in podcasting world last time, but this is kind of an offshoot of that,
but we're also going to talk, uh, I'm about kissing. Talk about podcast expo, what we're going
to have there and some other things, but we just wanted to have a podcast about the state of podcasting.
And I think that's probably what podcast brothers is going to be all about over the next few months.
So anyway, podcast brothers is Tim Berkwin and Emil Berkwin. And we are brothers with, uh,
love audio, love the internet, and so podcasting is a natural extension of that.
Check them out at podcast expo.com, the podcast brothers. I really enjoyed it.
Uh, these guys seem to have their heads, uh, on straight. I think I think sounded pretty good.
Looking forward to the next show. And I was listening to Donandru. Um, I had fallen one show behind
and at a certain point, of course, I thought, oh, wait a minute, my, is my iPod are working
because I, I missed them, but, uh, I figured out that they, um, they, it was like four,
they had some garage band problems. I got a, I really have to call, um, call Drew and, and Don,
well, that's, of course, what I was thinking. I got to call, um, because I want to help Drew out with,
with some, uh, recording, uh, ideas. I mean, I've, I've got a different set up that I'm using now
that I think would be pretty, pretty good for them as well. Uh, of course, you know,
I need to talk to Don, eventually. And then this comes through on,
I'm, I, I river. Stigarettes, f***ing cigarettes. That's what, well, you know that always gets
my attention. 12 hundred people die a day from smoking. Yep. That's insane. That is insane.
Think about everybody, you know, that's only when 12 hundred people, right? No.
I don't know. With the show, we know a lot more now. Yeah, we do. Some of you
intimately. That's right. Yeah, no. So here's, thanks for the phone sex. Mm-hmm.
Yeah, there's a few comments. We can't play at the end. A little little risky and naughty.
Just to me. What does that mean, Drew? You can't, what is like, it's like the FCC going to
come and arrest you. Why can't I want to hear him? Just, you know, do a not say for work thing
before any, well, I, send an MP3 file. I know. They never send the good stuff to me.
Just, I don't worry. What, yeah, right here comes. And I'm Korean, I are going through a
rocky part of our relationship. Yeah. Why is that? He's not ready to settle Don and have kids.
He's with a new wife. At this point, Christina heard this. She's going like, hey,
hey, doesn't she know that I'm here? Yeah, I think she does. That has a husband.
Yeah, I can, I can send a wife. I can see the conflict. Why? He's so kind of like you, though.
Are you upset about that? Yeah, um, you guys listen to the sad story. Adam,
he doesn't ever call me. And I was even, I'm playing cool, you know, like I'm playing hard
to get. Like, I barely ever send him any emails. And like, I never ever, um, really talk about
him anymore in the show. But, yeah, he hasn't called me. What do you, why do you think, Joe?
Maybe it's my fault. Oh, you scared him away. I might have. The real reason, Don,
is, I've been unfaithful. I'm sorry. And I think it was just a one-time
fling, but I have been unfaithful. I've been listening to another woman. And I got to tell you,
she's, she's, she's really doing it for me, Don. Well, hello there. This is Violet Blue,
and you're listening to Open Source Sex. To find out more about me, visit my website,
tinynibbles.com, or simply Google my name. Tonight's podcast is about white cotton panties.
Actually, it's about the feel of a tight corset, or better yet, the way a rubber dress restricts
shines the skin, and sometimes you can see right through it. Would you like it if tonight's podcast
was about the nasty things I do in high heels to let us? Oh, yeah, yeah, please.
It's about all that. Tonight's sexual fetishes are on the menu. What they are,
and how to make the most of them to get off and get off right. I regularly lecture about fetishes
to the students at San Francisco Sex Information. The nation's only ask anything sex hotline,
and you can actually visit them at www.ssi.org. When I talk to the students about fetishes in general
and how to answer questions about fetishes from callers, I also do something for these students.
I seldom do when I lecture. I share my first fetish experience. Okay.
Would you like to hear that first fetish experience on the daily source code?
Yeah, I thought so. I didn't even really know that I had any kind of a fetish,
but I was in my late teens, and I was working in Upper Hate, Hate Ashbury, and I was working
at a used clothing store called Buffalo Exchange. While I was working there,
I bought a corset from someone over the counter because I was one of their clothing buyers at the time.
And there was just something about it was this ratty ugly old fashioned corset that really,
really tall, long cotton kind. It was pink, totally not my color. I kept it for myself,
and I took it home. I was dating a man at the time who totally thought fetishes were achy,
scary gross, and the people who did them were sick, and even though he was like a rocker musician,
and stuff like that, he totally just thought those people were all fucked up. So I had this corset,
and I really wanted to wear it. So I waited until he was at van practice one night,
and somehow I got myself into this corset. I don't know how I did it. I mean,
I used a door knob actually to tighten the laces because I was by myself, and I tightened it,
and I tightened it really, really, really tight. And I wasn't wearing anything except the corset.
I wasn't wearing any panties, I wasn't wearing a top. I wasn't wearing a shoes,
although I did put some shoes on, so I can see what it looked like with a pair of high heels.
And the minute I had this corset on, I just felt, it was like a switch flipped in my head,
and I was so horny, so instantly, so fast. I walked over to the bed.
Okay, so if you want to hear what happened, you'll have to listen to open-source sex. It's a podcast.
You can find it in the sex mode of the iPod or an order directory. That's Violet Blue.
Check out at tinynibbles.com. It's great. We got to do something about our mic.
She has a great voice, and you know that when she's getting into saying something really
sensual and sexy, she really uses her voice, but it's just we got to get a little better recording
about that. That's all I'm looking for.
Hi Adam. I'm the fat posh chap from the Cotswolds. If you're not my testicle, it's to change your
knife. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. You're the what?
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my. Hi Adam. I'm the fat posh chap from the Cotswolds. Okay, the fat posh chap got that
from the Cotswolds. If you're not my testicles to change your life, visit the future podcasting at
www.mypods4cast.co.uk to have a good day now. Okay, so of course, you know that I would do anything
for my daily source code listeners and after a promo like that comes through on the wire,
you know you've got to go check it out. So I went to my pods4cast.com and it was pleasantly
surprised by a financial podcast that actually determines how stocks will perform based upon
well based upon his testicles. Hey everybody and welcome to my pods4cast. Each and every week
might not will change the course of your life. This week they'll make you rich. Maybe have the names
and prices of the 5, 500 companies that have performed best over the past month and also the
5 company who's performed the worst. My selection will be based on the following system.
I would ask my sack a series of questions. I would then cup it as high as I can. The design
of my body means that one nut or settle in front of the other. If my right pod is in the front
when I drop, then the answer is yes. If the left pod is in the front then it's a no. To get from
10 companies down to 5. I'd need to choose which of the two lists I use. So my first question will
be should I use the top forming companies. I will number the resulting list from 1 to 5. I want
to choose this list fairly and as it's an odd number I can't just present half. Need to group
three either with one and two or with three and four. So last question should I group three
with one and two? This will be repeated until we have a result. I must stress at this point
please don't hold me responsible if you lose your money, your friends, your house, your wife,
your kids, or anything else if you trust this system. As this is my podcast and debut
really as untried so probably for the best if you don't put too much money down. Right here we go.
Obviously before any event like this we need to check your equipment.
So I hope you've got a lot of those playboy players. Conditions are um
well good to firm for the record. The top five winners are man group
capital group, SAB Miller, Pearson and Rio Tinto. The top five losers are Anglo-American,
chorus group, chorus, three-eyed group, Existura and Ken Energy.
OK, SAB. Should I use the top five companies? The cup? The drop?
It's a yes. OK, SAB. Should three be grouped with one and two?
No, no, SAB. The drop? It's a no. This is a great exact. Should I use the top group of one and two?
The cup? The drop? It's a no again. OK, the three remaining companies. Number three,
SAB Miller, currently trading at 870 pens. Number four, Pearson, currently trading at 633 pens.
And Rio Tinto, currently trading at 15 pounds, 35 pens.
Sack should I group number three with the number four? The cup? The drop? It's a yes.
OK, SAB. Does the winner come from the group containing three and four? The cup?
The drop? Two close to call the cup? The drop? No. We have a winner. It is Rio Tinto,
currently trading at 1535 pens per share. Most excellent. On next week's show, I'll be helping
you choose your lottery numbers with the first calls. And also giving the results of how
this share has done. Thank you very much. Goodbye. I love it. We should just, you know, we should
call, we should need to talk to the Sack. That's right. Whenever we have a question about what's going
to happen in the future, we just need to ask the Sack. Hey, that's it. I love you, John. I love you, Drew.
I love you, Dave. Morning, doing a night. Good night, Incident. And I'll see you tomorrow.
And that's when we'll be back with another source code, which will come to you from Miami,
FL. And I'll have some broadband, so give it a shot. I mean, that MP3 file again,
adamantcurry.com. And of course, please leave a comment on my weblog www.curry.com.
Okay, about 11 30 here, 40 minutes for two minutes for the show for today. Perfect timing.
In seven hours, I'll be getting up. No, okay. Actually, I'll be almost out the door.
For seven o'clock tomorrow morning, I'm out the door. And I should be arriving in Miami
around 2 p.m. And I'll probably be able to stay away from the podcast or maybe I'll be uploading
this one. Didn't work out the airport. All right, everybody. Happy new year. Here's
looking at a great 2005, maybe a healthy and happy one for everyone. I'll talk to you tomorrow on
the source code. Bye-bye.