Delta Sierra Charley 2-2-6
A voice 65 million years in the making.
I'm at a mysterious.
I'm like a horse.
Rated R.
117 not admitted without current.
Well, we prepared to move on to the ceremony.
Nothing could ever prepare you for what awaits you.
At the ceremony.
16 million dollars worth of airplane strap to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
It's fantastic.
It's incredible.
And it is Tuesday, August, August 23rd, 2005.
I really did have, well, not quite 16 million dollars worth,
but I didn't have an airplane strap to my ass today.
That's why the source code is so late.
It's 10.
Actually, it's 10.05 pm.
Coming to you from the Curry Cottage,
and the affluence suburb of Surrey.
It's Gilford.
This is your daily source code.
Oh, I don't know if you can tell,
but I've got the whole new equipment set up connected properly now.
I mean, I can even do my nails with this stuff.
It's so freaking automatic.
I guess I'll have to geek out a little bit
and tell you a bit about the setup.
By now, you know that the,
was it, I was talking to Steve Leaves over at Surrey.
It's, he, he didn't call the podcast table.
He called it the, the podcast complex.
That's right.
It's the complex.
The podcast complex that my father-in-law built for me.
It's downstairs.
And Thursday.
The movie.
I've actually had to hire two movers to come and help me
bring this huge thing up into the, into the office.
So tomorrow afternoon will be clearing everything out day,
clearing all the decks,
moving carpeting out,
moving the current desk that I'm using over,
you know, towards the wall.
Then I have to move the bookcase away from the wall.
So the door can open all the way.
Otherwise this thing won't fit in.
Then we get it in on Thursday.
And then I have to basically just drop everything on top
because the wiring is all done.
All right.
Uh, pod save music coming up.
Plenty of promo's for you.
And, uh, some audio feedback.
Now what do I do?
Like, good 30, 40 minutes show.
Kick it off with a mashup that you're just going to,
it'll bring tears to your eyes.
A shout out for the magic rocket man,
aggro one on the source code.
Like you know me.
You look right through me.
I'm rockin' blind.
Ready, go rock.
Go home, girl.
It's said that this is mine.
You'll help to let me and let's get out of our wall.
But try to understand.
Try to understand.
Try to try to understand.
They won't make any dick.
Oh, her what brought me the meritor...
We would try to witness till my singing when I'm jogar.
Play them side or the board again.
Where have you known it, maize but Why don't you ever let this spell life
all over, or somewhere else.
I sure learned that, I've tried realize their own song,
I'm just one-horse naive and growing up in a hole range
and cut me in.
They are an ordinary destiny.
Listen to how, oh, girl, mama, cry in the phone
To sum those my baby and my girl to be at home
But try to understand, try to understand
Try to understand, try to understand
He's a magic
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Everybody with me is out of pace
I can't zoom and run
Come on, come on
I can't withstand you
Come on, Kanami, say the smile
I can't less than available
I won't you woman from a child
But try to understand, try to understand
Try to understand
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
oh, oh, oh, no, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, ahhhh...
I'll come play and you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you,
I know, know, know, no-one. I'll be right here. You, you-you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you, your, I'm a rocker-feat. These are the things I'll found. Come on, come on. darling, I wanna come on, that I'll rock you,
Baby, you're not very rich of it, baby
I still want to find you
I'll be in the jungle today
I hope we'll be in the jungle today
Baby, you're not very rich of it, baby
I still want to find you, baby
I'll be in the jungle today
I hope we'll be in the jungle today
Baby, you're not very rich of it, baby
I still want to find you
Come on, girl, let's stay with us
Come on, girl, let's let's get out of here
Come on, come on, let's stay in
Come on, let's stay in
Come on, come on, come on, let's try our best
Please imagine me
Yes, yes, yes
I would pay money
I would absolutely pay money to receive mashups
Like that
I'd grow one, got it off a mashup town dot com
Awesome
I was just, you know, I was thinking
We could probably make a, well first of all
We could misuse serious satellite radio
And we should do like a mashup top 10
Or something like that
Just to get this stuff out there and a legal way
But you know, you have all these different music services now
And there's basically two types of music services
You have iTunes where you buy a song
It's DRM
And if you lose the song then it's gone
Right, so you basically have to track your own data
Unlike other services like audible
Actually
I like what they do
You also download an audio book
And it's, it's DRM
So you can't copy it or send it to anybody else
And you can, I think you can, as with iTunes
You can use it on up to five different devices
Not too sure about audible
But if you lose it, you can always just go back to the library
And download a fresh copy
That's what I like about audible
I think iTunes would do that
So that's one model
The other model like Rhapsody
Or the Yahoo Music Service
Is you pay a monthly fee
And then you have access to the entire catalog
Which can be up to
I think what is it now?
A million, two million songs, something like that
And then you can basically use as much as you like
But I think it'll only work on one device
And if you stop paying
Then everything that you downloaded
Self-destructs
So that's a whole different model
But it's also working very well
So why couldn't we, you know, basically
Turn a couple of mixers loose
And maybe we could have a mashup channel
Which you could subscribe to
And it would be, it'd have to be at a pretty low cost
Maybe it just, it should just be a part of Rhapsody
Maybe that's where, I mean, it could be done totally legal there
And I guess somehow we could figure out how
It would be micro payments
Because, you know, how many songs
Were in that mashup, right?
And then there's still going to be something
Left over for the producer
I hope
And then we could actually, you know, turn some of this into
At least a beer money for the guy
So we're doing these mashups
Because it's outstanding
I would definitely look into that
I promise you
So I got the new, I got the new set
This is the same gear that I used
On yesterday's show
Only I'm not in the garage
Right now I'm up in the studio
And what the only difference
Actually, this Yamaha workstation is so cool
Because you can program it to record
On to its internal hard drive
Right now I have it set up
Pretty much the way my old mixer set up
Was only, it has all these great effects
And EQ settings and processing
All built in
And I've really relearned a lot about audio
That I just forgotten
Because, you know, the unlike like pro tools
Whether it's a lot of, you know, click and drag
And graph work
And I find that it's so easy
That, you know, actually you wind up
Just kind of guessing how to do stuff
And the interface on this digital workstation
It's like a, you know, a black on yellow
And display
Kind of like a, one of those, uh,
It was a T-R-S-100s
You know, remember those with the built in
300-bought modem
So that's kind of the size of the display
It has some rudimentary bit graphics
Really, uh, pixel graphics I guess
What do you call them?
Just, you know, little like drawings
Of markers and stuff
It's really low-fi
Um, but therefore, when you go into editing
Effect or EQ setting
You know, it really has the basics
And it's very, you know, you really
Get into it because you have to pay attention
To this interface
It's so crude compared to what you can do on a computer
That I really learned a lot more about the way
Forms and about attack and decay
And, you know, all kinds of
Just all kinds of
Do you hear that by the way?
That's my other Mac is freaking out
It's, uh, it's overheating
Um, so now I've routed through
Something, and I'll stop with a geek talk
About the audio on a second
I've routed through the internal bus
I've routed everything
Out through the, uh, valve compressor
And, uh, man, it sounds like I'm one of those pirate ships
On, uh, on AM, you know, the sound
There's nice and pumping
My balls aren't really as big as they sound
Let's put it that way, okay?
On this big episode of the Delta Park project
Some hot penguin on penguin action
Jason Anna and Ichiro out in right field
Name this band
Plus, it's magic
We predict who's going to win the next season of Survivor
Go to our website at DeltaParkProject.com
Hard show
Content that will make you walk the dog
And kiss your mother
Well, you know, they spend hours on the script
Written at the last minute
It recorded on modern British equipment
Recorded on the cheap
What's the result?
The publicly left
And downloaded by mistake
Sorry, Kiwi Hanka
Lovely tautar
Gary Dring
Sounds like a girl
Clever little pod
Two people, chat
So, um, this morning
My whole day kind of changed
Literally due to road and weather conditions
This morning
Got up bright and early
The wing commander was bringing the 1802RG over
To take my in-laws back to Rotterdam
It was a beautiful sunny morning
Here in Gilford and at Farrow
At my local airfield
And, um, so, you know, we took off
We were kind of on the heavy side
I have to say it was an interesting take off
Long use of runway
You know, because I knew my in-laws
Did buy stuff while they were here
And it was a lot of baggage
So, we didn't fill up the tanks all the way
Um, and literally went over the English channel
And then just as we hit the, um, the Dutch side
Right near Zeeland
Zeeland
Boom, full clouds
We had to go, uh, instrument, uh, flying IFR
Um, which is cool
Because that, uh, turned into a, a training lesson for me
Because that's my next step is to get my instrument rating
Um, so, in the, in the clouds
You're seeing absolutely nothing
And you're just listening to, uh, air traffic control
Giving you vector
So, you know, now turn right to, you know, to this heading
Um, and then go down to 2000 feet
And, you know, you just follow that
And, you know, there was a sudden this little dial that pops up
And that's your glide path
And if you keep it right on right in the right center there
Um, eventually you break through the clouds
Which today were at 300 feet
And boom, you know, there's the airfield
There's the landing strip right in front of you
And then you just kind of put her down, right?
And it's fascinating experience
So, we dropped them off
Then, um, we'll even, I went to do a couple of touching goes
And some training at, uh, Midasay Lont
Which is kind of back in the same direction
Um, did some touching goes
Good crosswind, you know, like 25, 30 knots
So, it got some experience with that
It's a little harder to land an airplane
When the wind is coming from the side
Um, you know, gasped it up
Had a quick little lunch and then got the weather report
And it's going to be shit here tomorrow
And there's no instrument landing system
So, um, we wouldn't be able to come back in tomorrow morning
And maybe not at all tomorrow if it really stays bad
Uh, so we made the decision to come back today
Um, so that did put some extra flying time in that
I hadn't expected and, uh, also dented my wallet for a hundred bucks
For the hotel and Antwerp, which I couldn't cancel
Uh, but okay, so we flew back
And, um, you know, and I said, well, I got, uh, got some time here
So, that's when I reconnected all the gear
And actually, um, just got off the phone with the San Francisco office
Things are rocking out there, I can't wait to get back
Um, CC Chapman and, uh, Chris Rockwell
Um, of the daily download, uh, of the poop caster
Uh, he's out there
Um, and uh, they're hanging and they're, uh, talking all kinds of stuff
With about pod safe music network and the integration with pod show
And gosh, it's just, it's good things coming on
Including, um, um, uh, uh, pod caster delivery network
That's what we're going to call it
Pod caster delivery network
Hmm, that's a nice ring to it
Stay tuned for more information
And yesterday, I talked about, uh, a rack
back and the war on terror and about the price of oil and well on behold he
might gmail some audio feedback well produced by the way cleverly disguised promo
hey Adam it's Chris from the financial aid podcast and financial aid podcast.com
with some audio feedback of an oil and gas prices from yesterday's show
if you're looking for more information about why oil and gas prices are so high your
first stop should be www.opensecrets.org there you'll find that to the top 10 campaign
finance contributors to the congressional committees on energy art oil and gas companies and
electric utilities if there's any wonder why the legislation about oil and gas
that was just passed in your energy bill is so slanted heavily in favor of oil and gas
companies the answer is in the campaign finance details daily source code listeners
you want to squeeze every drop of gas out of their energy dollar continued to yesterday's
in today's financial aid podcast for eight tips on how to save more money at the pump
thanks a lot Adam
people don't have the internet and the only way as podcasters and podcast listeners can
get this medium across the way that it's a win win situation is by making sure that
the the malls the bowling alleys the hotels the donut shops all the coffee shops
have access to Wi-Fi this is the way that a lot of us who have PDA sync up every day
this is the way that we can get the message across to the vendors out there they're missing
out on listeners and they should they should sponsor podcasters there's a lot of hard work
to be done and I still don't understand under you know 2005 why internet access is an available
over the whole world in a way that's cheap and affordable and this is a win win for everybody
why isn't that people don't get it this is the way you can make money but you can also
enjoy something and this is it's critical because I see a lot of people that are interested
but they have no real way of connecting so that's the message how do we connect the world
right on my brother mark kill so a lot of messages there mark really appreciate it
I want to say regarding yesterday's talk about Iraq and the war on terror and oil as you
heard in the financial aid podcast I got a lot of email about that and all of it was really
thoughtful and well put together not everyone agreed with what I was saying but no one
jumped out and flamed you know because I think I did hit some points for almost everybody
and there and some things lots people didn't agree with but I really appreciate all that
feedback and there's no way I can respond to it all personally but I've taken everything to
hard and everything into account and you know we'll we'll see if my opinion changes over time
and how things play out basically see how to couple of things in my list oh you know that
viox stuff that that the woman won the lawsuit 235 million dollars I think it was
my in-laws and we're actually prescribed that both of them for a while my mother-in-law took it for
like a week and I think my father-in-law who actually is he has a quadruple bypass and I think that
you know this this viox stuff gives you heart attacks you know so they were kind of
freaked out about that I don't think that one week of use can do too much damage I think this
is really prolonged use but that's still pretty scary man you know and stuff like marijuana is
outlawed and viox is out there you got to wonder do we have our priority set rise
listen to the reverse engineer's show the official podcast for the rock band the reverse
engineers
they've been featured on tech tv sky digital satellite radio in the UK and the David Lawrence show
it's all been discovered there's no need so much more can you hear what the buzz is all about
as we reverse engineer the making of their latest album Max Q and get the stories behind the songs
visit iTunes or the reverse engineers dot com to subscribe to the podcast today
the drama's had exploded
the multitudes went forth and cast their pods in the direction of all who would listen
and casting their pods in this manner they were henceforth known as pod castors
I've got your podcast right here
welcome to the future table where trend watcher and futurist Richard Lem discusses topics like
the future innovation and entrepreneurship do check www dot future table dot com to visit the web pages
which are mentioned during this future table please do send your feedback and suggestions for other
topics to future table at trendwatcher dot com
trendwatcher and futurist Richard Lem is available as a keynote speaker forum leader and brainstorm
moderator check www dot trendwatcher dot com for more details in this episode you can listen to
the interview recorded by Richard Lem at the R&D lab of British telecom and hip switch north
east of London. Hydrologist Ian Pearson and Ian Neut are talking about their new technology timeline
you know I have no idea what that's about but I thought it was really interesting for a couple
of reasons one it sounds like the the announcer is Dutch I'm pretty sure that's a Dutch accent
although it was referring to something in the United Kingdom and then I heard a pitch for
you know some professor guy who's available for weddings and bar mitzware as I was like that's
pretty interesting so I just thought I'd play that one for you before that you heard the promo
the band that's doing their own podcast was the reverse engineers the pod save music network
with this some cool stuff going on you know this is the place where podcasters can go to
get music that they is pod save they can play on their podcast and it's really like a discovery
system because you can see what other podcasters are playing and then we have these top 10 lists
of most listens because you can just go in and listen if you don't want to if you don't have a
podcasters you just want to listen to them tunes so you can see what's been listened to the most
which usually kind of follows along in relationship to the pod plays now I was talking to Chris
and and CC about this we're going to have to come up with an algorithm that refreshes that because
right now it's just you know the top plays of all time and it's going to be more dynamic so that
refreshes on a weekly basis and then we can have a real top 10 playlist which is exactly like the
big guys have you know so we're going to work on that what else I hope the store opens up one of
these days so you can actually sell through the pod save music network which is at pod save music
network.com and then we're also going to do the top 10 pod play once we have that worked out
with the top 10 pod plays on serious satellite radio and you know see if we can get some
get some broad distribution and some listenership for for these great bands because I mean
and that's just bands it's artists I mean it's all kinds of stuff going on over there
and every single day we're tweaking tweaking the site and be sure to you know send some feedback
there's a link on the site if you have any ideas because you know we're really you know just
trying to create something really nice here oh and by the way if you you know podcashes have to
report when they when they've played a song not all of you are doing that and I'm going to figure
out a way to incentivize you to do it but right now I'm just going to beg and plead if you
played something please report it so that we can keep track of that and so that we can you know
have better data for our top 10 list okay speaking of pod save music I this one actually came off
of the top 10 pod plays list pod save music network dot com music dot pod show dot com
I think I've played just about everything that's on the list except for this song and
you know at first I thought well it just sounds like kind of like an emo band you know and then I saw
let me see that from there from Stockholm Sweden I figured you know what the hell
stranger things that happened with those bands
like electronics
I leave, it's all the chance of you say
But I was saying I was mad
I was happy or sad
I'll hide, you think I need to suffer
But the grass needs the green
And the sun needs the green
Like the gas leaves the blue
And the red leaves the green
So I'll see the sun
If the grass needs me
I'll hide, you think I need to suffer
Okay, rock it man, it ain't
The bomb happys and hide from Stockholm, Sweden
Pods safe on the daily source code
And that's it, just about 30 minutes is promised
The August 23rd edition of the source code
And I will be back tomorrow with another edition of the show
If you have iTunes
There's a new episode of the odd finder that's out
Which should not be pretty good this week
Dr. Dave did his magic on the show
And there's also the Spike Lee episode 4
Which is supposed to be 4 or 4 but turns out to be 4 or 5
Which you do not want to miss
Because it's on the set human-numan shadow casting Spike Lee
And that's exclusively to Apple's iTunes
Well worth it though, I think you'll enjoy that
Feedback at amacurry.com
www.curry.com is the website
And of course daily source code.com is where you can find
The podcast feed
The latest show, if I post it in the right place
I have this show on us
Okay, so I think that's
Wait, don't hit fast forward yet
I wonder how many people do that at the end of the show
So damn man, there's nothing left to say
I'm just going to skip to the next track
I guess I'm just tired
I'll try and do tomorrow's show a little bit more early
Okay, take a note, I have such a backlog of promos
And stuff to play, it's unbelievable
Stay subscribed, thank you very much for listening
DailySourceCode.com
Dr. Tomorrow, bye bye
Thank you for watching
Another pod show podcast
Stick it in your ear