Delta's share a Charlie to eight.
Two.
One, two, three.
A $16 million worth of air in playing strap to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticky and crispy.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Fantastic. It's Adam Curry.
Hey, man. Just free wheeling a little bit, you know?
Hey, I'm back at the cottage everybody. It's Friday.
Didn't want to miss the opportunity to celebrate that with you.
So source code, come and act here.
And let's get into the spirit, Charlie.
One, two, three.
Just give me the second chance for Christmas.
No living alone. I can't see you crying.
The standing beneath the mistletoe.
Don't face a glow. I don't fire your side.
I feel I've been lost in the wind and snow.
I watch your beauty and its haunted.
It must be looking right through me.
I want us to forgive this.
Just give me the second chance for Christmas.
I will wait for you under these stars until I see the sun.
You're the only one, the only one.
I love you.
Just give me the light on your Christmas tree.
I am acting cold on your stereo.
That she is back where it's out of the breeze.
The top is without an angel.
I never lied and conveyed it.
I saw the forest for planning.
I want us to forgive this.
Just give me the second chance for Christmas.
I will just give you the second chance for Christmas.
Oh, candy butchers.
That's excellent.
Give me a second chance for Christmas.
Just showed up on the pod save music network along with what to do about Michael.
They have joined.
Welcome, guys.
Hello, everybody. This is the daily source code.
There's no business doing a podcast after having travel.
Transatlantic from San Francisco to London.
There's too much fun.
It's Friday.
What a weather change.
I left it in the 70s.
Beautiful sunshine, very clear skies.
I didn't see a lot of missed this past week that I was on the west coast.
The frost is on the ground.
It was almost.
It was just a little bit of a freezing when we landed.
I don't know.
It just kind of motivated me.
You'll hear me slurin' over my words and tripping it over the place.
I did sleep on the plane.
Once again, another great virgin flight.
I'm paying it through the noseboard and loving it at the same time.
It's an amazing product.
Was it really that simple to make flying that much more enjoyable?
Whatever he did, I think it's really the excellent configuration of the airplane.
Do you hear this microphone?
I don't think I have the high all now.
The one that I want.
I think I have to do some configuration to make it work properly in the cottage set up here.
I know one thing.
It doesn't fit in the stand.
I have a jam through a hole in the top of the podcast complex.
It really does sound like crap.
Maybe I should switch to the other microphone.
I think that's probably going to be better until I figure out how to configure this one.
Okay.
So Thursday, just to keep you up the speed on what's been going on, what we've been thinking about.
I was getting picked up to go to the airport at a quarter to two.
It was, hello.
Hello.
Hey, babe.
Come on in.
I heard a sort of a different sound.
A different sound?
Just like you are in.
Oh, that's why it seemed better.
Yeah.
So that's why I came in, I thought something's wrong.
Wait a minute.
Oh, no, there you go.
Oh, okay.
I was just saying, I was saying, wow, this microphone sounds like shit.
Are you stoned?
No.
Are you out of it?
I mean, you are tired.
Yeah, but I wanted to show.
It's Friday.
We have to celebrate.
It's good to see you.
Tell the listeners.
Put your headphones.
I was asked, no, because I'm going, I have things to do.
Like reading the paper.
Excuse me.
The deal is reading the paper.
Um, you know.
Did I know what?
Well, um, no.
Have you?
Tell the listeners.
But what?
I was asked for the, for the Wizard of Oz.
By Yoke from the end of production?
No, I, I know.
I just started the show.
Mm-hmm.
So, uh, but I wrote it down.
I remember to talk about, well, why don't, now that you're here.
It's a privilege.
I have to say.
Now that you're here, why don't you tell us about it.
Oh, that's it.
Well, well, no, wait a minute.
Now, say, so you were asked by, uh,
Yoke from the end of production.
This guy's huge and theater.
Yeah.
He does all the musicals in, like in New York.
Yes, so when Mama me, you know, he gets the license for that.
And he produces that.
And then I'm sure, you know, he'll do every single way.
You know what, Ron said, I'll get to that in a second.
Yeah.
So they asked you for what?
For one of the, uh, major roles in, in the, in the Wizard of Oz music.
In the Wizard of Oz music.
In the Wizard of Oz.
And I said no.
Well, first you said no.
No, I'm all the way.
Because this is probably in Holland, of course.
It was in Holland.
Would you do it?
I'm maybe because Christina's in school the whole day.
If it did.
It's seven days.
And so what I would have said, maybe,
you know, let me do it for a month or you know,
cos that, like they do here.
Sometimes Americans come over and they are in the theater in London.
They do that for a month and go back.
And then they can say, I was always on the.
I was a website.
I was a sister.
Exactly.
See then you're real.
Imagine enriching and enriching and enriching.
Right.
So I thought, you know, but let me ask you a question.
What have been a nice experience?
nice experience and take no offense, but I'm pretty sure it wasn't for Dorothy. So what
are the other roles? No there's also good one. Is that Galinda? So it doesn't
matter it would have been a wonderful experience and we sure. Yeah but you know I'm
all the way here. I'll let them jump out. So you didn't have the headphones on so you
didn't hear me. Okay. But I'm here. I'm here for you. And for me. And for my daughter. And that's it.
So it doesn't matter. You look great babe. Well thank you so much. You know when you're not there
you know always sleep like a log. You're fine with the eye can sleep. So Patricia's saying well
you know I've seen it. I think because of the energy that you produce at night that I have
restless nights. So it's really not good that you're sleeping next to me was basically what you're
saying there. Well of course I love it you know but the moment we fall asleep and you you are very
I mean heavy, heavy, deep sleeper and I'm all very jealous of it. Oh yeah I'm out like I'll
and I go to sleep in three seconds. Yes I'm a light sleeper because I'm a mommy and I want to hear
everything and I want to hear everybody breathe and I think so yeah and what I said to you was
I have an idea that my bed sleeping thing comes from your sleeping thing because I'm always
awake or awake a couple of times. I wake up a couple of times. I think it's because you have
so much energy in your body. There's so much going on in your brains and your brain just keep on going
even if you're asleep I know that. I'll be you have sweat attacks and you have I don't know
what your attack is but I have an idea and maybe somebody who's listening knows all about it
yeah. I feel your energy and it wakes me up. That's what I think. What do you do?
But how come it? Well that's possible. I believe that. I buy it but how come it doesn't wake me out
because I'm just sitting there generating all this energy. Because you're dead tired. No you're
good sleeper. I mean I don't know you're you're deeper than that. But my brain should be resting at night.
It shouldn't be crunching. Yeah you're I think your body is resting but you brains you know I think
they never sleep. They just go over the whole thing in a whole day. Now for you that's a lot.
A lot of things happening in a whole day. Yeah. So yeah. My theory. My brain is at least a doing
something. Yeah. Yeah that might as well be. I'm very happy your brains are doing a lot.
So Patricia who by the way flies in my airplane more than I do is paying a surprise visit to her dad
tomorrow with Christina. Oh, hold on. Did I just lose you? No. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah it's going to be
big surprise. He wasn't feeling very well. He was 80. He's 80 now and his birthday was last week this week
getting off the week. I mean. And so 80 is quite a lot especially for somebody who has four
bypasses. So he wasn't feeling very well. And so I thought you know I'll uh I just surprise him and
make him happy. You know. Oh yeah. Well don't surprise him too much. Man's had five passes.
Don't come in. Don't make a mishaw. Yeah. I'm going to go out for dinner but he doesn't know we're going
to be there. Christina and I know but make sure he doesn't he doesn't freak out when he sees you. No
he will. No. I'm not that far away but it's still you know it's good it'll be quite a surprise.
I'm not coming from Australia. Australia oh I have some stuff from Australia. Yeah I heard that.
Okay. Look if you can understand here then you have to put the hand. No no I'm going now.
And uh oh. What do you do myself on paper here? Okay baby. Okay honey. Thank you. Okay.
I love you. Bye. Okay so you've got a little update there. What I was going to say before
Patricia came in is that Thursday was all a pod safe music network day and you know getting
development team together because you know well we basically as I said in the last source code
to get the pod safe music network really rolling we got to have you know some dedicated development
on that and which means we we're hiring for that. I think you'll see that show up on
podshow.com. There's a job link. I think there's a job link. Please tell me that's a job link.
That's got to be let me just say maybe even be up there right now. Hold on and you
couldn't get all this information from the show notes as well. And by the way I want to thank
the everyone who's doing the show notes on on the wiki. It's so wonderful. It makes my life
so much easier and I think you I'm because I always check the show notes out and I see
there are also people put comments up there. It's it's really good. It's detailed and you know
sometimes there's little mistakes in there but then the great thing is I can go in and I can
correct it. Let me just see a news about us come on it's got to be something here employment
opportunities. Okay. Wow let me see if web design and developer. Okay. Yeah this is like five or six
openings there. Alrighty. Oh we have a this is this is very cool. So it's starting. Advertisers are
starting to support podcasting. We have a new sponsor on the pod show podcast network. It's
and I was really happy when I heard that they were coming on board because like you know this is
definitely a sponsor I want to talk about in my show. It's EarthLink Internet and if you're I got
to tell you I'm I'm the old guy on the block and I've been you know old school internet I learned
about the internet I had a dial-up connection to what was it panics internet in New York City and
basically you you would you would tell that in and later of course SSH but first you tell that in
and then you have to start a slip connection you know by typing a command to get that going on
on and a unix prompt and then you could start up your TCP stack and then you could you know run
a couple of applications and the one that was really used the most even when I was starting off with
this command line based go for protocol you know this is from the days when I was around and I saw a lot
of ISPs internet service providers spring up in those days and there were some you know some real
core companies that were you know that were really based on the engineering and the roots of the
internet and I've always considered EarthLink to be one of them and prior to their sponsorship
I've always held an EarthLink account I've used them for webmail and I always had a dial-up account
with EarthLink you always had that my back pocket if there's some situation where I just get stuck
you know without any wireless it doesn't happen that much anymore but so the you know they're
reliable you know they've always had that that old school internet type of reliability and
air about them and what they have of course is new school services and as a sponsor you'll be
hearing on the number of pod shows about their phone service they've also have a wireless email
and I just couldn't be happier that I'm able to select cool sponsors for this show that makes it
a hell of a lot easier all right let's get to some Gmail here because I also want to listen to some music
oh yeah um Todd was his Todd Lizer I think it is L-E-I-S-E-R he said up a a frapper map for the daily source
code I've pointed to it from curie.com and we'll definitely have it in the show notes for today
what it is it's if you haven't seen this frappers it's a I really like it it a lot it's kind of a
mashup of google maps and and flicker photos and you couldn't put a little pinpoint on the
google map where you're listening to the show from and you can add a picture in there and you know
some kind of caption the link if you want and so it's at frapper that's like the flicker
spelling F-R-A-P-P-R dot com slash D-S-C listeners so we'll have that in the show notes let me see
there was some audio coming up here oh this was a great one this is from Doug Dyson I read this on my
blackberry when I landed at Heathrow and I actually started to reply to him I thought no no no come on man
let me stupid I can reply to it no you read this to you hey Adam thanks for skipping over my
L-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R radio promo that I worked so hard on the other day so you could
instead play some other totally random feedback clips from your Gmail inbox it must really take
more than passion to podcast as seems podcasting is already at the who you know click stage
you know I gotta tell you that I had increasingly more email is coming that it sounds like this
saying oh you know the mainstream media is taking over it's all ruined and at every single phase of
growth in podcasting I've heard these voices and sometimes are the same but I think they're actually
they're probably in this case even some new ones because it is growing and it's growing rapidly
and people get very protective of something they love and you know if you send me a promo on
let's see when was it the 14th you're pitching and moaning about me and calling me
part of a who you know click you know like five not only three days later I mean come on
man I mean this there's no rhyme or reason to all this I just pick whatever I can get and I play
whatever promo comes my way and since you've pitched a moan about it
will you please make the voters say for our eastern listeners good evening radio audience
good evening here and now for our western listeners say good afternoon radio audience
podcast for robots podcast by robots I'm Linda and I might from all robot radio dot com
an experiment in creating reducing and publishing audio content that's right exactly like
all robot radio dot com is robot announcers robot musicians and robot poets robots telling stories
and robots on their own talk shows robot professors and robot spirituality robot news and
security alerts but even more than all of this fun stuff Linda all robot radio is all about
helping now a robot brothers and sisters prepare for the inevitable time when robots will be heard
so true like this is the only robot podcast for the well informed and well-rounded robot
there's something for both robots and humans at all robot radio dot com so what are you waiting for
subscribe to the or robot radio podcast at your well you double you double you or robot radio dot com
all right not radio dot com huh okay yeah it sounds like you worked hard on it that's for sure
okay uh oh man I've been trying to actually manage some of these uh oh what's this do I have a
call coming through or I'm sorry excuse me let me just see what this is is this uh pdobe's oh
amen an interview oh man okay well the interview will just have to wait we're talking right now
I've been trying to manage my Gmail and actually tagging stuff with a DSC label and then going through
that and then moving something to a today or yeah today label which means for today's show
and you know the only thing I can't do is and it would be wonderful I could if I could rearrange
the order um because I would let me control the flow of the show a little bit better but I at
least I've qualified what we should talk about today and I'm not just hitting it at random hey
Adam says a rolf after having heard it on your show oh yeah this is a lots of emails about this I was
so on these enthusiastic to buy the what to do with Michael song by candy boochers and iTunes guess
what it's not available here in Switzerland interestingly enough the iTunes error message I got
is not you can't buy this song in your country but just your search was not successful the buy on
iTunes link on candy boochers website provides the same result man this kind of stuff pisses me off
when I see the digital divide is right around the corner now I'm ready to buy music legally
and the facility seem to be there too but I'm prevented by of doing so all the best rolf so I've
received a lot of those types of emails uh particularly from uh see uh I think New Zealand Australia
and uh other uh basically anything outside of um outside of the United States because I'll
have all these different music stores and I guess you have to clear every song through every music store
and as you know I've been thinking a lot about this uh about this stuff and we had some pretty deep
conversations yesterday as we were uh briefing team on um what were you know the direction we're
taking the positive music networks so of course we're you know we've talked about the commerce
transaction I'll get to that in a second or the the commerce piece and then there's also the um um
the unlabel so those two pieces are gonna have to start to fit together and I think we have a
pretty clear vision we already you know we're going in pretty much the direction we were we were at
right now um but as you start to think about selling I don't know if I can if I can go go this
deep on this stuff because my head's real fuzzy if you think about selling an MP3 versus uh any
other file format that has copy protection in it forget it digital rights restriction some call
a digital rights management you know we all know we're talking about i've heard other you know
some uh who was that i think it was uh okay maybe it was on twit that i heard him talking about
the MP3 if it's a DRM that the value essentially is uh is zero um you know once you you've sold
that you you make one transaction but it can't go anywhere I mean I know I'm not making any sense
right now but if you think about it what is the difference between an MP3 with with a song or an
MP3 with a podcast now they're both MP3's which means they'll both play on you know on any kind of
player uh almost any player today does MP3 if not you you basically can't even be in business it's
barrier to entry they both contain data um they may be of roughly the same size although one
seems to be a lot larger uh that would be the podcast because it's longer and so it's a larger file
but it's still one's in zero's it's still sound um except um the format of what you hear
of the audio signal is usually a song well we all know what a song is and we all recognize what
a podcast is but what's interesting about it is there's all this talk about copy protection
and all that they're not just talk there's all this copy protection on music
yet here we are just freely distributing our podcasts on MP3's
and look at what's happened to the growth of podcasting because these MP3's work everywhere and
I don't even think it's about money but maybe that that's it it's two different ways of monetizing
audio one way for that particular format is through the purchase model which is almost like a
donation only it's a pre-defined donation and then the other is um based on no revenue model
or based on other ones such as sponsorship and advertising uh
what what I find fascinating is and I was reading you know I'm uh what was I think time magazine
on the plane um where time and time again you you indeed read you know to thwart pirates
that's basically the type of language that is used when when talking about DRM and and why it's
implemented we've never actually had a chance to try it to try and see if it would work with just MP3's
free and clear and if what people would just pay for it I mean if you want to steal it if you can
steal it anyway it doesn't matter if it's if it's uh DRM you know anything that I can play
off of my computer I can record you know so I can easily make a make a copy if I'm willing to go through
all that but it's not even an issue of ease it's uh you know like there's some wide scale
operation where people are you know baking up millions of MP3's you know that so that it has to be
automated you know so it just makes no sense really um it's really because there's a guy in the middle
a guy in the middle who is seeing that the artists can go directly to their customers and they
can have a direct financial transaction and that's the piece that needs to be enabled and I think
that relationship is actually going to be pretty healthy particularly when you see how enthusiastic
people are getting in on the ground floor with an artist and kind of growing up with them
it's the same type of relationship that I saw with some podcasters I think and she sent me three
emails and I think it was Marilyn her name is Marilyn pretty sure who sponsored Mark from the
tartan podcast co-sponsored his his trip to the podcast expo you know it's that kind of relationship
and it's about it's not more than just the music it's about going to the shows and it's about
you know some form of interaction and buying the t-shirts and you know and promoting your your art
and that's that's the piece and you know so in the middle there's not a lot is needed I think that
the one you know how many had these great conversations you know what what what is making this happen
what is becoming really fun is podcasting is the discovery mechanism this is the thing that
Silicon Valley still hasn't figured out they're still talking about and I'm sure there's there is a place for
for matching up you know for recommendation engines of course for comparison engines you know
if you like that podcast you like this one but really when people are just talking on their podcast
and playing music and and we're listening to other podcasts and you know that's how we discover
and it doesn't have to be a text based you know search discovery type mechanism it can be just
part of listening and you know don't expect it to grow like wildfire immediately let it flow let it come
and and that's the you know that that's kind of the what is the word the ecosystem that I see
that is that is emerging and all the different services there I want to send out a you know a CD
to someone who purchases that with you know with nice liner notes and you know maybe something else
package with that that's what CD baby does and you know all these pieces are there who needs the
record company it really isn't necessary there's just no added value particularly if you look at the
if you look at the financial side of it you'll get such a minor piece from from the old system
and you'll have such a majority piece of each transaction literally
of this new system that's emerging that it will be really it will be worth it you'll make more
money with less hassle and you'll have more fun it's that simple and anyone can join in you know
anyone who wants it hello hey baby
wow pretty you are looking like Kate Bush now get in front of the microphone come on doing the
pond of get over there here this is Mike over there here is the lovely pod princess good morning everybody
have a mother I did the one but that it's good to see you honey look great
get close to the mic it goes to the mic you too dad yeah how was school yeah sit through house
drama the whole time and I fell asleep for the results what I was sleeping in the results you
guy keep going on and on and what was that for house drama house drama no like how we have the
groups which is close to the mic you gotta get close to the mic you know how we have the groups like the
houses yeah yeah what like the hair in Harry Potter yeah yeah what house are you in again
linecaster we lost we always do we suck oh you strive for such greatness that this I'm so proud
minute that's why oh okay well help him you weren't in it because it's for the younger kids oh okay
Gotcha well you couldn't you have coached the younger kids oh they already had additions for that and
I missed it my coaching younger kids what did you miss it you got to talk in the mic baby
yeah because it cuts out you got to talk into the mic well move the mic around so you can talk
into the mic and look at me there you go there you go okay
why my phone is sucking it does no my fault no no I didn't say it was your fault huh
I did that all right listen I'm gonna I'll finish the show and I'll come down and we'll play
can I have your digital camera oh I want to talk to you about that I want to I want to actually
try to buy you one on the airplane yeah yeah but they didn't have it so when we just go get get you
one because I want to can I test it out I want to see if I can do it and put it on the computer and
stuff it's fun yeah but why don't we go get it where we want to get your own camera tomorrow I can I'm leaving tomorrow
uh you want to take it with you no you don't want to take it to Holland oh it's just for
personal my space used what are you going to do are you going to put camera slot pictures
I don't remember slot pictures I just can tell like cool pictures like you're sort of my space
standard pictures the one where it's like camera dude I so wish I had I had come up with the
my space it is a really cool it's fucking cool everyone uses it I'm addicted to it right now what
will you use it for you just sit there the whole day and message people and add people and
just use it to write stuff you even have a weblog on it right could we add podcasts to it
you could because they have um my space music where you can add music that you play on your home page
and it's like my space safe so you can add it on to it yeah my space safe is that they're calling
it's not called my space safe but it is because the music that's that you can find on there is
safe to play on your own right page so they have something kind of like it I'd be able to have
you listen to the pod save music that work anything there a little bit yeah got some okay stuff
we got a whole bunch of new stuff and we got uh you heard of epitaph records no now we got a whole
bunch of now we got some you got some pretty uh we got some pretty big names in now now what talking
to the microphone what are you on camera I do give a shit I love you I mean I give that back
you're all you want to call outside yeah now you love hey would you please go look at
positive music network and tell me what we need to do okay is there no USB stick
um oh hold on one second
now you will you you take the pictures first and then I'll get you the USB thing okay
okay bye bye bye oh man okay let me give you this
do you believe anything is possible we do where are flink
we believe in an internet that's safe from viruses and scammers we're Earthlink
we believe your personal information should be just that personal and we believe your
internet should be a friend not a fo we're Earthlink make this smart choice visit earthlink.net
and discover what our internet experts can do for you earthlink we revolve around you
fries does mean he has a breaking weather to tell you about listen for the breaking news here
on popwether.com when weather news happens and it happens fast you sure listen to popwether.com
and tune in live to radio.ncwx.com get the latest example from usagweather.org
part of the hurricane's project and internet partnership radio
no you know I'm seeing more of that I'm seeing more a news base podcast I'm really loving the
idea loving the idea um they're my blackberries cutting it again with the help um I like the idea
of customized news so far um I still seem to have either read everything or was not interested in
the you know the pieces that were available that come through basically you know several hours
after after it's put together which of course is many hours after the news is created but there
are some like longer features let me see I got a great this is also very cool huh who sent
no oh man I got a forward from match for something that oh yeah here it is this is Brian no
Brian no um I first discovered him through well I can't remember if it was through the my Maryland
podcast or for was the other no I think I discovered him first I don't remember how but he has the
the Frank truth podcast which is all about the life and time of Francis Albert Sonatra
oh man and of course with the with my going purely pod safe he you know he really freaked out
because and I tell you with with with due cause because the Sonatra estate does not mess around when it
comes to their copyrights and you know so Brian of course is you know it's you know it was podcast
about his passions so imagine how horrible it is not to be able well you can still talk about it but
without the music you know you just it's that's almost impossible so I can only imagine if I
couldn't talk about the stuff that I like to talk about on my podcast that would be that's just horrible
like horrible thought so he's now converting that energy into into some other stuff and this thing is
the he's Matt he so he he felt also you know he loved mashups and he knows that I stopped my mashups
playing mashups you know he's trying to look for some kind of format and he came up with is what he
calls the the world news mashup this is the one from see from yesterday I think but you got to listen
to it he basically just read stuff off of his aggregator and I guess it's the you know just the
the short descriptions and yeah and that's the podcast you have a listen to this you'll like
world news mashup the news doesn't get any better now from our aggregator today's stories
US authorities say they will stop the first test by 22 runs as Pakistan bowl names a new security
advisor after last week's suicide bombings president Bush has traded his tech support career
for at least one infected machine after refusing to let a man dance with his girlfriend
Bush's nominee to succeed out in green spanish federal reserve chairman Richard Lustin
aka Mad Weinstein pledged yesterday to protect little policy makers while continuing anti-war
protest and experimenting with recreational drugs friends say green spanned said yesterday that the
US use of white phosphorus remains willing to invest in the deadly each find in one string of
bird flu as a key you in summit on the net opens in Tunisia police in Switzerland sees a collection
of thousands of families made homeless by hurricanes after an aggregate one-to-one draw in the
World Cup qualifying playoff how widespread is the damage from Sony's XCP root kits software
news statistical evidence says 568,200 networks including military and government targets
likely contain a found out lesbian and atom curries peaboring hands meanwhile the case against
Uganda's opposition leader goes to the intelligence agent as election protests are banned
and finally today where the held at Aaron Brown go news nights sucks now thanks a lot seen in the
mix of swam rickering
I was like whoa when I heard that it just blew me away for a second you know what he actually
sent me a demo of I guess it must have been the first episode that he was doing and I listened
to it and for some reason I didn't parse it you know and now I'm realizing what happened it's
because when you hear news like that that's how it goes by you know you never really kind of
whatever you know sounds right sounds really urgent sounds important and now that I'm hearing
that he's just literally mashing up news headlines like oh wait a minute now and I like it I really do
whoa
excellent dude keep in comment there's actually there's also a
world news mashup.com so you can subscribe to the feed over there excellent idea love it okay
just quick a couple things here Colin Wade monk heard you on the podcast about you know don't
rob musicians FYA you don't have to register your work with a copyright office for it to be
copyrighted your work only has to be in a fixed medium of expression for the 1976 copyright
revision tell people to save the money until there's money to be made okay yeah that that's just
the only reason I mentioned that is because that's the process that you have to go through for
Ask Capra BMI so yeah once you write something the minute you lift your pen from the paper that's
basically you're there you know you have a copyrighted work okay this is from Bob Bichler
Bichler great meeting you last weekend in Ontario well listening to Delta Sierra Charlie
281 I heard you struggling to find some good upbeat music one to point you to someone the
potting music network from New Jersey is named okay yeah I'm gonna open this up then his name is
Sean and how do I pronounce this more mail-o more mail-o more mail-o CC's played him a few times actually
when I when I played this track as I was getting ready for the show I recognized it being something
that the CC played in action and it's good that's Bob Bichler from the ordinary average guy podcast
the cow is something you can't take it with you anytime you're working hard and have a
week it's y'all's here I'm gonna try but there's some old ways to reason you know with the
level baby how long has it been I'll sent you lead in all the line get the hell out of my face
we're getting my back we're just doing it we're out of the world there's always the same
we're out of the world we're out of the world we're out of the world we're out of the world
we're out of the world we're out of the world we're out of the world we're out of the world we're out of the world
the vobbled me in the happiness I have to fill out up with things you better change your position
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
oh yeah yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
Turns out the same, in the end
I haven't done it
Well, I haven't done it
But this guy is only
There's a way, oh, oh
Baby, but I'm happy, love
Oh yeah
You can't dream of this in my world
I think I can help you, baby
Oh, oh, oh, oh
What's up?
I haven't done it, but I haven't done it
We're getting my back
We're just doing it, we're having a day
Well, I haven't done it
It's always the same, I haven't done it
We're having a day
Yeah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Baby, but I'm happy, love
Oh, yeah
I've had enough
Sean
I mess it up again
Let me get it here
Oh, oh, oh, oh
The ID3 tags weren't, oh, messed up
Sean Moore below, okay
P.S. as the ordinary average guy
No, I don't work for Sean, I just dig his tunes
Yeah, I hear you totally
Well, we've had a different Friday type of show today
I realize actually that you have two different homes
that you're living in, you are expecting things to sound
Like they sounded for the past week
or you were and then things sound different
And I'm realizing that the, you know,
have these Apple, Harmon, Carden, whatever
Craydon, speakers with the subwoofer
It's really nice, but it's not like
The acoustics that I'm used to
Of the MM50 that that's what I have
The iMac in the, in the condo hooked up to
And that has, it has, I don't know
Is it like I almost want more direct sound
And of course, I can slip the iPod into it
It's just, it's a minebender
So, daily source code.com is where you can subscribe
To the podcast feed, it's also, there's a one-click link
In the show notes and on curry.com
It's all over the place
And he feedback us into to me, Adam at curry.com
You know, my Gmail, by the way, after I got that
Super geeky extra, extra action space
They gave me four gigs
Instead of the usual two as a special
Special geek feature
I'm already up to 85% of that
Three and a half gigs, it's outrageous
They can't grow fast enough
To provide me with the space I need
With the requirements I have, it's unbelievable
That's, anyway
Promotes.podshow.com
If you have any promos, I promise what I'll do
And who knows, I might even do a show over the weekend
Since I'm kind of in the vibe now
And tomorrow I'll have my thoughts all straightened out
And maybe I can explain a little bit more
What I was attempting to talk about today
So I do appreciate you listening to my ramblings
Well, so we have to talk about it
I think that's it
Let me just get some one more piece of pod
Say can use the take us out just into the weekend
Let me just grab one of my favorites
So I play this for my tunes and I have to make a
Was it like a magic playlist where they call that a smart playlist
That says no podcast otherwise
The podcasts, even though they're label podcasts
And they're in a special podcast category
They'll show up and they'll play in a shuffle
Which is not what I want from music
So let me see
How about we do
Oh, this is cool, we'll just do a little bit of
Awesome jazz everybody
Yes, the take you into the weekend
As I want you all to enjoy
With yours and yours and yours
Stay subscribe now
Here's the Marriott Jazz Quintent
One other pod show pod cast
Stick it in your ear