Delta Sierra Charlie 1-9-2
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed what you can hear since radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something or nothing to say.
It's Adam Curry!
You are a bitch!
Oh yeah!
I apologise, I'ma dick!
Oh dick some respect!
Wanky stuff!
Oh yeah!
You're an unfamiliar dude!
B-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d.
I bet you were hearing that wild cherry sign,
I was like, what is that?
7 things is 78, something like that.
Really think I'd give it shit shit shit
Well, what a hell of thick. I never did without that色 fashiony thing. The colour all
You're a bird man
A new man made me cry. I hate you
You know, I'm an idiot
of the G-Move, the of the G-Move.
Have you been drinking?
Oh yeah.
It's the MTV.
It's the TV.
It's the Disney.
What you just said is one of the most insanely idiotic things I've ever heard.
At no point were you even close to anything that could be considered irrational thought.
Everyone in this room is now dumber for having lessons to it.
To it.
Oh boy.
It was $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Done the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this genre.
Hey everybody.
How you doing?
It is Thursday the 9th of June.
Yeah.
As expected.
Didn't have my head on straight yesterday.
Like it's ever on straight.
Apologies.
Yesterday was not Tuesday.
It was Wednesday.
But of course it was actually still new music Tuesday.
Because we hold those on Wednesday.
Wednesday is here on the daily source.
Right?
Beautiful weather and gill for it at the Curry Cottage.
Man.
I'm a little bit fuzzy today.
I think that's kind of what happened yesterday.
How often is it happen that you actually think for an entire day that is yesterday?
Oh my goodness.
And we got a lot lined up for it today.
Found some funky stuff that came into the email.
I've got an amazing blues song for Pod save music.
Of course the obligatory promos.
No hit to this today.
The young palette was a pretty sparse but that's quite okay.
What we've pulled for today is voices from the vault.
So play along with your movie, a trivia brain.
Okay, I've been on the phone all morning.
Still lots of crap to clean up in the Netherlands.
It's really hard when you move from one country to the next.
The more you've participated in the community, the harder it is to extract yourself from it.
You have no idea how hard it is actually to shut down contracts for power.
And electricity, gas, parking garages, you name it.
There's always someone with a handout from more.
Which is a little bit discouraging but it's not anyway.
So it's, it hasn't been kind of a downer morning.
But I'm not going to let any of that.
Not one single bit of that takeaway from the fun that I have every single day doing this show.
At least when I have time to do this show.
Take it off with a mashup.
This is in light of, well, the jury is still being out on Michael Jackson.
I think you'll like this one.
Don't stop movie Billy Jean S. Club 7 versus Michael Jackson.
Right here on the Daily Source Code. How about a baseline?
All right.
I'll take synthesizers then.
The center is by Derek Peters.
Got another Dutch guy.
There's a face.
Everybody's moving through the rhythm.
That's a side.
It's a crazy world.
But tonight's the right.
It's the two eight stars.
Don't be left behind.
I just feel the music moving through me everywhere.
And don't pass the nation baby.
We don't need to care if there's a place to be.
If you need the right and you can't shut up.
Then you take you back.
And just go.
When we're married, baby.
How can season with your eyes?
It's very rough.
It's not the way.
It's wrong.
It's right.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
Round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round
, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round,
round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round
Don't shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout, shout
Don't stop and move in
Forget about you feel tonight, let's listen to your heart, let's clap the skies
You know, it's a reason why, let's listen to the sound, let's thank you for the love
You know, it's a reason why, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's
listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to a sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let's listen to the sound, let
my friends playing Michael Jackson on the daily source code down the
reason for that. Actually by the time you hear this podcast I don't know
the jury may still be out the jury may be in. I still want to pledge my
support from Michael Jackson. I met the man. I think he's if anything he's
asexual. We've discussed that many many times on the source code but what
really it really sucks is all these other stories that crop up and I just
have to feel a little bit of that. Because I've witnessed this myself. I
see there's a what is it that was a CNN article. Michael Jackson's going to
lose the Beatles catalog and you know and they report this as research news but
you know the first paragraph alone says according to people familiar with
the transaction you know it's like I've had so many people guess about my
finances or about whatever is going on with any kind of companies or sometimes
even legal hassle and you know what happens and this has been identified by
many people and once you start giving out interviews and seeing that what
comes back is not what you meant to communicate of course it is what you
communicated because that's a two-way street you know it's whatever you say
whatever the person hears they probably already have a story written in their
head and they're just feeling the blanks and their own blanks and they miss out
on the on the bullets you're shooting on the on the live load so that is it is
your miss communication and that's just something you got to learn and yeah
you can never really get it 100% the way you want it very rarely I would say
but people take really cheap shots they really do in the press it's yeah
it's they forget that there is a person behind Michael Jackson and it's funny
because I was I had an email conversation with Father Roderick from the Catholic
Insider and he he put up a really funny interview with the Arnold Schwarzenegger
today at Catholic Insider.com now he didn't really interview the governor
but you probably heard that Schwarzenegger is podcasting himself so he
spliced it up and he put together an interview with Arnold's answers it was
very cute it was funny and obviously you know was meant as a joke and he's
getting all kinds of flack in the Netherlands which is a country that that does
this all the time you know saying he's politically motivated and what what
Father Roderick is really noticing now is he's getting some fame and when or
notoriety or recognition or whatever you want whatever you word you want to
use once you're out there you start to slowly develop a target and the
more you're in the media in the in the press the larger that target becomes and
it just seems to be it's always been this way I believe but it seems now
more than ever you know when news organizations and news programming is
looking for something shocking something you know that we can identify with
and they're looking for the next thing to roll out well we all can identify with
drama so what's happening to Michael Jackson is the identification of drama for
the audience not that we have the same type of drama but right and high and
getting kicked down that's that's you know the rollercoaster that's pretty much
what it seems to be and and in the Netherlands people really love doing that
to people who are notorious or famous or or recognized in the media so I'm
saying a special prayer for my buddy Father Roderick for sure it's P-dog no it's
not it is yeah look at this P-dog this is P-W Fenton create we're a radio for
radios digital flots and I'm here to tell you I am a big fan of Mad wine
steams yeast radio I am also here to make a confession anyone who is
listened to digital flots and knows that I often tell personal stories from my
life but I think that you should know that there are still some things I haven't
talked about one of those things is that for my whole adult life I have secretly
felt that I was a lesbian trapped in a man's body I just can't help it ever since
puberty I've just been attracted to women oh I'm so glad I got that off my
chest thanks Madge you rock my world and I'm not ashamed to say it
hello Adam my name is Dawn Coco when I'm a blind person from Sacramento
California I do a podcast called blind tech on this particular program will
explore windows programs from a screen reading perspective I'll teach you the
ins and outs of some of my favorite programs how they work and how you can best
use them you can subscribe to my podcast by going to feeds dot feed borner dot
com slash djc that's feeds dot feed borner dot com slash djc I look forward to
chatting with you and I hope you'll enjoy my podcast as much as I enjoy
producing them thank you yeah right on good to see the blind casters joining
the fray and that's interesting I've had a lot of conversations recently
about something called accessibility of your Mac user then you you recognize
this it's in your system preferences I know Windows has something equivalent but
I'm not quite sure what it's called maybe accessibility as well I don't know
and it's basically how the interface reacts with spoken with spoken digitized
voice to tell the the user what it's doing or what the mouse is doing or
what button you're hovering over etc and let me to think excuse me that's
let me to think that or to wonder if iTunes actually has good accessibility and
if we need any additional accessibility specifically for podcasts I couldn't
think of any off the bat but then again I'm not in the blind situation so I
I you know maybe I should pondered more maybe you have some ideas maybe some of
the blind casters out there some good ideas and please let me know if if
iTunes has good accessibility built into it at all probably does because I
think the Mac is is generally reasonably good at that and I was talking to
one of the developers on the iPod 11 team Andrew Grummit the other day and
he said that that's one of the things that he's really concentrating on is
getting a lot more accessibility built into iPod 11 so that's very good news
and out there's big markets big markets are opening up let me see what else
oh man should I do this now yeah I'm going to do this now this was so funny I
got an email yesterday home I have to get on my browser here was it dawn's
blog I think it was hold on I'm going to open up what is this opening up now my
computer is this opening up Safari or yeah it's opening up Safari okay this was
a cloning warning complete conspiracy theorist theorist blog post from
Don's blog and of course I'll post the link in the show notes listening to
the recent Steve Jobs keynote at Apple's worldwide developer conference I
was struck with a similarity in voice between Roz Ho who was one of the
Microsoft that she is what is she oh Microsoft Mac business unit leader and
the venerable Bill Gates so this is what Don is basically saying he's saying and
if you saw the worldwide developer conference keynote thing you know Steve Jobs
usually brings people up on stage and one of them was Roz Ho who looks very
cute in the picture here on Don's blog and so she's the Mac business unit leader
over at Microsoft and what he wants us to do is listen to the original clip of
Roz so I'm going to click on that now see what she says thank you Steve is getting
to be quite a habit to be here it's my pleasure to be here on stage today and
to be involved in the exciting changes from Apple for choices than ever okay so
that is Roz and then and here comes Don this is the same file process
through garage band with the tone lowered a fraction and he says is it
was getting to be quite a habit to be here it's my pleasure to be here on stage
today and to be involved in the exciting changes from Apple I'm telling you I
think Don has a point here there's something going on it could be that Microsoft
is spinning out clones and they're everywhere
hello my name is Scott and I'm Kelly and we're the creators of my virtualband.com
I'm my virtualband.com members from all over the world collaborate on mine
try to record songs for instance members can take a tune like this
and turn it into this
you can hear more great songs created at myvirtualband.com and our podcasts available at
www.radio.myvirtualband.com and if you're a singer, songwriter or musician and
would like to join in the fun simply go to www.myvirtualband.com register and you
can start collaborating today until next time I'm Kelly and I'm Scott rock-on
all right I think that's you know it's not a new idea people have been collaborating
on on music on the internet through MIDI sound files etc for a long long time
what was it called myvirtualband.com I had an idea for them all of a sudden virtualband.com
there we go so they have a podcast let me see blah blah blah myvirtualband featured songs
okay because here's here's the big idea I think for these guys let me see
yeah exactly they don't they're not doing it okay so the idea here is you create a soundtracking
you upload that in some form of in some form that can be imported into someone else's music
program and they can add tracks and then they can re-upload the result of that so
here's what I think is a really big idea what if you created an RSS 2.0 with enclosure
feed to a podcast feed for each of those songs so basically I could subscribe to a group
whether a participant in the group or not I could subscribe to what they're working on on a
particular song so when the first original is released you know the one that everyone's going to
work on that automatic comes into my iPod or my iTunes whenever and I can listen to that.
now when someone does something to it and uploads a new version then that new version would
flow to me automatically and I could actually be a bystander witnessing that creation in the process
I think that's a pretty hot shit that would really rock pod save music now on the source code
and dear the lights come on darling let's get real close
because I want you to hold me tight
I want you to break all day and all in just for a night
let's let love have its way
and to feel your tender hands all over my body
and my face you both get lost in ecstasy
has little
And a heart, finger tips
We live for all loves
With fantasy
Every chorus
Little brain pure
Happiness
Tonight is love
In the past
Didn't mean
Oh, I really love
In the instant scene
If you left a thrill
Because of what?
We'll share
We don't belong
Each other
Tonight
It's time to play
We'll get along
We'll see next to Cine
Oh, little, little, little
And we
Let's play
We'll get along
We'll see next
Oh, little, little
And we
Just where we're just here
We
Let's play
We'll see next
We'll show you
Every heart
We'll see next
We'll show you
Every heart
I just want you to hold me to touch me baby
Warning, expert of coming.
Fuck American Idol.
You hear that you think, well, of course that has that has a record label, right?
Uh, uh, pod safe music.
Hold on, let me just stop that for a second.
Lady Bianca, let love Habit's way.
Man, I was just holding it throught by that.
That was great.
Links on the show blog.
Yeah, let's play along.
Good sun to 16.
Go over to the voices from the vault.com website.
Follow the link to the voices from the vault.
Telling to page.
That's voices from the vault.com.
If you can identify the voices you might,
then the likelihood of a brand new high-punch of all.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
The master is waiting up.
I'll let her go and get this for it.
Cutty on the fire.
See you soon.
In the vault.
There you go.
Had an overture voices from the vault.com.
Can win a nice...
From the vault.
Oh, man.
I love that.
The imaging is just awesome.
Hey, now I got a nice email from Aaron from Bitterman Circle.
What's this?
Is there more on that?
Or is this like some secret message?
So, back mask, can we need to do here?
Yeah.
From the Bitterman Circle podcast.
And he has invite...
Whoa.
Spider.
And he's invited Christina and I to...
And a friend, actually, I think,
to go and head on over to the Weasers Show as a coming through town next Tuesday.
So, that'll be pretty cool.
Maybe we should podcast some of that.
At least, hopefully we'll get backstage.
We can do some of the backstage podcast and got another.
All right.
That's it for today.
Nice.
Nice round that offer on 30th.
Oh.
That works for me.
Tomorrow we'll be Friday and...
Looking forward toward the weekend.
I'll have plenty more to roll out for you.
Hot safe music, promos.
Mashup or two.
Mashups are going well.
By the way, really appreciate all the suggestions you've been emailing in.
For those mashups, it's Mashup for podshow.com.
To submit your podsafe music to us, podsafe podshow.com.
And for everything else, submit at podshow.com.
Feedback, Adam Curry.com.
Audio feedback, also welcome.
If you want to touch the MP3 file, not too big please.
I think I'm at 84% now on Gmail.
I might too big limit.
So either they start upping it again.
Give me that infinity plus one or I'm going to have to start
leasing some whole mail with attachments.
Show notes on daily source code.com as well as on www.curry.com
where you are free to comment.
Our guys at the latest show and of course the podcast feed
a dance source code.com.
Okay.
Patricia's out shopping still.
So when she comes back, I'll have to help her with that.
I'm going to hop on Skype reveal USA.
Start working with everyone in the company,
desperate all over the world.
From Belgium, the Netherlands, the UK,
the New York, the San Francisco, Chicago,
the soda, Tampa.
Man, this is getting a good name.
I have a thought it would.
Thanks again for listening.
Stay subscribed and I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Bye bye.