Deelda Shara charli, 23,4…
You're DJ...
Ay you!
Now continues!
Your DJ...
Has only just begun...
Oh, $16 billion worth of air
playing strap to my ass.
In the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
And it is September 2nd, 2005.
The thank god it's Friday. It's nip the store's coat.
Everybody, thank you very much.
Bigger all birds for that wonderful thing.
God it's Friday.
Opening takes me back to my radio days from the 80s.
It is Friday coming to you from the Curry Cottage on September 2nd, 2005.
Your source code with a lot about Hurricane Katrina.
And some exciting news back here back at home.
The bar stool has arrived.
Tom Hickey was over here and see about an hour and a half ago
from winningsupplies.com.
And brought me this beautiful fire retardant bar stool
that is perfect for the Curry Oddcast Complex.
Of course, I'm posting a picture of that on the web wall
later today.
And obviously I think to winningsupplies.com and the show notes.
So I am completely set.
My feet don't hurt.
I got this and say I'm here on the left.
And other accrued commands which are important to the show.
I'm just looking at the line up.
I can already see the show is going to be long.
It could even be like 45 or 50 minutes long.
There's so much incoming sound that I want to share with you.
We have on the scene reports from one of the domes.
I have to get to watch one of his interviews with refugees.
And we've got many, many PSAs.
And I have a new system set up so that all of these are available for you to download
and use in your own podcast.
We're talking about that later.
Exactly how that works.
But it should be pretty self-explanatory.
To start it off, let's see.
Art from mashup town sent over a mashup.
He says it didn't think that he'd heard this one on the source code.
But he thinks it's one of the most technically perfect mashups he's ever heard.
And I have to agree.
Let's see.
It's Brad Productions.
Switch of course is brought to you by a mashup town dot car.
Mashup town records actually.
There you go.
It's probably one of the most successful 80s records of all time.
Dreaming in your sleep.
There's so many feet as close about me.
You're always playing with depth because we haven't managed to what I've seen.
Hey, you bailin' sick of y'all.
You're deaf and livin' restin' y'all.
And walkin' on the crooked mouth.
Hey, you're deaf and dumb.
You're party-parin' living.
Watch it's equal to you, but careful.
What you give in, Bill.
You're fever-turning.
You're shakin' as rich in.
You can start to love a good time for stuff you've been.
Can you feel a little lie?
Dream on.
There's no time for hesitate.
In vain it's ready, pain is waiting.
Price do it, check your cadence.
I'm on it, I'm invited.
Been a creep beneath the fallen skin.
It's a list without a lift within you.
There'll be fever-turning, shaking as rich in.
You can start to love a good time for stuff you've been.
Hey, you're deaf and dumb.
You're party-parin' living.
Watch it's equal to you, but careful.
What you give in, Bill.
You're fever-turning.
Can you feel a little lie?
Dream on.
How many times would I live at?
I said how many times would it live?
How many times would it live at?
And I'm your colleague, but I'm so shame upon the universe
It knows its lines, it's where we're heard
It's not you and it's dragged you down to where there is no hollow ground
We're holding this, it's never found
And it's not the coming, it's hard, it's hard living
Watch your teeth, I'll kill you, but careful
What's the difference?
There'll be a fever coming, it's shaking, it's twitching
Because you're not sure over, but that's what's up you get through
Can you feel a little love?
To be free-more.
The Brad Productions, mashuptown.com, dreamin' your sleep, mashup here on the Daily
Source code, and before I upload all of the show notes, I will be sure to put in my iTunes,
my brand new iTunes affiliate link to the Romantics, of course, one of the foundations
of that mashup talking in your sleep, because Andrew Makado, who I believe works at eBay,
heard my call the other day when I said, hey, I've been denied an iTunes affiliate status,
and he knew some people, and he started some instant message sessions, and got some email
going and loan behold.
I was approved.
I love it.
Thank you very much, Andrew, and I will do you proud and do you just as my friend.
I'm also going to put in links to the hittest songs, which I haven't been able to do
yet, because of course, I haven't listened to the hittest to keep it a surprise.
So that's cool.
And I saw that youngpalette actually, a youngpalette.com, started putting iTunes affiliate links
back into his weblog, and I saw you already sold seven.
So it's getting somewhere, it's doing something, it's doing some good.
So I'll be sure to put in links, iTunes affiliate links, to all the songs played in mashups
and hittest, etc.
Again, Andrew Makado, my man, thank you very much.
So the new bar stool, how can I describe this thing?
You just have to take a look at the picture, which I'll post, not as a part of the show
notes, but as of just on curie.com, it's fabulous.
It is exactly the right height for me.
It would be too low for someone smaller than I am, but of course, they wouldn't have
this monstrous podcast complex, this is height either.
But it's great.
And during the mashup, I was actually sitting there, it's got a nice gas damping system,
so I could bounce up and down a little bit and just kind of, you know, giving us a little air
cushion ride.
They're very, very nice.
Tom Hickey came over earlier today from winningsupplies.com and installed the bar stool,
which was not a very hard process, of course.
It was nice, nice meeting him, and he is just outside of Guilford.
And if you were looking for a great bar stool, because yes, I was giving this one, then
winningsupplies.com is the place for you.
So I've been playing with Omni Outliner Pro version 3.
And I discovered something new, which I'm pretty high on right now, that you can actually
drag MP3 files or any audio file into the outline and check this.
So you can, so I have next up is the daily download, and then I expanded the outline
and underneath there is a little quick time player.
And I can actually play it right from the outline, I'll give you an example here, warning
the following show.
So that was played right from the outline, I could actually probably do the entire show
just from this outline.
Unfortunately, when you collapse a node, it resets the sound clip back to the beginning.
If you could queue it up and it would stay that way, and it would actually carry over
that way when you save the file, now that would be the cuts me out.
So it doesn't do that, what it does do is when you export it all to the dynamic HTML version
of the outline, which I linked to at the top of all the show notes, you can actually
click right on links, as you expand the node, you can click right on the link and you can
download the audio file.
So from today, we're going to test this out and see how it works from today, you'll be
able to download all of the promos, mashup, hit test, everything that I have in my outline,
you'll be able to access from the show notes, which I think is a great way to do it.
Also, when I export to OPML, same deal, right, so you can take this OPML file and
parse it and you'll also be able to to grab all of the actual elements used during the
daily source code.
So that I think is it is mighty fine, and I'm just realizing that I did something pretty stupid.
Damn, I wanted to have this piece queued up of the daily download, and I didn't even
load it into, I did load it here, but I don't think I queued it up, let me just start
this, oh man, I blew it, I really blew it on that hold on, because Chris Rockwell, I'll
make it available for you to download, you said, do you have you got to listen to the
show, Chris Rockwell, who of course does the daily download, did a poopcast experiment,
trying to dump off of the second story roof of his house onto a target down below,
and he's afraid of heights, and what was so funny about it, and I listened to the show,
the trisha, of course, walked in, she wanted to admit it, no woman will ever admit they're
fan of the daily download, I don't think, and it was so funny, he was trying to coerce his
wife into going down and seeing where the load dropped, and so she basically, I'll just
tell you the story, so I'll go downstairs and take a look, and then she doesn't, and then
this is legendary line where Chris says, she just doesn't care about the show, she doesn't
want to go down and participate, she doesn't care about the show, dude, you're pooping from
the roof, women don't, and don't like that, it's really awesome though, you have to listen to that,
link to from the show notes, of course, at dailysourcecode.com, so Hurricane Katrina, without
it out, bad fricking news, and it's very, very hard to get any context of the situation,
I've been to New Orleans many times, and Patricia and I have been there during Marty Graw,
MTV Live, Marty Graw, it's a fantastic time, we were there with Heather Locklear, and I think she
was just with Tommy Lee at the time, and everyone was showing their show and their tits, and even
Patricia, she had a lot of beats, let me tell you, and so it really does hit home for just anyone who
was visited there, PW Fenton of digital flotsome did a short special edition of his podcast,
which is just, it gives me goosebumps, or gave me goosebumps when I listened to it. I encourage
you to go listen to that edition of digital flotsome, it'll, I think it really will give you
another perspective, or someone else's perspective on New Orleans, oh man, I've been down there,
I've had some good times in New Orleans, and it's gone, this cleanup could take a really,
really long time, and it seems like a lot of the preparation that could have been made was just
botched, so I'm sure we'll be talking about this for many, many months, if not years to come,
and the podcasts are jumping into it big time, and I've received so many different
audio files that I just want to play a couple for you, and I'm just going to run through a whole
bunch here because there's some good stuff, and everyone, of course, is pointing to the same thing
to redcross.org, please donate whatever you can. This is Brian, with the special announcement urging
your support for relief efforts to the victims of Hurricane Katrina. My wife and I were married in
the city of New Orleans, Louisiana, and the days that we spent there together are some of the most
memorable and wonderful of our lives. We have great memories of the places we visited,
candle mass on Sunday morning at Old St. Patrick's Cathedral, and so many other wonderful places,
and all of the great food in that city. Also, we have lots of affection for the wonderful
people that we met there who were so kind and helpful to us during our stay, like Jerry and Lee,
from Lake Heralons, and Wendell from Commanders. Of course, right now, the people of New Orleans,
and people throughout the South Coast, are suffering terribly as a result of Hurricane Katrina,
and they need our help. upwards of a million people will be homeless for an indefinite period of time,
weeks, maybe months. So I'm sending this message out to urge you to keep the victims in your prayers
and your thoughts, and also if you can, make a donation. The American Red Cross has already begun
the largest single disaster relief mission in their history. And they're telling us right now that
every donation is critical, and every donation can help no matter how small. I visited their website
this morning on the web at www.redcross.org and made my donation and it took about five minutes.
You can also call the 800 number but expect some delays there, but that number is 1-800
to help now. If you visit my website at www.nobe.com, that's n-o-e-b-i-e.com,
there'll be a link at the top of the page for Hurricane relief efforts, and links from there to
both the Red Cross and the Salvation Army USA website where you can donate. And those are the two
largest organizations leading the relief effort. Please do what you can to help, and thank you in advance
for your efforts. We're all concerned with the disaster from Hurricane Katrina, and here at Radio.in
HCWX.com, HurricaneProject.org, and podweather.com. We're going to help with the efforts to get the
people infected back on their feet by donating to the American Red Cross. Please visit our website
radio.knavcwX.com, HurricaneProject.org, and podweather.com, click on the Red Cross Vanners to make
a donation directly. We will also be donating any funds created from the purchases on any of the
sponsor banners on those sites. Additionally, RadioNVCWX will match the funds created by you clicking
on the Google ads on those sites. RadioNVCWX, donation drive will last through September 30, 2005,
and all many received will be given to the American Red Cross. So please visit Radio.knavcwX.com,
HurricaneProject.org, and podweather.com. Click to make a donation so we all can help with the long
recovery from devastating Hurricane Katrina. Hi, this is Steve Gilmore, the Gilmore gang. All of us here
at Podjo and the technology community in Silicon Valley are hoping that you'll find it in your
hearts and minds to support the people of America's Gulf Coast, as they struggle with the devastation
of Hurricane Katrina. Whether it's through the Red Cross or online web communities or your
local churches, mosques and synagogues, please give them money, time, or just plain hope you can.
It all will make a difference. Thanks. Hi Adam, it's Richard. Somebody sent me this audio comment
which I think is really, really interesting. So I just woke up, but this is from Dutch TV coverage
of the Hurricane Katrina, and it sounds like it's, I haven't been paying attention to the coverage
here in the US actually, but from what I understand, this is probably a lot more accurate and
it definitely displays why there's need to give a lot of money to these refugees. Okay,
here it is. Thanks Adam. We got a few, we got to steal from each other so we can say,
about it a few hours ago. We're going to dive at each other because I haven't had nothing
to walk on.
I like this.
Ooh!
Can you see one?
One, two, three.
Wow!
The other one's up.
We have regular ames on!
Absolutely.
Sorry.
No!
He's bad!
Surface cause success!
o6d seul-a Live Moth,
est people to just realize it's also a party battle!
No food no rem kennen nothing.
Whatever we here we've been taking a
Million for, you girls arrived.
The thing got the food right here
never shodding right here
this world's a foreign country
All the way, away, away.
Noogly don't want you to
Hey !
Yeah, hey away !
Oh no!
I did it!
No!
Say it, don't give us the guts!
No, no, no!
Look, gave right there.
No!
No, don't give us the guts!
We're going to know I won't.
No!
We've got no man to get out of this just like you!
But we can't even.
Not about Rowing Come It's not about Rich people, poor people, it's about people.
Nobody wants to hurt anybody in this city, nobody wants to hurt these people who have these businesses.
There's nobody in charge, the National Guard,
there's the police, there is nobody, somebody needs to contact charge and put organization
and get these people to safety to get them close, the basic things that they need to live
from day to day.
People are dying, they're dying, babies are dying, they're all dead over there, right?
Not dead in the jail!
People are dying, we still have it out here.
Yeah, it's pretty chilling stuff.
Thank you, Richard Boosting for sending that in.
I found another podcast.
I think that came in through email.
The Zip 71101 podcast.
And that's by Ron Stroop.
And he actually went into one of the refugee centers and spoke to a young woman,
which is I think you'll really hear a couple of sides of what's going on right now.
Did you listen to this?
Well, I'll just call it a sound seeing tour.
Okay, I'm excited.
The Hirsch College team now have clearance to talk to people.
And the entire floor, the bottom floor of the Hirsch College team is filled with mattresses,
people reclining.
There's a couple of TVs here and there.
People are watching TV, sitting in lawn chairs.
People are bringing in food and clothing.
I talked to one volunteer that told me there's another 200 people coming in on a bus
and just within the hour.
So I would say estimating from position I'm at now that there are over five or 600 people
just on the floor.
And many are walking around.
It is cool in here.
And there are no windows.
And if you want to go to the restroom, of course you have to leave the building,
the facility, not the facility, but the main floor.
And go out to one of the server restaurants.
Volunteers have tables set up and they're working throughout the entire complex.
Bringing in food, clothing, as I mentioned.
Some of the refugees are reading the newspaper.
Others watching television while others are talking.
And just sitting somewhere reclining.
And there are elderly.
There's a few walkers of wheelchairs.
And from this viewpoint, just about what you're sitting on television.
They need warrants.
Only it's 300 miles away.
It's three-four.
So there must be people here from Louisiana, Mississippi, as well.
So we're going down on the floor here.
And we're going to talk to folks to see where they're from and how they're doing.
Okay, what's your first name?
Tami.
Hello, Tami. You're from where New Orleans?
New Orleans.
Same for North Paris.
Okay.
And can you tell me how long you've been here?
This is going to be my third nice sleep in here.
Okay.
And have they been taking care of you?
They've really been taking care of us.
We've got a lot of clothes, lots of food.
They have a lot.
They have countless available for everybody.
There's plenty of volunteers.
There's so much food.
There's so much hell.
That's great.
They even keep on animals here.
Have a dog, go back.
Oh, really?
Have you heard anything about your home?
Everything's on the wall.
Everything's underwater.
Did you live near downtown New Orleans or in that area?
Yeah.
Oh, I got a new name.
Shall met.
Okay.
My whole family stayed behind.
Did they?
Have you heard from your family?
No.
The only person I have with me is my twin brother.
Okay.
And you guys, how old are you?
25.
Okay.
And your parents?
They haven't heard.
They stayed home.
Have you made any attempt to reach them?
Or do they have cell phone?
It's on work.
It still phones aren't working.
Okay.
So, you're pretty much at the mercy of whatever happens in the next few days.
Have they said anything about when you'd be able to leave?
No.
No, they said we could be here for a couple months.
That's correct.
That's what I've been hearing.
And the president, I don't know if you've seen the news in the last hour or so.
Right now, in the city of New Orleans, people have already,
the government's already, you sent National Guard troops in.
And there were over something like 23, 24,000 people in the super dome.
And they were back in waiting in my buses and taking them to the Astrid home.
I guess you've heard that.
Some of them have come here.
Some have come here.
Yes.
Okay.
And they had to, you know, give them a shot.
Wasn't that everything first?
Because it was in contaminated water.
And the bodies that overflow.
Yeah.
They're telling us over a thousand bodies right now,
that they know a one state trooper told one of my colleagues that.
I'm really, I was really in the paper.
They just push the dead bodies.
Right.
That's right.
Are you a college student?
Yeah.
Okay.
I was going to say school soon, but not anymore.
But I also have to rebuild the light here.
Exactly.
That's what everybody, everybody pretty much is saying.
We'll find a job in Texas.
And that was in Texas.
Okay.
I'm free for it.
This is the third child I've been to.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Since this half.
Okay.
A lot of people are saying they're going to stay here and find a job and live here.
I don't have a home to go to.
Did you drive here?
Okay.
So you have a vehicle?
I don't know if you've heard this, but someone said there was a three-foot shark going
down to Nal Street.
Oh, no.
And there have been reports of alligators and snakes.
And so this is a good place to be.
You don't want to be there at this particular time.
I've had, I've had like seven different families.
I already come up to my trying to die.
I actually, um, tomorrow.
This lady came to see me today and told me that she, as she has a turtle.
And it's got two bedrooms.
And she lights it up and I brought my brother.
And she's going to go clean it up.
And she's just going to find a job.
Great.
And so we can get out of here.
And she's letting bring my doll.
Good.
I've cried a thousand of the tears.
Like I'm, I'm so tired of crying.
It's like, I don't even have a family anymore.
This is the only family in my head.
Get your brother.
And he's, he said, he's, he's so devastated.
He's like, he wishes he would just stay at home.
Because he can't take that whole family's call.
I hope you hear from your family soon.
I hope so too.
Thank you.
Hi, this is Michael Butler from the Rockham Roll Geek Show.
I'm here to ask for your assistance on behalf of the victims of Hurricane Katrina.
Now I live in Florida for most of my life.
And we had hurricanes pretty much every year.
So we're pretty used to it.
But we never had any hurricanes that were as bad as the one that just recently had in New Orleans.
So do everybody a favor.
Go to redcross.org or call 1-800-HELP now.
You can donate as little as $5.
And your donation will provide 8 such as blanket, shelter, food, and drinking water.
You know, do your part.
I'm going to go to PayPal as soon as I finish this message and donate more than $5.
So I hope you roll too.
Thanks a lot for listening.
Thank you, Michael.
Oh, there you have it.
It's, uh, man.
Shilling, absolutely chilling stuff.
You got a link in the show notes.
In case you can't remember redcross.org.
Pod show, of course, getting involved as possible with everybody putting up redcross
banners and donating funds and doing what we can.
And we really, uh, I'm pretty pissed off at our administration.
I'm, you know, it's too simple to say President Bush.
He's just a PR nightmare in this case.
Really, really fucked that one up.
Um, but our administration, uh, did not do a good job with, uh, with our citizens.
And in this case is the golf course that could be the East Coast.
It could be the West Coast.
It could be your coast.
It could happen to you.
Uh, I think we need to deal with, uh, after after we get the situation stabilized,
which could be weeks, it seems.
And we definitely need to, um, you know, we need some inquisition and all this.
How could this be so ill-prepared when shit.
Every single weather channel and weather person knew what was going to happen.
It was predicted and, uh, the relief came way too slow, uh, way too little way too late.
And, uh, when all of a sudden done, uh, I think there will be, uh,
what's that?
Uh, car alarm.
When all of a sudden done, uh, someone will have to account for, uh, how this was handled.
Because this is not the way, um, the United States is supposed to work.
Okay, daily source code. How fucking bummed out are you now, huh?
I have a little bit, let's see if we can, uh, kick it up a level here.
Hi, Adam. It's David Gary from Chub Creek.
We love the daily source code.
Hey, time to kick it.
Did, did you kick it?
Nope.
Did you kick it?
Well, can you kick it?
I wanted you to kick it after I said that.
Okay.
Hi, Adam.
It's David Gary from Chub Creek and we love the daily source code.
Kick it.
Potcho.com makes no claims regarding the quality of its potchoes or the sanity of its producers.
Listen at your own risk.
Hey, man.
Why, it's me, Luis.
Stand back.
Well, we could die like this in children.
You can at least count your blessings to the music as great.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, everyone's a critic.
But Senator Jez is right about one thing.
If you want the best music available from Independent and Pod Safe Artist,
then look no further than Reggie Felicity.
Located at Reggie Felicity.net.
The Reggie Felicity Potcho also features my world view, which is kind of excuse seeing
as I'm an American city boy that somehow found himself stuck in small town rural England.
So come in, kick back and enjoy.
It's more fun than five monkeys in a unicycle.
Well, at least as fun as a unicycle with a flat tire.
I still have to fire that guy.
Reggie Felicity.
All righty.
This is your daily source code.
We're moving into the weekend big weekend.
I turned the big four one this weekend.
And I've got a couple of birthday greetings coming up, which were sent to me,
which I love to play.
But first time we got all you casting with Adam Curtis.
Come on in, young.
I suppose you think you know what you're using.
I do.
What do you hear?
The artist.
Young bowlet.
Hey Adam, here's another hit test.
This one is sort of a rock and roll version.
So here we go.
This is intro number one.
Oh, and I'll try enough to sing along.
Okay.
Oh, what was that?
Over one, I guess.
And number two.
Oh, man.
It's going to be a typical Friday and Adam sucks so bad.
He swallows.
And number three.
Okay.
That's a romantic.
I know that one.
Romantic sort of like about you.
Oh, man.
Haven't done this before in a while.
Let's hear the answers, young.
Let me know.
And times us.
This is the core.
One from 1980.
That's not the song.
Laundy and Colmy.
It's from me up.
Call me.
Answer number one in today's hit test.
It's Laundy and Colmy.
And this is answer number two.
John Cougar, Melanchoun.
Don't run the city's in the car.
Oh, girls.
Okay.
In the USA.
Feet of cars.
Cars and drivers go.
Boom.
Bam.
RCDUFA.
I know.
Yeah.
I'll get an in the USA.
But 86, John Cougar, Melanchoun.
R O C K in the USA.
Hey.
RCDUFA.
R colder number two in this.
It's an answer number three in this one.
The Romantics.
So, in the 90s, well, this is what I like about you.
That's what I like about you.
And so, number three, the romantics.
And that's what I like about you.
Well, I couldn't help myself singing along with the song, but the mic was closed, so there was no problem.
Well, this concludes hit test number 56.
You know what to do with hit test at gmail.com and with the young polette.com, J-A-N-P-O-L-I-T, and dot com.
Well, I hope you enjoyed this one.
See you next time for next week for a number 57.
Until then, have a nice weekend.
Bye-bye.
Thank you very much, young polette.
Man, I didn't do too well.
You come through me often, by saying it was, I mean, jungle melancham definitely rock, but the blondie thing threw me off a little bit.
E-mail from Dan Romeras says, I'm a newbie.
I'm a newbie.
When iTunes 4.9 came out, I was introduced finally to the wonderful world of podcasting.
I want to make a name for myself in podcasting.
How do I start?
I'm a PC user, boo hiss.
I know I'll have a Mac soon if it kills me.
Well, Dan, why don't you head over to castblaster.com.
It's perfect for the PC.
And it'll get you on your way.
It'll get you started recording and your show notes and everything's pretty much baked in right there and pretty soon.
I have a feeling you'll have some extra bits that will be added to castblaster.
Wouldn't it be neat if there was something like a podcast delivery network?
Even neither of that was for free.
I've coined a new phrase.
It's called Soundvertizing.
Now, I think it was yesterday that I asked you to stop and look around.
Look at whatever you see right now.
It could be a road sign.
It could be a house.
It could be some other object.
And whenever you see that object, you're going to remember Senseo.
I just had to pick something, right?
Renato said, I was listening to the daily source code of work when you did the Senseo thing.
I was looking at my screen.
AS400RPG ILE code.
If you want to know.
That means I now get even more distracted than ever.
Thanks.
But it's worth it.
Okay.
And it seemed to work as well for this Sean.
I'm a teenager.
I'm not going to talk about the teenager conversation.
I try to make a little money over the summer by cutting lawns to help pass the time.
We're cutting the lawns.
I listen to podcasts.
Normally, I follow the same pattern when cutting a certain lawn.
I have experienced the same thing as DGA.
I guess that's who sent in the original comment.
When I get to a certain point when cutting a lawn.
I remember something someone said on an interesting conversation in the podcast.
When I reached that point, the next time I cut that lawn.
I feel a little better now than I know that other people have the same problem.
I don't see it as a problem.
I see it as a fricking feature.
We've discovered something pretty big here.
Okay.
Time to wrap this up.
I got a couple more sound bits to play for.
What are we at now?
I'm not too bad actually.
36 minutes.
Cool.
Tomorrow will be my birthday.
September 3rd and I turn 41 and a couple of people were kind enough to send in some birthday greetings.
Hey, they're Adam.
It's Howard Greenstein.
And Barry Carl.
And we're just promoing here to wish you a happy 41th birthday.
We're going to sing you a happy birthday song together.
But then I remember that Barry got all the singing jeans in the family.
Yeah, good idea.
What a Barry, take it away.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday Mr. Curry.
I feel so old.
Happy birthday to you.
Boy, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Funnyness and sainace and you like the sound of Barry's voice.
Not usually a retaining Marilyn Monroe.
You should check out the podcast.
Confessions of an indie girl podcast at www.BarryCoral.com.
That's www.b-a-r-i-k-o-r-a-l.
Happy birthday, Adam.
And bye-bye.
Happy birthday to you.
I will, I will, I will, I will, I will, I will, I will.
Stop making your kids do that.
Kayden, Austin, Dorf. Thank you very much, Kayden. That was so sweet of you.
Devin, put you up to it. You're daddy Devin, right?
And there was another bird in your Christina-Heter birthday last week on the 27th.
And I got a little audio snippet from someone called Jude Fan.
Hope this doesn't fill up your Gmail. What didn't
it's only like 22 kilobytes. You'll find out why.
I'm still working on getting them to say podfathers. So your birthday wish maybe a little bit late.
But here's the one for Christina. Stop putting your kids up to that.
All right. And then definitely one of my favorite ones that came in.
And that'll do it for today's daily source code when getting to the weekend.
As the biddies also wish me happy birthday greeting for Adam Curry.
Happy birthday to you. It's a ski us too.
Happy birthday, Suska. Happy birthday dear Adam.
Happy birthday to you. We miss you. Come see us sometime.
Incidentally, at least for the next week or so, all proceeds from our CD sales off of CDbaby.com
will be donated to the American Red Cross to help aid victims of Hurricane Katrina.
CDbaby is also giving up their cut on the CD. So that works out to $11 a desk.
So if you've been holding off and ordering the list of ESPD's CD,
I think that was a pretty good time to do it, don't you?
Live from the van. It's been a cast.
Thank you very much, girls. And happy birthday Suska as we share the same birthday September 3rd.
That's it for the source code for today. Have a great weekend, everybody.
And please put the people in the golf course.
In the golf course, states and your thoughts and prayers.
And in your pocketbook, whatever you're going to buy this weekend, don't buy it.
Just give that money to the Red Cross, Red Cross, dot org.
Maybe you have a couple beers last. It'll really make a difference.
Alrighty, we're heading into the weekend. I have no idea we're going to do tomorrow, but
just chill out. I usually don't make up the deal of my birthday. Certainly not 41.
Don't it's just nothing to celebrate.
Get no. Remember when your parents were 40 and you thought they were fucking ancient?
Now I know. Send off your promos to submit at podshow.com.
If you got audio feedbacks, send it to adamaccurry.com.
Please think about your ID3 tags and the way you name the file.
Make a descriptive, make it so we can really use it.
And I would highly appreciate you not attaching the email, the files of the email.
We'll just stick it up on a server somewhere where I can download it as much easier.
In the show notes for today, which you can find on DavySourceCoat.com and www.curry.com,
click on the link that takes you to the full outline.
And from there, you should be able to download any of the elements that we're used in today's show.
So let me know how that works for you. And if it was useful at all,
it probably will be for a lot of those promos and PSAs for the hurricane release.
And feel free to use them to talk recently.
Have yourself great weekend, as I said before. Thank you very much for subscribing.
If you're not subscribed to DavySourceCoat.com, thanks for listening everybody. Bye, bye.