Now keep in mind, and I'm an artist, and I'm sensitive about my shirt.
Yo DJ!
Hi, yo, John McLeod!
Your DJ has only just begun.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Can we do this?
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
We don't need no sticking friends, man.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
Hey, everybody, it is Monday, May 2nd, 2005.
The power on the door.
It's really got to watch my buttons there.
I'm on the cast-blaster.
I hate you.
Welcome to the daily source code coming to you from the lovely and plush Ian Schrager Cliftoel
in San Francisco, California.
I'm Adam Curry, and he is your source code.
The power on the door.
So today I'm actually using the auto feature on cast-blaster on the latest data,
which I'm not quite sure how it's working,
but at least it shouldn't be over-modulating.
The level should be okay.
I'm on the wireless live mic.
I've got the little box in my father-in-law,
made hooked up to make sure that the line output,
go to the microphone and put all the technical bits
or put together.
And we've got a lot to talk about today.
I mean, echo a lot.
Thanks for subscribing.
And welcome.
So right now, I got to be honest,
my head doesn't know where my ass is and vice versa.
I've been traveling so much.
We weren't really sure that we were going to come out to California.
But, you know, stuff in New York was, you know, went well
and very interesting.
And so now we've got a couple meetings on Monday and Tuesday.
Then I'm going to head back, so I'm literally here with,
I think, two pair of underwear short.
But, of course, in the fine Dutch tradition,
you can wear them twice, right?
Inside, outside.
Oh, man.
So yeah, I went, we got in, you see, yesterday.
And basically, I was up at like, you know, six o'clock
because I guess my body was already used to New York time.
I guess I'm going to, in the midst of all this,
I think I skipped a day or missed 24 hours worth of something.
And I'm just like, you know, the middle of the day.
I start clapping out and getting really tired.
So up here, one of the upper floors,
you can kind of, I close the window.
Being kind of here, the rumble of the city down below.
And this is the first source code since the strategy cast,
which boy did we learn a lot from that one, eh?
So here's what I learned.
I learned that if you don't know what you're doing,
it doesn't matter how much pipe you have
because we essentially had 200 megabits
of unmetered bandwidth ready for the strategy cast.
And it certainly wasn't enough.
It just crapped out, you know?
Which essentially, from a technical standpoint,
tells me that with the current state of technology
where we are and the way we're distributing podcasts,
you know, you need a lot of resources.
If you want to do a show that's longer than 40 minutes
and that, you know, is something that people want to listen to.
Of course, you know, the theory with podcasts is that
your iPodor will download that during the night
or hopefully during some kind of off-power
it's not everyone's trying to get to it at the same time.
But essentially, there was so much demand for the strategy cast
that everyone was clicking on the download link
from curie.com and dailysourcecode.com
and it just, it totally broke everything, which is amazing.
But it also told me a lot about how far away we are
from, you know, from really getting all this stuff right.
I mean, you have to know that to have 100 megabits pipe
just one, that's like $3,000 a month, you know, an unmeted pipe.
So, you know, at this point, we have to figure some other stuff out.
Otherwise, you just can't, you know, be popular.
You can't have people really wanting to listen to your stuff.
Or, of course, I want to say, well, you should have, you know,
compressed it to lower bit rate or chopped it up into two files.
Well, you know, yeah, I'm not a, I'm not a technologist
per se, I'm a geek and hindsight.
Yeah, there's a lot of things I could have done.
But, you know, that's not really for the masses, you know,
if you want to create a show that's, that's, you know,
some time in length.
And whenever I record something in the I River, I always just kind of uploaded directly
from whatever the I River recorded it in.
And so there were some mistakes there.
We could have half that, by compressing it at a lower rate
or is it higher at a lower rate, splitting it up into multiple files,
all kinds of load balancing.
And, of course, everyone was talking about bit torrent,
which is, I really, this is something we should test.
And I'm going to gladly give up the daily source code to test this.
Just don't worry.
You know, how do you switch?
Well, first, I don't think you really can switch.
And there's still, I'm seeing about 30% of people listening to the daily source code
are not coming from, from iPod or clients.
They're basically just clicking on a link on the website.
So we, you have to remove that, which I think is a mistake,
because you don't want anyone not to be able to get to the show.
So it's either that or having, I don't know.
I really don't know.
But how do you switch to, how do you switch your current feed to a bit torrent feed?
You know, do you have to, you know, then we get into this,
oh man, we've been through this.
Do you use multiple enclosures?
Do you post it twice?
I mean, all stuff we got to think about.
And if you're out there and you have some ideas and some solutions,
I'd love to hear about it, because it's, it's going to be challenging all this stuff.
But on the other hand, I'm incredibly excited because I've been hosting,
most of my stuff on dot mac and by the way, I want to thank the Apple dot mac team
for allowing me to eat up just tons of their bandwidth with my little dot mac account.
And they are totally letting me slide on that stuff because, you know,
people have been shut off and, and downloads have been crippled for much less
bandwidth usage in the past.
So that was extremely cool and it's really appreciated.
But man, we've, we've got some stuff to figure out.
And thank you all very much for, for the responses.
There's, you know, over a hundred comments.
Most of it about the, the download and that was tough.
And of course, once that got fixed, and a lot of interesting comments on the,
on the weblog itself.
And lots and lots of email, lots of people checking in, lots of people with interest.
I really appreciate it.
And it's just the beginning of God knows where this is all going to take us.
So I'm very, very excited about it.
Let's see.
I wrote a couple of things down.
Oh, first of all, on the way out on the plane, I was listening to, you know,
my regular download of podcasts.
And Rock and Roll Geek, Michael Butler, Rock and Roll Geek.com,
had the most awesome podcast.
He did it with one of the, I think there's a guitar tech or
well, one of the road crew for currently, who's on the Wieser tour
went to his hotel room.
This guy has his own podcast.
It's a bit of a man.
I should have written that down.
Hold on a second.
Let me see if Rock and Roll Geek put that on the show notes.
Bit of a man's square and bit of a parking.
Oh, yeah, man.
Rock and Roll Geek.com.
So I've got the, this hotel that I'm in, which is a,
it's a great hotel that's really funky and it's almost
screaming for a sound seeing tour.
They only have a wired internet connection.
Now I have my Mac and the, and the, the tablet with me,
of course, I'm recording this on on the data of Cast Blaster.
So what I do is I plug the wired connection into my Mac and then use
that to basically become a base, a base station.
Oh, shoot.
Why is this not working?
Oh, I hate this.
Oh, here we go.
Let's see.
It's going to be in here in this show notes.
Oh, right.
Even took pictures.
Cool.
Yeah, Aaron.
That's right.
Aaron.
Bit of a man's circle podcast.
There you go.
That's what it was.
Bit of a man's circle.
B-it-t-e-r-m-a-n-c-i-r-c-l-e.com.
If you want to hear a great podcast that's coming from the road as,
you know, really to get an idea of what's going on behind the scenes,
right now on the Weezer tour.
It's a great podcast to listen to.
And Michael's podcast with him was just fantastic.
Learned a lot, actually, and they played some cool tunes.
And see, and then we got in.
This wacky hotel, which has, you know, Ian Schreger is,
I guess he's a designer.
He designs the wackiest furniture.
And some of it's completely oversized, like huge, like,
chrome-sized chairs and the restaurant.
All different sizes and all very, you know, kind of like gothic,
yet also classic and colonial and all kinds of styles
mixed through each other curtains with light shining down.
And it's just an awesome hotel.
And all the beautiful people in San Francisco are all hanging out here.
It's so wonderful.
Hi, everyone. My name is Zoe.
And this is my wife, C. Hello.
We need to tell you in about 30 seconds about a new,
slightly different show called the Shonapodcast.
The Shonapodcast with Cecilia and Zy.
www.Shonapodcast.co.uk.
Shonapodcast is a language spoken by over 8 million people in Zimbabwe
and it's a running territories and buys Zimbabwe's all over the world.
And since I already speak it, Zy is going to be learning it.
If you're interested in foreign languages,
or perhaps you know someone from Zimbabwe,
and would like to learn some Shonap, then you should enjoy listening to the Shonapodcast.
In each episode, we introduce a few Shonawatts,
and we often talk about Zimbabwe music, culture, and traditions,
and even current affairs with Zimbabwe hits the headlines.
Please visit our website and have a listen to the show at www.shonapodcast.co.uk.
There's s-h-o-n-a-podcast.co.uk.
If you subscribe to our feed, you find out why we're making the Shonapodcast,
why we sound so different,
and why Zay has simply got to learn some Shonapodcast.
Alrighty, the Shonapodcast.
And this Windows machine is really freaking me out.
So, the second one is connected to my computer now,
all of a sudden, why does Windows do that?
Why does it keep trying to connect to different wireless networks?
Now, I'm connected to the city-net public with very low signal strength.
I don't get it.
Okay.
Thanks for all the feedback on the cast-blaster data.
Now that we've sent our data as yet,
the people are still responding to the daily source code created with the application.
And I'm using the auto feature now,
which essentially, because all these different promos and pod safe music
and the hit tests are all recorded at different levels,
this really does do a lot of the auto-leveling,
but then the minute you hit talk,
it's going to kind of duck the,
it's called auto ducking,
D-U-C-T-I-N-G.
It kind of fades down the music so you can talk over it.
So, it gives a little, like, a more choppy or mix
when I turn the mic on and off,
but, well, that's a Tesla, see how it goes.
One of the meetings I had in New York,
I wanted to tell you about with one or music group.
This was the weirdest freaking meeting I've ever been in.
It was cool because there were technologies from W-M-G there,
but there was also, you know, some vice-president guys
who were more on the, you know, the digital delivery side
of the Warner Music Group.
Now, there really only four record companies left,
of which W-M-G is one of them.
And we had talked to one of the big cheeses over there
on the phone, like a week and a half or two weeks ago,
and, you know, we're basically talking about pod safe music
and how, you know, how promoting cool songs
and bands is back with podcasts, right?
Where you hear something you like,
you play it on your podcast, you have permission
as a pod safe tune,
and you can get people excited about it.
And as we've seen with the Sylvia's Bitties,
you know, people turn out to actually want to buy the record.
So, we think that's a very interesting model,
and we're going to be doing a lot of that with the CC Chapman.
We're calling the pod safe music network,
and you'll be hearing more about that in the next week or two,
of course, podshow.com is where you can stay up to speed,
and of course, we'll be talking about it here on the source code.
But we finally got down to actually making the real suggestion.
And the suggestion, I told them exactly what I do.
You know, like, I go to iTunes Music Store,
I purchase a song, and then I play it,
and I would gladly pay instead of 99 cents.
Excuse me, I would gladly pay five bucks.
You know, put a little, you know, on the back catalog,
right, we're not talking about, you know, the J-Lo's
and all the new million platinum selling records.
We're talking about the back catalog,
which probably doesn't sell all that much,
but is available in the iTunes Music Store.
You know, like Chicago Saturday in the park that I played,
and we said, well, why don't you,
you know, make a feature in iTunes Music Store,
or, you know, obviously at the set up that relationship with Apple,
wherever you buy your songs from,
you know, if it has a green star after it,
that means you can, you play this on your podcast,
and when you download it,
you essentially would pay five bucks, five bucks,
and that would be sufficient for you to play this on your podcast.
And that would, by the way,
because then it would be treated as a digital download,
and I'm starting to become almost like a lawyer now.
You wouldn't have to pay AskCap or BMI,
and the artist would get theoretically,
would get a piece of that in the publisher.
And of course, the author, the composer.
They didn't get it.
Literally said, well, yeah, we think that would be very interesting.
And I remember this is five times the normal sale price,
five times.
That would be great,
but then they said, well, still,
we don't want that MP3 to be in the clear longer than two weeks.
So your podcast would essentially, and literally,
I said, would have to disintegrate.
You know, like, it would have to blow up,
and couldn't be kept online for longer than two weeks.
So you totally missing it.
And by the way, when you play it,
your podcast that goes down to a much lower bit rate,
it's much less high quality,
and you're probably mixing it with talk,
or whatever you're talking over the intro we can with.
You know, everything we've talked about on the source code,
we suggested, and they just said,
no, you know, we feel that you still have to,
you know, make it go away.
You can't, as they say, and this is the phrase
it's stuck in my mind.
We don't want MP3s in the clear.
And it was so disappointing, you know,
and if I were, you know, Peter Saterra,
or any of the guys from Chicago, which we use as an example,
I would be fucking pissed off.
You know, here's a chance to make a quintuple sale,
quintuple on one that's half the price of the CD,
for just letting me play it on the podcast,
and the record company is turning it down.
Absolutely mind boggling.
Now, on the other hand,
the technologists who were in the room,
I've had a real nice kind of offline conversation with them,
and they are doing some interesting things,
but now you got to think that if the top is thinking that way,
we're just not going to get very far with this stuff,
which is really quite a shame.
I had them.
I'm glad you allowed me to approach your giant microphone
to promote the Pirates Week.
I use the pseudonym Ragnar Danjold,
while I'm letting my vacuum tubes cool
and try this podcasting thing.
Although it's not real entertaining,
I'd like to think I'm helping the shortwave pirate radio community
by relating logs, news items,
and technical information for the Pirate Radio
DX and hobby with my podcast.
A hobby cast, if you will.
I tend to stick to North American shortwave
and some mediumwave pirates,
but everyone's so well,
a Euro Pirate makes the leap across the pond
to be logged by a lucky few.
So here's my 32nd promo.
I'd be honored to be included in your litany of the undeserved
The Pirates Week.
Okay, now I get it.
That's why I sent two files.
One is the intro,
and then one is the actual promo.
I'm sorry about that.
I'll play that tomorrow on the show.
I'll get the second promo going.
It's funny though,
because I used to be a,
I guess, yeah,
basically a shortwave pirate.
When we had, I'll back in the day man,
you had CB radio,
which of course you had the 40,
the 40 channel CB radio,
but then you had something called SSB single side band,
the LSB, the lower side band,
and then USB, the upper side band,
which effectively gave you 80 more channels to play with.
And what we had figured out with all these,
solid state logic CB radios
is that you could snip a diode
that was connected to one of the chip sets,
that would expand with another 120 channels,
only in an upper range.
So CB is like 27 megahertz,
and this would basically take you the 28 megahertz band.
And that's officially a ham radio band,
but it was really quiet there,
because of course there are not a lot of people
who would jack their box to make it do that.
But I remember just with a regular CB radio,
which on side band,
and this is a little geeky detail,
I would output like 12 watts, peak envelope power,
that I was talking to people in Ohio from Amsterdam.
You know, I had an antenna on my roof,
and as I actually there was a group called the KMG,
which was the Kiss My Grits group group,
and some of those guys had huge six foot antennas
on the back of their car,
and they'd be driving around Ohio,
and I could actually talk to them
if the conditions were good from all the way from Amsterdam,
and it was quite a trip.
I am kind of a little bit of a short wave
part of myself from way way back.
So the thing that didn't happen in New York,
which I'm bummed about,
is the Paris Hilton interview.
Reason for it,
believe it or not,
she has a new PR firm.
And the new PR firm said,
well, we're really trying to limit
the amount of promotion that Paris is doing for the movie,
and I was like, you fucking idiot.
Basically what it means is whenever you hire a new PR firm,
the first thing they do is they discredit everything
the old PR firm had set up,
say, oh no, we're not going to do that,
that's a bad idea.
So these people really didn't do their homework, I feel.
And it's quite a shame because Paris's podcast
could definitely use a boost,
and I wanted to give her some feedback.
The first show was out there.
I haven't heard the second one yet.
It sounded to me like she did a little intro
that she probably did cut in the green room somewhere
at David Letterman.
And then basically they took the audio from,
I guess a TV documentary,
or maybe it's the House of Wax show on MTV
that they're doing.
So that's a shame.
It could have been better and quite honestly,
I had a whole bunch of good questions,
including Mads Weinstein's,
which I did not get to ask.
Wanna get to know Paris?
Two men to the Paris Hilton podcast now.
It's the Paris Hilton podcast.
Been 24-7 with Paris Hilton
on her countdown to the House of Wax.
That's right.
All Paris, all the time.
To give Paris Hilton podcasts,
go to www.houseamwaxmovie.com
and click on the podcast link.
Well, if you'd actually do some of your own stuff,
Paris, you know, just talk to us for a little bit.
That's what you want.
And I know you're listening to the daily source code.
Just talk to us, just sit somewhere,
and you room, you hotel room on the plane,
and whatever.
And just let us know what's going on in your life.
Although I did kind of like the behind-the-scenes stuff,
and I wouldn't mind if it was a little bit longer,
but too bad.
Too bad.
I guess David Letterman's still
still rates much, much higher than me.
Oh no.
What evil work?
In the heart of men.
The shadow, no.
Come down for blast off.
X minus 4 minus 3 minus 2 X minus 1.
Hey, Adam.
We've heard you podcast.
We're talking about old radio dummies,
such as the Green Hornet.
We'd like to invite you to check out our podcast.
Bautar's old-time radio.
Where we deliver the best old-time radio
to your doorstep daily.
Shows like,
oh,
be a suit, it is pot-shape.
Awesome, dude.
I really enjoyed this podcast.
I mean, we can learn a lot from it, actually.
And yeah, I think it is actually pot-safe.
That's deemed as pot-safe is probably in the, uh,
uh, what do you call it?
It's, uh, in the public domain, uh, by now,
really cool to hear some of that old stuff.
And, actually, I got a couple of ideas,
and I was listening to it.
All right, time to some pot-safe tunes.
Um, this is, uh, I've actually played a song
by, uh, out of warranty before.
I remember I told you the story about the,
the original bass player for Wild Cherry,
the more Wild Cherry play that funky music.
He sent me another tune,
and it was especially the beginning of the song
that really struck me.
Uh, listen close.
Here's, I don't have.
I don't have a flash.
He flash with scent.
I don't have a laptop or a plug.
I don't even have a plug to listen.
But I'm going to...
I just barely made the downtown transmit.
All my changes were laying down the aisle.
Everyone is looking at me cross-eyed
as I drop the floor to steal my smile.
Oh, it's a beautiful tunnel, right?
Got a wonderful knit-town sightseeing.
It's all over my mind, tune-like.
I'm burning brighter than the city lights.
Now I don't have a fancy foreign sportscar.
I don't have the latest anything.
I just want to get to her this evening,
so we can enjoy this little thing.
Is it a serious relationship?
Only time will tell me if it's real.
Love or just not feeling over hands,
and with fingertips across my...
Oh, it's a beautiful town, tune-like.
From the bridge I have a lovely sightseeing.
It's a vision and a pair of jeans.
Like a movie or a man.
Oh, it's a beautiful town, tune-like.
From the bridge I have a lovely sightseeing.
It's a vision and a pair of jeans.
Like a movie or a man.
I don't have a Rolex or a diamond.
I don't have a TV-level seats.
I can't drink that fancy cam,
but she ain't no.
I need to put some shoes from my feet.
Well, I don't have a flashy glass website.
I don't have a laptop or a hub.
I don't even have a clock to listen.
But at least I'm sure of love.
I'm sure of love.
Yeah, stick it in your ear.
I don't have out of warranty.
Love that.
Don't have a flashy flashy website.
Don't have a laptop or a pod.
I don't even have a pod.
Was it pod to piss in?
I've been just whistling that tune all day.
I took a walk after breakfast or kind of brunch today.
And a CC Chapman sent me a couple of podsafe tunes to listen to and play on the source code.
I just couldn't get this one out of my head.
So I want to play that for you.
And out of warranty, as far as I know, actually doesn't have a website.
So as maybe if they do, I'll get that info and I just haven't seen it in the emails or
or found it anywhere.
Of course, I'll put it up in the show notes.
And that's one of the things that we're going to really,
really make possible for the podsafe music network.
So that could say, go check this out, the podsafe music network.
There'll be info about the artist.
You could see important for podcasters, of course,
is what's being played a lot on different podcasts.
And of course, you'll be able to link to buy the CDA.
And if I have my drill, there's if we can figure that out.
Also to download it and buy it digitally, I guess.
So looking forward to a lot of cool new music coming on to the scene.
I tell you that.
Let me see what else they have on my list for today.
Oh yeah.
So of course, we announced our pod squad,
who invested in really investing the creativity and talent of a number of great podcasters.
And by the way, that means that we're literally helping them financially
through a number of different ways so that they can, you know,
take, you know, basically spend the time on creating podcasts.
And we've created production companies with them,
so that they can start to produce more podcasts with other other people
who may be need production or have a great idea.
And there's just all kinds of cool things that are going to be coming up
very soon.
And one of them I'm very excited about is Steve Gilmore.
He will be bringing the Gilmore gang back,
which means our weekends will be complete again.
And also a new feature, Gilmore Daily.
And I just sent him, he got a,
he now has a tablet and I just set him up with
a date of cast blaster and immediately he's got all kinds of ideas
how he can make it even better.
If you haven't heard yet from us about the cast blaster beta,
it's probably going to be another,
I think another week until we actually send the date is out.
And then it should be, I think no more than two or three weeks of
testing until we can open up to a public beta and everyone can enjoy.
At least, I'm sorry to say anyone with an XP,
when those XP can enjoy, I wish we could do it for the Mac,
but then again, you know, Mac people are already so incredibly
privileged with the machine they have.
Hi Adam, I'm glad you allowed me to approach your giant microphone.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, we already did that one.
I'm sorry, this is the one I wanted to play for you.
Hello, I'm Thomas Vanhoff, a journalist and a podcast of
from Germany.
I started podcasting in October 2004,
first with summerstellet.net about potsafe music from Germany.
Then in January 2005, I started Vanhoff's wonderful world of science.
The German science podcast.
With Nicole Simon and Garrett von Arken, I found it's sushi radio DE.
Some tidbits of podcasting.
This is one of the most popular shows in Germany.
Because I am listening so much to English spoken podcasts
and for improving my English,
I decided to develop an international edition of my science podcast.
And here it is.
A new star is born in podcast heaven.
Sciencecast.net.
Every Sunday evening on the net on sciencecast.net.
What's in the show?
Science news from all over the world.
Sometimes fresh reports when I'm in the wild.
Some sound seeing and some funny things.
So have fun with it.
Enjoy the show and send me comments on mail.
At sciencecastmail at gmail.com.
Sciencecast.net.
Every Sunday, the latest news from the world of science.
All right, totally dig that.
Of course, summerstellet.net has been around.
One of the early podcasts.
And of course coming from Germany.
It was a funny.
It doesn't sound a little bit like the Pope.
Just a teeny, tiny bit.
Okay.
So here's a sign for a dam announcement.
This is a cool one.
I'm very excited about this.
No more than two weeks ago.
We were talking about the concept of an open podcast.org idea on satellite.
Where would be great to have a channel where we could expose more people
to podcasting.
And depending on when you're listening to this podcast, you may or may not have heard the news
that Pod Show has struck a deal with serious satellite radio to bring you four hours of podcasting
every single day.
And I am so jazzed about this because now we're talking in audience of almost two million people.
And these guys are working their ass off to get more and more subscribers to serious satellite radio.
They're looking at probably 20 million by 2007 or whatever.
And it's gone.
You know, every single new car that is sold in the states now, I think, has either the option
or it's standard.
You have a satellite receiver in there.
Well, we did it.
Yeah, I put in a couple of calls.
I told you about that on a previous daily source code.
And there was definitely interest.
Now, these guys, of course, they only have so many channels.
Yeah, it's like 150 channels.
But they only have so many.
And there's all kinds of stuff already on the Tony Hawk M&M.
The Howard Stern will soon be on serious satellite or at the end of the year,
and now we have the pod show on serious satellite radio.
And I am so freaking jazzed about this because, first of all, we're going to open it up,
so that anyone can consent in your podcast or your promo.
I mean, it's seen this really as a huge daily source code,
which is actually it's quite a, it's a big task to put this together.
But I've been very lucky to be able to team up with PW Fenton from the digital
Flotsom.org.
He does, I've talked about his podcast a lot.
And he just really knows how to do audio.
So he's going to be working with me on that.
He's going to be really doing all the production.
And we're going to open up a couple of ways for you to send in your,
your promos, your podcasts, whatever it is, and check this out.
I'm going to put all kinds of mashups in there, pod safe music.
If you have a podcast where you play licensed music,
not a problem because serious satellite's going to pick up the tab for that.
So, you know, you could do whatever you want,
and we're going to put it on serious satellite network,
which will be, I think it's, well,
I guess we start all the way at the end of the spectrum, right?
We're on channel 148.
But we did it.
We really did it.
And I'm extremely excited.
It's going to be a shitload of work, but it's going to be awesome.
So, in the next couple of days, I'll have details on how you can submit your podcast.
And, and of course, you know, the whole point is to promote your podcast.
So, make sure that if you're thinking about submitting something that there's a way for people to
subscribe to, you want to give out your URL and where your, where your podcast feed is.
And also, I'm going to try and,
what we don't go with doing the source code and try and get more listeners for podcasts.
And also turn more people onto podcasting.
And it's going to be a great place for people to sample podcasts.
And I think starting off with four hours, which, of course,
I'd like to move to a 24 hour channel,
but let's start off slowly and see how the submissions go.
And if we can get enough content in there to fill it up.
I'm pretty sure, as we grow, it'll work.
But I am very, very excited.
I did want to thank Steve Leads for, for basically, you know, setting it all up.
Steve is the guy, and I've talked about this with Ken Clarke on the MTV Chronicles.
He's the guy that called me in 1987 when I was in, in the Netherlands and said,
hey, you want to come and work for MTV.
And he's the same guy hooked up.
The, the serious satellite radio deal.
I have a picture on serious satellite radio.
Totally jazzed about it.
This is your captain speaking.
Yo DJ, are you done mixing it?
Yeah, yeah.
If so, please invest in your league belt,
they hit this to the back to take off.
The hell is this?
Oh, they're casting with...
I'm curious.
It's a great deal.
It's time for the hit test.
With y'all, pull it.
All right.
Hey, Adam.
This is Y'all Paulette with another hit test,
and this one's a bit different because I'm still on a Skype call
with the hit test announcer guy.
The hit test.
That is not included.
Battery sold separately.
Hey Kevin, I doing...
Good John.
John.
Okay.
Can I have a birthday soon?
Really?
Gonna be 42.
42 man.
You're getting old.
I'm gonna be ready for the concert.
Thank you.
I'll have to get this.
Well, of course you know me.
I'm too cheap to send you anything across the big ocean,
called the Atlantic.
But how about this?
How about a few?
All right.
Just like the music for the next hit test for Adam.
Me?
Yeah, you.
How many do I get?
How about 10?
Well, I guess he, uh,
he'll only do three.
Three. Okay.
But of course, that's one rule.
Adam is supposed to know them.
So they have to have been hit somewhere in the,
in my lifetime.
60, 70s or 80s.
Exactly.
My life, sir.
Yeah, hit to the 70s and 80s.
Okay.
Or the 90s.
But then they can only be American hits.
Okay.
Those are the rules.
Are you up for it?
I'm up for it.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Well, Adam, um,
what is the same as always is that I've got three clips lined up.
And this is clip and intro.
Number one.
Sounds like.
Ten and ten.
Keep on moving.
Two.
Something like that.
Absolutely.
No clue what that is.
This is, uh, tough.
Y'all.
And the final one is a bit short.
This is number three.
What?
All right.
Just give me the answers.
I suck.
There's no way I get any of those.
You're probably yelling at your iPod, right?
So up.
This is answer number one.
It's sold to sold.
I have that one.
It's sold.
My name'schoice.
Your name'schoice, my name'schoice.
Put the word down the chair.
So you got it.
Hey.
shortcut.
See your guy there.
Oh, for tips.
The answer number one in today's hit-est, so to solve and keep on moving and it's recorded
from vinyl and it's great to hear those correctly sounds again.
Answer number one and this is answer number two.
It's from 89, so I hope you know this one, the stone roses, this is full skulls.
I wouldn't have known that one.
I think I've ever heard the song before.
The stone roses, answer number two.
I hope this has been a hit in the United States also because else you won't know what this one is.
Fulls gold, answer number two and this is answer number three.
The easiest one also to share the split, but there's the easiest one.
Sting and Englishman in New York.
Of course.
Well if you knew that one at home.
Being an Englishman in New York, answering number three in today's hit-est.
And I'm already looking forward to the next one.
I hope Kevin, you will do a great job searching for music.
Looking forward to it, you're on.
Okay, well see you next time.
Well Adam, thank you for playing this one.
Thank you.
Yes, time for another edition of the hit-est.
And of course, as always, hit-est at gmail.com is the address for feedback and the web address is
www.yompolet.nl or.com.
That's J-A-N-B-O-L-E-T.nl or.com.
And you can find all information about hit-est and the separate hit-est podcast on that page.
Well thank you for listening, see you next time.
Bye-bye.
All right, John, thank you very much.
Oh, yeah, Kevin, thank you too.
But again, the hit-test.
And that is it for the Daily Source Code for the second of me.
And I'm going to see what time is it now.
It's so, man, I'm going to have some dinner over here.
Okay, thanks again for checking out the Daily Source Code.
A lot of exciting stuff we had to talk about today.
And I'm sure there'll be more in the coming few weeks.
So you want to stay subscribed.
Okay, you can find the podcast feed at dailysourcecode.com.
Feedback to atomacuri.com.
If you want to send me a promo, don't send me the MP3 file.
Just send a link to an MP3 file.
Put in the subject's DFC promo.
If you got pod safe tunes for me, put pod safe music in the subject line.
So I can route all that to the proper folders.
And of course, you can always leave a comment on my weblog www.curry.com.
Thanks again for listening. Have a great week, y'all. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.