Delta Sierra Charlie
Two
Seven
Six
There are no secrets
I
Intermediate you
Don't be a liar
Adam Curry
For $16 million worth of airplane
Strap to my ass
Done the next generation radio content in my ears
You don't need us
Thinking crazy
I like to think I'm flying
You should be sure
I'm guessing
It's a battle curry
Good morning everybody
Coming to you from Curry Cottage
In the affluent Surrey Subherpa
Kilford
It is your daily source code
odd father and transit
Only back in the cottage for about
20 hours
Then I'm off to Los Angeles
For the expo
We're talking about that about pot save music
On some other stuff
I'm sure we'll conjure up
It's Wednesday
Stepped out of my doorstep
Wednesday
Morning look real fun
Took a glance at my wristwatch
Getting in my breath a time
Let my little girl
Sitting pretty in the bed
It's just my arms
I trust this guy
Time to clear my weary fear
Wednesday morning
Take my blues away
It's gonna be a part of the day
Wednesday morning
It's come so many times before
I used to cry
I want to pull my life
But I'm not going too many more
With a miss Johnson
I saw school boys skipping by
Took a dome
To my head
What I feel
What I have
Climb my hands
Kicked up my feet
Dance around
They're y'all so sweet
At least I'm doomed
But I see
The music was a treat
It was a step on a hand
Take my blues away
Wednesday morning
It's gonna be a part of the day
It's come so many times before
I used to cry
I want to pull my life
But I'm not going too many more
With a miss Johnson
I want to pull my life
But I'm not going too many more
With a miss Johnson
I want to pull my life
It's called so many times before
They used to fly over for my night
But I might go to
Not go to it, whoa
Not it, whoa
Not another one, no, in all
When's the morning? You can find that on the pod save music.
Connect, we're going to music.podshow.com.
Well, good morning, everybody.
Coming to you from from the curry cottage.
Boy, what a what a whirlwind trip I had the past two days.
Oh, I hear all kinds of hum and stuff here.
What the hell was going on?
I have to. I slept in microphone, I think.
Oh, so I'm sorry about yesterday's show.
The travel schedule and the meetings and oh, man,
everything was messed up.
But for those of you just joining the daily source code wondering what I'm talking about,
I received a couple messages two days ago that the record industry and also the broadcast
industry in in the Netherlands and more than likely in other countries in Europe
were banding together and are going to put their foot down on licensed music being played
on podcast.
And so I had an opportunity to go talk to a couple of European parliament members about
this. So I jetted off.
Now, the European parliament is kind of divided between Brussels and Luxembourg.
And it's supposed to be like one month or in Brussels, the next month or in Luxembourg,
it could be longer than a month.
But pretty much they're divided and people are all over the place.
And I guess some of those parliament members have a banking business in Luxembourg
that look down there as well.
And I really was really wanted to go there and talk to some people.
Well, for two reasons, one, I wanted to find out what what the general consensus was,
what the thought was, there is different thinking in Europe about things like patents,
although laws are now being put up and past that may or may not be what everyone would like
who deals with patents.
There's a lot of copyright issues that are being discussed and directives are being created.
And so he was a great opportunity for me to go and talk to some folks about it.
And certainly did.
The other part, of course, was G's.
Is there no way we can find that we can kind of use some kind of,
you know, I'll be honest about it.
If I can use political leverage to turn around in our advantage, I'll do that.
Because isn't there some way we can figure this out.
But essentially, here's what it boils down to.
Using licensed music on podcast will only work if a form of DRM is implemented,
so that after a certain amount of time, the show, the show that you created,
basically dries up and goes away.
And by the way, I have to say, I'm not completely against that.
I think there are, you know, shows have a shelf life.
My show has a much shorter shelf life than Don and Drew's, for example.
They have, oh man.
I think some people have every single episode of Don and Drew and the creating entire archives
and collections and CDs and there's a whole subculture of that.
But source code is, you know, I don't think there's much reason to go back and listen to one.
Because I'm basically promoing shows that you want to check out today and, you know,
so the shelf life much shorter.
So I wouldn't mind if the show went away, but, you know, then you come into the whole issue.
Well, then you have to use digital rights management or DRM for short.
And that means that, you know, you can resort to only really a couple of different types.
It'll be, um, uh, well, I guess, looking at the, uh, looking at the portable player market
if you want to have, and that's really what it's all about.
You know, this is not because, oh, gee, I need to play licensed music.
So badly on my show, but I also want to give my audience what they want.
So that's, you know, the audience loves the hit test.
The audience loves mashups, not all of them, but, um, so that's why I want to do that.
You know, not, not like, oh boy, you know, I want to be in with the hip crowd and want to play
J-Lo, no, that's not necessarily it.
So it's, it's a request, you know, and, and that'll only work if it, um, if it's DRM,
and the only way to DRM it to keep my audience would be basically to use apples.
What does it fair play? I think is what they use, um, and I'm sure there's the be a way.
So, well, it won't be copyable. I don't know if they can make a show expire or not.
I'm sure they can, you know, then maybe just adapt the software somewhat.
But then, you know, how about all the other folks who don't use, um, iTunes and iPods.
So I don't see a workable solution there. Maybe maybe maybe all the bulls DRM would be applicable.
But I'm not quite sure we're that with all of their initiatives. And, and again, you know,
this is still kind of about the free airways, you know, that's, that's the whole point.
So, and I went through tirelessly explaining that, you know, that it's a good thing,
and that, you know, the only presumption that I kept hearing over and over as well,
it's too easy to steal the song. Well, first of all, you know, and hit test and mashups.
It ain't that easy to steal the song. You can't undo the mashup and the hit tests or just little snippets.
But, you know, it just, it was back and forth and they keep coming back to,
well, you guys have to give a little, said, no, fuck you. I didn't say fuck you. I said,
said, you know, why should we have to do that? You know, this is, it's so backwards everything.
It's not like we live and die by the 1.5 million songs that are available online, you know,
to download and put on your music player that you pay for. You know, it's not about that.
It's a more of a cultural thing. I mean, G's songs have been passed down through,
through the ages, through history, people sing traditional songs. And of course, those that are in
in the public domain, we can continue to use witness jingle bells, which is, as you look at the
podcast music network. There's a great new version of that. But it's also an opportunity to
to create new music. And that's really the only direction I guess we can go into promote new music
is through pod save. And by the way, I'm so I was in Brussels in the next day in Luxembourg.
And I have to say that, yeah, I got the attention. Yeah, we had the meetings, but everybody in
those two places were completely focused on France, man. Wow, people are running freaking
scared about what's going on there. In case you haven't heard about it. And I must say there's been
quite a lack of mainstream media attention for what's happening. There are riots for two weeks now.
And the riots seem to consist of mainly like 14 to 18-year-old young men, predominantly from poor
areas in France. They're pretty much all from Northern Africa, from Algeria. And I guess they're
fed up with their situation. And the way they're expressing that is by writing on the streets. But
really the one thing that seems to have caught on is the idea of burning cars. That seems to
get all the attention. And so I think now, as of the count from last night, there's over five
and a half thousand. Can you imagine that five and a half thousand cars have been burned?
There's already been one death. There's been 1,500 arrests. And it's a big mess. And I think it's
by the way, I'm not one of these people who thinks that, oh, this is a Muslim problem. I think this
is a government problem. It's happening all over Europe where Europe invited a lot of Eastern
nations to come on in. Because plenty of work will give you health care. We'll give you child care
and come on in. Come on over. And we got plenty of jobs for you. And they did a horrible
shitty job with integrating these groups of people. And now we have second generation who are
not integrated have very little hope. And this is how they choose to express that, which I
obviously don't think is the best way to do it. And by the way, where are the parents saying,
hey, yo, dude, get your ass in here before I kick it and put down that rock, put down that
on the Dove cocktail. So anyway, they're all freaked out because this is something that could
easily spark to any number of countries. We're already seeing a little bit of this happening in
Germany and Berlin. I think there was a couple of basically copycat actions that took place in
Brussels itself. You hear that? No, I don't have a minute. I forget keep forgetting to turn my
Skype off every single time I start to show. Another country where this could just explode would
be the Netherlands. So that, you know, phones were ringing off the hook and these guys, these
Parliament members, are they Parliamentarians? Parliamentarians? That was like a really just
called the Parliamentarians. They kind of are that way, I guess. So long, long, long, long,
story short. Not very successful. It's completely hammered into my head that the only way to go
for me at least and I'll advise my fellow podshow podcasters and anyone else who's listening
within the sound of my voice to be very, very careful what you're doing because they, you know,
look, if these guys can go out and sue college kids, high school kids, grandmonds, sounds great,
doesn't it? They're suing grandmothers. Me up to the tune of 150 grand. I'm sure that they'll be
happy to take on some podcasters and we're all very, very visible. In fact, we're all going to be
damn visible at the, at the expo, at the end of the week, this, this upcoming weekend. So,
thank you very much, Koso and Katya, they already created proud to be pod save logos,
little music player there with a condom over his head, fantastic. So I received many, many,
many comments that had some time to look over them last night in this morning. And there's one
thing that did disturb me a little bit. People saying, well, you're not being transparent about
the pod safe music network, because pod show owns it and you're driving people towards your music.
And I'm like, whoa, let's just back up one second and evaluate what the pod safe music network is.
Okay. This was built more than half a year ago before they're even, we started on this before
there was a pod show company, even. And Ron and I funded it out of Bro Pocket because we were
excited about what was happening. Ron's in musician. I'm, you know, I'm a, I'm a dumb blonde DJ VJ.
And we were excited about the prospects of what this could be. The only reason for this
pod save music network is to act as an exchange. And the exchange is based upon a very simple
license that is kind of agreed upon once you sign up as a podcaster and once you sign up as an
artist. And it's an agreement that, hey, look, the art, you can play this song and promote it,
along as you report back to the network that you played it. And of course, there's links to the
artist's websites all over the place. And it's, at this point, it's up to the artist to monetize
on that. Certainly with our unlabel idea, we want to help musicians to monetize on that.
And for the, for the artists, they have every right to take their song off the pod safe music network.
It's, it's really, it's quite open. Go ahead, read the terms. If you have an issue with the terms,
bring them up so we can discuss them. We've done that in the past and we'd be happy to adapt the
terms if it seems to be the right thing to do. But there's, except for maybe a little bit of advertising,
there's no huge monetization scheme in place for sending people to the pod safe music network
other than it's just easy. You know, shit, the, the term pod safe, I think Dave Winner and I came
up with that a year ago, perhaps, maybe a little less now. But just, you know, it's like,
come on, people, yeah, go to garageband.com. You can do it. You can get stuff there. And if there's
no blanket license, if you get something from garageband.com, so you still have to do the work. I just
want to, basically, I want to make it easier for myself. Give me a place where I can always go to,
don't have to think about whether I can play this on my podcast, just know that if I like it,
I can play it on my podcast. And the benefits of the pod safe music network is that podcasters report.
So right now, I think we only have the top 10 of all time. We're coming out with the top 10 plays
of the month of the week and of the day. And you can see which show has played, what songs?
It's a great referral network. That's, that's all that it is. So to Molly, particularly, who wrote
a just a nasty comment, like dude, you know, come on, give a little bit of credit here for the work
that CC Chapman and Chris Rockwell did and Sue, you know, they put this together.
Okay. Anyway, so I'm very excited about moving forward and putting this behind us.
It really blows because man, do I love the mashups? I really love the mashups. Lots of people
saying, hey, why don't you do pod safe mashups? Well, if anyone sent me a great pod safe mashup,
I'd use it. I haven't heard anything that I liked. And of the thousands of mashups that I've
received, I've only played a very small portion because I thought they were good enough. And some
of them probably even sucked too bad. But I wanted to put a mashup on. And I'm bummed, you know,
like the backtracks podcast, fantastically produced stuff, really cool, young polette. He's, and
polette is bummed out, really, really bummed out. Because, you know, this was kind of one of the things
that he had a lot of passion doing it. And we never had any financial range when he just sent me
stuff and had happily play it. And of course, he had, you know, maybe to make like 20 or 30 bucks
a month from the iTunes links because there is no money in being a middleman in the licensed
music business. Ask Steve Jobs, he's making pennies, ask Napster, ask Rap City. These guys
are not making money. They have to give up so much to all these different agencies with their
handout that they're literally stifling everything. So what I'm trying to do now is inspire
young to come up with something new, some other new short form feature because it's really
truly is he's a great short form feature producer. So I'm hoping that it'll, they'll come up with
some more stuff. And hey, young, anything you want to try, man, just send it to me. No,
and all that throw it right on. So we will talk about the podcast Expo today.
When I wrote on a couple of things here, man, I have such a busy day. I have a whole list of
things I have to take care before I go. Because here's the deal. I'm going to,
what time are we at now? I'm going to Los Angeles, then I drive straight up to Ontario.
Thursday night is the Podsafe Acoustic Jam that I guess the Podsafe Music Network is actually
underwriting it. Oh, gee. More money out of pocket. But it's good, you know. I think Brother
Love is coming. He's going to do an Acoustic set. I have no idea. CC Chapman is arranging all of that.
So I'm very, very excited to see what kind of vibe we can create. Then of course Friday and
Saturday is the Expo. Sunday, back in San Fran Monday, in the office for just a little bit,
then I got to go to Washington, Seattle, Washington, to speak before all of the brand,
I think it's the brand managers and media buyers of Johnson and Johnson. Dude, those guys make a lot
of stuff. You may think they just do a certain amount of products, but they actually do
an Acubu lenses or they own the companies. So that's Tuesday, Tuesday morning, then I hop on a flight
back and then I'm in the office Wednesday. And then Thursday, I have to, well, have to, then I'm
coming back already because Patricia is paying, don't tell them, okay. Then I'll have a computer,
so I don't think they'll hear it, but Patricia's going to pay her dad who just turned 80 a surprise
visit this weekend. So I have to be home to take care of the end of Christina's going to. So I have
to stay home to take care of the cottage and the dogs and then I'll be home for
thing two weeks and then off again just before the holidays. So plenty of Gmail to go through,
I don't know if I'm going to get to most of it. And brand new is the promo upload system.
I got to come up with a better name for that. If you go to promos.podshow.com,
there's basically a WordPress weblog there. You register, you can set up your own username and password,
and then you can create your own post and just throw the URL in anywhere on that post,
you know, just copy and paste it wherever you put up a file on your server and it will automatically
be turned into the podcast feed, which you can subscribe to, down at the bottom, there's a little
link to the RSS feed. And now the promo is just drop right into my system automatically. It is so
incredibly cool. And of course, you know, you could also subscribe to the feed. And if you're
if you've got a podcast that you're, you know, might want to promo some other stuff on,
you're welcome to use it. So, let me give you a couple of those and I'll be right back.
This is Mr. Morgan. And this is Qdog. And we're from cool shot on the tube.
What is cool shot Mr. Qdog? Cool shot is a movie reviews. It's talking about TV. It's talking about
pop culture. It's talking about a lot of shit. A lot of shit. A lot of shit. And this is what some
of our listeners have had to say about us. I love cool shot on the tube. It's possibly one of the
best five guests I've ever listened to. Thank you, Governor Arney. You're welcome. Now one of
that you missed the Billy Conley. I think it's brilliant. I've never heard anything like it in my
way. If you like listening to people talking about movies, people having a good time, people
hacking on each other, you should come to cool shot on the tube. Listen to us. I have a good time.
We're about that. www.co.sh-h-i-t-e. That's far as I'm concerned. I had never listened to any
other podcast. I mean, who would do that?
Well, Australia, Adam.
Australia? But are you really listening? I don't think you heard non-terrace yet.
Everybody up to date on non-terrace, our podcast. My name is Sandra tonight. And I'm an
of blonde, also known as the blonde. I'm the blonde, natural blonde, 100%. And I am the
brunette. That's right. My life is nothing, like the pages of Us Weekly. But I live in LA.
I work in Hollywood. Here I have all of these very talented friends. And I wanted a place where
I could showcase these talents. And let's talk about what real life is like for us, right?
What a lot of animals in Hollywood. For bringing light to what can still easily be glossed over
as a programmer and Hollywood life. We're going to include a little music. Yes.
It's courtesy of the Podsate Music Network. Podsate Music Network.
So to check out the under-exposed talent behind the scenes in Hollywood, visit non-terrace.com
N-O-N-T-O-U-R-A-G.
No, hardly hold their podcast arena.
Are you podcasting, click-cast addicts? You need to fix your content to static. Now it comes out
of me and your grandma's house, grab your hot pot down and get loud. All the streams out of the
vengeance, stuff about engines. And no, he didn't retire. He brought it down with the USB firewall.
Oh, I love my corny in the man football. I couldn't even hear before, just for the rest
that it's on the MXL. All right, he's saying you're going to hell. Keep your pace with the
kicks and frees up. As if I cast once a week up. Just another man on the scene.
And babe, this is Jason from JasonNosed.com. And please turn your hearts as beats this way. And let's
bring you in the music, bring you live, and your news, bring you everything that you want,
tell me which one I will put it on the Wicked Podcast and jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump, jump.
Incoming subs-based, click-off. Click-off, click-off, click-off, click-off, click-off, click-off, click-off, click-off, click-off.
Hi everyone, this is Rev Tim from the Rev Tim podcast, fresh from the San Francisco Bay area.
Now if we can bring you a little bit of hope and inspiration, our job has been accomplished.
We want to help you build positive relationships with your spouse, with your children,
with your friends at your workplace and just help you to find out how God wants you to be a better person in this life.
You know, God has a plan and a purpose for your life.
It is not for disaster, but it's to give you a hope and a future.
Check it out, the Rev Tim podcast.
Just go to Rev Tim.com and click on the show no point.
Yeah, Rev Tim, I have a feeling he'll be at the podcast or it's not actually podcast.
It was the portable media expose what it's called and on Tereo this coming weekend.
So here's what I've been thinking about.
I'm going by the way, that's probably clear right now.
I've received so many emails from people saying, hey man, looking forward to seeing you there.
I'm like, oh, this is going to be horrible because the last thing I want is to this is how it usually goes.
You know, you're talking to someone someone else comes up and then,
oh, can I talk to you about this and I, oh, I want to say this and hey, just one second and it's and I love the attention.
Don't get me wrong, but it's just, it's not productive to have any real meaningful conversations.
So here's what I'd like to do for today when you hear this, please send me an email sent it to atomoodcurry.com and put in the subject line,
which we make it easy, see you at PME, there you go, see you at PME and just so I know who's there because I want to try and set up some,
I'm going to be there for a couple of days, so I want to try and set up some kind of schedules that I can meet with people who want to meet,
you know, I want to hook up, I'd love to put some faces to some voices and lots of people have questions and would like to know,
you know, how maybe they can work with us, just send it to atomoodcurry.com, see you at PME and so I can kind of put a list together and then we'll be on a lookout for you.
I've got to find a place where we can have, you know, I think what we're putting together is a place where we can meet and chill and this also goes for pod squadters,
members of the pod squad who are already in the family. This is your very impersonal invitation.
It's just too much, this, you know, everybody wants to talk and everyone wants to hang out. So I'm going to try and coordinate as much as possible.
And if we don't get around to it, you know, please don't be pissed off, you know, it's just as I guess there's 2,000 people coming or something.
And I pretty much assume that every person who's going to be there is is very enthusiastic and interested in podcasting and has lots of questions.
And so hopefully we can get that all together. A couple of pieces of feedback I want to share with you today.
Yeah, my really want to get this out because again, it's just bugging me. I heard your podcast Monday regarding what the record companies are doing again.
And I'm not in the recording business, but I really am getting frustrated by everything sounding the same, looking the same.
And here it is, you know, there is this great tool we have. It's podcasting.
I'm one of a hundred million people ready to embrace something different.
I mean, if an artist can understand that this is a great on-ramp to get notice, I mean, I'm ready to give you money. I promise I will.
And there's people out there, all they want to, they're tired of the radio.
They're tired, they want, they're looking for juice, they're looking for something that's exciting, that's real.
And you can tell the fake stuff from the good stuff.
And please, all I'm saying to anybody out there with talent, let it out there.
I mean, if I had some talent, I don't care about the money so much right now as it is, to let your gift out there for the masses to know what it is.
And that's what pop you. We've got to stay together on this because podcasts are right on this.
This is a correct way of going. And this is what's going to make us win in the long end, long run.
It is because it's right. And it's about time we all stand up to all the BS out there.
And we say, no, this is how it's going to happen because we need it.
This is a change that is going on now. And if you don't do it this way, guess what we get?
The same old crap day in and day out. I'm tired of it.
No way, the door has been open just a little bit. And that's enough for me.
And I hope it's enough for millions of other people out there.
Thanks.
Right, I'm Mark.
Thank you very much for this feedback.
Well, it's true, you know. And by the way, that repetition, it's kind of, it's logical.
It's not mainstream media's fault, you know.
They can't narrow cast or do only like the roadhouse podcast, you know, you can't.
It just won't work. It's, you can't get an audience big enough to justify the infrastructure needed to broadcast that.
And, you know, even clear channel only has, you know, only has, you know, 2,000 radio stations that they own and control.
Well, podcast alley, I think just passed 10,000 podcasts.
You know, so it's obvious that this is, it's a breakout, you know, you're right.
It is totally a breakout. And I predict that within the next couple of years what will happen is there will be a meltdown.
Podcasting will make licensed RIA, licensed music irrelevant, irrelevant in culturally irrelevant.
Let me put it that way because I think people are migrating more, you know, everyone has time for their independent stuff.
That's just becoming more, you know, people are tuning out to tuning out from mainstream and tuning in a little bit more to the alternative side.
All it takes is a little bit of trust in your customers.
So I do predict that once, you know, the math is really simple on this stuff.
But once you get to the point where you have a song that people like.
Let's say there's the, right now we have 10,000 podcasters.
I think that it would be possible for one song to catch enough fire for 10% a thousand podcasters to, to want to play that song because they really dig it.
I think that's, that's very, very possible.
We might not have hit it yet.
Maybe we have and we just haven't been able to track it properly yet. I'm not sure.
Now, it's also not completely unthinkable that each of those thousand podcasters would have a thousand listeners, you know.
I think that's that's reasonable.
I think I think that there's plenty of shows out there that have anywhere from 500 to 5000 listeners and definitely more than a thousand.
So what if they all played one track?
Well, when we do the math, a thousand times a thousand is a million. So you'd have a million people hearing that track.
Now, of course, there's some crossover you may be subscribed to the same show, but come on.
It's a much better tracking mechanism than being used right now for radio with people filling out diaries.
And then there's this BDS system. It's just, it's an old fashioned system.
But when we have, you know, when we're able to expose music to a million people, watch the back catalog open up.
Please, it'll happen. It really will.
And there's so much untapped money there.
There's, you know, there's back catalogs are huge, much larger than the one and a half million songs that's available on iTunes today.
It's just a matter of giving people access to it and the people want it.
So I think that's probably what happened.
And this will happen across the board. Once it's evident how large this movement is and how many people are participating in it.
I think we're going to see some changes until then, you're right. I'm really excited about a lot of the new music and the artists that are out there.
Still want to talk about the, because the interesting wired article I read about the podcast, the podcast expo, the portable media expo.
There's other places you can meet up with podcasts.
If you can't make it to the expo, there are these, you probably heard of meetup dot, I think it's meetup.com, we'll meetup.org, meetup.com, I think.
Well, the meetups. So there's podcasts or meetups.
And in San Francisco, there's one.
I think it's the first Wednesday of every month.
I have successfully been able to schedule my flights wrong every single time.
So I haven't been able to attend a single one.
But I do know that lots of pod show folks go there and there's audio folks and podcasters.
And I believe Michael Butler actually organizes these. Now actually, I'm sure he organizes them.
And someone sent me a piece of audio from the most recent one, which must have been just the other night.
It's really nice to hear what what people I work with think about me.
So please ask questions.
This is Michael Butler.
The meetup.
My name is Kevin Ostrowski.
I've yet to have a podcast, but I'm working on a few ideas.
I work over at Pod Show.
Well, is the name of that company?
Pod Show.
Okay.
I understand some other cool people work there too.
Yeah, we got a nice crew.
And here's another developer.
Oh, I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm here for the drinks.
My name is Colleen.
That sounds like a real pod show employee.
I'm here with the drinks.
And I don't have a podcast either, in fact, I listen to the radio.
What are you doing?
So what do you do it?
Oh, my goodness.
Colleen.
Dude.
We got to work on the last.
What are you doing?
I'm in the pod show.
Pardon me?
What do you do at Pod Show?
Uh, cause a lot of trouble.
And uh, do some software stuff.
I bring people together, really.
I build cool shit.
It's like hand-holding between listeners, musicians, and...
You might know any cool shit that's in the pipeline from Pod Show.
That's what you listen to daily source code for.
Really?
No.
You don't get any information from the daily source code.
I'll give him a break, poor guy.
Okay, Colleen, little star.
Michael Butler gets a little checkmark there.
Okay.
I'm just keeping a tally here.
The meetups.
Wonderful stuff.
Let me see.
What should I do now?
What am I?
Man, I've been doing it.
What are we now?
Almost more than half an hour.
Okay.
I want to talk about this wired article that greeted me this morning as I woke up.
First, I'll do a couple more promos.
Get those out of the way.
The fourth annual Southern California Linux Expo is coming.
It will be February 11th and 12th 2006 at the Western Los Angeles Airport.
Scale 4X will build on Scale 3X.
We've moved to a new location, which has allowed us to expand the Expo.
We'll have more speaker tracks and more tutorials designed to show users of all scale levels.
What open source can do, and Scale 4X will offer more boost space for those interested in showing how they've made open source work for them.
If you're interested in presenting on a topic, the Scale 4X call for papers open through November 20th 2005.
For those staying over, the Western is offering special hotel room rates for the Expo.
Whatever your interest in open source, Scale 4X has something for you.
Park fools!
What are your sources?
You don't have to do.
What?
Are they drawing on these park lines?
Turn me a bit, Volio.
Look upon by death.
I do what keep them.
Hey there, Adam.
This is Sean J from Shakespeare Cast.
Live from the streets of Verona, Italy.
Where it looks like the cavealts and monogues are getting a little hot and heavy again.
Anyway, I just wanted to tell you about our new podcast at ShakespeareCast.com.
Or we're doing full cast recordings of Shakespeare's plays.
Oh yeah.
Calm down, everybody.
Full cast recordings of Shakespeare plays one act at a time.
Well, right now it's more like one scene at a time, but we can't all start out as the pod
Father now can we?
So head on over to ShakespeareCast.com and find out if Romeo and Juliet will make it this
time.
Oh, who am I kidding?
It's a tragedy.
Anyway, I love your show, but that sounds like the prince.
So I'd better get out of here before I get stabbed, poisoned, hung, or find out that the young
male page I find myself strangely attracted to is actually a shipwreck young woman.
Oh, sorry.
Wrong play.
Shakespeare cast.
Does that not hear?
Pot show should only be enjoyed under the supervision of a podcasting professional.
Warning.
Do not attempt this at home.
Alright, coming up, I'm going to take a look at this wired article that came out
some kind of riff between apparently I have a riff with the portable music expo.
We'll get into that for sure.
Oh, man, I played these roles before.
Wake it up the neighborhood.
Why are the women?
Why are you drinking me to your door?
Why don't we have an even there before?
How much drink it's got to do with my hair?
Yes, needs a one-one, take care, take care.
Can't smell the passion.
I don't know what I'm meant for.
No, I'm not meant for the child at all.
You got me feeling good.
Why are you not the neighborhood?
Why don't we have an even there before?
How much drink it's got to do with my hair?
What do we have to do with my hair?
Why don't we have an even there before?
How much drink it's got to do with my hair?
Why don't we have an even there before etton's on the better together?
Why don't we have an even there before?
How much drink it's got to do with my hair?
We have an even there before?
I've been on the name of the world
Yeah, I know.
Yeah ah.
Yeah yeah
Why do you wanna be above
right in theuj
Wherever you want something
Yeah yeah
I ain't never brought it down
Why do you pick that one
Where you can make it
You ain't never brought it down
Who was that?
Take me to it
If we'd fooled your women
We accompagnoned our neighborhood
That's right
on the source code music.podshow.com is where you can find that. So I don't know if
you've seen this yet, I'm sure it'll show up in the show notes, which of course
you can find at dailysourcecode.com or curie.com. Oh man, huge controversy
brewing in the podcast world. You should read this article. It's so typical. So
it apparently wired is the reporting that I, that I, interestingly enough,
have an issue with the portable media expo. I'm not quite sure what happened
here in all the communication and, you know, geez, these guys, the podcast
brother started this idea over a year ago. I was, I've always been very
supportive of it and, and I've promoted and played bits from the show and I've
talked about it. I think maybe, you know, they said something on one of their
shows. I'm just going to paraphrase here. Oh no, I'm sorry, it started, it did
start with me. I said, I, I didn't think that the portable media expo was the
right venue for us to, you know, to get up on stage and talk about what we're
doing. And I think there, quote, was, look, where the Detroit auto show and
pod show was for that's weird that they're not there or something to that
effect. And so somehow it kind of got out of hand. I think Aaron, the pod
pin, who does marketing communications for us at pod show. Maybe you got a
little bit excited, you know, and when he heard that and, you know, Aaron's a good
guy gets, he's passionate about it gets worked up. And of course, what happens
then is the press loves a good controversy. Well, let me just tell you, the
expo is a fantastic idea and I supported 100%. I just want you to know, my
actually our approach, my partner and co-founder of pod show Ron Bloom, we've
been in business for like 12 years together. We've had many businesses. The
last one we did together. We took public. We had 700 people. You know, it was
huge operation. But never, ever, ever have we paid to play, I guess is is
what you could call it. Because here's here's how trade shows work. Basically
you sponsor the show. And then you get to put a speaker up on stage to do
often the keynote is offered or some other spot. And then you can basically do
your commercial. You do your ad about whatever product you're you're promoting.
This is exactly what Audible does. And by the way, a company like Audible,
this is how they operate. And this is the way they understand doing PR. Audible
has not been the force in pod casting at all. And now they're a platinum
sponsor. And, you know, they they paid. And so they're going to have a
speaking slot. I'm not quite sure if Don Katz is coming or someone else
representing the company. And they'll be rolling out a pod casting service
that that I know about, but I'm not glad to tell you about, which so I won't
know, damn announcements. So, but that's kind of the way it works, you know,
and we've never felt a need to do that. And, you know, when you're looking at
and it costs a lot of money to do this, you know, it's anywhere from 25 to 35,000
dollars. Well, first of all, we have nothing to announce, per se. I think there's
going to be a lot of announcements at this show. So, I'm much more of, hey,
let me just hang back and see what everyone else is doing and announcing. And,
you know, we've we want to be wise with how we invest our funds. And we
typically invest them in podcasters, which is the root of all of this.
You know, we're trying to help people do this full time. We're, um,
we're investing in the, um, in the podsafe music hold-down, uh, Thursday night.
You know, there's, uh, there's a couple of grand in that, uh,
to, you know, get people out and put people up and, uh, and get the venues
squared away, um, you know, so it's, um, it's, uh, that's what I like so much about,
actually Dave Wein are really solidified this for me a couple of years ago when he started
doing blogger con, which is the unconference. You know, it's, um, you, you go to a university
in this case, which is a, you know, pretty much a free venue. And, and I've always sponsored
blogger con. You know, I'll be the first to put down, you know, as much as Google did,
you know, I think we both put down a thousand dollars. I love that. I mean, that's the way it is.
There's no advertising. Um, it's, it's just free form communications. And, uh, to be honest,
um, uh, I think this is probably surrounds whether I should have done a keynote or not. I have nothing to say.
I mean, I got plenty to say, but that's what I love saying on the daily source code.
Little secret that not many of you know, I really, really, really do not like speaking in front of
audience just strange as it sounds. I love the little protection of my windscreen and my microphone.
I'm not big on doing that. It's like that Johnson Johnson thing I mentioned earlier, man,
they got a drag me to that because I mean, once I'm actually into the groove of it,
and I kind of treated like a show, then I'm, yeah, then I'm vibing on it. But, um, oh, no, because
I'm, I'm not funny. I'm not particularly quick on my feet. Um, I like to have things prepared.
And, yeah, it's just, it's, uh, it's different than announcing a Michael Jackson video, you know,
it's just much harder. So, um, so, and then what am I going to say? Hey, everybody, here's the
pod father. Thanks for coming. Come on, man. That's not for me. Um, and we actually, um, put together
quite a, uh, quite a little schedule of, uh, flying, um, different pod show podcasters in, uh,
getting, uh, making sure that we can meet with everybody who wants to hook up, um, trying to
bring some good cheer. You know, and then I got a little messy where, you know, we wanted press credentials
for Steve Gilmore and Madge Weinstein and Madge Weinstein was refused to press good to credentials.
So, that kind of got to, what's that, huh? Uh, yes, thank you. Yes, that's mine.
You're too late. You can't be on the show. Now, only have a couple minutes left.
Oh, I'm sorry. Didn't you see the red light revolving in front of the door, which means you can come
on in and that means you can come in. Red light spells danger. Thanks, baby. Okay, let love you.
Love you, too.
So, um, right, right. So, you know, that's the trade shows to me, you know, sponsoring that
is sponsoring the trade show business, which is great. And, uh, and I hope that the, uh,
the podcast brothers are very successful. I hope this is a recurring event. I think it's fantastic.
You know, it could easily be as, as big as any other, um, expo or trade show, uh, but
you have just never, we've never, you know, spent any money on that. You know, it, it comes from,
from the roots itself. And that's what we want to put our money is in, uh, in podcasters who,
um, strive to quit their, their day job. I think that there's a lot of people who would love to do that.
All right. So, I want to help you do that. Um, and you'll be hearing a lot, uh, um, certainly if we,
if we have an opportunity to hook up or if you see any of the other pod squatters, then, um,
they'll be telling you about the audition and, uh, all the good stuff that is, uh, that is to come.
So, no bad blood, my brothers. Not at all. Not at all. And that's it. Um, I'm going to start
packing. I have that whole list to, to, to work off all that stuff I got to do. I appreciate the time
you took, uh, this morning and I will talk to you either tomorrow or Friday. Bye bye.