Warning.
The following podcast contains extremely annoying geeky talk about studio setups and mixing gear.
Yeah, we're off to a great start there.
Hey everybody, it's the day to source code.
It's Friday.
Oh, man.
Okay.
I think that her maiden voyage is going to turn out just fine.
Well, I'll be just some levels here.
If you hadn't seen the picture on curry.com yet,
I got some new gear that I'm testing out today on the source code.
Oh, okay.
So besides the usual stuff, we will be discussing the studio setup.
I can't believe I finally broke down and did it.
I went out to the music store and I got everything I need to create.
More or less exactly the sound and the connections between different pieces of equipment that
I've wanted to do that I've been trying to do on software on my computer.
I just went ahead and bought all the outboard gear and I am totally loving it.
I hope the sound is starting to come along there.
So at this point, I again want to warn you that I'll be talking a lot.
I'm particularly beginning about these new boxes that I've purchased and I set up
and all the different pieces and how they all fit together.
But I also have a hit test coming up.
Something that was listed on your pod safe, but I'm not quite sure it is.
It sounds more like a mashup.
And I got another podcast to go along.
Listen to it together.
Okay, let me just try one thing here.
First thing I want to do is switch to the other microphone.
So I did that almost seamlessly.
Now you're on the live microphone so I can get up and walk around.
And I need to go over to the computer you see.
So that doesn't sound too bad, does it?
Hold on a second.
It makes back to the first mic.
So that's the, this is the sure the SM7.
I'm not quite happy with the way it sounds.
It's a little high on the S6.
Have you ever heard people who speak like that when the S?
And it keeps on singing.
Isn't that annoying?
It surely does bug the hell out of me.
Okay.
Let's see if we can get this going.
When you grow up, let it hit like a good boy out of.
And your mama digs it shine a perfect sun.
Something different.
Oh, the girls are seeming like you.
Because your pants are like you don't fit in the pool out of fun.
But now your girl is going to miss an annual house.
It's got an empty bed.
The folks are wondering about the wedding.
They won't listen to what word you said.
We're gonna take your mama out on that year.
We're showin' what it's all about.
We're gonna jack the phone from cheap champagne.
We're gonna let the good times all roll out.
And if the music ain't good, well it's just too bad.
We're gonna sing along the metalwood.
Because it doesn't mind if the new world lives.
If you're different man to make us good.
You're day breaks, you're my days.
You're finding that all the words you've kinder.
Just sing along when she no longer needs you.
She wakes up, she wakes up.
She takes a time and doesn't feel she has to run.
She no longer needs you.
And then her eyes, you see nothing.
Don't sight out the love and be out of the tears.
Cry for no one.
I love that you're the last to be used.
You're the last to be used.
We'll save the Eltern with a gun.
Do you want to do me up?
I don't anathal.
You can save youroko family.
You're a full grown man.
You want to be hurt.
And yet you don't really hurt.
When she says her love is dead, you think she needs you
And when her eyes you see nothing
No sign of love beyond the tears, cry for no one
I love that she'll never last tears
I'm always down there, I'm always down there
I can't sleep, I'm always my girl, I'm always down
I'm just a girl, just a girl, just a girl
Don't let them down, don't let them down
I know what I'm all about, forget I can't come out
If they don't know, my heart will hurt
If they don't know, my heart will be going
They'll shake my cheeks, they'll always be going
They'll walk my way up to sleep now, I'm always down
I didn't even mention Tonight actually at that moment
If they were better I'll never think I could
They'll go get her, I got her with me
Just a minute on her, you and I
Run to the abyss for all sorts of love
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, want a lot of love we, good start, yeah, that's my time, we both of you guys like you
Oops, sorry, that was a rather abrupt fade out there.
Oh, I was really digging that too.
From DJEarWorm.com,
Scissors, Sisters, Beatles, George Michael,
A Reath of Franklin.
It was almost like a mega mix,
and a traditional mashup.
Right, too.
Okay, so let me tell you what happened this morning.
I went out, well, first of all,
I dropped Christina off at school,
and then I went to Anderton's Music Store in Guilford,
which is just as you enter the town,
the road kind of a busy two-way lane street,
and I was able to pick up a cup of coffee
at the gas station just before it
because they don't open until 930.
So I read the newspaper,
didn't have the financial times,
read the Guardian front to cover,
basically, waiting for the store to open.
And really nice guy, sales guy named Andy,
helped me out, and he knew what podcasting was.
And so I tried to explain to him,
you know, what I was looking to do.
And I'd purchase the,
Con the Soundcraft Compact 6 Mixer,
which I put in the show notes for yesterday's daily source code.
So you can purchase that,
and if you buy it,
then I actually make 5.25%
until I sell another 70 items,
when I move up to 5.5%.
But it's actually product those movies,
pretty interesting.
So he already knew what gear I had at home,
and I told him, you know, what mics I had.
And basically, what I wanted,
I wanted a preamp for the microphone.
So, you know, I can do a little bit of effects.
You know, I have a little bit of the,
I didn't put reverb on,
I put just a very little faint bit of,
what is it?
It's an echo plate actually.
And a little bit of compression on the microphone.
And I don't know if it's too much or not,
I just can turn out once it's all compressed to MP3.
You know, it may sound horrible,
but I've been working out all day.
And what happens, you know,
as you're fiddling around with sound,
at a certain point,
you just don't know what you're hearing anymore.
It's really hard.
So let me see.
And actually, as I move over to the mixing board,
I'll switch over to the second,
the lavelier mic,
which I have on,
which I have here on a second fader.
Okay, so I'm in front of my 19 inch rack.
One of those 19 inch tabletop racks,
to do the job,
because I had two pieces of gear,
and I also had the M audio fire wire box.
So on the top,
it's kind of a cheap thing,
but it's a multi-effects,
it's a TC electronic dual engine processor,
the M300, everybody.
And so it has compression,
which is running only on the microphone,
because I took an insert from the mixer,
so that's basically inserting it into the line,
before it goes into the compression part.
But after the mic preamp on this other beautiful box
that I bought,
which is the TL audio, TLA,
ivory series.
This is the stereo valve processor.
And what that means is actually,
it has tubes in it,
and tubes were used before transistors.
And actually,
it's getting harder for,
to find the replacement tubes.
I think Phillips and Holland actually pretty much
makes most of them at this point.
But most audio files swear by the sound of two processing.
So it's two units in one.
It's four units in one.
It has two channels,
and it has a microphone preamp
with a limiter.
And then that's where I've put the insert
to go out to the effects generator.
After the microphone preamp,
then it comes back,
and then it goes through the compressor,
and then it goes through an equalizer,
which has a pre equalizer,
and a main equalizer,
and I have the two link together
so that provides the stereo output signal.
And of course,
I'm still recording on my very trusty,
I River IPF799,
which is now also listed on curie.com,
and another fine piece of equipment to buy.
And I got some mic stands,
which actually I'm struggling with right now.
Hold on a sec.
So I'm back on the main microphone,
on the sure.
Yeah, I got one of those really,
you know, those boom mic stands,
and I finally got a windscreen for the microphone.
So the piece,
and I say Patricia Pi's podcast,
it won't plop too much.
That's saying for better, excuse me,
a little Dutch that slipped in,
it's much better in any case than it was.
So hooking it all up was really quite a feat,
actually,
just trying to figure out all the routing
in which wires go in wire,
and Andy had drawn me a diagram,
which came in really handy,
handy,
and he's diagram.
And it's kind of worked out.
I think there's a slight hum in this microphone,
though, excuse me.
That's probably because I haven't really cleaned up the wires,
yet Patricia's nagging me,
and she's right, of course.
Oh, and I got a second boom microphone
for the handheld that I had,
and a windscreen for that.
So Patricia and I can both sit here and do,
you know,
we can do a PPP,
triple P podcast,
but with all the luxury that you'd expect from,
a studio that actually works and everything all together,
which includes like the headphones,
so I have a separate headphone extension jack,
and it's no longer with latency or delay.
Oh, by the way, I've also routed one output from this mixer
through the M audio fire wire device,
which goes into the, this is the cool part,
goes into the,
my old laptop,
which the screen doesn't work anymore,
but that's hooked up to the big cinema display.
So I have a monitor output,
I'll turn it up now.
It's delayed a little bit,
because that's basically the latency that I used to deal with.
That's the delay I used to have on my headphones,
when I was talking,
and of course,
the delay that most of you recognize,
if you're using garage band and sound flower,
and eventually this is the shit that crops up,
so,
oh man, there's such a big,
big hole in the software market,
to create something that actually works for us,
but we're not quite there yet.
Maybe it's hardware, I'm not sure.
Oh, and I also, by the way,
a lot of people sent me schematics and diagrams,
and how to create a T-splitter that I can plug my iPod,
and my microphone into simultaneously,
without having the levels get all messed up like they were.
And basically I need to 10k own resistors,
and in order to box,
I ordered the resistors,
and I ordered the three and a half inch jack,
so it's going to be completely cool.
Of course,
I'd already placed the order,
and I realized that in order to do stereo,
I have to have four resistors,
instead of the two that I ordered,
and I'm like, what kind of dork am I?
In ordering two fucking resistors,
at 50 cents a pop,
I probably should've just gotten a couple extra
just for the hell of it.
So anyway,
back to the desktop,
because you see,
and I put a picture up on curry.com,
the laptop,
which really has all my production stuff on it,
has my outline for the show,
and the quick time player in sequence,
is to the right of the 19 inch rack.
Now, that's not very convenient to sit,
and do the show.
So I opened up VNC.
I don't know if you know what VNC is,
but it's basically,
it's a cross-platform open source application.
There has many clients for all different platforms,
and you can control a desktop.
So seeing is it's on the same network,
there's almost no delay in dragging stuff around,
and basically I've brought the desktop
on the power book that runs everything up on my main screen here,
on the cinema display,
and I'm just kind of controlling it with the mouse over here.
So it works.
I have a setup that is almost starting to look official.
I feel kind of official too.
Right on.
Okay, so that's the new setup.
Now let's move on.
I want to talk about here.
Oh, I got an email from Craig Patchett,
who said that recommends keeping the eye river
that's saying the device I used to record my sound scene tours on,
and also now I'm using it as a final end recorder.
Keep it away from your cell phone,
while you're recording,
he says his IFP795 got reset to 00.0020,
20 minutes into a recording yesterday,
after some weird interference with his phone,
while the two were sitting next to each other.
Which is pretty frightening,
and Craig and I mailed back and forth a little bit more,
and he said that actually the recording was also lost,
and this is something that seems to happen more often.
So when you're doing those sound scene tours,
and you're recording and put the cell phone in the left pocket,
put the eye river in the right pocket,
but that sounds kind of weird though,
that's not something that really I guess should happen.
But before warned, that's what's going on.
It's kind of fun in the UK today.
It's Red Nose Day,
and I don't know if you've heard of this.
It's affiliated with Comic Relief,
oh, this is those birds.
And not just on television,
which really does drive it.
They've been ramping up to this day
for the past couple weeks,
and celebrities doing a version of pop idols,
and just everyone kind of really good fun,
and just everyone kind of pitching in.
You can tell that people are really into it,
and they're really surpassing their boundaries
of what they normally might do on television
because it is for a good cause, and it's for kids.
And you can purchase these red noses
at different stores, Saintsbury is one,
where we do a lot of our grocery shopping,
and people are wearing them.
Right, you know, you drive by the gas station,
they might be wearing two red antennae headset balls,
kind of, you know, like the Martian balls,
whether it be red with red noses on top,
or that actually have a red nose, or a red nose pin.
And it's just really cool.
And tonight is the big grand finale.
And I guess there's a big TV show
to go with that or whatever,
and you still kind of get the feel here
when something, you know,
a big Saturday night or Friday night show
is on the BBC, that a lot of people are watching.
Oh, shoot, what time is it?
603. Oh, man. Oh, damn.
Oh, Christina is, I just remembered Christina's out,
and she's not coming home until later,
in Patricia and I have dinner reservations at 6.30.
Okay, so I'll just be able to make this before,
oh, man, I gotta get dressed.
I look like shit, I gotta be here.
Okay, well, then let me just move on quickly
to Michael Jackson, but following the news.
Man, I just want to say again,
you know, what people are saying is one thing
and what the evidence will be is another,
and I still have a hard time believing
what's being suggested,
and the press is just using this and having a feel day,
and is really, really, really not giving you any information
that I think is anywhere near the truth,
so we just really gotta be careful.
Tim, you know, more importantly,
you know, let justice take its course,
which it will, I believe in the justice system.
It should also work for entertainers like Michael Jackson,
but his life is tiring, you know, right now,
and I can feel a little bit of his pain,
and it's definitely, you know,
it would give me a headache and make me throw up
all day too, believe me.
But justice will take its course,
and you know, let's just lay off a little bit
on all the name calling, you know,
even just saying wacko, jacko, which is so easy,
you know, but there is a guy behind that,
and there is a family and friends,
and it does hurt, it really does.
So, backslash on rant.
Now let's listen to a cool little podcast
I ran across the other day.
Behind the scenes, February 14th, 2000,
listen to the opening.
We don't need no stinking transmittance.
Love that.
It's behind the scenes,
an inside look at what it takes
to put together a podcast
and make it work.
Check it out.
So basically, this is a podcast
you want to subscribe to if you're new to this scene.
It's a great package,
and welcome back.
It's a great thing to request for a 20 minute edition
of Behind the Scenes.
It's Monday, February 14th, 2005,
and I have to tell you there is no love
in the air tonight, at least not when it comes down to.
And you'll have to listen to the show to find out why.
It's almost like the Craig Patchett show,
but that's okay.
But that is a cool podcast.
It's behind the scenes,
and this was indeed the show about the RIA.
Listen to the next videos talking about it.
The legalities of music in podcasts
as you're going to find out over the next
20, 30, or who knows how many minutes of this show.
I have spent a lot of time this week
researching the legalities of music in podcasts.
You know what's cool?
It's now I can really regulate the volume
of these podcasts and these promos
and the stuff comes in too hot or too low.
I can really crank it up.
And the compressor does a lot of work.
So yeah, yeah, I'm totally liking it.
Okay, let's do this then.
Let's get started.
Thank you.
I'm still a little bit tired for the hit test.
I mean, it's bright, right?
I'm right.
Hey Adam, pay Adam this is Craig Shumaker
from the Polymorphic podcast.
Oh, okay, right.
In order to keep you on your toes,
Yann and I come up with a twist for the hit test for you.
Uh-oh.
As an alumni of Headbangers Ball,
you'll be able to recognize these songs by their guitar cell.
Oh, no.
Now it shouldn't be too hard as they're all hair metal bands
and they've charted with these singles.
I'm so scared.
Number one.
I don't know because our cell is.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, man.
Woo!
It's definitely a Friday hit test.
But, uh...
Number two.
Where's Michael Butler when you're here?
Where's Michael Butler on?
A number three.
Yeah.
Oh man, fuck good.
Oh no way.
Are you ready?
Here's the answer.
No, no, no, no.
Number one.
Straight.
I'm gonna turn it down.
I want to hear it right now.
Okay, I didn't.
Let's pretend I didn't hear anything.
Oh my, second.
Um, like, I was moving my windows around
through the VNC connection and got really slow
I'm really slow and I'm like trying to stop the hit test from playing and it won't stop.
But now I've got my Skype window just, okay, here we go, stop.
Good, I see that Michael butt goes online.
Let's see if we can get him on the Skype, he'll be able to do this.
I know he will, hold on.
I've got to hit this button here so that my microphone will play through to him, hold on.
Come on buddy, be home.
Skype says he's there.
Come on.
I need him now.
You know, I gotta say I'm the guy that always has my Skype on a way.
Even though I'm here, I just sit here clicking windows, closed and rejecting them.
Ah, he's out there.
Ah, shoes.
That's a bummer.
Oh man.
Okay, you know what, I'm gonna keep it though.
I'm not gonna play this hit test.
I want to keep that one from Michael Butler.
I want to do that with him.
Let's play this kind of weird mashup that I found instead.
So more hit test after the weekend and we'll do it with Michael Butler.
We used to stay all the way.
About all the way around in the grave.
And I know when you lost that.
But I just had to learn that.
You lose my time in the past.
Didn't know that I could find the change.
Ground up on your skin and the sweat.
She is facing her.
Nobody will need to join me in the world.
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
Oh! My name is Bob.
Ghalf.
I don't believe in it.
But
I just have to frame your head.
The shot never came.
crowd of people turn away
but I just had to do everything
I know time
So my favorite movie of all times Willy Wonka's Charlie and the chocolate factory.
Oh, I love that movie.
Okay, so I gotta go because there you go.
I'm getting Skype from downstairs now.
I have to shave, I have to do my hair, which of course I'm taking these long as it
used to.
Hold on, now it's Ron, hold on, let me just tell him I'm going out for, yeah, get a kick out
of this.
Oh, that's like, is that working?
Yeah.
Hey, Ron, I'm recording the show.
Yeah, I just saw you nailing with him.
Like I'm recording you now.
Hey.
Okay, hey.
So anyway, I gotta go out, Patricia and I are having dinner and we're having sushi
so I gotta run, but, um, talk to you later?
Yeah, this makes sure you get the cook stuff because, uh, something fishy about it.
Okay, my mom.
Okay, I'm a lot of goto.
Talk to you later.
Bye.
Okay.
Oh, shit, I could have done the, the test with him too, with the rocks on his ass shit,
whatever.
Okay.
Dude, I, I, I do, and do that.
I promise you, I will, uh, hold on, see, do you hear that I'm getting Skype messages
now?
It's distracting me.
I should shut Skype off.
I'm doing this, really.
I promise you, over the weekend, I'll get a hold of Michael, uh, Butler, Rock and
Will Geek, and we'll definitely get him to do the hit test because that's should
that'll be a, uh, who would, I mean, I'll never know, but he should certainly know
at least some of them, right?
So that's it for the source code, little shorter than normal.
I'll work on the door.
But only by 11 or 12 minutes.
Comments at amcurry.com.
Send a promo there as well if you're showed you want to.
Yeah, my got to do that too.
I got to fix the 350 back at gmail.com.
Um, or leave a comment on my weblog www.curry.com.
As always, the latest show in the archives can be found at DailySource.
sourcecode.com.
That's also where you will find the podcast fee.
That's it.
I'll talk to you over the weekend for sure.
Take care.
Bye.