The Resource Code April 22nd, 2005.
Your DJ has only just begun.
$16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
The next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk.
I'm just kidding.
Coming to you from the cottage in Guilford and Lovely Surrey UK.
It's your daily source code.
Hey, everybody, how you doing?
It's out of my curry and the big green thing, chilled out.
Relaxed.
I've got the cast blaster on the lap.
Got the high powered microphone and the boom kind of like flowing over the green thing.
This is the way to do a show.
Let me tell you.
I mean, I could even be doing my nails.
Got a pedicure on doing this.
This is great.
Oh, man.
I feel fuzzy today.
I really do.
It's been such an incredibly long week and tense week.
Lots of traveling, lots of flying.
Thanks for all the comments and feedback on the sound seem to or from yesterday.
It seems like even though there was quite a bit that I recorded,
including driving around with taxi Eric and the Dutch Marines.
The actual flying lessons, the training sessions seem to grab everybody's fancy.
I must say it was without a doubt my favorite part too.
Of course, whenever I sit down and do a show, my phone immediately starts ringing.
Just put that over there.
Alrighty.
So it's the last day of the week.
It's early here.
It's five minutes to eleven.
I'm trying to get into a regular rhythm again and get a swing going here,
so that I can pretty much get back to my schedule every single day.
All the traveling definitely messed it up a bit.
So I had some time to browse through podcast alley.
See what's hot.
I had a chance to look at the new podcast that comes through an iPod.org.
Also, the promo has been coming in.
Thank you very much for sending them in the way I requested.
If you want to send me a promo, send it to Adam at Curry.com and put in the subject line.
DSC space promo and then whatever the heck your promo is about.
Hey, Adam.
This is the song we're at a Craig Manganella from Rockaway.
Crings New York.
And I've got a podcast.
My fans is a great way to communicate gig dates.
Another important thing about my music.
The fans that subscribe to my RSS feed also get to hear my new songs.
So immediately after I record left track.
So if you have listening to like indie music, tell them to come visit my site, Craig'sMusic.net
and subscribe to my podcast.
Hey, you know what?
I see more and more musicians these days doing that and starting to understand the power of the podcast and what you can do with it.
You know, necessarily have to even, you know, record a show or anything.
You can just have a website and just put your new music in a podcast feeds.
The people can receive that and enjoy it and listen to it.
Show notes are pretty important with that stuff.
Because you want people, you know, once it's on your MP3 player and, you know, just kind of shows up there.
You know, it's, it may not be easy for people to find out where it came from.
But I think that what you should be targeting in that case is probably the podcasters themselves.
I had a couple of phone conferences last week with some people in the, in the record industry.
And they're not, you know, they're not all evil.
I'll tell you.
In fact, they're running scared.
The record industry, the music industry is really worried.
If you, if you had a chance, or if you have a chance, check out Forbes.com.
Send Whitmore, wrote a very well researched piece, I thought, or at least,
regarding the music industry part about the rights and what you can play.
And he, he does the deadhead podcast.
If you've never heard that, you should definitely check it out.
And he went around to all of these, and I think there was five or six of them.
The agencies whose job it is to collect money for the use of records from music,
whether it's in an elevator, on a radio station, on a podcast, on a download, on a stream.
You know, whatever it is.
And basically, everyone said, well, we don't know yet.
Works still kind of waiting to see what happens.
And I think I understand why they're waiting to see.
That's because the record industry, who, of course, are totally on to podcasting.
No, what's going on?
They're listening to them.
I mean, we know that I had a meeting with Harvey Leeds from Epic Records.
And, you know, he even wants to do his own podcast.
So they clearly see the promotional value of it.
And, you know, it's, it's going to be a business decision, which, unfortunately,
lawyers will also help the record industry make.
But when I talked to them, I said, look, there's one thing that we don't have on the radio anymore
that we do have in podcasting.
And that's the whole concept of somebody really promoting a song or a band or an artist or a CD,
or whatever, because they genuinely like it.
And that's what radio used to bring us.
It used to, you know, used to be able to flip on the radio and hear some excited, hyperactive DJ
saying, man, I love this record.
I got to play it again for you.
You know, where the day is when, when a disjockey would lock himself in the studio.
And would say, you know, and would defy whatever management had told him and was going to play this record
every hour until they dragged him out and dragged that record from his cold dead fingers.
You know, that used to happen, believe it or not.
It used to happen quite a lot.
And just the excitement about about a piece of music that you really like passing that on to people.
That's the best promotion you can get.
I mean, when, when do you, when you get interested in a band when someone says, hey, check it out.
Now, of course, we have that on a one to one basis.
We've had that on the internet for quite a while.
And I, and I don't like the word independent music or indie music or indie music scene.
I think pod safe is a much better way to go because if we can create pod safe music.
And maybe that, maybe that's something that we could talk to Lawrence Lessick about.
Who, of course, does creative commons.
Maybe we can create a pod safe license, which is just one of their standard default that you can select,
which basically will give any pod cast or the right to use their music on a pod cast.
And perhaps the deal is that if you do that, then you at least have to point back to a place where information can be found about it.
So, you know, there's something brewing here that really is.
And, and I'm going to try and make it my business to figure out if we can, if we can push that through,
if we can get the record industry to understand the incredible value of this type of promotion.
And it's for, and it's for a number of reasons because you have basically, I think you have like three.
You have three types of music that that we have to look at licensing.
One, of course, is I think the least interesting for pod cast is, you know, the, the top 100.
You know, whatever's being played on radio now and is being sold by the millions is not that interesting to us.
Because you can get that somewhere else.
If you think about all of the great back catalog and some, you know, bands that who have just kind of, you know, well, they're old now, right?
And they have all this tremendous amount of music that, you know, longer are exposed to because radio's no longer playing it.
Yeah, I think, well, let me take that back.
Sidelight radio, of course, is very good for back catalog.
But think about it, you know, I've played a couple of really old songs here and immediately I get tons of email of people saying,
Oh, man, I, I had never heard that Chicago track before I went out and bought the, bought the CD off of iTunes or I bought that particular track off of iTunes.
That happens all the time.
So I think there's a tremendous amount of value in back catalog.
Very much like Amazon, you know, there's so many books at amazon.com, which you just can't find in a bookstore.
So what do you do? You know, Amazon is large enough and has the right type of infrastructure to have pieces of catalog like that, which a normal bookstore just has doesn't have the space for.
So out of print, out of date, out of fashion, but still full of very wonderful, good memories for anybody who's ever heard is song or want to reintroduce to a particular band.
Look at green day for Christ's sex. I saw them at Woodstock too.
Yeah, I tell my daughter for her Woodstock too is the original Woodstock, right?
Yeah, she says, wow, this guy's been around a long time and, you know, I was able to introduce her to green day who now, of course,
you know, really have a revival on their hands and are, you know, doing tremendously well.
But I also am able to pick up songs for her and introduce like the sex pistols and the clash and early rolling stones.
And yes, of course, she all she can recognize a Beatles tune from a million miles away.
So that's the kind of stuff that is very valuable and that we can do a lot with on podcasting.
And then, of course, there's the pod safe music, which is this enormous amount of music that is being put up online for people to enjoy.
It's being used to promote people's, you know, an artist's gigs where you can see them.
Some of them want to go up to larger distribution and would like to be in record stores and perhaps they actually want a real record deal.
I don't know if, you know, I don't know if I'd want one personally.
I think there are a lot of people who are not interested and would like to see if this can be done on the smaller scale where you may sell less.
Right, but you can be keeping a lot more of what it's actually being sold.
So I'm very excited about some of the conversations that have been going on.
And maybe as I said, maybe it's a good place to start that we come up with a pod safe creative commons license that can be easy for musicians to understand.
To bake right into their MP3, I know there's tools available for that.
Maybe that's something should, you know, be a part of the creative commons site.
I don't know, but let's think about that because there's a lot going on.
He had him, this is Susie Chase and my pod cast is the groove.
And our of the best of today's R&B and classic soul.
So there you have it, Adam, my podcast promo for the groove.
You can check me out at Susie Chase Osborn.blogspot.com.
As Susie, why see H-A-S-E-O-S-B-O-R-A.blogspot.com?
I know it's on.
You have a great day, Adam.
Thanks a lot.
All right, holy macro, that's a very long URL.
Okay, I'll put that in the show notes as along with all the other URLs for the promos that I play on the show.
Again, if you want to send me a promo, send it to DailySort.
We add to adamaccurry.com, put in the subject line D-S-C space promo.
That way my filter will be able to catch it, so I have a nice bin of promos that I can just go into and choose a couple for each show.
And then also put the name of your promo in the podcast.
As I said, I was looking at iPod.org today.
The scripts are back running and stuff is updating again, and there's still quite a backlog of, I think, several hundreds of podcasts,
but I just can't post all at once, you know, because we'd have a tremendously large page on the homepage.
So I try to, you know, get as many on there as possible and try to keep the flow moving every single day.
And at the top of the list, this morning when I looked was mashuptown.com, a weekly mashup podcast.
So I immediately went over to the page and oh yeah, found something my like, this is booty station on the DailySort's code for Friday April 22.
And then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over
to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and
and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over
to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and then I went over to the page, and I went over to the page, and then
It's been a long time, you and I
Oh yeah, stick it in your ear baby.
Shooting station.
Of course, Stevie Wonder's superstition mixed and matched up with pretty dishes.
That is art.
I love it.
Can't get enough of the mash.
You're a pure, pure, pure, cool laser sounds.
Pure.
You're a fantastic daily source girl.
That's all that I'm cool.
Hey Adam.
This is my D from my daily commute.
Possibly the only podcast brought to you from a moving car.
I'm on over and listen to me mues and wax rhapsodic while treging off to the daily grind.
Subscribe now at feeds.feetburner.com slash my daily commute.
Yeah, okay.
I don't know if it's the only podcast from a moving vehicle.
We've done quite a lot of that.
Remember Raymond Port who pulled up next to me and was listening to a source code.
Well, I was recording a new one.
Yeah, it's been happening.
But it doesn't matter because I love listening to people in vehicles of all kinds.
It's just something about it.
And I had a great visitor here yesterday from the BBC radio forum.
A radio legend literally.
Peter Day, who works for Radio 4 and also BBC World Service.
He does the shows.
He presents in business and global business.
And it was great.
The setup.
But this has been set up a long time ago.
And I thought that, you know, I don't know who was coming over.
I had no idea who this.
Well, I knew that he was well known Peter Day from his from his work.
But I had never heard him because I'm not quite sure when his show airs on radio 4,
when he's on the on the world service.
And this, it was, oh, man.
I mean, this typical English, you know, distinguished little bit older,
but sheveled gentleman shows up and with a big booming radio voice.
And he was just, you know, it was actually very nice to hear a,
you know, just one of those old fashioned, beautiful warm, you know,
wrap you in a blanket type voices.
And it was funny because he came all by himself,
came in from London to the train to the cab, came to the house.
And he had his, he had a little mini disc recorder to record our interview on because it was a radio interview.
But he still had the old fashioned gray, you know,
two big, two ugly BBC approved microphone.
That was attached to it.
So, and he was really looking at my high river and, you know,
with just a, a glint of jealousy in his eye saying,
oh, wow, I wish we could use these, these types of machines.
This is what the BBC should be doing.
And it was great.
He went, you know, way beyond the, you know,
what is podcasting?
How did it come to be?
He was really into the, okay,
what does this mean to me and my 35 year career in broadcasting?
And it was just a wonderful conversation.
And this guy has interviewed presidents and prime ministers and popes and,
and you name it.
And he had some great stories.
And I was just coaxing him the whole time saying,
man, we need you.
We need you to come into our community and help us out.
Teach us.
You know, it's not just about what kind of mic you use and how well it records.
But that is of course something that's important as well.
But what decisions do you make?
How do you get a conversation going?
How do you pull the information out of the subject that you're interviewing with?
How do you make it a conversation?
And then when you edit it down,
what do you put in there and why do you make those choices?
And also I said, wouldn't it be interesting if you could take all of that material?
Because we sat here for at least an hour and a half yesterday.
Just nonstop talking, Patricia actually was laughing out loud because you said,
you guys, you're sitting up there because he was upstairs in the office with me.
So I can hear every single word downstairs because you're all talking with those big radio voices.
So real sweetheart this guy was, and smart.
Oh my god, I had to work overtime just to keep up with him.
But he had all the right questions.
And of course he promised that he'd let me know when it'll air.
I'll shoot him another email just to remind him to do that.
Because I'd love to put a piece of that on the podcast.
Because he really did understand when we talk about the monoculture and basically dismantling that
and making it possible for anybody to broadcast.
He was really onto the big ideas of that.
And it was just so refreshing to have someone talk about that and really want to know what the implications can be.
And he did say something interesting though.
He said, you are one of the gap closers.
And I thought that was a beautiful description because I did only close 5% of the gap for this all to happen.
And that's something that keeps coming up in conversation.
And so when we talked about the music business and how can we change that and how will it change?
And what will happen to traditional radio.
And of course that's not just what radio is.
In fact, we did stumble upon some interesting things when you say radio.
But really that used to mean radio receiver would used to be after that came transistor radio receiver.
You have a radio transmitter, but radio has now become a description for what you hear on the radio.
But of course, that's not really all the radio is radio used to be the green hornet and the lone ranger.
And now these wonderful plays and shows that were acted out.
And the BBC still does just fabulous soundscapes and interviews on location with people.
So you can hear and you're really there on the spot.
And it's not just soundbite and boom, we're back to the studio.
So that's all the stuff that we're going to relearn.
And I hate reinventing the wheel, but we are going to do a lot of that as we all kind of get our chops together and figure out what we can do with this.
And I'm just I'd love to get a guy like that into our community and podcasting.
So I'm trying, I'm doing the best I can.
Hello, my name is Scott and I'm Kelly and we're the creators of MyVirtualBand.com.
I'm MyVirtualBand.com.
Members from all over the world collaborate online, try to record songs.
For instance, members can take a tune like this.
And turn it into this.
You can hear more great songs created on MyVirtualBand.com and our podcasts available at www.radio.myvirtualband.com.
And if you're a singer, songwriter or musician and would like to join in the fun, simply go to www.myvirtualband.com.
Register and you can start collaborating today.
Until next time, I'm Kelly and I'm Scott, rock on.
That's kind of cool.
So I guess with myvirtualband.com, you can pick up tracks and add to them, which is a very cool idea.
I wonder if you have to do that on a standard setup or if that's all MIDI or how it works,
but it sounds like there's a great place to go collaborate with other musicians I presume.
I'm still, of course, beta testing, the cast blaster application, which is this beautiful
little console that I record my podcast with.
At least when I'm back in the green thing studio at the cottage.
And on that promo, I was really weird.
My level, my meters just were all over the board there.
I'm not quite sure it was going on.
Also, I've gotten some feedback that, although the microphone sounds good now, that sometimes
the songs either sound out of phase or still a little too boomy.
And I really, the only thing I can come up with, because this is pretty much,
there's no cables, there's no routing that can really go wrong and put it out of phase I presume.
I think that the sound card that's built into this tablet is probably just a piece of shit.
And that's probably what's causing any trouble.
If you're hearing any, that's probably what's causing it.
You know, what is it like, a 16-bit sound card, which probably, you know,
I don't know how that works, but it's probably doing 12 bits or something like that.
Hey, that's what you get when you buy in a Veritech laptop, ladies and gentlemen.
I love the show's and YouTube are a riot, and Alex from Switzerland says,
Charlie and Carol made Israel a place of life and laughter.
Matt tells us, I just want to do right, and let you know that I'm addicted to Israelisms.
Israelisms.com is the version only irreverent weekly podcast,
that's the most puking promo I've heard in a long time.
That reminds me of top 40 radio is right back in your face puking,
but okay, we get it, and it actually is a pretty interesting podcast.
Israelisms.com. It does make Israel a shining place, and it's nice,
you know, it's the same thing as when I went to Iraq,
and I've said this before, you know, you have this vision of what the place is like,
which is totally been created by MSM, mainstream media has given us,
and we know why, because like hey, you know, wait a minute,
let me just stand in front of the shell out building and then take the picture,
or, you know, let's do the stand up over here with all the children who are playing in the mud and the,
and the drag, you know, that'll really tug on the hard strings of America
or television, a global television audience.
And then when you suddenly are there, and you notice that life has continued to go on,
and people are, you know, getting married, and having children, and creating work, and jobs,
and building houses, and of course, that's not everywhere in Iraq.
But, you know, the same goes for Israel, you know, when you think of Israel, you think immediately
of terrorists to a side bombers, you know, that's pretty much what is conjured to mind immediately.
And if you hear that, Israelisms.com podcast, it will give you a different perspective, I think.
Yeah, no, I know for sure, which is just another beautiful thing about what we're doing.
And here's a problem I want you to listen to, because I was kind of amazed that this kind of show is cropping up
as a podcast. Well, I'll talk about it in a second, listen to the promo first.
If you haven't yet listened to Rainbow Gossips, you won't know which singing star and the
snazzy found online looking for love from the internet.
You also won't know which news anchor posted this confession of an affair in an online forum.
You also may not know what old spies Jerry Hallewell keeps in her bedside cabinet.
There's no point in knowing a really good bit of gossip about the rich and famous, unless you pass it on.
Traditionally, focus shared such tidbits of the garden fence or at the water cooler.
Now, Rainbow Gossips gives you the chance to share your gossip with the world.
It really is very simple. You write to us a lot of gossip and we put you in the podcast.
What could be fluffier?
So, but you've seen a slab out shopping or plumbing, or you've witnessed a stellar
hisific, we want to know, and so does the world.
Pull us up or drop us a line.
And if you haven't been listening, subscribe to the Rainbow Gossips podcast
at www. RainbowGossips.com.
RainbowGossips, it's the global water cooler.
Fun.
Okay.
So, I think there's enough of that.
You know, I think there's enough celebrity television programs,
magazines filled with pictures of celebrities and gossip.
Is that really something that we need more of?
And I'll tell you specifically for my own experience.
This morning, as an example, at 815, the phone rings.
It's one of our neighbors.
And she says, there's a man standing across the road with a telephoto lens
and he's taking pictures of your house.
And, you know, of course, it's some gossip magazine
from, well, more than likely, from the Netherlands.
And it's like, you know, we have enough of that.
That's what those guys do.
You know, like, with podcasting, you can really, you know, get much more.
You can go much further than that.
Let's get Jerry Hal, howly well to do a podcast.
I'll be a lot more fun than just saying, oh, you know, here's what she was eating.
Here's what she was wearing.
And, you know, and the derogatory old spice.
You know, it's like that's so mean.
And, you know, there are people too, okay?
Really, it's mean when you say that stuff.
And if you don't know someone, you know,
it's like if someone said that about your friend or your family or your mom
or your wife, you know, you'd be pissed off if people were slagging him.
And then you'd probably do something about it.
So I'm not a big fan of trying to pull that kind of mainstream media ideas.
You know, there's so much more interesting things that we can
and we should be should be doing.
That said, Paris Hilton will be starting her podcast.
Hold on, I think it's, let me see, April 29th.
I'm not quite sure if this is a one-off deal
to promote the House of Wax movie or she'll continue doing it.
Of course, I hope she'll continue doing it.
And that will be one of the questions I'm going to ask her
because it's not 100% set in stone yet,
but we've actually narrowed down a day
and I'm working on the actual hours when it could happen.
But it looks like I can set up a Skype call with that Paris
and interviewer because the, well, here's how it works, right?
So the movie promotion is starting to crank up.
She'll do a big press junket probably in LA
and I don't know if she's going to other countries or whatever,
you know, if this is an international release.
But, you know, essentially they take time out for radio stations
and they've also honored my request
and it looks like we're going to get any to you with Paris Hilton.
And funny enough, what they were talking about
and they is Warner movies was that I would be able to interview Paris
for the Daily Source Code and I would be interviewing her
which would also be a part of her podcast.
And I don't know if that was their idea of hers, but I love it.
You know, so that could be fantastic.
What I'd like to know is what should we talk to her about?
You know, besides the obvious, if you have any questions,
send them off to AtomitCurry.com.
You know what, why don't we do the same thing
so I can filter out all of these emails, put in Paris question
and then as the subject line
and then perhaps even the topic of the question after that.
So I can filter it all out and I won't lose track of it.
And over the next couple of days,
we'll also discuss some of these questions and we can start.
Yeah, we'll do it like as much of a community as possible
if we can speak of a community here at the Daily Source Code.
Which I think we can?
I, yes.
Hello.
And Daily Source Code listener.
Yes, that's all you guys.
This is Ted.
He's a TEDbot.fund.ms.
You can go over to our show
and check it out for jokes, fun, and songs.
There's even unexpected stuff like this.
So come on over to TEDbot.fund.ms.
But you never know what's going to happen at all.
TEDbot.fund.ms.
Thank you.
This is Ted.
Okay.
Wonderful.
Keep in common.
Can't get enough of them.
By the way, it won't air today,
or we won't put it out today.
But Ron and I are going to do our strategy cast.
So I'll either all at least over the weekend
or we'll release it from Monday.
Maybe Monday show because Monday is a much better day for a lot of flow.
Let's see.
We're 30 minutes into it.
That means time for the casting.
Thank you.
It's time for the hit.
With your pull-ups.
Hey, Adam.
This is hit test number 34.
And as you'll probably hear,
it's a bit strange sounding.
That's because I'm testing my new setup.
I've got new hardware, new software,
and a new microphone.
And it's a bit cheap sounding at the moment.
I can't really think about that.
Unfortunately, it's a Blentronics headset.
I'm using it.
It's connected to a new notebook.
I've got a few days ago.
And it's the dot audio 90 headset.
That isn't cheap.
In fact, it's the most expensive non-USB version of the headset
available from my Blentronics.
But it sounds really cheap, and that's because it's probably
because it's made for Skype.
Oh, Scott.
And therefore, the mic has a limited frequency range.
And that is a bit of a shame because it sounds really shitty.
Okay, young.
First of all, I love it when you send me another hit test.
We're already up to number 34.
I can't tell you how much I appreciated.
And it doesn't matter.
It doesn't sound shitty, by the way.
At least your shitty microphone doesn't sound too shitty.
I'm my shitty earphone.
It's more like a telephone than a microphone.
No, no, no, no.
But I'm using a notebook to record this hit test.
It's the setup I will be using in the coming months.
That's because I won't be able to take all the external gear I'm using here with me.
So it's a bit of getting used to the new hardware,
also to the new software because I'm using better number eight of cast blaster.
I've been goofing around with the earlier versions.
And some changes have already been made by mic.
And I must say that mic has done a really great job.
Hey, hold on a second.
I have beta number five.
How did you get beta number eight?
That's what the job delivering this piece of software.
That is great.
It's tool to create a podcast.
And yeah, it is really great software.
Some new changes have been made since better number five that you've been using.
Well, kind of.
And again, that's what I get when I go on the road.
You know, I don't get all the latest beta.
You're using number eight also right now.
At least if you had the time to sort through all your mail.
Yes, yes.
I'm waiting for you when you've got back.
Okay, it has some really great additions.
I'm able now to start all the jingles or sound effects or clips with the function keys.
So I have one to f10 can be used to start and stop all the top 10 files that are preloaded.
And there's also a clear function, which clears all the files that you'll enter into the slots.
Yeah, cool.
That's.
Well, except for the mic, everything is up to standards.
And of course there's a hit test.
So if you're ready, we're going to start right away.
I'm ready, buddy.
It's number one.
Pick it.
Woo!
Papa.
That would be the best of my love.
Yeah.
LTD loves tenderness and devotions.
Great song.
Can't wait to hear the answer.
And this is number two.
Lower branding and self control.
Oh, you made it easy for me today, y'all.
Yeah, it's definitely more branding.
I miss her.
She passed away recently.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I should wait, I guess, for my time signal.
There we go.
This is the final one.
Number three.
Papa.
In my house, uh, vanity six or apelonia six, one or the two.
In my, or Mary Jangers.
Mary Jangers.
These are the answers.
This is answer.
Number one.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe.
It's a golden oldie.
Woo!
The emotions.
Oh, this is a bonus.
Okay.
I got half a point.
The emotions and the best of our love.
It's a number one in today's hit test.
And this is number two.
It's Laura Brannigan.
The emotions and the best of our love.
It's a number one in today's hit test.
And this is number two.
It's Laura Brannigan.
And the song is titled self-control.
I love this one.
And how this became a hit to still, uh, unknown for me.
Because it's a really shitty song.
No, it's great.
It still became a hit.
Laura Brannigan and self-control.
Answer number two in today's hit.
You're too young.
You're a member of this.
Answer number three.
The Mary Jangers.
In my house.
This is in my house.
And in good today.
Take a girl.
You can just leave my goal in my life.
Tomorrow.
Answer number three in today's hit.
Produced by Rick James, the Mary Jane Girls and in my house, and that's it for a hit this number
34 good one, entirely recorded using the cast-blast new software at 8th version of cast-blaster
and I just thought of a new addition to this software so I will go email that to my right away
and hopefully there will be a public release very soon because I heard that many people are very
interested in using this software and you should be because it is really great
okay well Adam this is the end of hit this number 34 I hope you enjoyed this one
and of course if anyone knows I had said with a better sounding mic please let me know
if that's at gmail.com and the web address is ympolet.nl that's j and b-o-l-e-t.nl
but Adam by the way you are right this is number 34 and I have still never met you
still never spoken to you in person so maybe you can change that in a very short time
because I will be gone in less than three weeks
well as I said this is the setup I will be using in the coming months
so I can't change a lot about it but please let me know what you think thank you for listening
and see you next time bye bye all right yon thank you very much my friend once again wonderful
and okay if I can make it over in three weeks I really have no more business in the Netherlands at
all there's nothing left for me to do there except visit family and I try to bring them over here
I certainly will try to hook up with you and if not you know it'll it'll it'll it'll it'll
happen for sure and I wish you of course all the best I know that you got some crap stuff ahead of
you and I really appreciate the fact that you just keep cranking out the hit test and I and I love
the feedback on the cast blast and I'm really honked off of myself that I haven't found beta 8
in my email yet so I'm gonna go do that when we close down the Friday edition of the show
thanks always for subscribing you could find the podcast feed at
data source code dot com that's we can subscribe to it and your iPod or your aggregator
and supports podcasting of course you can always find a way to show there in the archives
to listen directly just by clicking online
comments adamant curry dot com will leave a comment on my weblog www.curry dot com if you
have a promo send it off to adamantcurry dot com and put it in the subject like dsc space promo
and then put whatever the promo is about you got your Paris Hilton questions send it off to me
as well Paris question to add it to curry dot com and I'll report back on what we're gonna ask her
I have some thoughts by certainly not everything I can come up with
they have a great weekend talk to you soon bye bye