Daily source code episode 187
Something remarkable is happening here.
Radio is springing free of the regulated gatekeepers who've managed
or you can hear since radio is invented.
It's jumping into the hands of anyone at all with something
or nothing to say.
It's $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Than the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
Hey everybody, coming to you from Curry Cottage in Gilford, UK at the source code.
And today is June 3rd, 2005.
My name's Adam Curry and it's Friday.
Oh yes, and it couldn't be more beautiful today.
Everything I missed coming back yesterday or the day before with all the crappy weather.
It's back, we got sunshine and 75 degrees.
I always put me in the mood for a show.
I got a lot of stuff for you today and we may be interrupted because,
well, basically all the logistics at the cottage are messed up.
Let's see, this morning we had the plumber come by because our hot water was all filed up,
which means that I waited for hours before being able to take a shower and then I had a cold shower.
I was always there.
Somewhere to be now in the next 20 minutes, the blinds guys should show up.
Blinds, not blinds, they're going to hang up blinds to darken the bedroom.
Something I've been begging for.
I just can't sleep when it's too light in the bedroom, so finally got those guys square
away and maybe even today, the carpeted guys will show up.
Wouldn't that just be part for the corset?
Oh man, we got promos, we got some pod save music for you.
Let's see, pod save music from the Netherlands actually, so that should be fun.
I've got a couple of notes here.
I do have the remote microphone standing by in case the guys show up and we'll just continue
to show, I don't want to stop in midstream.
Maybe you'll just follow along and we'll enjoy the blinds guys together.
And as I was looking for a cool mashup to play, we're kind of low on the mashups.
You know, please feel free to send some in at mashup at podshow.com.
I figured I'd pull an old one out of the closet one that actually came across, so just while
I'm muckin' around on the iPod, I guess I put it on shuffle and low on behold this one showed up.
If the Beatles vs. Shaggy, let it be me.
Oh, you figured I'd pull an old one, so you'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along
and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along
and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow
along and we'll just follow along along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follows along along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we'll just follow along and we're along along along and we'll just follow along and we're along along along along
wonderful email in that said, you know, you really should free up some space on your hard
disk for the PowerBook G4, which I did. I sent me a great little application called What
Size. You can find that on version tracker. And I use that and basically it scans your entire
drive, color codes, all the files on it and folders so you can see where all the big stuff
is and easily delete it. So I freed up about seven gigabytes. So now supposedly you're supposed
to have at least 10 gigabytes free on your Mac if you're using OS 10 for swap files and stuff
like that, which makes a lot of sense and I thought that would basically remove all the problems,
but I still hear some skipping. And so I blame that on on the C yesterday and I immediately got a
response in in the form of audio feedback. Hi Adam, it's Dave Brightbill from Radio MacGuys at
www.mackguys.com. And I'm sending you this audio feedback and response to the comments you made
on your last podcast about Lucy Hardrives. And let me start out by saying that as far as I know,
Lucy does not manufacture any hard drives. What they do is they have manufactured for them,
some empty cases and these cases have the FireWire to ATA interface and they have the
the power supply and they have some jacks for the power and some jacks for firewire or USB to
money and what kind of drive it is. And that's the part that Lucy supplies and probably what's failed
and years now if you're if your case failed that's one thing and I'd be happy to put the blame on
Lucy if that's the case, but probably the hard drive itself failed and that's not Lucy's fault.
That's the fault of the manufacturer of the hard drive and hard drives normally have their own
warranties on them. So if you've had a hard drive fail you need to find out who manufactured the hard
drive in that Lucy case and contact that manufacturer and you know so you hold on a second.
That sounds like horseshit to me. I mean if I buy a car and there's a German electronic system
and it buy Bosch and that fails I have to go find out who made that and go and go talk to them.
That makes no sense at all. And by the way it's not so much about the fact that the
drives are failing it's the way let's see handles it. Although say as well we'll just give you
new one. They don't even want to try to fix it. They don't even want to try to recover your data.
I mean I feel that if you're saying this is a great drive and to me the drive is the case.
You know it's the case and the plugs and the lights etc. And I don't know what the hell is on the
inside. We have to break it open and find out. I'm sorry I have to disagree with this opinion.
So you nasty things about them if you want to but I don't think you should say those things
that's certainly about Lucy. Now I'm not an employee of a sea. I'm not a stockholder. I don't know
a whole lot about them currently. I know I had one time I was a Peter reseller and an Apple reseller
and during those days I actually would sometimes sell the sea products but I've used them a lot
in my own practice and a lot of my clients have their products and you know all hard drives fail.
That's the thing. I understand that a whole hard drives fail but
not you know listen I was going to tell me that I have to back up. What's I back up on?
Another hard drive? Hard drives are complex mechanical mechanisms and they have a moving
motors moving at high speeds. They have bearings. They have lubrication. They have all sorts of
mechanics. Yeah don't dribble up lubrication too. You know. Cancle parts they can fail and so they're
going to fail. I mean it's just going to happen. There's no there's no two ways about it. And as a
wise computer user what you have to do is you have to figure out how to protect your data and
you do that by backing up. And I know you know about it. There it is. You got to back up.
All right. Now I know I have 10 of these 60 gigalcy hard drives and I think six of them have failed
within a two-year period. That can't be normal and I've heard other people have the same problems.
And by the way it's not always the drive. It's also the it's what you call it's the interface.
It's the plug somehow you know something there that can fry and they won't even replace that
you know they'll say well you we can give you another drive and then you can do it yourself.
It's just I'm sorry it's just it's not cutting it. Let's see has not done a good job by me.
So just call it an official customer complaint that's all. And as you were you know anything like that
but you've been so helpful to me and in learning about podcasts I wanted to get back to you
and give you some advice on how to how to keep your your life saying much appreciated hard drives go.
So much appreciated. Remember like I say in every podcast and every podcast of mine with this I always say
there's two kinds of computer users in this world those who have lost data and those who will.
So back up early and back up often. Thank you. You know we actually have a saying an aviation.
There's two types of pilots those that have made a wheels up landing and those that really
they that I'm going to have a great great day. Thank you David. I really appreciate the feedback that's
Adam Curry dot com for your audio feedback. Adam Curry's pod shell greetings welcome to this
that there goes again there's my lucid drive failing. I love a stick in your ear.
This is Darcy and Holly show coming to you live from two different countries.
WWW dot Darcy and Holly dot com.
Hi this is our promo for the Darcy and Holly show. I'm Darcy.
Emily. And yes we do a podcast. We do a podcast on the Darcy and Holly show as you've
gathered and kind of just talk about stuff. Basically yeah. Stream of consciousness that's the
name of our game. Right because as the intro said we're in two different countries doing the whole internet
long distance relationship thing and so since we're on the phone all the time anyway we decided to
just podcast podcast it like that whatever conversations more than one actually through the
night so yeah so so that's what we're about and we're doing something different starting in June
a little bit different. It's a same sort of idea but there's a kind of a theme
in a really head of theme. Yeah because I'm going to go dark school with a toilet blind
and I'm going to go dark school starting June fifth and so we thought you would podcast make
experience so because I wanted to journal of it anyway so I thought why not just do audio and podcast
it. Yeah and we figured out people might interested. A lot of people would be interested anyway
because even if you're not blind the way blindness is portrayed in the media isn't always all that
accurate so we thought this would be kind of cool. And that's about thought so if you like dogs then you might
like like yeah but we're also going to be doing other stuff too so it's not interested in that.
Yeah so if you hate dogs then you should it's really anyway. Yeah he's going to be keeping me up
today as what's going on in the podcast you're going to be totally cut off. Yeah because they have
dealt with in the lecture so that's not so much what's dealt with in the podcast. Right. So I'm going to
be cut off so he's going to be keeping me up today so people get all of your kinds of things.
Yeah and if you want to listen to our website www.darsianholly.com which is www.tarcyand.coly.com
Yosuh. Okay so the blind casters do check in today. Gotta love that. Actually I was just
sitting here thinking for a second I wanted to know let me see NBA.com can I? I want to see how
the Miami Heat did yesterday. As the conference is heating up I haven't seen a skinny on sports yet
usually those guys always have a good take on on the games and a good handle on what's going on.
Let me see Heat handle piston so I guess that means good news hold on a second.
Okay so Miami beat Detroit but what did then what was the score? Oh man.
Oh here we go. Heat handle piston so let me say oh that's a video I'm not going to
see the video I don't subscribe to that. Okay well all right so they beat him but uh oh
could 88 to 76 right on go heat loving that and the reason why is because I happen to have a friend
who I see in tickets. So hopefully the final game will be played in Miami then maybe I can
actually go and check it out. Okay let's see um I don't want a couple of things that I've got an
excellent piece of match Weinstein for that I want to share with you we'll have that in just a second.
Also there was some comments left yesterday on um in the on the show notes at curie.com
by someone called the comic strip blogger and I guess that's the same guy who's mobile phone fan
but you know despite the fact that mobile phone fan is somewhat peculiar in his postings and
and the stuff that he says and that he post on his own weblog the comic strips he does are just
fantastic and uh there's an RSS feed for it so you really should subscribe to that comic strip blogger
uh I'll provide a link in the show notes but uh he's really um I mean this is you know mobile phone
fan comic strip blogger wherever you are you've missed your calling dude you know you shouldn't be
post your art is completely there now I understand what you should be doing do more of those that
is absolutely phenomenal um you know he picks up stuff from the blogger sphere the potters sphere and
and creates little three or four paying cartoons about them and that just fantastic so uh give that
one a check uh one else that I have probably well I was listening to a couple about oh the CC
Chapman had a great uh uh accident hash podcast the mellow hash should check that one how it is
truly mellow and there's some great songs coming out just phenomenal this pot-safe music stuff
the the quality and did I tell you that um if I did tell you when when when I met with Steve Jobs
he was when you were talking about about pot-safe music I guess the iTunes music store now
hosts and sells 11,000 different tracks that are independent music um and you know we're talking
about you know what what is really the difference now between the pros and the non-prose you know
I don't know when we call an amateurs um and we both agree that there really isn't that much
difference particularly because Mick Jagger had uh had called him as of course Mick does he usually
call Steve as on on the weekends and uh and said you know that he was using garage band
apples multi-track recording application for recording some tracks for the next you know
whatever the stones are doing and I think you man you know all that we need now is just you know
the way to identify and and promote talent and get them out and let people know about it and that
is exactly what I hope we can do with the the pot-safe music network to be released very very soon
just to let you know most retrieval is back
hey Adam just wanted to let you know that mostly trivial is back our friend Brian Pippa has moved on
to bigger and better things and has let me take over the show so now you can listen to mostly
trivial with your new host me Johnny B here's the taste mostly trivial
today's category is
which one of these is a hot spicy Indian dish is it a chicken curry b Adam curry
see Patricia pies or D madam curry usually I get the listeners about 10 seconds to think about
about but we don't have time for that if you answered C Patricia pies well she's a hot dish but not
Indian if you answer D madam curry well she's neither a dish nor Indian but she was hot
from all that radiation and if you answered B Adam curry well he's dishing out great podcast that's
for sure but all of you would be wrong and if you answered A what was A oh yeah if you answered A
you miss the whole bit but you are still correct
for a more general fun and a short podcast trivia game go to mostly trivial.com
this is your host Johnny B signing off see you later Adam how right or thank you very much
trivia yeah okay hold on let me just turn on the other microphone here let me see if I got that
working no oh here we go got to turn that on hello hello why is it so soft oh man that's not what
we agreed to hold on I guess I have to turn up this oh yes there we go okay so I turn the
transmitter on and the blind guy the blind guy is here so hold on one second we just check the
there we go I'm going to go walk in home one sick come with me I'm this little sound seeing tour of the cottage
alrighty you get one or two here okay do you need anything do you help for
huh okay and the curtains can stay up but you need to take those down okay beautiful
oh no mess today I'm sorry no mess day it's alright are you happy to hear that Barbara
oh yeah no no no no no no I'm finished with biscuits and then I'll just move
everything just from here okay do you want your room done today would you want to leave it till next week
you can leave it till next week I haven't been there long enough to make a mess yeah but by next week
it'll be a danger zone and a danger zone exactly okay well let me know if you need anything then
with this okay great I'm right next door in studio b okay dokey let me let me get back here okay
now we switch to the other microphone there we go all right so once again everything's taken care of
here alrighty Patricia should be back any minute she was out in the city so it's got to keep my eye
on this you know make sure everything's going okay um latest yeast radio um that came in
was yesterday's episode I guess for the second of June it was titled the worst of magic
and I don't know what magic was thinking because this to me is actually I have to say
some of it is the best of magic maybe maybe that's the whole that was the whole point of this but
I wanted to share one piece with you which just it's such a classic magic bit it's like two minutes
or something like that but it's so good and I really encourage you to check out the entire episode
because there's so many different bits in here that are so classic magic I love it check it out
this is magic uh doing a keynote speech you ladies thank you so much for allowing me the honor of
speaking before you tonight it is truly the greatest of pleasures for Mag Weinstein to be invited
as the keynote speaker for the world's very first convention of female carpet cleaners
now before I get started please join me in inviting the all might he goddess to share these moments
with us now take a deep breath that's right breathe now lift your arms over your head like this
and breathe out that's right push it out and relax and in and out
I think pretty thought so as to invite the greatest goddess into our room think of lavender and
color lily paintings picture yourself taking a bath with epsom salts surrounded by a favorite
very nice wide homemade candles and your cats oh my I think it's working I sense the
oceans warm fills my groin and my breasts yes now the goddess is here and she is ready to speak
through me hi I'm Mad Weinstein by now you've all probably seen those silly yellow silicon
lands Armstrong bracelets haven't you well if you haven't figured it all out then let me explain
it to you very clearly you see here in americant we don't get health insurance provided for us
we get DVD players desperate housewives and iPods instead as a result we americants
have conceived of a very novel approach to fighting disease we wear ugly jewelry and accessories
you heard me ugly jewelry when was the last time you saw a pink breast cancer ribbon that was
tasteful looking huh and the t-shirts don't even get me started on the t-shirts if I see one more
suburban mallet bearing closeted lesbow waddling around with her love handles bursting outside
of her ridiculously tight avon three day walk against breast cancer t-shirt I may have to go on
a side and then they have to wear those fucking family packs with the water bottles strapped to
their fat asses who the hell gave these bitches the idea that they need to slip three gallons
of water around with them during the one lunar eclipse they decide to go move their fat asses out
of their goddamn hog and dogs stained couches give me a break these women haven't
have enough water in their asses to drown a camel and don't even get me started on the lunar
bars oh and those ribbons ever since the days of Jimmy Carter and the Irene hostage business
we americants have been obsessed with those horrible flimsy broaches is there a color that has
not yet been used I don't think so but those yellow bracelets are really what put me over the edge
first I saw my spin teacher wearing one over at the cheetah gym and I couldn't figure out
why in other wise fashion conscious gay man would want to adorn himself with certain ugly
piece of garbage then I started seeing co-work as wearing them wait watches were wearing them
my herbalist my acupuncturist my yoga teacher and even my holistic goddess worship
cabala therapist was wearing one so I looked it up on the internet and found that those bracelets
are inscribed with the words live strong on them and they serve as a means to tell the world proudly
I stand against campsite
hi Adam my name is Braden and I'm aura and we're the home theater guys the host of the
HD TV podcast we talk about all the latest news and high definition television and home theater
we also do product and technology reviews informative how-to's and answer listener questions
but we need to ask for your listeners help you see we have a dream yes it's a dream that
one day all the original MTV content will be re-blocked and high definition you know all those original
MTV DJs some of the most attractive people to ever grace the small screen
forget aliens yes I or even Monday night football we need the top 20 countdown
and if we can just get enough people screaming I want my HD MTV we may have a chance
remember the days when music television actually played music and at the glory days
and boy were those VJ's talent or what for more information visit our website at www
htguys.com next for your support okay you know a lot of people say that to me oh man
MTV doesn't play music anymore but you know their business those guys they noticed I think the
first time they noticed that long-form programming which is you know like shows was with remote
control remember that with Ken Ober and Kari were and Colin that was a great show and that
pulled in tremendous ratings for MTV at least because MTV I think used to get on average from
music programming but like a 0.5 or yeah probably on average is 0.5 rating and they started to hit
double digits so the one well I guess full single digits 1.0 and 1.1 and 1.2's on shows like remote control
and like any business you know the more they could get the more they could get more viewers more money
basically higher rate cards so it morphed but you know let's not forget that MTV has been around
for over 25 years now 25 years and when I scan through the music channel through the channels on
my TV here or in the States it's plenty of music being played all over the place and
to my name Barbara I love a coffee yeah yeah oh the way wonderful a little bit of cream and sugar
just one one small yeah thank you very much Barbara I had an introduce you guys formally to Barbara yet she
drops by the cottage once or twice so we well when Patricia's gone she drops by almost every single
day to get up my shit he's really nice she's well it's the big clean Friday's big clean up day here
anyway what was I saying oh yeah okay so I've been looking through scouting around today you know
that after going through my my mail I still have only 4,000 on red messages came up with a
couple of interesting musical things happening in the Netherlands I'm going to play a pod save
music tune by Dutch band in a couple minutes but first a kind of a remix which came from Patrick
Kicken he's a I think he's a it was a DJ on radio Veronica and he also has a weblog and this
one's been bubbling through the Dutch pod a sphere it's called the MSN bubbling remix and if you
very used MSN messenger you'll get it immediately
ok
Thank you so much for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video, thanks for watching this video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I
will see you in the next video and I'll see you in the President's video and see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I will see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in CUBE Anyways, I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video and I'll see you in the next video Dingen
school, but it's happening all around you. Yesterday, today, tomorrow. Join me, Matt
DiTilo, as we explore that which came before. My podcast, Matt's Today in History, is a
five-minute romp through the river's mountains and fields of what brought us to where
we are today. You can find Matt's Today in History at www.opakelucidity.com.
OPA, QUE, LUC, IDITY.com. History with an attitude, the past with an opinion. It's
Matt's Today in History.
Uh-huh, I love that. That's a great podcast. I'll put a link to the podcast site and show notes.
Of course, in my own show notes at DaddySourceco.com and query.com. Oh, man. So this weekend, I guess
we're going to try, as I told you yesterday, we're going to try and catch a show at London's
West End. Um, you know, if you have a way to get tickets for a good, I think we want to go to
like Chitty Chitty Bang Bang or something like that. If you have a way to get tickets easily,
if I can order them online, I haven't really done a lot of research, but I figured there's
enough people in the UK listening who could probably help me out, that would be much appreciated.
Uh, let's see, PodSafe Music. This is, I told you's going to play a, uh, a Dutch band.
The name is Silence is Sexy. And, uh, we actually played this on the Pod show on series.
It's got a lot of cool response to it. They've played at the infamous parody, so an Amsterdam
and nighttime in Rotterdam. No, the place is very well. Here's reptiles on the source code.
How much does it take to think the world out of this?
Seller, we left with all the extra pets.
You're leaving me so much there.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
We are in class. The sun weighs away. We space to let it shine. The sun's bright.
And don't you try to have your,
let me have it in another run.
Some stay alive and feel like proud of you.
Are those wouldn't make a ribbon in the sky yet?
Do they leave a song this day overloaded up by their marches, be eyeletless and us
SILENCE is sexy reptiles on the source code from the Netherlands you heard it here first
at Barbara just brought in the coffee guess what it wasn't a sense sale it was an instant
coffee oh that's cool oh by the way I've gotten so many different reactions to the
sense sale mentions in the show I'm not sponsored or paid by sense sale at all I'm
just a fan of the coffee sure I've got a link to buy a sense sale machine but you
know that's just that well that is for money
I'm the proud salesman of hundreds of sense sale coffee machines all right so I
guess what we'll do then is we actually do get to the West End this weekend we'll
do a part we'll do a review of whatever show we see we'll do a family podcast
review as I struggle to get back from West End in in the A8 with the steering wheel
on the wrong side of the car driving on the wrong side of the road alright
everybody thank you very much for tuning in stay subscribe to feedback of course
add them to curry dot com for your audio comments or on the weblog curry dot
com as always the latest podcast can be found at dailysourcecode.com that's
where you can find archives the shows as well as the podcast feed you know what I'm
missing somewhere between the 15 disparate servers that I have I don't have the
first source code which was actually named daily source code if you happen to
have that somewhere in your archives I love to receive a copy I've a feeling I
stored it on one of those will see hard drives the bus that's probably where
it went all right stay subscribe to everybody take care have a great weekend