POT show, you press play, we do the rest.
With the share of Charlie, two nine or seven.
It's a science formula, not too far from me.
I don't know how many years I've done right there.
One out of all could have seen me.
Made I couldn't cause, like vampire bats different,
I'd have brought you to your city that way.
And you've got a funny way.
I'm showing off you, bathroom surgeon.
You said you were just cooling down from the bathroom.
There's something I should tell you for me.
Me and I have much time in my life.
I've never had a life yours.
Stars at night are big and bright to thin your eyes, music.
Don't know what's on me as my old grown-up, damn well I did it.
I'm not much of a gesture, but I just poison food for you.
You might just see all your food.
I'm royalty my king of fame.
There's a lot of info in this world.
You're at it, it's cool.
The Alcaline trio
Queen of Pain from the podcast, music, knitwear, musicgrotpodshow.com.
Michael Buttler today is Potshoe HQ, and he says, do gaboricorzers know
And so I went looking for it, lo and behold,
Alkaline trio, it's from 2002 and I'm pretty sure
Christina will even totally love this song.
She's probably familiar with them.
Again, J.J. Records, lots of independent record labels
are now coming online, coming onto the Pod Safe Music Network,
offering up a selection of artists that they have signed
to the label.
This is so cool.
This is just beautiful.
I've had a great day.
You have no idea, well, I'm going to tell you
how great my day was.
I started off very early.
We started right now with this morning at 8 o'clock.
And oh, man, I got some cool stuff for you.
Even though I got to say my stomach's a little bit upset,
I know if that was, it's probably from the flight,
or I don't know.
What did I have for, after I think what I had,
I had a croc mushy, a cock, mushy, cock,
cock, cock, cock, cock, cock mushy.
They was the bean soup.
I could have been it.
But my stomach's a little bit upset.
But otherwise, at a great day, we just have all kinds
of fantastic meetings.
We're getting so close to really start to unleash
some things.
It's almost not funny.
And I had another long chat with the Chris Rockwell,
better known as Mr. Poop Caster, who is leading
development in the podcast, music network.
And yeah, I really do think that we're going to have
our purchasing.
He says by Christmas, so I'll give him until the new years
before I start bitching and moaning.
But that means that you'll be able to, as a podcaster,
of course, to still be able to play songs in the podcast,
music network, you put your link in your show notes,
you report back into the network.
And your listeners will then be able to follow the link
from your show notes, go straight to the artist's page,
and then actually purchase the track on a track by
track basis.
And the purchasing, I'm not going to tell you anything
right now, but I'm really excited if we can get together
what we discussed today.
That's going to be awesome.
And what's that?
40 tracks went up today.
It's just unbelievable.
If you want to know more, go do music.podshow.com.
And if you need help or have any questions,
give Michael Butler a ping.
He is the original Rock and Old Geek from Rock and Old Geek
podcast at Rock and Old Geek.com.
So have had a major Gmail problem
for the past shoot.
I'm going to say more than 30 minutes.
I keep getting server error.
Gmail is temporarily unavailable.
And here comes, cross your fingers and try
getting a few minutes.
We're sorry for the inconvenience.
That's a typical, that's Google culture for you right there.
No, I'm refreshing.
I'm going to Gmail again.
And I still get the error, which is a real bummer
because I've become so dependent upon Gmail.
Not just for the regular email stuff,
but I have a whole system set up with rules and filters.
And if I forward something from the Blackberry
with a certain code in it, I can tell you
because it only works from my Blackberry's address.
I put in DSC in the subject and then I just
forward it and it gets put into a special folder.
Actually, a label is what they call it.
And then I just want to prepping the show.
I just go through the entire list and I got all my stuff.
So I've been diligently forwarding things into my Gmail.
And there you go.
Gmail has screwed up my podcast today and try one more time.
See if we can get anything going here.
Hold on.
Let me see.
I can go to Google itself.
Let's see if all of Google is down.
Oh, man.
Hey, if you're listening to this podcast on serious satellite radio
stars, 103, welcome everybody.
This is a podcast.
And you're going to hear probably most of it.
If we go over the a lot of satellite window past our time,
of course, that means that Pacific Coast Hellway will be coming in.
You'd have to download the podcast to listen to the rest.
OK, so Google works.
Now let me try Gmail again.
Loading.
It's contacting.
It's waiting.
It still says loading.
God, this sucks.
Man.
Oh, this pisses me off.
OK, well, waiting for that to load.
I want to tell you that there's a new podcast for one-one podcast
that's a Rob from podcast for one-one.
He's kind of the, it's really like the, he talks to people
the people behind the podcast.
Shit.
No, it's still broken.
Goddamn.
Temporarily unavailable.
I am crossing my fingers.
I'm standing on one foot.
I'm praising Murphy.
All that good stuff.
So you can find podcast for one-one podcast for one-one.com.
And as promised, Rob interviewed Madge Weinstein on the podcast.
And you definitely want to check that out.
Particularly because Madge is celebrating her one-year anniversary.
I think the one-year anniversary show was yesterday, or was it, yeah, it was yesterday.
And it's cool to listen to this pioneer of podcasting and get to know a little bit
more about everybody's favorite, bloated Jewish, extremely angry lesbian.
And I'll tell you what.
Let me get it.
I can't, I can't stand it anymore.
OK, I have something to show you guys.
As you know, those of you who are unfamiliar with this podcast or just start just tuning
into podcast now, we have something we call sound seeing, a sound seeing tour.
So let me just say that again, because people often don't hear it right.
Sound seeing tour.
So what we're going to do is we're going to take a little trip.
I got my mobile microphone.
I have a wireless microphone set up.
And I connect that to my I-River, I-F-P-799, and with that I can record virtually anything
anywhere I go.
I'm really happy with the sound quality of this thing.
And so if you have an opportunity, you might even want to close your eyes because all
of the ambient sound is really going to add to the experience.
I want to take you on a little sound seeing tour because I have something to show you
that I'm very, very excited about.
Something to be talking about for many, many months here on the daily source code.
Have you figured it out yet?
OK, hold on.
Let me just switch mics.
OK, let me turn this on.
Hold on a second.
Let me see if I get this.
Here we go.
Oh, I am so excited when I'm going to demonstrate to you.
OK, hold on a second.
Right, I got my code on.
We're going to, the sound seeing tour is a very specific one.
It's something that I've been wanting to share with you for a long, long time.
Just get my keys here for a second.
We're going to go on a little trip.
We've never actually done any sound seeing in the condo.
How are we?
Yeah.
OK, let me just make sure I got everything here.
I want to take my digital camera.
We're going to need that.
Let me just make sure what is this set to.
Portrait.
Now we don't want portrait.
We want scenery now.
The hell though I want here.
All these different things on my camera.
Night scene, night scene.
Why don't we do night scene?
No, that won't work.
Are you curious to know what we're going to take a look at now, aren't you?
OK, let me set this to, I'll just set it to Portrait.
That should work.
Right, turn that off for now.
OK, let me see.
Just double check, double check of the keys.
You know, living by myself here in the condo.
Pretty damn important.
So make sure that you got your keys with you.
All right, let's go.
Hold on.
Ah, some trash.
I'm going to take care of that first.
There we go.
Right.
Now hopefully, won't meet anyone on the way down.
Because of course, I'll feel like a total idiot talking to myself as usual.
Let's just go to the trash shoe here.
Hello.
Coming down at you.
24 floors.
OK.
Let's, uh, I'm never actually taking the elevator to where we're going today.
Oh boy, that was fast.
OK.
Now, let's go.
Great.
No one in the elevator.
Perfect.
Let's go down to that one.
So we're going down to P4.
The, uh, the elevator I'm in is actually set for, uh,
for, uh, for a move.
Somebody's moved day.
It's got the, you can hear the dull sound.
Oops.
Someone says coming in.
Hold on.
Let's stop here at 60.
Good evening.
Good night.
OK.
Sorry about the radio silence there for a second,
but I didn't, I forgot.
I didn't have my cell phone with me.
So I couldn't pretend that I was talking, uh,
I was going to actually reach my pocket.
I was going to pull it out and start talking.
But, uh, realize I didn't take my phone with me
because it really interferes with the, the I River,
which I'm using to record.
OK.
We are here at P4.
Let me start telling you about, uh, the story.
P4, of course, is for parking.
So yesterday, I told you about,
ah, excuse me, since say I only wish.
I told you about this, uh, car that I saw.
Parked right near our brand new office.
And, uh, that I put a note underneath the, uh,
windshield wipers saying,
will you sell me this car?
And today I got a call, uh, this morning from Isabelle.
And she said, uh, Adam, I said, yeah,
she said, well, you left this note on my car.
I just want you to know that I've actually had it up on Craigslist
for a couple of weeks.
Um, and, uh, yeah, it's for sale.
And ladies and gentlemen,
I present you with Trinity.
That's me kicking the rear bumper.
This is without a doubt.
Exactly. This, this car was meant for me.
It was, it was built for me to purchase.
Um, it is a, what color is this?
I'd have to say it's kind of like, um,
like a really old banana yellow color.
And, um, someone else in the garage.
It's a Mercedes turbo diesel 300.
Actually, it's a 300 TD.
I'm just getting the key here.
And it has a bio diesel sticker on the back.
I'm going to go to the front here.
It is without a doubt.
Let me just get in the car.
The ugliest.
The ugliest car I've ever seen in my entire life.
Uh, so I'm in, I'm sitting in the driver seat right now.
There's, um, it's a little, uh, crack here on the windshield
down, uh, almost in the middle.
Another star here on the left of the windshield
where, uh, stones have clearly hit it.
So, uh, I get the call from, uh, is a bell.
And, uh, she, uh, lives in the neighborhood,
or she's staying in the neighborhood.
It doesn't really live anywhere right now.
She said, and as she had purchased this car,
which, by the way, has a name.
The car's name is Trinity.
And it's a she, uh, and that's been explained to me,
um, is a bell who, who sold me the car,
is a yoga teacher.
And, uh, definitely, um,
uh, she was just like a young, cute hippie chick.
But she purchased a Trinity with a girlfriend of hers
who then, uh, bowed out of the deal
and so she really couldn't afford to keep it herself.
She bought it for, I think she paid $6,000 for it.
She was asking for $7,000.
Of course, I said, uh, yeah, I'll pay you five.
Uh, and we wound up kind of, uh, in the middle there.
And, uh, and it is already completely outfitted
with a biodiesel engine,
or with the biodiesel conversion on the engine.
Now, it's a turbo diesel.
And this thing, uh, currently,
as of today, rides on 99.9% vegetable oil.
It is a, I mean, this is not a blended thing.
Um, she usually fills it up in Berkeley
at the Berkeley biodiesel gas station,
which, of course, will be a sound seeing tour
for this week.
You know, we're going to go over there and fill up.
Um, and it, and it runs like a charm.
It's, it's just the most unbelievable experience.
I've already, of course, driven it around town
with a little bit from office to office.
It's, uh, manual.
It has a wonderful, um, uh, radio and CD player in it.
And that's about all the luxury you're going to get.
I still haven't exactly figured out how to get the seat to go down.
I don't know if it, the seat can go down.
I got to go back and I've got it.
Everything tilted.
Uh, let me just see where the, uh,
I'm going to open up the, I want to open up the,
the bonnet.
That's what we all saw.
Let me just check here.
This, uh, hmm.
Where is that thing?
It's got to be around here somewhere.
Hmm.
Well, B, maybe it's in the glove box.
Oh, shoot.
Now I got to see if I can, well,
maybe, uh, there's no inside class.
Here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to start rough.
Just so you can listen to the engine.
Now you have to let the coils pre-heat first.
Uh, otherwise you can burn those out.
Okay.
It's done.
So let's crank her up.
Listen to that puppy per hour.
Come on.
Let's go look at the engine.
Wait.
I'll take my camera.
It's going to take some pictures of.
Alright.
I think there's, uh,
somewhere there's a thing here to open up the,
good.
There we go.
Pull that out.
Isn't that it?
It should be it.
Damn.
It opened perfectly this morning.
Oh, let me do that in a second.
Hold on.
You just take the picture of it.
So you get a perfect view.
Okay.
That's, uh, front view.
I can't really do it.
I can try and do a side view.
There's another part, part next to it.
Okay.
I'm going to take that picture.
Right.
Now let me take a picture of the back.
You hear?
This is running like a charm.
Just beautiful.
Okay.
Shot of the back here.
And, uh,
Oops.
You just got a lighter shot there.
Beautiful.
The back seat.
It actually has a reverse seat in the back,
which I think I explained, uh,
on the show yesterday.
So you, uh, literally can see six people in this.
I'm going to take it to the office tomorrow because, uh,
I'm moving in.
It's a perfect automobile to move shit with.
Now let me find the, oh, here it is.
That's, that's the.
The release for the bonnet.
Okay.
Now let me get the little thing here.
Hop.
Ah, there she goes.
Listen to that engine per, huh?
Okay.
I'm going to take a picture of the, uh,
the biodiesel conversion.
Which is basically a filter,
and a bunch of tubes.
And I'll take a shot of the entire engine.
Which looks kind of like a junkyard.
Ha ha.
Hold on.
There we go.
Boom.
Perfect.
Got it.
So you can hear.
And it is a turbo diesel.
So let me, uh, rev up the engine.
We can listen to our wine.
Hold on.
Listen to this.
You can still listen to that.
One, two, three.
And it's still on this.
One, two, three, four, five.
Now I can't be five, seven, this.
Huh?
Well that's interesting.
Maybe you don't want to have five series.
Or only.
I mean, it's four plus one.
Brand new battery.
All right, listen to this.
Listen to that engine.
Maybe listen to that.
You can hear the turbo.
Listen to that.
Ah, so sweet.
Okay.
Drop the boner again.
So.
Oh man, the smell was perfect.
You can.
Ha ha.
Let's see.
There's a radio in here.
Oh.
Oh man.
The smell was perfect.
Ha ha ha.
Let's see.
There's a radio in here.
Oh man.
Let's see.
There's a radio in here.
But I don't think the.
Oops.
Fader.
Volume.
Source.
CD.
I don't think there's a CD in there.
FM.
Now we're done in the bottom of the garage.
So this is also a power.
What if I hold that?
We'll return it off.
If I just hold that down.
Yeah.
Perfect.
Okay.
So.
This is it.
This is Trinity.
This is going to be my experiment.
While in San Francisco.
This is supposed to be a daily source code listener participation project.
Okay.
If you live in the Bay area and you're inclined to help out with this project.
I'm looking for people to help me with two things.
One.
We've got to clean this puppy out.
We've got to paint it.
We've got to you know.
We've got to pimp this bitch out.
That's what we've got to do.
Oh, it's I'm just looking at the.
At the Odom and 145,253 miles on the block.
Wow.
But speaking of clock.
It's internal clock is right on time.
I've got a.
What do I have here?
I've got.
Shoot.
I should do an interior picture.
Now shouldn't I?
Hold on.
Let me do that.
There we go.
So he's me.
Take my glasses off.
So I can look a little bit more.
You mean?
You see how that turned out?
Oh, cool.
It looks very good.
So I'm going to need some help on the artwork.
I definitely want to turn it into.
It's almost the perfect.
It's almost the pod show colors.
So it's a perfect ugly yellow, which we have to turn into kind of like a line green.
Besides that, what I need is I need help in making biodiesel and learning how to do it.
And also I guess just getting into the whole culture.
And I think that when we do our sound seeing tour to the.
Biodiesel gas station in the Berkeley biodiesel place that will probably meet some interesting people over there.
So I'll be sure to.
Oh, there's also a check this out.
It has a sunroof.
A completely.
Oh, man.
Completely manual sunroof.
What was that up?
This thing is awesome.
It's got everything I ever could dream of in a biodiesel clunker.
I'm so proud.
I'm so happy with this thing.
Okay.
Let's, you know, the pipe there.
And turn it off.
Good.
Alrighty.
So make sure that you go to daily source.
Lock this.
Make sure you go to daily source code dot com.
And I'm or curry dot com, I guess probably.
There will always be a link somewhere on the show notes so that you can.
Take a look at these wonderful pictures of this absolutely wonderful automobile.
And it's not just mine.
It's yours as well because we're going to really experiment on this puppy.
And let's see what kind of fuels we can get in.
We're going to throw pure vegetable oil in.
We're going to do all kinds of stuff.
We'll go to San Francisco restaurants and pick up vegetable oil and cooking oil.
And we'll measure it performance.
Well, it feels like it has about 80 horsepower as I drove it home from the office today.
So it's great.
I'm totally in love.
My, the new woman in my life is Trinity.
Okay.
I'm not going to bore you with the ride back up the elevator.
I'll catch you there in about four minutes.
Right now, let's crank up some drive in music.
music.
I'm on a dead end street.
Like a dog in the rain.
I'm lost the sand.
Where I'm headed is a memory.
Where I'm going looks like where I'm feeling.
This could be a scene of a whole lot of miles.
Of the world in the wrong direction.
Let put in my youth.
These past me back.
And I wish somebody else would drive.
I could stop at the station and ask the red chunks.
But you know that ain't cool.
Come by, man, for a dollar and a half.
But I'm way too confused.
Little friends, I never met.
Said I know the way you go in.
I'm through the keys and said, get down.
And we can take my car.
But only if you don't drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive.
music.
Oh, you gotta drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive
drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive,, drive, drive, ride, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive, I am driving, ride, drive, drive, drive, drive, drive and ride, drive, remote that road away driving it's really awesome, driving, brakes, for 30 example, like we said, tell the radio station, putting pressure on my control, drive, pasta, fast control, drive, drive, very powerful bitte load today
couple of the songs by Jimmy in the past and it's so cool man to go to to the
network and our PMN as we call it around the shop and just look for drive
song just a search for drive and boom there it is like four pages of songs
about driving is just fantastic okay little so I'm back up in in the condo
studio as you can tell from the difference in sound let me see if G mail is
back up and rolling god this is really a problem see how dependant we come on
the shit still a server error these guys are in some trouble man I'm telling
you this is not good at all okay oh I want to welcome a new member to the
pod show family this would be the pod show headquarters family mark Sierra
who is who's been working with us on a kind of a part-time basis as our
financial controller I think we I think run and I basically threatened him and
said dude you are you have to you have to come and work for us otherwise
you're gonna take you out you're too good and it's great you know when you can
get a financial rock star we love we love technical rock stars and graphic
rock stars graphic graphic design and Mark is he's a total rock star when it
comes to to finances particularly because well as you can imagine once we get
cranking full steam pod show is going to be cutting a lot of checks to a lot
of podcasters oh yeah so welcome Mark great to have you aboard you know
what luckily even though Gmail is down I still have the promos dot pod show dot
com website so that means that I do have oh actually there's a comment here
at the top let me see what we have at the top of this so this is just off
there's been submitted today we had one two three four five six seven eight
different submissions let's let's listen to this first promo if we don't like
it we'll just kick it out okay you're now entering another world and audio
world with a music of tomorrow is brought to you today a world where you can
experience adventure excitement that karaoke and more
with your
intersellers world at wwww dot sal door dot com that's c-a-l-d-o-r dot com and
see what the fuss is all about
all right let's move on to the next one
I was rich in pride
running on fire down the sunset street and the zerg skip from the glitchcast so
I was listening to Monday's show and I had to check who an amp I was just
looking at it calling but as I can assist my feeder atoms because you opened up
the show with the song that we just just debuted two days ago on the pod
safe music network and on our show the glitchcast this is Chris Mills living the
dream and it starts off with that pointy lyric about Richard fire I'd actually
just seen Chris a couple weeks ago at the fee fee here in New York City and like
any other great artist I see I'm trying to persuade him to bring their music up
to the pod safe music world so thanks for playing the song and it's gonna show
him the power podcasting real quick to have a whole bunch of people focused
in on it and if you're looking for other great independent music come check out
the glitchcast at glitchnyc.com slash glitchcast we're breaking just about a new
artist a week and some of them are really hitting the big most excellent okay Eric
thank you very much you know it and I'm just thinking about that I have to go
to my account in the pod safe music network let's let me go to my my podcast
page I had not yet reported that I played that song so hold on a second this is
something we got to fix I keep having the log re-log into this thing we've
kind of like write a cookie or something gonna make that easier see go to my
playlist I love this interface it's so easy okay oh I guess they already did
report it oh okay already done oh groovy that's easy while we're here in the
browser one more Gmail check hello Gmail are you working waiting for mail.com
this is gonna be shit okay oh that really that really really bugs this shit
out of me that it's not working okay let's talk about something else that I wrote
down on my list of things to discuss with you I have recently changed I've
made a life a very important life decision and there's been a big change in
my life and I think most men will be able to understand what I'm talking
about when I say that I have switched from the Gillette Mach 3 Razor to the brand new
and I picked this up at Sainsbury's in the UK the brand new well it's not really
brand new I guess but it's the Wilkinson 4-bladed system and I've got to tell you
I am really digging it now we were actually a part well Ron and I with our previous
company think new ideas so this is a pre 2000 we were a part of the launch of the
Mach 3 the Gillette Mach 3 Razor campaign it was the most I mean this was like
you know that's a multi billion dollar business this Razor business and we went
to all the you know to the labs and we got the whole speel and whole low down on how
many times a man actually pulls the blade across his face with each shave which is
over a hundred times and we think about you start counting it you're like yeah
that's easily a hundred times and how the blades were made of you know little diamonds
shits on there and and the one and actually I remember someone from another advertising
agency raises hand and said oh can we you talk about that the blades last much longer
and I'll never forget the look on it was a VP on on this face it went completely dark
and he said we never ever ever talk about the life time of our blades so they
actually do not even tell you how many times you could shave with it I found with the
Mach 3's you could you could you could last almost a week with one razor with the
disposable or you know with one of the click things that you throw out I've had about four
shaves on the Wilkinson now I'm definitely a wet shaver I've tried the you know the
the dry electric razors and that how it just burns my face up so I'd love to hear what you're
using and what you think of the Wilkinson this is not a paid advertisement this is just me
purely out of interest you know it's interesting to switch once in a while it's almost like
when you smoke a different kind of weed you can get really used to to some kind and then you
smoke a different kind and then it really makes a difference by the way I'm down the stems here
on the condo this is this is bad news have we got no Gmail and we're down to stems Christman what
there was the word coming to so drop me uh drop me some feedback out of McCurry.com and if you
can please I'd really appreciate if you could put the the MP3 file up on a server and just
send me a link to the server so here's something that came in and of course I don't have
my Gmail handy so I don't remember who sent it to me but there is a there's a website called
boycott-riAA.com and apparently this link has been making the rounds in the blogosphere and the
Paddle Surrier and I want to share a little bit of audio from that site with you right now which I think you will enjoy
recording industry association of America
hello
well I recollect the days when music was free you could take from the radio burn and see
now but all right I didn't want to know about me my address but number five is cute you're
fidgety we still got privacy while the prison we've letting you spy on me how many tricks are
going to be letting you try on me trying to be silent on the empty trees but you protect your corporate
privacy keep your phone number hit from the food policy you cut to presentably hide and seek to hit the
number to call the you did some creak that's a five oh one oh one oh one two oh two seven
five oh one oh one oh one oh one oh one oh one oh one why do you call our IAA starting the
negations the cops should be looking for the real procetrations the killers the races the rapids
set a fucking with us for a season two hundred this race a little finger if you feel me loud
these are gonna be in the Zara fucking show leave us alone if we're worse come on like a
if you want the time in your home there's no such thing of that publicity even if you've given
it away for free so join us in the 24th century where we find the new songs on mp3
it brings you to check out the jeek rockster card in p2p to pull the number now to help them
team and if you call for work you call this three seven five oh one oh one oh one two
seven seven five oh one oh two oh two is an area code and we're dialing seven seven five
and then we'd be dialing the one the one one can't reach the band now the RIA takes a stand
capable labor can reach you by the man so what's the plan stand I've got a short of ten
and fail they gotta change up the industry make it all available on mp3 listen to people like
you and me and make us want to pay a monthly fee as long as I'm a lyrical catastrophe
go ahead and grab it it's completely free and gotta pay your dime to listen to me so cheer this
song in the arc the industry seven seven five oh one oh one seven five oh one oh one two seven
five oh one oh one you sure to get the permission of your parents first
five oh one oh one seven five oh one oh one with sixty million strong yeah freaking
hey you know it hey that is cool r i boycott dash r i a a a dot com that's uh where I got the song
from also apparently there's another URL zugg dot com zulu uniform golf dot com that's maybe
we can get the song as well uh oh man uh it's fantastic you know it's uh the something I've
been meaning to talk about and I don't really have all that much time left before the satellite
window closes everybody um it's about the levies that are special taxes that are put on a blank
media i think they started with the cassettes blank cassette tapes where the r i a a a would actually
there was it like a special tax that was put on top of the price of blank media blank cassettes
is when it started and that money went to the um I don't know if I went to the r i a a a or to ask
have b m i now that I'm not sure if it's probably the r i a a and they then of course distribute
that completely fairly amongst the artists who are of course being ripped off because home taping
remember that home taping is killing the music hmm seems to me like they did pretty well
um same goes for blank CDs now let me post this question to you because this happens uh in fact
I heard that um in some countries I don't know if I think it was an australia there was a 25 dollar australian
currency uh levie or tax put on the sale of iPods which recently I believe the owners
through a class action lawsuit now can get their 25 australian bucks back but I know that many
countries have considered this and I'm sure in the future the r a is gonna push that through that there's
going to be a tax on iPods and other MP3 devices now here's my question okay what right does the r i a a
have over podcasters for getting a piece of that money think about it for a second is there any
difference I mean they're they're talking about people putting MP3 files on these players
my shows an MP3 it gets put on the player you know I do work I'm creative uh there's absolutely no
difference in fact my uh file is much bigger so maybe I should even get a higher percentage of that money
and how will that work and how can the r a a defend that they're the only ones that should be
receiving the cash think about that for a second think about that and if you live in a country where
there is a tax on MP3 players please let me know I mean you know what screw that forget MP3 players how
about CDs I definitely know that are most countries in the world CDs there's a special tax on
CDs that goes to the r i a a a and to record companies I mean there are so many people who burn
podcasts on the CDs to listen to them in the car I think that we deserve to get a piece of that
if you're a lawyer if you have any uh special knowledge of this please feel free to
to jump into the conversation here so anyway um I don't really have time for another so
man I want to play another song but I really don't have you know what I think I can just fit this
one it this is from Atlanta this came through uh Ron's nephew Adam Bloom it's uh outfit called
the brew and it's uh it's kind of like it's kind of like uh some kind of hip hop it was a
crunch crunch funk or something like that
it's too fist and bottles with the Yakima system swing back and forth with that stop first image
showing it's all around every shape full of fashion yeah kick it in and we'll see another vision
me my way to the boot after mine what to the room so fuck up the room just step through
ninety nine bottles got my liver filling up look at mommy right damn I just put some tongue
next you saw mine and you need to spill the jealous put it down for my trousers on the round for
it's almost like, anyway it won't rain
Let's check, we'll be the right shit for Mark
Come on, let's get them drunk
And then I gotta get lay
I don't piss for the dollars
Cause I just got paid
Get sick, get sick, get sick
From a dad and take a fuck
And let a loser get lucky
Damn, girl, you look so fine
Don't you wanna get shoved
And I gotta get mine
Everybody would drink
And let's get it on
And go back to my place
Cause the three in the morning
Drop damn pennies
To lose their skirt
To let something to my bed
To do a little work to turn that
Cause I like it like that
Give me 10 minutes
And I'll call with you again
And I'm gonna try to drag them home
Some hot land at the prou 99 bottles of beer on the walls where you would find them
and you'd find that at the Podsake Music Network.
That's it for the Daily Source Code for today.
Let me see DailySourceCode.com is where you can find the latest show and the Podcast feed.
If you want to, you can subscribe.
Actually, the best thing to do is copy the link underneath that orange on a white XML icon.
And they go to advance an iTunes and then subscribe to Podcast from there and just paste in what you copied.
Oh man, I got to fix this compressor.
That's really, it's a shitty ass sound.
And subscribe to it that way because sometimes the iTunes feed gets caught up and hung and you know, then we just, it's no good.
Adamacrate.com for all of your feedback.
And I'll be back here tomorrow for the Home Day Edition of the Daily Source Code.
Thank you very much for listening.
For those of you who are subscribed, please stay subscribed.
And I'll talk to you guys soon, bye.
Hello.
Pod Show.
Live in your podcast.
Play in hours.