Delta Sierra Charley 2-6-7
You know the weird guy in the corner of the office who always has his headphones on?
That's you!
Hud choke
There are no secrets!
Only information you don't get out of!
Adam Curry
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass
Do the next generation radio content in my ears
I like to think I'm flying into this jerk
Just take it!
Hit in the hump at full speed, it is Wednesday, October 26, 2005
Good morning everybody from Yes!
I'm not a sunny northern california, the first day is actually raining in the morning
I mean like real rain drops you fall on on my head stuff, you know?
Yesterday we had a bit of that, but today it's foggy cloudy
Finally I know what to wear
It's just gonna be shit today, that's easy
It's just our last day of the day
Time now 3 minutes before 9 in the morning of Wednesday, 26
Major friggin bummer
All flights full until Saturday
Put you of course will have made my trip out here almost a full two weeks
And that means I've got to do laundry tonight
I only had 10 days worth of underwear
It's okay because whisking from Reese makes it so fluffy
It's so fluffy and soft
Another source code ready for you and we've got it full of feedback today
I don't know what it is but all of a sudden everyone started sending feedback
Some of it based on actually most of the based on this show which is nice
That's all the less talking I got to do
By the way, some of this feedback is definitely not appropriate for a young year
So if you're listening to this on speakers you may want to take that into consideration
But it is very fun
Even got some video feedback actually a piece of video I want to share with you
Which would be kind of a theater of the mind thing
And obviously some appropriate positive music
Started off though once again a dub from mash up town didn't he just as he sent me
What was it hate mug?
Which is IDC's mashup
Watch you by mashuptown.com
A new day and other morning after
Leaning back on my chair and a greasy spoon cafeteria
Last night was some bit later in a snow
Power wave again way back in the light of day
Chatting shifts in at the wall table
Telling jokes playing with the soul
Lookin' out the window
Girl brings two plates of full English over with plenty of scrambled eggs and plenty of fried tomatoes
Get my phone out
That's a give this girl a shout
See if she had a nice time, that's night up town
Ask if she finds his trying to again sometime
And the count drops the phone right away
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
My baby no man's around because you love the soul
And if I know but show
I'm not way really jobin' it
And it counts like, oh, you need to hold it down
Put your phone back, quit staring at space and it snag
That's that
She'll want you much more for not hanging on
Stop me if I'm wrong, stop me if I'm wrong
Why should she be the one who decides where
Fritz off for I know I know I'm wrong
Now the girls rude
And she's rude, but she screwed right through you
You're beyond your knees, too
We get together before we get together
We labor except we're so supreme
Without a way that's killing the ground
You've put the sinky s' in, you never know
Little workmaq, little workmaq to rock men's
Mix the pot mix the pot mix the pot mix the pot mix
Lock the dispensation
We're now with that heavy heel
I can take it believe it, believe it
I'm like funny sweet, it's not like that
Yeah, till like a friend, till like a sad jump in which you clouts and that
Do you really think I act like I'm telling you I'm serving the ACS and it's a game set of match
Perfectly in control of this skull
I want the lead roll, I've been folded, I'm holding you to hold
Bill sold, high speed gold
Game over, game over two Cole
All right now
And now
Not as cooler
Oh, I can hear you
I say, well, what's cooler than me in tow
People
przikoy
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right NOW!
That's why though, you can step up you get the harder
Oh no, y'all
Oh you'all
Oh you
I want to see y'all on y'all man is behind y'all
Let me see you
I am your neighbor
I give a no more shinkie
Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake
it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, Take it, shake yeah, shake cold,aga good match jump in your hand, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it
sent in that I want to go through them all and I realized that once you listen to it
and I kind of sketch a lot and put it in there, put it in my line up, that the ID3 tags
just don't do it for me. So you know, I've got everywhere, it's like feedback feedback
for daily source code. You know, put some more information in your ID3 tags, please. You really
help this podcast throughout. What you hear in the background is the T-Cettle heating up.
I've switched to, you know, really more T in the mornings since I seem to be doing the
show earlier and earlier because I really want, you know, try to get into the office
around 11 o'clock in the morning. And it kind of works out. Get up at seven. You know, when
I do it at seven o'clock, the alarm goes. Actually, the alarm doesn't go. The blackberry
starts doing its thing, which is built in alarm. And then, you know, I kind of roll over,
hit the snooze once, hit the snooze twice, maybe. So like I did this morning. And then,
we start going through the email. That's until 8 o'clock, then get up kind of stumble out
of bed, you know, roam around, get my first cup of tea, and then start lining up the show.
So that can start rolling at nine. And then, you know, once I'm done it, around 10 and 10
to 11 is uploaded. But have I told you how much I love doing this stuff? God. This is such
a great gig. This is what I've been dreaming of. It really is for years and years. Somewhere
there's a picture of me. I bet you I have this at home. I bet you my mom put that into a
scrapbook somewhere. There's a picture of me. And I was like four or five years old sitting
in my parents' closet with a broken reel to reel tape deck. You know, one that's really old
fashion ones with a wood casing around it in the plastic quarter inch reels on it. It's not
a quarter inch. Yeah, a quarter inch. Yeah. I guess it was a quarter. They was a two track.
I don't know. Definitely a quarter inch. With a microphone, you know, looking like all
sheepers with my extremely white blonde hair, little, you know, porcupineish hair.
I got to find that and put that up on the, on show notes somewhere if I can. Well, I look for
it when I get back. So almost two weeks. Man, I better start putting some salt
Peter in my food, you know. Ni Hao from Asia, Adam. Hi. This is Ram Miranda. This is talking
from Singapore. You've heard some of the other feedback from Europe. So you've been going
from Africa, plenty from the US. I think there's even one from Australia. But I don't remember
hearing any podcasts, promos from Asia. So many, many podcasts, promos from Asia ran. But that's
okay. We welcome you. So I thought I would send a little bit of feedback. Maybe a quick little plug
from my own show. Sure. As far as first I want to say congratulations on your new Mac equipment.
As a die hard Apple of Dusius, I am jealous to the Mac. All I can say.
Do you hear that? It's like stuttering. It's not him. It's it's either his recording or my playback.
I hope it's not my playback. I can say as get a plenty of ram for your equipment and don't
forget to back up, back up, back up, back up. As far as feedback, there's two little requests.
Maybe for you to consider for your show. One, I love the wiki notes for the new show. They're
really great and the links are good. But in some ways, they're almost too good. It feels like I'm
reading a transcript to the show and there's been a couple times where I take a look at the
transcript notes, but for listening to the show and some things have been kind of ruined and
aside from just the hit test. Well, you know what that is. And that's kind of interesting when it
comes to the show notes. In my mind, show notes is something you look at later when you're in
show note browsing mode. But I guess some people do go to the show notes to see if the show is
going to be interesting. I don't know. Or if the topics are going to be what they want to hear.
That's kind of too bad. Maybe, maybe consider delaying the show notes more. I don't know.
It's what are other podcasts there's experiences with that. Do people go to your show notes to
find out what's on the episode or do they go later to get more information? And I think the show
notes should be pretty detailed. But that is one of the reasons why I'm kind of happy the show notes
aren't really right there in the description of the podcast because that does, I think that does
make people probably wrongly not tune in. Because I say, wow, you know, G, I may not be
interested in biodiesel. Whereas it could be a totally hilarious bit about a biodiesel. And also a lot
of times I do a lot of traveling and I'll record two or three of the daily source hodes and onto
the iPod and just listen to them on the airplane. So it would be nice to see maybe we get a
in conjunction with the wiki notes, a strip down RSS, a beat of the show notes, maybe just a quick,
you know, the one lineer is on what it is just to have something for the iPod and for those of us
who don't want the surprise of the show ruined, that would be great. The other thing would be,
as I'm kind of learning on my own podcasting, I'm a professional journalist. I was
been under the print side and this is really my first foray into the broadcasting or podcasting
element and I'm really enjoying it. But I thought, and I think your show is really great about
bringing a voice to some of the other podcasters and the whole revolution that's taking place.
But it'd be nice maybe to hear from somebody established like yourself and a professional
about ways that the rest of us may without the resources or the talent or especially the experience
ways we can bring our own podcast up to that next niche and just make them that much more
listenable and enjoyable. Okay, that's real easy. Has nothing to do with money, has nothing to do
with talent. It only has to do with one thing, passion, because that's what seems to be working and
I get asked this question all the time. What should I be doing? How can I make it better? It's simple.
It's not about your voice, it's not about how you mix stuff, it's not about the quality of your
audio, that may be things that you're interested in, that may be a part of what you're trying to
convey or what you want to have as your overall product and that's something that if you're interested
in it, you'll find your way through that. But passion, that's all that it's about,
pick something you're passionate about and if people can hear your passion in your voice while
you're talking about whatever it is you're talking about or while you're creating, it doesn't
have to be talking. Whatever you're creating on your podcast and it could be just for one person,
passion is going to do it time and time again. That always shines through. If you're going to give us
a little classes on podcasting 101 from your own views.
That's one other thing that I saw on, I think it was the Fagrogator, which is the video podcast channel
from qpodder.org. Imagine why I'm staying managing that. I'm subscribed to it. It's really
interesting. Some great videos coming through. I saw someone do a short video podcast about their
setup. That's what I'm going to do. I'll do that. Maybe I'll do that right after I'm done with
the show today. Just so you can see this setup and see what's working. And by the way,
when we started off with podcasting, I particularly was very specific about not using any outboard
gear. I wanted to make sure that it could be done on just any computer that had a microphone,
or that had a microphone jack for you to plug one into. And that's actually where Cas Blaster
came from. If you haven't seen it, please check out Cas Blaster.com. It is the perfect way to get
started in podcasting. It'll take care of all of the bits that are perhaps somewhat confusing,
levels, and how do you mix stuff in that? It takes care of beautifully and it creates your MP3
file. And pretty soon, it'll be, I think it'll be two buttons cast and blasts. That would be
really tremendous and maybe it's really helpful to some of those those of us fell along the way.
Anyway, a quick plug for my own show. It's called Miranda Wrights. It's an offshoot of my written
log. It can be found at the ITMS under Miranda Wrights or at Randcast, R-A-N-D-C-A-S-T.com.
As I said, our American journalist, I've been working and living here in Singapore for about
five and a half years. And my podcast is kind of centered around that what it's like living in Asia,
not being Asian. Myself, I do a lot of sound-seeing tours with my wife. A couple of places we've
been here to Singapore, Bali, Tunisia, about a week before the last terrorist attack. And recently
had a trio of sound-seeing tours from Europe. I do a little bit more on travel tips and because
I've done some riding. In fact, I have a couple of both hopefully coming out about Apple,
the iPod and OS Tiger. I try to do a little bit of max-inturek tips now and then just for my
own hobby. So, if people would like to listen to Tunian, that would be great to continue feedback
and laser. I can improve my show and just wanted to say, okay, for somebody here in Asia,
it doesn't listen to the radio at all. I would say, I get all of my 100% podcasting,
broadcasting, information, solely from the podcast. So, I just want to say once again,
thanks for being in inspiration and we'll keep listening, thanks for that. I'm gonna take care.
All right, thanks for the feedback. And Rand. Rand, Miranda. I get all my stuff.
Excuse me, I get everything from podcasts as well. That's basically where, that's my whole
information flow these days. And I do miss some stuff. You got to get some mainstream in there.
Otherwise, you wake up one day and you're like, huh? That happened? I mean, I,
yesterday I watched, last night when I came back from dinner, I watched the John Stewart show.
I had never even seen the mugshot of Tom Delay. And I thought it was a joke.
I thought it really was a joke until I kind of dawned on me that that really was his mugshot.
Last night was fun. Went out to dinner with Ron, his wife, Marta, and Ron's mom, Wilma,
who was in town. That's right, Hurricane Wilma, come blowin' through town, everybody.
I was hilarious. We had a great time. I had some great food. And I got back and it was just, you know,
totally wrecked from good food, fantastic wine. Just rosy cheek, you know, just sprawled out on the
couch, was just able to catch John Stewart and then rolled into bed. Again, this morning, as I said,
the blackberry went off and I was like, well, I could do it with at least three or four more hours.
And now I'm feeling the workout from Sunday. So that means that I guess either tonight or tomorrow,
I got to go back to the gym and got to keep out, got to keep out, got to get that cholesterol down.
See, should we do some Gmail feedback? Do some regular comments? Let me see. I just want to run down
this list because I have such a backlog. Let's see, this is about bio diesel, okay, Graham says fuel cells
were invented in 1800. Okay, haven't seen any fuel cell cars really on the market yet. Let's see this.
Oh, a lot of people sent in, you know, I asked you to do this test to kind of draw schematic of the
condo before I released the video podcast. And I think just about everyone who sent who did that said,
you know, this is exactly the way I imagined it, the theater of the mind worked really well. I described it perfectly.
And also I have to say that, you know, the way I created that video was of course to my mind's
eye, you know, the lighting, the music, the vibe. So I guess we're completely in sync on that.
Let's see what we have here. Hey, Adam, Apple should sponsor the show.
Yeah, you get a new iPod video, start doing video podcast and everyone into DSC once an iPod video.
You're a driving force in the economics of consumer electronics says Nick Casavall.
Yeah, that's right. It's funny because I think that if Apple actually started to pay me for that,
everyone would hate it. That's what, you know, when we do this and say it was stuff,
everyone's laughing and it's fun. And then the minute you do the same thing for a product that actually
Podger got paid to do, then it sucks. We've got a lot of experimentation to do still with the
with advertising. And I have some ideas. I definitely have some ideas. Okay, so this is cool.
This is from Phil Walker says, I've only started listening to podcasts and I say I'm really enjoying the
source code having this episode blah, blah, using my pocket piece PC and 7 iPod. However,
I thought you might like to know that iTunes kicked off in Australia yesterday. Let me see if that was
yesterday in Australia. That would mean today in Bangladesh. There's been heaps of good publicity on
the opening. Much media discussion of this kind of media versus CD and traditional delivery methods.
Might, although I'm not a nerd, I am convinced that web-based media is the go. It's really
catching on here and makes us Aussies feel like we're part of the rest of the world. And hey,
don't worry too much about the time gap between California and New York. Think of us. That's the only
reason why I can't get Patricia to move to Australia. I've been there. I love, I mean, I got to
I love Australia. Work hard, play hard. You've got the kind of the the properness of the United
Kingdom. You've got all the luxury that the United States might have to offer. And something we
call chiselahide from the Netherlands, which there is no real perfect translation, but chiselahide
is kind of like coziness. So I liked it. I had a great time. Oh, man, I should find that documentary
I did. We had, we did some wacky stuff while we were there. But, well, welcome. Although, of course,
the Australians were already a part of podcasting for quite a while. Now, I guess it's going to
burst wide open. So if you're new to podcasting and you're just listening to this
through iTunes, this is going to blow your mind. It really will. And yesterday, I said that I was
confused about all the stuff going on in politics right now. And I wanted some feedback on the indictments.
And, of course, the the Myers nomination. And, of course, people complied.
Greetings, Adam. All mighty pod father. This is Tim and Kelly from Supreme Court Watch podcast.
We, uh, listened with great interest to the latest daily source code when you dropped the
name of Harriet Myers, the Supreme Court nominee. You know, it's not a problem for it to be a
little bit confusing for you because it's confusing for us as well. Kelly, what do we know about
Harriet Myers? Well, I think the better question is, Tim, what don't we know about Harriet Myers?
And that's one of the fundamental problems with this nomination. She has been a nominee to the Supreme
Court for weeks now. And we really don't know anything more about her than we did the day she was
nominated. One of the very few things that we do know about her is that she is and has been for years
Bush's personal lawyer. And from the outside looking in, it seems as though that's the primary
reason she was nominated to be a Supreme Court justice. And hey, we're not the only ones that
have an issue with all of this. In fact, some of the president's most stalwart supporters that are
normally behind everything that he ever does, they're defecting in droves because they just don't trust
that Harriet Myers will vote the way that they want to on the Supreme Court. Hey, this is a really
complicated story with unprecedented politics and it just changes every day. For more information,
check us out at Supreme Courtwatch.org or search for Supreme Court Watch and iTunes. We're news,
views, and insight on the future of the Supreme Court. Thanks Adam. You. Thank you. Subscribe,
by the way. I appreciate that. That's very cool. Seems like, I don't know, it seems like we're
kind of just looking into mainstream media now. Like we're in this weird flocks, you know,
you've got the current administration and all kinds of trouble and certainly in trouble in the
quote, polls and trouble internally and with these indictments. What indictment, by the way,
Ron and I actually look some of that stuff up yesterday. What is a grand jury? What is an indictment?
And it's a little different thing you would think, actually. I don't even want to get into it now,
but the way it's presented is different than what it really is. None of it's good, clearly.
But what I'm going to little concerned about is everyone's really good at kicking down and
particularly when the guys are down there kicking them real hard. But, you know, but then what,
you know, we still have three years with this president. So, I think we need to get something in order
somewhere and something's got to happen and just gloating over it isn't really going to do much good.
And, you know, I'd like to move on, man. We've got a country to keep, this is still the best
country in the world. It's the best country to live in. It's the best country to do business.
It's a great country to fall in love in. It's a great country to drive in. It's just, to me,
it's, and I've lived in a lot of different countries. And so it's kind of a shame to see that we're all like,
ha ha ha, guys down, you know, and now what? And now no one's standing up to do anything. And that
who was on John Stewart last night? Al Franken, who I think is an extremely smart guy.
And, you know, it's just joke after joke after joke and, and I guess he's running for,
or talk about him running for Senator, which could be interesting, but, you know,
I don't know. I'm just not impressed with anyone yet on any, on any points anywhere. You know,
where's the guy? Where's the leader? Where's I have the leader right here? This is the leader,
the next leader of the free world. Hello, Adam's Curry. This is Cheryl Murkowski, 25 year old,
beautiful woman, Smoker, and owner of three fourths of a long. I've appeared nude a number of times,
including while recording a program with my gal pal, why the wisdom over at luckybitradio.com.
Now, I want to know why the fuck you cut off mad yesterday. She's just trying to help people out.
Not everybody's a fucking billionaire with Chinese. Let's see everywhere.
Flying, we're a giant a mobile sitting there with a huge horse cock like you. Okay, sure, mad,
may have huge vaginal lids and a pubic mound like nobody's business, but it's all
gone and grew pot-safe mash-up or all explosion. Okay, I mean, I have my own pot-show podcast,
but at least I don't cut off the form of Luna. Okay, Jesus. Anyways, I love you Adam's Curry,
and just remember, respect the bloated lesbian and don't cut her off. Have a fabulous day.
Man, look, hey, look, it's not like I didn't warn you at the beginning of the show that this was
not for a young years. Oh, man. I would vote for Cheryl. I'm afraid of Cheryl. That would be my choice.
I got an email from Rusty Bender. What a great name that is. Is that a stage name, Rusty?
If not, it should be. And let's see, that we had a whole email thread. He said,
start over the friend of mine used to belong to a joke death metal band. They did a couple of
songs that mentioned your name. As I said, it's meant to be a joke or you're interested in hearing them.
And Rusty, of course, is from the strange brain radio podcast. And, uh, and I've well,
what am I going to say? No, of course, I wanted to hear that. Now, this goes back to the MTV
days. Ah, yes. Just to let you know how loved I felt, often, in those late 80s, early 90s.
There's all coming. Your jacket is clear. You are such a risk to get off the air.
Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring.
Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring. Dye in a ring.
Death corpse from their blood, whips, and vomit CD. I just made me feel warm all over.
You'll ask a pod show. Yeah, it's real. We're no Adam Curry and we're no Don and Drew Show.
And we certainly didn't win any pod casting awards because we're too new for that. We're just podcasters,
pod casting from Anchorage, Alaska. That's right. I said Anchorage, Alaska. We're the biggest state,
you know, we're bigger than Texas who claim if Alaska melted, we would be the biggest state.
What a bunch of crap that is. Anyway, if you got a pod show, you got a gig, you got a promo.
Kick it to us and we'll plug in. Hey, and if you're a subscriber, you can go over to our website at www.alaskapodshow.com
and read the show notes because you would really have nothing else to do. Hi, this is Matthew Evel.
You know, pod casting is renewed my faith in the music industry. I'm not kidding. The just one
who thought that all the radio stations were only playing with their corporate vote rewards
were telling them, a long comes this new medium that's run by people who actually love the music. They
listen to the music. Independent artists like myself can share our music with people around the world.
Oh, it's making a wish. Check out my new album, Bearing Coffee at www.mathewebel.com.
So I went looking Matthew. I don't think that the new album is on the pod safe music network yet,
but of course, very familiar with Matthew Ebel's work. So when back into the playlist and
yep, lo and behold, there's one that I played before and I'd promise myself I was going to play a
couple of pod safe tunes I'd played before to kind of keep the rotation going, you know, just one
of day is not going to do it. Something that PW turned me on to. Sally went down Matthew Ebel on the
daily source code, Sally went down. Sally went down. Sally went down.
Sally was ravaged, sweet saw the woman. Every song that she fills her room.
What you got, come with me, I'm not too happy now, what's a good like her gonna do?
Saturday never made it to the road, never saw the lack never even heard the drink coming.
Saturday I went walked on the track, meant where the rails took and never thought to love back.
It's Saturday not that she was doing right, but she went home early, but she never saw the lack never heard the drink coming.
It hit her in the back, Saturday went down, Saturday went down.
Saturday didn't want to get involved with the scene before her.
Keep it down walking on the track, maybe they were just ignore her.
But she kept her head down, she kept her head down, she kept her head down, she kept her head down.
She didn't listen to the man before her.
Saturday!
Saturday never made it to the road, never saw the lack never even heard the drink coming.
Saturday never walked on the track, meant where the rails took and never thought to love back.
It's Saturday not that she was doing right, but she went home early, but she kept her head down.
It hit her in the back, Saturday went down, Saturday went down.
Matthew Ebel, went down.
Filling the pages, that's CD He Did in 2001, it says here, interesting.
So I can't wait to hear the new one, Matthew, very cool.
Check out the website.
Patricia's gotten into some trouble while I've been over here.
She's locked herself out of the house twice.
Actually, once she left and she put her keys in the bag that she didn't take with her.
And of course, Christina didn't have keys.
What happened yesterday?
She went out for a walk on the downs, which is right behind her house.
It's beautiful, just a hundred miles of nature.
You walk right out the back gate and you're kind of through it.
Like a tunnel of trees, it's so idyllic.
And then you're on the downs, she went for a walk and she left.
And she closed the door, the back door, but we rarely lock that up.
We're just going out for a couple minutes.
Please don't break in now.
And so we have two dogs still.
And Jesse, who's a, you don't really want to mess around with Jesse.
She's a golden retriever, a shepherd mixed your mud.
She somehow managed to lock the door with her paw.
But it's just like it's a dead bulb.
As you push it down at the bottom of the door, click it locks.
And she actually wound up having to have some come over and break a window to get in.
But here's the part, the two days before that, because this has happened with one day in between that she's locked herself out.
She went around to the neighbors and known was home.
And then on the left-hand neighbors who, oh, we know, but we haven't really hung out with her or anything.
She got their son to climb up with a ladder and go through a window that was open in Christina's room.
And then climb through and then go down to the front door and open it up.
And she said, boy, he was really cute.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, how old was he? Oh, you know, 1920.
That's the same age when she found me.
Should I be concerned, listeners? Should I be worried?
Be it away from home this long?
I don't think so.
But you know, we've talked about Patricia and I missing talking to each other.
Just about now, missing some other stuff.
Hey Adam, this is Michael Carino from the digital media cast experiment.
After doing the experiment for a number of months, my wife started considering herself a podcast widow.
And of course, that kind of neglect isn't good.
So when the new season of Survivor and the apprentice started,
I asked her if she wanted to do a podcast about these two shows after each episode.
She said, yes, which means now we get to spend more time together.
Furthermore, she's now listening to podcasts.
You know, she's got to figure out what the other podcasters are doing now.
And she's starting to get into the podcast culture and community.
This is all goodness.
Now we sides on widowing my wife for these two shows.
Armed share apprentice and armed share survivor are both growing in popularity
in over 22 countries worldwide.
You can check them out at tubecasts.com.
That's TUECAS.com.
But this is just the beginning.
We hope to be adding more television-based podcasts to the tubecasts.com fleet.
Even now, I'm talking to podcasters and even conventional media personalities
about doing tubecasts on other TV shows.
For the conventional media folks, it's an easy way for them to cross over
from their hell to our Navana.
And for the podcasters, it's a way to broaden their audiences.
So check out tubecasts.com.
Maybe you'll want to do one.
Any questions?
Just go to tubecasts.com.
Looking through the Gmail here.
This is pretty interesting.
Apparently, let's see.
Apparently, Senseo, or Senseo, but believe me, it's Senseo.
It's trying to build up their brand name in the US.
And what they're doing is, sorry, the blackberries interfering there.
What they're doing is, if you send them a picture of your coffee maker,
they'll send you a Senseo for free.
I think you only have to pay the cost of shipping.
So that's kind of weird.
You know, these guys are trying to do some kind of gorilla marketing,
yet they're passing right by podcasting,
and we've been working so hard on using them as an example.
It's a fuck you.
Can't say anything but that.
I'm no more Senseo from now on.
I'm going to figure out a way to break you to break your,
your jet, the Jedi mind trick I played on you with the burping.
I'm going to figure out a way to reanker that to something else.
Just pisses me off.
These guys, they're not doing the right thing.
We've really done a lot.
With a lot of fun, by the way, that to figure out new ways of advertising
and doing it for absolutely nothing.
And now they're doing all kinds of cool gorilla marketing stuff.
I can just see them, you know.
Yeah, well, we've got all the podcasters talking about us.
Screw you.
I'm sick and tired of that.
Hey, Adam, it's Michael Spectre from Melbourne Down Under.
I just thought I'd give you a bit of feedback on
data source code 264 where you would talk about podcasts and lectures.
And whatnot, it would encourage students to skip lectures.
Many universities already provide their lectures in MP3 format.
And some of the more forward thinking,
you need to learn learning students to already download these lectures.
So while it's not at this stage, traditional podcast,
students can actually get access to the MP3 formats.
This is great for external students, but also the last,
as you said, for students who miss lectures.
Some of the more forward thinking infrastructure providers
to universities are actually starting to bring our assess
into their services, such as the iLecture system,
which is also like to appear in the US.
So it allows them to actually drop an audio file
into the system, produces an RSS feed that allows people to
subscribe.
And you're right, it's so many changes that will take place
within the education context, not just for students, but with
the incorporates and how we can deliver enhanced
podcast or OPML files that bring together
not just a single stream of content, but alternate
streams of multiple content to a student all in one go.
So a lot of exciting times ahead and thanks for the show.
I was an every day.
Michael, thank you, thank you, thank you.
I was thinking about that.
I think you have to do it the other way around.
Of course, it's great to be able to have an RSS feed
from either a certain course, a certain class,
a certain professor, a certain lecturer.
I think it should be turned around.
And I didn't know the universities had these big systems
that can do all that stuff.
That's very exciting because what I'd say is turn it around
and give just like, if you haven't seen gigadile,
check out gigadile.net.
It's a very interesting thing that Andrew Grummit
from the iPod 11 team put together.
The way it works is you can create a channel,
and he's built it in a very open fashion,
which means that anyone can,
I guess you can set it up however you want,
but the concept is anyone can add not as whole show
but an episode to the feed.
So I could be an intermediary for you.
In fact, I'm thinking about setting up a video
channel on gigadile for exactly this very reason.
So why wouldn't you make it so that every student has
their own RSS feed that this university system can put stuff through?
So you get all the stuff automatically that is meant for you.
Think about it.
Think about a professor having the opportunity to say,
okay, here are my students for this particular course.
I'm going to give them this particular podcast.
And that could be an MP3 file,
but it could also be a PDF for a word document.
I mean, Jesus Christ,
think about the power of that.
Fantastic.
And I want you to think about something else.
It's kind of nasty.
But have you the last time?
I'll do it in a second.
Let me do something else first.
This came through in the cockpit cast.
Of course, we know there are plenty of me.
I'm way into aviation.
There's lots of great aviation podcasts.
You can find that at IndiePotter.org under the aviation note, I believe.
And so the cockpit cast, which is done by a pilot for a major airline,
and he's got a big plane.
And that's he's got certainly got some millions worth of airplane
strapped to his ass.
What he's done now is he created a little video of an approach
to the San Jose Mercury Airport.
And he literally put his video camera right up in the front,
like on the dashboard, if you will.
And well, it's not going to mean it.
You're not going to see it, but listen to this.
So we're 100 feet off the ground, just about to land.
Copilot's calling it out.
50, 40, 30, 20.
Oh, I'm seeing the runway.
10.
Right.
Still five feet.
Five feet off the ground.
Boom.
No, it's wheeled down.
Ah.
You won't believe what you see.
This is the view that people pay money for.
And what a racket that thing makes.
Just fantastic.
I love it.
Also isn't approached to San Jose,
and I think also an SFO approach.
And there you go.
They're off taxing off the runway.
Oh, man, that is just so cool.
So cool to see that.
So I think it's stuff like that.
That's really going to be great for video podcast.
Show little bits of stuff that you normally wouldn't see anywhere else.
And only people who are in that certain vocation.
Okay.
Now I want you to do it.
Do you remember the last time you were really sick?
I mean, sick to your stomach sick?
Like, just, you know, really, really.
I mean, you know, when it just, you can't help it.
And you're just spewing and you're puking all over the place.
And you feel horrible.
And just as you think you're done, you,
oh, man, here comes more.
Senseo.
You're coming to my podcast.
I didn't put cast.
You were more well computing on PDFs.
You've been listening to you.
You are more hardware, more software.
Go wish them.
Give them tips on tricks.
And he isn't.
Tomas Riffon-Goydine, or Cleamon-Shopin.
It's a lot of art.
It's huge, huge, huge.
It's the roadhouse podcast and it's a new hour.
Every Saturday.
I've been stepping out.
Try to find.
Subscribe now.
And I tune to roadhousepodcast.com.
The roadhouse.
The finest blues you've never heard.
I've never heard.
Perhaps, I've been deleted.
When I'm stepping out.
Shoulda been standing.
Hot chill.
Should only be enjoyed under the supervision of a podcasting professional.
Warning.
Do not attempt this at home.
Hello Adam.
This is Jagatemek from Lublin Poland.
I'd like to thank you for inspiring me to start my own podcast podcasting.pl.
I started podcasting February and I liked the idea so much that I began promoting it in Poland.
And I'm happy to say that the podcasting vibe is picking up pays in our country.
And we now have people podcasting in Polish from Poland and abroad.
So thanks a lot for that Adam.
And give my best to Patricia and Christina.
Before I go, I would like to say a few words to the listeners of the Daily Source Code,
who may not know that they are drop Polish podcasts out there.
Listen carefully, as there is a little surprise for you in there as well.
We have an vision from the Jewishiri.
At the time, radio that began hisumental vision
accompanied by spy-ver tulee to the country,
inBMK and Control.
While still being emotional, each person wants to try to tutenspublicly.
Not meant to talk to innocent young people,
or to hear it any scare.
podcasting of posts.
I would like to ask you how you would like to ask your fans to listen to the post
podcasts, which you can find in the description of the podcast, thank you for your
questions.
You know, I have a thought there that maybe that was Dyerim Curry Dying Polish, I'm
sure the comic strip blogger, aka MS Mobile's Guy, will be happy to translate what we just
heard there in that short little promo.
Before that, we also heard a German promo.
I heard some of just kind of skip by, I don't care, I don't care, I just want everyone
to enjoy.
I want people from all lands to be able to tune into this stuff and enjoy it.
Okay, so for the C. tomorrow with Thursday and Friday, it'd be cool if you sent me
and some stuff for Friday.
Let's make Friday a big ass party show.
I want the best mashups, I want the best real rock and podsafe music.
I want some, you know, just some, thank God it's Friday, we're ripping towards the weekend
type of stuff.
We do that.
That would be cool.
Let's have a big celebration, because if we do my last day, unfortunately, it's going
to take that long because I was planning on kind of mowsing back on like today.
It'll be my last day in San Francisco for then go back and of course, I'm going to come
back briefly to the West Coast.
The idea is I do want to go to the podcast that I spoke, I'm not sure if I'm going
to be able to make it.
I don't think we're going to do any, well, I told you, I'm not going to do any damn announcements
because that doesn't seem like the right venue for what we want to announce.
So let's party it up, y'all, okay, nothing else going on today, just more, more rain here
in Northern California, please feel free to send any type of feedback to Atomiccurry.com
and I beg of you to please give me some context in the ID3 tag so I know what the hell
is going on and what to expect.
If we do that, it's just going to make it so much better because years from now, when
we have search engines that are doing all the right stuff and searching the ID3 tags of
MP3 files online and you know Google is going to figure that out.
Once we've got all that going, then we will be prepared for it.
So more work on the ID3 tags, please.
DailySourceCoat.com is where you can find this podcast and the podcast feed.
If you want to subscribe to it, you can do that with iPod or Lemon or you can do it with
iTunes or FreedDownloadedApple.com.
I'll be back tomorrow for the Thursday edition of the source code, everybody.
Take another podcast, stick it in your ear.