Don't see her, Charlie Chippel too.
Yeah, I gotta start.
Hello, everyone, and welcome to the Daily Source Code.
I'm here with my dad and my mom, and they're both now recovered from the flu.
So, pod, father.
Tell us how you're doing.
Represent, he's supposed to.
He's supposed to.
On the East Coast, we ride to the day we die.
Oh, what?
It's just from the side.
I don't understand.
Amsterdam or Rotterdam.
Rotterdam.
Right.
Are we in, can you move over a little bit?
We're in Berkeley, California.
It's on the other side of the bay from San Francisco.
And we are recovering.
Yeah.
At the wonderful Claremont, resort, and spa.
But before that, I want to explain that to you.
I'm sorry.
This is not like Oprah, where you get to grab the wine.
Excuse me, Oprah.
Oprah, Oprah.
What I want to say is, don't forget the trip in the plane.
No, no.
That was just a positioning where we are.
When we were still had our flu.
Well, let's go back.
Okay.
Let's go back in time.
The last time we spoke with our listeners.
Listeners.
Yeah.
It was Monday.
And we got, what are like, 121 comments?
And a comic strip.
And a comic strip from the comic strip holders.
And the comic strip holders.
What do you want to say about how you live.
Did you see that comic story?
What do you love?
What do you want to say about how you live.
What do you learned about how you live?
Did you see that?
Ah, the comic strip.
The comic strip blogger did a comic strip of three of us.
Yeah.
I want dressed with wrinkles.
Let's wrinkles.
Please.
You don't care what he says?
I think it, yeah.
Does he know me?
And I always was pretty accurate at time.
He would wear some butt-hand.
Thank you.
You are sort of a beavers.
Sure something.
Okay.
So we were sick in the hotel all the way through Wednesday.
Yeah.
You were really, really.
Please, just how sick was I?
I have to say, Adam is never sick.
Right.
And normally when I am sick, you immediately have the chicken chicken.
Yeah.
I make an old fashioned ginger chicken chicken.
Which is brew?
Yeah.
Because you are always good.
And Dr. Still don't know why it is so good.
It really, really helps.
Can we confirm your...
I can't explain it.
Can we confirm your a witch?
Yeah.
It's got the brew brew.
So I couldn't do that.
And there is nothing worse than being in a hotel and being sick.
Right.
You feel weak.
Now, thank God we were there.
You know?
No.
It was just me and myself and I.
Yeah.
Could have been.
I would have been.
So we were in New York City, which was the hottest time of the year.
I was 90 to 95.
The moment you came out of the hotel, it was like stepping in hell.
Yeah.
Okay.
It was so hot.
I forgot all about that.
Yeah.
I didn't even think about that.
This time.
I mean, either really.
No.
I wasn't thinking.
But when we lived in New York, I remember that the one summer.
We stayed in New York.
And we said, we'll never stay in New York.
I said, okay, that's it.
Yeah.
Let's move.
So.
Let's just not.
Just a little dry cough left.
Yes.
Just now.
But it's nothing compared from what you had.
Okay.
And.
So.
How was it?
What?
How sick was it?
Yeah.
I was just explaining.
I want you to really, really, really sick.
Talk about the symptoms.
I've been seeing that for a long time,
shivering, sweating like crazy.
And I had to sleep.
There wasn't.
Another bad or anything.
I had to sleep in the bed.
With me.
With you.
And I had to sleep on a little part of the bed.
Because the rest was soaking.
Soking wet.
Now think about it.
My mom said had a very good.
Um.
Explanation.
Yeah.
And she's thinking about.
Theory.
She said.
Now.
Can you imagine the next person that has to lay in that.
Oh, disgusting.
Because you know, it's seeped all the way into the box.
Oh.
The box.
You know that happened before.
So don't even.
We like.
We can.
Yeah.
Well, not not like.
No.
I still.
Okay.
I spilled on the floor.
And I ruined the couch.
What do you always do with home?
Yeah.
Really.
Made yourself at home.
That's clear.
So yeah.
These were the.
The sweating nights from.
Right.
Yeah.
So we said.
Let's go.
What?
We were.
We originally planned to go to Vegas.
Yeah.
And then.
Let's not do that.
Let's not go to Vegas.
Yeah.
We literally work.
Because you know, traveling makes you really, really tired.
Yeah.
Especially when you're not feeling well.
So we had.
But we said we wanted to go to San Francisco, which was our.
Our idea anyway.
Yeah.
And our plan.
And so we did.
And.
Boy.
That was nasty in that plane.
Well, before we even got to the plane.
Uh.
We.
First we had.
I did a smart thing.
Yeah.
Because I knew that the traveling to Newark Airport from the east side was going to be a pain.
So first I got a huge humongous penis extender limo.
Yeah.
So we at least would drive in comfort.
Because we shifted.
Yeah.
It was nice.
And now.
So this was Christina's first time in a.
In a pimp daddy limo.
Oh.
Yeah.
And what did you think?
It's a lot less fun.
Yeah.
A lot less fun.
It looks.
Yeah.
I got nothing so actually.
No.
It's not.
And it's actually uncomfortable.
Yeah.
In the back seat.
The side seat is shit.
And the movements that the limo makes is not very nice.
It's experienced.
Couldn't even record on the corner.
The back up.
It's useless.
So then we got to the airport.
And you had your first experience with.
T.S.A.
The transportation security.
My God.
That's what happened there.
I see.
I'm old enough to know how it was to travel.
And you know.
And travel by plane.
It was wonderful.
So we had little white gloves.
Oh yeah.
It was wonderful.
It was just.
Such a wonderful experience.
You know, you.
The people of the.
I was called the.
The.
Security.
The airline.
The airline for example.
They would spoil you.
You know, they were.
They respect you as a client.
Yeah.
And is everything okay.
Can we do something for you?
Can I say anything?
You need.
Are you comfortable?
No, of course.
Need a pillow.
Of course.
Do you need a blanket?
You're comparing first class service.
No.
Well, even.
Right.
But, but you don't get that.
Economy was nice.
You didn't even get that with first class.
No, you get a reused pillow.
But so first we had.
Yeah.
I'm.
Actually talking about 30 years ago.
Yeah.
30 years.
Okay.
But the problem starts when you have to take your bags.
First you check.
Check your bags.
Then you have to take them.
Back again.
Yeah.
And they go wait and line.
You have to lift them off again.
If the list.
So if you.
A tiny little woman with a very heavy suitcase.
With humongous knockers.
You know, what do you do?
What do you do?
You need help or something.
So you have to carry them off again.
Yeah.
Put them on your on your trolley again.
Then.
Then drive to.
Right.
The trolley to another side.
That's when you have to lift them off again.
Yeah.
Give them to a couple of very slow motion.
Do it.
Do.
No.
We're in the line.
And they said, oh, you've been slept for.
You're the VIP.
And we were like.
Yeah.
You've been selected.
I was laughing.
Oh, that sounds nice.
Yes.
Yeah.
So we directed to the line.
They come with us.
Yeah.
Yes.
And I was smiling.
We had one way electronic ticket.
So immediately you get selected to the.
Social.
Special treatment.
And I know I remembered.
Yeah.
And so we.
If I if I have to touch any sensitive area, I'll let you know.
And I'll let you know.
And I'll do it with the back of my hand.
Yeah.
What could you just like grab my sensitive area?
I don't know.
Why that tone?
Yeah.
Nobody did anything wrong.
It is a hassle anyway.
Why do they speak to you like that?
They scream.
And they're.
Yeah.
The grass.
There is the whole day.
I'm sure you wouldn't be.
No.
It would be much.
It would be fun if they had a little rap.
You know.
It's like, you know, they enjoyed so much that they have the power to.
That it does feel a bit like it.
To command people the whole day.
Yeah.
It does feel like that.
A little bit.
That's horrible.
And only Americans do that because not in England.
And then we got on the plane and immediately they gave us real knives.
Yeah.
We were.
I was like.
Yeah.
We sort of medium class when we were.
And I'm had a guy next to him.
Oh.
He was doing office finger.
I was looking at him.
I thought first.
I thought.
My God.
Is he biting his nails?
There's nothing left.
He has nothing left.
He moved onto this finger.
Then I saw that he was actually biting on the rest of his fingers.
Oh.
Yeah.
And I said, you know, like you have nothing.
You have nothing else to do.
So you're.
You're.
You're looking at what is this guy doing?
Yeah.
You know, before you.
You kept.
Bring it to my attention.
No, then, you know, as to I noticed that the guy was eating his fingers constantly.
Yeah.
They were red.
They were almost.
He.
Eat it to the bone.
Oh.
So this was a very nervous.
I'm sure.
I was.
Yeah.
Did you call that a tick or a direct kind of a thing?
What is it?
Fucked up.
Yeah.
It was horrible.
And constantly constantly.
From the storm to the other fingers.
So I said that to them.
And I said, and I'll look at him.
And from that moment on, his appetite was gone.
He said, he turned his shoulder to the guy.
And it was his health trip was ruined.
His fingers looked like pencils that you had sharpened with the pen.
Like he was.
No.
Like his finger was in a pencil sharpened.
Yeah.
That was disgusting.
But anyway.
So that was it.
And so we were not having.
And we didn't have any appetite.
No.
Not at all.
And then we got in late.
And because it was very busy.
But I was very proud of you, huh?
Because, you know, you actually have physical discomfort from pressurized cabins.
We'll get to you in a moment.
Get to you in a moment.
Pressurized cabins and lack of oxygen.
Because of my heart condition.
It's just, you know, not a joke.
But I was very proud of you.
Yeah.
And people who have heart conditions are very sensitive to pressure.
You know, and it was, and it was a full plane.
And you could sometimes, the captain just let the pressure drop it a little bit.
You know, and then it goes up again.
And then you think, my god, can breathe at the moment.
And then you feel, oh, feel better now.
You know, it's, it's sort of up and down.
And we had the nice first class.
First class seats right by the toilet.
Which eliminates the entire first class part.
No.
That was life.
I am not a Gucci perfume.
It starts right.
It almost like.
No.
Now before actually we, before he, someone took a big crowd.
I heard, no, no.
I heard a mom screaming next to the door was actually really next to us.
Yeah.
Right behind me.
So every time you're, oh, yeah.
You know, flush it.
But we weren't even in the air.
And normally you don't go to the bathroom where you're not in the air.
Because you know, why should this another poop story?
No, it's not.
But I heard a mom say, hello, hello.
You done that out because, you know, we got to go.
We had to go.
We have to go out.
Yeah.
And, and, and she opened the door and I saw this boy sitting with his pants on his
clothes.
And mom, I'm not done that.
That's how.
And she closed the door again.
And then while she closed the door, we got a knife.
My lawn.
Move.
Oh, the sort of a menu.
And instantly the, um, the person came around.
Which was a home of, you know, of course.
And he came out gay guys always fun.
And he looked at me as my god.
And that was actually designed to take out my Gucci and
a few months, spray a little bit.
And after that, he was okay.
Right.
And you were friends with the poster for the rest of the food?
Yeah.
We really did each other.
We bonded.
Yeah.
We bonded right away.
There at that moment.
Yes.
And so then we got in the, there's nothing else on the flight.
Oh, except the Christina was freaking out.
Because of like three thunder and lightning.
Thunder and lightning.
Okay.
It's fear of flying disease.
It's not.
It is no.
But your dad's a pilot.
I did that in the word.
You were asleep with your mouth open.
I can't judge by that.
No, but if you're in an airplane.
And you see all this bolts of lightning.
Don't you immediately think of one of those films.
You think, oh, shit.
We're getting struck by lightning.
You're going to go down.
And then you get turbulence.
No.
And you feel everyone shaking.
And the plane gets hit so far away.
And then, of course, I kept waking mom up.
What are you?
Wait.
What are you waking mom?
It's a muckney.
I feel really bad.
I don't know.
I just like that.
I get a heart attack.
She's not allowed to.
So, you know, she knows that because she was a baby.
And she was about four months old.
She already, you know, we took her to Holland.
She's used to it.
I don't understand it.
Why she flips.
I don't know.
Wow.
Okay.
Anyway.
It's from the movie.
I have from the movie.
So then we got in.
And of course, the car wasn't waiting for us.
No, right.
So you had saw your father.
Oh, my god.
Not, not again.
Yes.
So there was no car.
And but we had a suitcase as real.
Yes.
While we were waiting.
We had to watch over some questionable suitcases with his guy with a beard.
And we really said.
What was it?
You said.
I mean, a breath.
I mean, I'm going to get blown up.
I'm going to smell like airplane.
That was okay.
Yeah.
Because it was not a suit, guys.
He was actually a package.
And we had.
Oh, and stuff was like taped up in a cardboard.
Yeah.
Really wrong.
How come eating it?
This guy's like, I bet he got special treat.
Can you keep an eye on it?
And the guy goes away.
And we're looking at.
We're like those things.
That's what everybody thinks that these days.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
And Adam comes and I say, you know, we have to keep an eye on that.
I'm bad.
Give me a minute.
Have me taken a minute.
I'm impressed.
So anyway, so we got a cab and the cab brought us to the hotel.
And it was like 130 in a morning.
Yeah.
132 plot.
Now 130.
And it's a huge.
Hmm.
How can you explain this place?
It's on a hill obviously.
It's one of those.
It's on a hill.
Think straw hats.
Do you have a picture?
Yes.
Yeah.
We're people.
The girl's staying out.
And the movie dirty dancing.
It's sort of the family resort.
Everyone has like the hats.
Yeah.
There you go.
That's both.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You can go.
I mean, in the old movies, when they had the straw hats.
Mm-hmm.
And they've a very old fashion.
They've a hassle.
Oh, who was it?
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
I'm not that old.
Yeah.
I'm not talking about straw hats.
No.
I'm safe.
It took some ages.
Good.
Nothing to do with straw hats.
Yeah.
Exactly.
It's Mr. Membo.
How's that?
It's okay.
Good.
And.
Which is nice sweet.
Which looked out at the air conditioner.
Yeah, first.
Yeah.
And I say, well, that's very nice.
Well, it's not going to do.
You were not in the mood for it.
No.
I am not going to accept this.
I'm on another room.
I thought, good.
Yeah.
Screw that.
I don't want to.
Hey, I had.
I went to this whole thing on the phone about the baby.
Right.
You wanted to baby you after all the sickness and.
Yeah.
And we were still hockey.
So.
And there we go.
The men.
You got the manager.
Well, of course.
The hotel.
So get the manager.
Because a lady downstairs.
Because it was in the middle of the night.
No.
She didn't know.
She was not in the mood to.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Change the room.
But you did it.
Yeah.
So this place is.
It's nice.
And we sat out in the sun yesterday.
And today.
It wasn't a sunny day.
No.
Today was another sunny day.
We drove into Berkeley.
Yeah.
And you know how you know their songs.
And Scott McKenzie.
If you're going to San Francisco.
Well.
You know.
It's still the same.
Yeah.
All those hippies selling the same.
Tied.
Beats and flowers in the hair.
Oh.
It was cute.
It was like.
Time stood still.
Yeah.
And I got a full ring.
It brings me out of the forks.
I bought a ring.
Yeah.
It sounds really bad.
But they bend it and make it look like a ring.
Yeah.
It's pretty.
I have an order of ring on.
It's from nice.
Nice.
And no spoons actually.
And he makes beautiful jewelry out of that.
That's what it was.
Very good.
So anyway.
This is a very special edition of the Daily Source.
She haven't even mentioned.
Because one year ago today, I did the first Daily Source Code podcast from the castle.
We were still living there.
And what did I say?
I was actually in the comments.
I haven't listened to the show, but you then said somewhere.
Something like, well, what did you say?
What are you going to stop talking to yourself?
No, no, no, no.
I said, are you ever gone to earn some money with these?
I don't want to do this.
You know, is this work?
Is this something you're going to earn money with?
Because, you know, you put a lot of effort in it.
And time.
And I said.
And what did I say?
Why is it going?
I always said, okay.
I like the bar for a long time.
I got one, two, two.
Yeah.
Hey.
We had a lot of testing to go through in the beginning.
I've sat on the early days.
Yeah.
That's right.
I mean, Christina, you were there throughout the whole.
I don't remember the process.
Well, I was too busy being on the good shot at Message Board.
Thank you.
And you were in the paper, right?
Yep.
So the word is out that Pod Show company that Ron and I started received funding from a group
of really top-notch investors out here in San Francisco and Silicon Valley, which is
Clienter Perkins.
You haven't met any of these people, unfortunately.
I hope that maybe you want to.
Yeah, if you want to.
Yeah.
Definitely.
We can set it up.
Let me cool.
Clienter Perkins, Sequoia Capital.
And then Ram Sri Ram.
Um.
And that's really exciting.
Yeah.
I mean, the daily source code listeners had heard about this.
Of course, I couldn't talk about it on the show.
But it's been a big part of what we've been doing.
It's very good job.
Unbelievable.
So.
And Monday, we actually are in our office.
Yeah.
The temporary office.
And then we're going to start figuring out how we're going to spend this money
to grow Podcasts.
Yeah.
Right.
We kind of have an idea, obviously.
Yeah.
That's great.
That everything you ideas ready in your head.
I know that.
And then to celebrate Christina did something very nice.
She.
I did something nice.
Yeah.
I know.
What did you do?
You went downstairs.
I got you in a point for a floatation.
Yeah.
Yes.
And I did.
15 minutes of floating.
What?
That was so far away.
Yeah.
No.
Fifty minutes of floating.
So I went downstairs.
Yeah.
And I want to tell you about my floating experience.
Because you didn't want to tell us.
Now we want to know.
So first of all, you are where you're swimming trucks.
You're going to have to make it really.
They want to know.
It's floating in the back.
Yeah.
I want to make sure they had a float box that would be good enough.
Sure.
It's only one person.
It's one person deal.
It looks basically like a big kitty litter box with a door.
Literally.
Like the ones that our cats dump here.
Really?
Yep.
And now, of course, why do you float?
Salt water probably.
Yeah.
We're not talking salt water.
We're talking like.
Like 800 pounds of salt.
Oh my god.
So you have to show it.
Something like some chemical salt.
I don't know.
I didn't.
Didn't sound right.
Whatever it was.
And you get in and then you lay down and you float immediately.
You just floating.
Yeah.
And it's only like maybe that deep like a foot deep maybe.
And then they go really good about that.
Well, this is this is the question.
Yeah.
What is so good about it?
I'm not quite sure yet.
Because you're basically you're sitting there floating.
Yeah.
In the dark.
Are you supposed to fall asleep?
Yeah.
But you're in like salt water.
And then you get on your face and starts to crackle and dry.
Yeah.
And then accidentally.
That's not good for you.
I touched my nose.
And then of course, you know me.
I would taste it.
And it was like burn.
It's like putting my tongue in battery ass.
Oh my god.
That's your face really go deep in the water.
They give you one of those airline pillows.
But then your hair is in the water.
And it's like, man, I didn't do that.
Do you would fucking.
You would say, I'm you.
You would look at that thing and say, I'm not getting in there.
And as I'm walking there.
I need music.
Yeah.
Point.
Now they want to see you.
Yeah.
No.
Except.
Yeah.
But only the.
The blink blooms.
There was no melody.
The starting blink blooms.
Yeah.
Ash.
Oh.
And as I was walking there, even.
The woman was saying, have you ever done this before?
So no.
Oh, some people don't like it.
Oh, that's nice.
Are you telling you for that?
Yeah.
If you have to pay $70 for it.
Really?
I'll come back in ten minutes and check and see if you still like it.
Oh, I don't know.
Money bag.
It was.
But you know, I said, would you like to go?
Because I was late, of course.
The full 15 minutes or just the remaining 30 that you have.
I'm good with the remaining 30.
By the way, a guy in the.
In the.
In the locker room.
I says your Adam Curry.
I said.
Yeah.
Yes.
He says.
You're home like a horse.
He said.
I'm.
I forget.
He's.
He is.
That's bad.
I forgot.
It's not hard.
Boy on.
Well, I forgot his name.
He said.
I.
Congratulations on your financing.
Oh, that's nice.
Yeah.
I don't want to bother you because you hear a few relaxation.
Yeah, that's right.
So anyways, then I got out of the fucking salt.
You like it.
Yeah.
It was a great sensation.
It was it was like waitlessness.
It was very much like being in space.
So that was cool.
But it was so.
After all, you think.
Okay.
Yeah.
It was like.
Okay.
That was.
Do they expect you to sleep or.
No.
What is it?
Did you go in into a.
So what about you turn over and you like.
Well, actually it was nice because you can really stretch and stretch in ways
that you've never stretched before because.
You're waitless.
So I think.
So I could really stretch.
Yeah.
I think it is.
I'm paying.
Yeah.
I think they come.
I came up with it.
Because of people with pain.
Yeah.
I think they'll be very.
I mean, it felt nice.
That was nice.
But it's just, but you're not going to fall asleep in the.
Luke warm salt water.
Been.
Come on.
And it's dark.
Yeah.
So.
But then.
Yeah.
There's more.
The guy.
And the guy said, hey.
Got a cigarette.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Yeah.
I took a shower.
Have you seen the showers here?
No.
It's a fucking car wash.
Oh, you have.
You have lower nozzle.
And you can control the temperature.
And it's a big shower.
I mean, big shit.
This is what we when we build our house.
This is what this is what I want.
They could do the middle section.
Yeah.
And then you can determine if you want.
Oh, my.
From for the top section.
Or if you want the big dome.
Yeah.
And that was really nice.
That was really nice.
Yeah.
I stood there for a long time.
Touching myself.
Oh, God.
I didn't.
I didn't need disgusting.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
I'm going to San Francisco.
And we're going to.
I guess we'll pick up the key and go.
Look at the place at the pad.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then we'll go find.
And we'll go buy a sleeper sofa.
Yeah.
We can stay.
No.
Oh, didn't we?
Didn't mention it.
We went when we were in New York.
We felt a little bit better the last day.
Excuse me.
Now you were sick.
I was sick.
I was still not.
But we.
We'd already agreed to have dinner.
We agreed to have dinner with our old neighbors.
And New Jersey where we used to live in Verona.
And that's actually where Christina grew up.
And where she went to school.
And where you.
Well, actually, that's the house that you always talk about.
Yeah.
The house you grew up in there.
My roots.
And where Christina was born.
So she wanted to see it.
And she wanted to go back.
Because she was always talking about it.
And we did.
And these neighbors are very nice people.
Very nice.
Dennis and Barbara.
She's a French teacher.
She goes to France a lot.
And she's.
She's nice.
And he's too.
And they invited us.
And we went to a restaurant with them.
And then we went to the.
And we were.
We went to the monument of the 911.
And it had.
Because they used to use one place where you could look over all of New York.
And I used to go with my dad a lot.
So now they brought us up there.
And the walls.
It's a cliff.
Yeah.
And yeah.
They put walls up.
No.
There was always a wall.
And that's where you go up.
Like on Santa night.
And there are a lot of.
Yeah.
And you take something to drink.
There's a lot of guys.
We bring their girlfriend there.
Yeah.
To sit in a car and stare at New York.
You can see it.
It's beautiful.
It's gorgeous.
It's a treasure.
It's on Eagle Rock Reservation.
Yeah.
I have to show you something because there's something very beautiful.
And you can explain.
You can explain Christina.
Well, the whole wall was a lot of the all people that died in the 911.
And they had a big statue.
Where had a big eel on top.
And then it looked like a book.
And it had.
The firefighters and the policemen that died in the whole thing.
And they had made out of candle wax somewhere around there.
And they had two twin towers out of all the candles.
People put there and that flowers everywhere.
And I was really sad because you would read the list.
And you saw like families.
And you could read a whole story out of it because you saw.
You saw like a two year old and then the monster.
Yeah.
And you thought, oh, they probably brought them up there to the top of the twin towers.
And then the thing collapsed.
Yeah.
Ah, horrible.
And you could see people from a month later from everywhere.
From England, from Sweden.
And I mean, so many people from all over the world.
Yeah.
And he said something that kind of many things.
All these people can imagine they don't exist anymore.
And I thought that's really weird.
That they all died that same day.
They don't exist anymore.
And especially that if you if it's evening.
It's around about 11 o'clock.
It's a beautiful warm night.
And you can see New York.
And then when people tell you these things.
And we were staring at all those names.
And you know, something's happening inside.
And think, what a pity.
What a pity.
Hmm.
Yeah.
So that was a beautiful evening.
And also because we, uh, Christina saw her, um,
I'm a much childhood best friend, best friend, Leila.
Oh, sorry.
I don't know.
That was fun.
Um, so we had a, we had a wonderful night.
We had a wonderful night to see.
And I think we.
Uh, it's good to see your old neighbors.
Yeah.
And now to stay in contact with them.
Definitely.
And, um, so New York was a bust.
Except for that.
That was nice.
But well, we forgot how hot it could be.
And it was out of the hottest time.
Because there's, that we always turned right when we walk out the door of the hotel.
Right.
Oh, because we already explained the last time that it was a boutique hotel.
So the boutique hotel.
That means also sort of strange healthy, not so good for 14 year old food.
But you know, whatever you try.
But it's not what you expect.
And it's not much.
Just a pile of healthy things.
And I like it very much.
But I wanted, we had a little kitchen in the room.
So I was, um, my plan was to get some groceries.
And, you know, make some nice snacks and, and sandwiches.
And you do feel good.
Yeah.
And, you know, make some eggs or anything or sandwiches.
And, and buy some good cheese.
For, of course.
And, but we couldn't find anything.
There was no soup.
There wasn't.
Delia.
The last day.
Instead of going right, we went left.
Take a walk in the woods.
And I'm walking left.
Well, actually, across the street from, on the left side,
was a beautiful, amish supermarket with rude,
the most delicious fresh food you've ever seen.
Yeah.
I was so angry.
You said that yourself.
Wow.
All those days.
You know, with fruit and fish and salad and beautiful,
big tomatoes and cookies and fresh crispy bread.
Yeah.
Your mommy instinct makes you very angry now.
I really, I was very angry with myself.
You saved us a lot of heartburn.
I'm sorry about that.
No, no.
Yeah.
He did.
He had a lot of heartburn.
You mean your acid reflux disease?
It really, really came back.
Yeah.
You could take it with this pill.
And then one week, it'll start working.
Or you could just drink some goddamn maylocks right now.
Yeah.
What you had a big bottle of maylocks,
maylocks.
Next to my bed.
Then we bring it on the flight, too.
Yeah.
First we're like, like, swig and maylocks.
We knew this.
And I have to say, being back in America,
you really need the maylocks here.
It's all.
I didn't want to say it was a part of the maylocks plan.
Everybody probably has that problem.
Because every had there is a commercial totally.
That says something about acid reflux.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Everybody has that.
It's all eyes out.
And I can't imagine why I've seen the, the,
you know, the dining food and, and, you know,
portions are big.
Very big.
So all this has a small cell.
It comes.
It's like, the rest of your body.
It's like the rest of your body.
Those big fat onion rings.
But how friendly are Americans?
They are very, very nice.
They're very nice.
Remember?
They're very relaxed and nice.
I'm very happy.
Yeah.
So simple.
I think I'm going to seem pretty happy.
Very happy.
Yeah.
I like that too.
And I think when I look at them, I think,
or they have no clue.
Do they?
You mean?
I don't know.
It's just like.
What?
You can't be happy?
No.
It's almost that they're not,
and it's not in reality.
It's sort of a, they all feel like they want to feel like this.
No.
What I'm in America, I feel like I'm in a movie.
Yeah.
They think they're in a movie.
That's our culture.
Yeah.
I know.
It's a group thing.
We have to be happy.
Like you're in Laguna Beach.
This is how we watch that episode.
Oh, please.
Oh, my God, Brett.
Oh, I'm too lazy to articulate.
Oh, my God.
They talk really slow.
Yeah, I know.
But that's, that's a show about teenagers trying to be grown up, which is just frightening.
You don't like that, dude.
It's a frightening program.
No, but it's just not.
It's bad for the general population and general health.
I think the sweet 16 show was just as bad.
It's bad.
That's bad.
That's really bad.
Yeah.
All right.
But anyway, it's an amazing country.
Pretty groovy, huh?
Wait till you see San Francisco.
Yep.
Did you have a scene yet?
No.
You're going to love it.
Only little part here.
Yeah.
No.
This is, this is Berkeley.
It's not San Francisco.
This is near Oktown.
Yeah.
Okland.
What's Okland?
Okland?
Where M.C. hammers from?
Oktown?
No.
Hmm.
Okland.
A lot of hippies.
I think it's going to be here.
If I look outside.
The poppers.
It's going to be clear tomorrow.
Yeah.
I think so too.
I mean, I wish we had missed very missed the meteor shower yesterday.
But the what?
The meteor shower.
Oh yeah.
I wanted to write them.
I couldn't wake up.
No.
You think I can sleep tonight in your bed?
Except you're going to Christina?
Yes.
I would lie.
Are you dry?
I feel moist.
I have not emanated any sap for two nights.
Oh, yes.
Casting.
No talk of sap on this.
No, you're more than welcome to join me.
Me and my friend.
Oh, it's something to sock on it.
No.
All right.
Christina.
You close it up.
I'll go over there and turn it off.
Oh, wait.
No.
So ended up.
Remember it was the anniversary show.
Yeah.
Well, kids.
This is the curry signing off from the anniversary show.
We're glad we could waste your time.
Once again with a.
Good.
Very much.
It's right.
I hope we irritate you just as much last time.
Peace out man.