Delta Sierra Charlie 2-6-1
I showed that car make no claims regarding the quality of its potchillers or the sanity of its producers.
Listen at your own risk.
There are no secrets.
Only information you don't have.
Adam Curry
With $16 million worth of airplane strapped to my ass.
Then the next generation radio content in my ears.
I like to think I'm flying into the future.
And it is Monday, October 17, 2005.
Good morning everybody.
Oh yeah.
This is about the earliest source code we've ever done.
For the first time I've seen the sunrise and northern California.
I've got to tell you people it is beautiful.
Good morning.
Welcome to the daily source code episode 261 coming to you from the Curry condo
in San Francisco, California.
Little bit too early for the cup of chinos.
I've got a nice cup of tea here.
And of course all kinds of crap going wrong with the studio here.
I don't know what I think I blew up some kind of input on the Yamaha.
It'll be 16 gulf.
So if it sounds a little bit funky then you'll know that it's just a little bit of buggies that have to be worked out after international travel.
Of course I'm still on the power book with the external drive running two external firewire drives today.
One for the playback from Megaseg and one for the recording with audio hijack pros or hopefully no skipping.
What a difference just a couple of weeks makes man coming back into the condo.
I rolled up the windows yesterday I arrived Sunday afternoon and oh my goodness.
I could see the marina.
Because the back of America building is completely gone.
Of course on the other side of my 180 degree view.
The enormous cranes that were rebuilding some other apartment are also gone.
So I've got a clear view.
I can see a lot of miles and miles.
As I said it is 10 after 7 a.m. getting it all cranking up to bring you a wonderful week of data source code.
We're going to kick it off with Arty Fuffkin brings a little bit of John Lennon versus Dr Hook versus Steelers wheel power walk right in the middle.
We're going to kick it off with Arty Fuffkin.
That's a Monday morning record of what Power Walk, right in the middle,
ARD of course, we're bringing that to us.
A lot of audio feedback today.
A lot of different things we're going to be talking about of course some pod safe
Music lined up.
I still have the shitty connectivity here at the condo.
You can hear by the way I got the windows open. I'm kind of airing the place out. It's been closed shut for two new almost three weeks
It actually didn't smell bad when I when I came in, but you know, I had a little bit of that kind of
recycled air feel to it if you know what I mean
So one of the things that has become very difficult actually, let me see if I can do that is
To read audio feedback
Because it's all on the Gmail and I have like almost no connectivity. Let me see if I can
If I can get to oh, actually, it's I've got like if you know if you have a power book you have that little
Kind of that little antenna indicator your signal strength indicator right in the top of your of your menu bar
So I've got just a little dot
And so when I hit Gmail, it says waiting for mail dot Google dot com, but I can't really do anything
Okay, so I'm just let me get rid of that. I will have to wing it then one thing I do know 100% for sure is
I got an email from Christina for my daughter
It was really funny. She says, hey, can't you help a brother out
Apparently my chemical romance is playing at bricks in academies somewhere around the
The week of the 6th of November bricks in the Academy of course being in in the hood and in South East London more or less
And I'd like to go to actually
But of course, everything is completely sold out. So here's our typical plea. Does anyone know if they if there's a way that we can get hooked up
Because you know my daughter said can't you help a brother out
She's getting very close by the way to wanting to do her own podcast. I can I can I can feel it
She's saying she keeps saying like I want to do my podcast, but I have nothing to say
So well, how about all those songs you were playing? How about all that emo stuff all that independent stuff you found?
Oh, yeah, what I could talk about that. So I'm hoping that by the time I get back
She'll be wanting to do her first god save what no pod save the queen was the title of her podcast very cool
So I'm gonna be here for the next
I'd say 10 12 days kind of depending on what happens. Maybe 14
Tough to leave dude. I'll tell you had my sister over
She arrived. Let's see. I came back
Thursday from the Netherlands from my business trip and of course, you know that because we talked about that on Friday
And my sister was there with the friend of hers
We had a great time. We actually we didn't get around to doing anything on the podcast
We were just having fun, you know we were we went out to dinner and we hung out and we talked and we laughed and
It's the first time in a long time that the my sister has come over and hung out with me my other sister willow is an Italy
And as two kids there. So it's not quite as easy for her to
Just jump on over, but now was it was it was really good fun
So of course what that also meant is that
You know by the time was it was time for me to leave
I left the house month Sunday morning at 830
You know Patricia and I and Christina we kind of had the feeling that we hadn't really had our bonding time
And it's true, you know how you leave and you and you just haven't had you know you haven't had that
Maybe it's that one evening together or whatever it is and and you just feel like
a little unsatisfied perhaps but
Patricia's rough man. She's she's got the another head cold
Which really fucking bites because what she has to have is she has to get one of those
Flu shots you know all of Europe is now talking about the the avian flu not the avian flu
Which is basically bird flu now we had this
Who will let me think when we had the castle the bird flu was was rampant throughout
Western Europe and we
Actually the the quarantine area came within half a mile of
Of the of the castle which meant we might have actually had to
Call as they say or kill as I would say our swans and our ducks and luckily it passed just
Just kind of before hitting us
But now they're talking about this avian flu and of course can be passed on from you know bird to bird but
Can also be passed on from bird to human and
Although they have no
Scientific proof that can be passed from human to human just getting it as human as bad enough because it's really like a bad bad bad bad
Flu and can last up to I guess up to 14 days now. This is really dangerous for older people or people who have other
Other health issues and of course Patricia has
You know has there a heart medication on that crap and it's really not good because coughing strains everything
So oh by the way got some great fucking news check this out
When I went flying with the wind commander
Edicford tenta Patricia's cardiologist of course I he became Patricia's cardiologist when we found out she had a
Problem and I went for the best guy. I could find and of course all the the top lawyers and and top physicians
They all fly
So we got him to help out and and boy that was fantastic and you know, so of course
He hadn't seen Patricia for a while. He has new cardiologists, but this guy's like the top of this field
and
It was a great hospital in Belgium which is in Alsta. They are the one of the top facilities in Western Europe for
For a cardiology related illnesses and treatment and he said
You know she really should have another
Another test done and this by the way is not really a fun test. It's a test where they basically shoot die into your heart valves
So they can see how your valves are functioning. He said you know with the cholesterol
Medication she's been taking and the beta blockers and all that other crap. He said it's very possible now
with some new technologies that have been developed that she could actually
have a a stand put into that one
bilateral artery that it that it closed up a bit and then she could actually you know
Probably stop taking most of the medication and that was a major major highlight of the trip
Excuse me just wait too early. So
I think we're gonna plan doing that
Because if they if they go in there to do the test and I see that the that the artery and this thing
It's just one small artery just a very minor one. It's one millimeter thick, but it was blocked for 90% so almost impossible
to put a stand in you know that's basically in
Angeo Plasti if you will you know little balloon ballooning there
If they find out that it's that it's you know less than that 10% open then they can probably put a stand in right there and that would solve just a
Shitload of problems but she was very very excited about that. I forgot to tell you guys that
Okay, enough of me crap in here
Looks like the setup is hanging in there. No skipping so far
I've had a back and forth email with podcasts Paul
Of course Paul is a lawyer in the United Kingdom and and a very active podcaster and
There's this new
Well, I thought it was a law. I got some feedback on it about
Music licensing and music rights that it's supposed to be rolled out across Europe now, you know the concept of Europe is
It's kind of funky these days as you know that
The French and the Dutch turned down the referendum for the for the constitution or voted no
Which really really stunted the growth of of the of the EU
But Paul of course is the guy who can always tell you
You know what's going on he has always legal inroads and so I asked them give me some feedback on what these new music licensing issues are in
In Europe and
Of course I asked them to do it in audio for me. Come on in, Paul
Hi, Adam it's Paul Nichols from podcast Paul.com and podloid.com
My take at them on the European-wide music license that I've read so much about
I'm afraid Adam whenever the word Europe is mentioned
I think you know this you know there's going to be trouble and there's going to be a load of old nonsense that follows
Europe is made up of 25
Disparate nations there are 25 different member states all of which have different laws
What we've got to remember as well Adam is the fact that laws don't necessarily cut it with the music industry
There are organizations that have their own conventions
Their own trade practices and such like and that when you terms up by 25 there's an nonsense
Now what you could have done is to bring out something called a regulation
That's the most important derived source of community law this becomes directly applicable in every nation
So if Europe says right this is a regulation everybody would have to follow it
They haven't done that
What they could do then is to bring out a directive which isn't quite as good
But they simply say to each member state look we want you to do this we want music licensing sorted
We want the usage sorted out within a year and here's a directive and then it's binding and then each member states sorts that out through
Their own national laws
They've not done that either what they've done on the Friday's to give simply something called a
Recommendation
It does exactly what it says on the tin unfortunately a recommendation is just that
What they've said to each member state is look boys we can see there's a problem well we could have told them that couldn't we a year ago
And we'd like you to sort it out please what's the result if they don't nothing
Some of the fried were bets of the drawing board
It is a step in the right direction because they realize that there are problems
Brom of fried if the music industry doesn't really take notice then I'm afraid nothing further happens. Yeah, that's my
Shit what is going on? It sounds like it's cutting off
Like it's cutting off the the end of stuff here. Yeah, man. I got to go through this whole setup
You know, this is all legacy issues from from my power book crash
Here's the here's the plan by the way on that
I'm hoping that around Wednesday or Thursday new power books will be announced and the meantime
I'm gonna get a one of those new find gold, you know the kind that I got bombed on new find gold the iMac G5s
Kind of get one here for for the condo and I was thinking of getting
Some kind of video converter so I can watch TV on that as well. I think there's a 20 inch right
So I'll just put the 20 inch up here and I'll use that for televisions
Well, I really like the idea of that remote control and kind of the media player that that goes along with that
I think that was actually
Excuse me. Do I have to tell you oh? Oh, yeah
Interesting how Sanseo is pronounced differently in so many different countries in the Netherlands where this thing comes from they say Sanseo
I've heard into UK Sancio
Sancio
San Amelia oh, maybe that's why I like it
Anyway, so I'm still running my old power book off of firewire drive
I've got two hooked up now one for recording on two and the other one is where the music library lives
So they're not reading and writing to the same disc at the same time. That's to keep the the speeds kind of in check
Because I'm recording direct to the yeah to the hard drive with audio hijack pro
Um, so
You know one thing I'm definitely gonna gonna do is I'm going to can I think the speakers on the
On the iMac aren't all that great at least not the one that I have at home the new one may have a different speaker set up
But I've got that
Logitech MM50 thing
I told you about
Actually, I got it right here. Hold on
This
Let me turn around so I can look at it. This is what I've been using for sound here in the condo and this thing is unbelievable
It's um, it's about the length of a loaf of bread, but it's much much thinner and it has
I think as four speakers in it's beautiful white it goes along with my iPod and
It has a slot right in the front kind of like a top front loader and you stick your iPod in there
It'll take um, it takes my iPod. I have I guess a third generation 30 gig
can take a mini and I presume a nano. I don't know if it can take the nano. I think it does
And it has a lithium ion battery on board. So what happens is when you plug this thing in
It gets power and it actually charges itself because it is portable
You don't need to run it on the AC adapter. It also charges up your your iPod
You can connect your iPod to your power books so you can synchronize and all that
But the sound that comes out of this thing is just so unfricing, believable
I mean I had this thing going and it sounds it's hard to explain
You know how you can walk into a room and then and you it's almost like the dynamics of the room or just
flowing with the
With the air coming out of the the speakers that's what it feels like it's really crisp and the low end is
unbelievable for such a little box
And I think I'm going to because it also has an external
An external plug so you can I I've been plugging it into my into my power book
You know I've been alternating back and forth because of course this iPod is not synced up to this power book yet
So I don't want to lose all of the songs that I brought with me
So you know I've been alternating back and forth if I got a little bit of connection that I'll play it off the power book
No connection then I yeah then I use the the iPod. It's the Logitech MM50 in case you hadn't noticed
They're sponsoring this show so we'll talk about that once in a while today was
Was obviously an important one because this is saving my life and it has some kind of
Built in surround sound system
Which I kind of like
On particularly on older tracks you know you click that on you can do it all from a remote control
And it gives a little bit more of an expanded stereo stereo sound
I was gonna say something else about it. I can't remember I like it. It's it's that you know if it was shit
I wouldn't tell it. I would tell you it was shit. I wouldn't talk about it
But it's really it's a pretty cool device. Oh, and now. Oh, man. Let me get my camera. Oh
Just cracked and it's coming through the window. Oh, you're gonna love this. Wait. Let me get a picture here. Oh shit
I got it
Let me see what I want
Pretty shot now. I just give me a freaking one of my supposed to take here. We go
Oh, this is beautiful. Okay. We got my cup of tea there
Oh shoot the flash wasn't supposed to go off home. Let me just flash off there. You go now you can really see as the sun
Oh, that's pretty my cup of tea in the foreground. Let me do it one more time
Okay, I'll post that one up on the show notes. You can look take a look at the yeah
At the MM50
That is beautiful with the sunlight just kind of a yellow glow wasping right over it. Oh, yes, we go the extra mile
Rob Coslo member him
Rob Coslo one of the first pod safe music artist certainly from the instrumental realm to really break through in a big way
He is doing something very interesting. He's been talking to me about it over email for the past couple of
I guess about a week and a half or two weeks
He's auctioning off a piano for a good cause of course I could tell you about it
But one of my but Robin CC Chapman take the honors
Hey everybody this is Rob Coslo and I'm selling one of my pianos on eBay
I'm gonna let CC Chapman here tell you more about it
Hey everyone it's CC Chapman from accident hash dot com and you turn cafe dot com
How's it going? Rob asked me to take a couple minutes and just explain to you about this really cool piano
He's selling now as you know Rob is an extremely popular artist
He's one of the most popular pod safe artists out there. He's signed record deals his music is everywhere
So this is a really cool collectible if you're a fan of the music or if you're just a fan of playing the piano
It's a brand new piano. It's five months old and it's in mint condition
It's a Yamaha P22 professional upright piano 45 inches in height
It's a nice black matte finish and comes with a bench
Now what's cool is this isn't just a regular piano this is something that Rob actually used
He bought it and used it as his practice piano and he's created several of his songs on this
So if you're a fan it's a really kind of a cool thing to have in your house
Say you know so when Rob costs those all over the place in touring worldwide and it's a huge thing
You can say I've got this from when he first started out and he'll also autographed piano
Which is really cool and if you win the auction it's totally up to you how big he signs it and where he signs it
No, personally I think you need to get it just this huge autograph right across the front of Rob
Costillar that's what I would do if I want it
But it's up to you if you win the auction which is really really cool and if the piano does decent
Which I think is cool is Rob's not only gonna pocket some of the money. He's gonna donate a huge chunk of it to some very good charities
You know things like hurricane Katrina and the Susie beat Coleman, you know breast cancer
Charities which is great and cool for Rob to do it because this is eBay and it's such a big item
US bidders are preferred but if the bid's go high enough
They will ship the other places in the world and the shipping will be different you know obviously
This is a piano it's a big shipping item
But the UK and her Europe shouldn't be a problem so swing on by and check it out anyways
So how do you gonna do is go to ebay.com and search for Rob Costillar that's ROB
COST
L-O-W and check it out or you got the Rob Costillar.com. I'll have a link out there
I know I also put a link up on my site so check it out. This is a really cool way to get a part of
podcasting in music history and I think that's really really cool and
Hopefully somebody will win it. I'm keep my eye on the auction because I want to see who wins it and Rob's gonna put you know
Your picture your link anything you want up on the site as well when you win the stuff so I think it's great
So seriously simply going on by ebay.com and put it in Rob Costillar and buy a piece of history
Whatever happened
To fail
Michael and Evo's winning it
5 4 3 2 1
Good to job curry
Yeah, that's out of the pod. We come growing. This is the dragon page winging it
The kick ass mystic ninjas
Hello everybody this is a joke most important. Oh Mike wants to open up a beer. It's got a little urine flavored
Michael, how do you recognize a flavor of your
We're lonely. We're so lonely
Yeah, they couldn't have showed up at a worst possible time
It's irresponsible. It's irreversible. It's irreversible
The dragon page what some guys do instead of dating
I have so much dick you wouldn't believe it massive amounts of dick. I'm going on a dickathon.
Uh-oh, really?
Holy cow
Oh
My word okay time for an Evo cult update Lynn wants to know Michael when you get your cult
Oh, you made a lot of people very happy
Right, yeah, you can stop it right there at that time. I'm just preparing to go like rub people's bodies for that
You have no idea our arms are so tired from our own stroke stop
Not touching that
Not touching that at all
I do not laugh like Scooby-Doo
Music now on daily source code episode 261 as I stand here my White House code and my black oak boots
Wanting to play this one for a couple of days actually funny got some time love spirals and walk away
All bats just want to take it on me
記
Close to the Fire
Really burn our hands
I won't believe it at heart
So then drop it to the sins
I won't go away
So now you're on my way
I'm on my way
So I feel safe again
So now you're on my way
And now you're on my way
Take a chance anymore
No, I'll go away
I'm on my way
So now you're on my way
I won't go away
This is one of the minor drawbacks of podcasting
You know when you get to choose the music and get to take care of everything yourself
Which is just beautiful
People who have worked in radio
No one I'm talking about it so nice
Not to get handed a list by a producer or a computer
Is that used play stuff that kind of fits the mood that you're in at the time you're doing the show
And it may not always be the exact same mood for you
If we're raining I might play some different songs
And it may not be raining when you are
So that's kind of a disconnect
But yet in a strange way a great connect
Because you kind of know what the vibe is
And I actually I brought my eyesight along with me
I'm contemplated recording recording video
I guess what I could do is I could record the entire show
Excuse me
In quick time if you have quick time I guess you have to have quick time seven
And you have to have the pro version but then you can just record a new video clip
And records an MPEG video which is of course exactly right and formatted for the iPod
And it might be funny to do that
I'm particularly funny to see what I do during the songs
I'm doing all kinds of stuff
So when I get a new power book or maybe if I get the iMac or something has a hard drive built in
I'll look into doing that
That's what I guess that's what Mary and Carla are doing
That Mary and Carla show man I told you about that right
So first they had those two guys they were podcast off
They were potting off against them
They're potting off back and forth with the tipsy girls tipsy chicks
You got to check that show out tipsy chicks
I think it's tipsy chicks dot com they're an iTunes
And it's kind of
It's funny because I think they're all they're all really smart and they're all very creative and talented
But now it's kind of like okay the tipsy chicks think that Mary and Carla
Okay, they're
They think that they're kind of dipsy
Oh man I've got to play the you know they they responded to me playing the promo and they shook their ass on the show for me
I got to play that for you. I'll make sure I do that for tomorrow's source code
Okay, we are at seven forty now and the minute I'm done with this show as it's uploading
I'm gonna hop on over to the office haven't seen the folks who will I've seen him on on video chat obviously on iChat
I'm excited to see everybody again and they have a demo
I think today at 2 o'clock they're gonna show me some of the new stuff for podshow dot com very very excited about it
To bring the world a steel guitar broadcast
Keynote
Every week
Potsafe steel get to our music
And nothing else
Potshow content that will make you squeeze the dog and burp your mother
Antibity in podcast antiquity the place for the latest down under news and views covering science
Knowledge by a tech the occasional weird and one of course
Sponsored music each week catch the wave and learn about how the bottom crowd contributes to global science and technology
You won't hear stories about sport beer drinking and rural races unless of course they have a techno band and typically in podcast download that and now at
Antibity in podcast dot com and while you're there subscribed to the theme hot news from the rest of the world
Antipodian anti-podian which I think is antipodian
If you're listening to this show on serious satellite channel 103 serious stars
This is the daily source code every day 603 Pacific followed by let's see what's today's lineup
Match wine steins, yeast radio and I've done a drew show on today after that then Steve Gilmore's attention text deep Gilmore's doing great
I don't I can't find the podcast of that show. I thought I was going to put it up on
Gilmore daily dot pot show dot com, but I haven't seen it there, so I'll now that I'm on the same time zone with them. I'll find out where they are because this is the show the new show is doing with the Mike Vizard
And it's like a half hour show a daily
Tech attention show. It's I like it. I've heard just a couple of them, but I want to hear every single one
I also haven't seen my serious satellite receiver. I got to see if maybe that was dropped off downstairs
Anyway, after a attention tech will have a DVD weekly with Don and Jared followed by CC Chapman's accident hash a full hour of the best in pod safe music
More features coming soon to the pod safe music network by the way
And we're still working. This is the week that we're actually meeting with a couple people regarding the unlabel concept and we're going to be talking to some folks about
About music licensing and boy, I've gotten so much feedback on this and I've been collecting everything and you know, it's stuff from like podcast Paul and and other lawyers people in the entertainment business
There's a lot of excitement about this and and as I've said many many times before we are recreating
The music business. There's no different than the changes we've seen in in history
When technological change came along with social change and new music forms were born and
You know, and industries had to more literally overnight in order to you know, or to even be able to keep up
Hey, Kurt
Digital slot pod the brand new podcast from universal press and get columnist Kurt Brando is already changing lives
I heard the first digital slot pod show and I woke up next day with a whole new view on life
Plus my surprise this was gone. I mean completely gone
I could barely believe it, but digital slot pod made me too much as taller
Finally, I could serve the web without my lifts
I took the digital slot quiz
Then I called my dad and he took it too
We we had spoken in eight years
Digital slot didn't just give me a good show. He gave me my life back
My friend told me to listen to the digital slot pod yesterday, and I said, are you kidding?
I don't even speak English, but hey you get me now
I know the digital slot called has an officially started yet, but I'm already telling people I'm at level seven
Listeners of the digital slot pod come away filled with gratitude
Thank you digital slot
Thank you digital slot, and please send me some brochures that I can pass out at the airport
Here, touch my head, G
Go ahead
Touch it
Speccy by digital slot
I love you daddy
I love you so much
Listen to the digital slot, digital slot.com
A better version of your life awaits
You just haven't downloaded it yet
Is something about Russian that kind of turns me on?
I don't know what it is
I noticed this when I was in in Russia
There's something about Russian girls speaking English that that's kind of cool
I wouldn't mind a promo for the source
You know, I've realized that I have never made a promo for the daily source code
I think it's also because I'm afraid to
People will be expecting so much creativity in such great production values
I don't think I can live up to the expectations
I should do that
Maybe I'll do that this week when I get the new, the new Max in
Oh, yes podcast expert, that's one I would talk about
So I'm definitely going
The idea is I'm going to go back in like 12 days
Go hang out with the girls for a full week
And then go straight to, I guess I'll fly to Los Angeles
And then we'll go, I think this place is, although it sounds like it's in Canada
It's not all that far from LA, maybe it's a reasonable drive from Los Angeles
So definitely going to go
And oh, by the way, please stop with all the offers for the helicopters and the
Biaches that just way too many offers for that, okay?
Stop it
Backtracks podcast
I think you know your hits backwards and forwards
Oh, yeah, you know what
Yeah, right
You're listening to the Backtracks podcast exclusively on the daily source code with Adam Curry
Hey Adam, you did pretty good on last week's Backtracks podcast quiz
We might have to make this a little bit more typical
Yeah, come on boy
Come on
Okay, here we go
Okay, I'm ready
Oh
Okay, I'm going to give up on that one
Yeah, time's up
Number two
Hey 19
I think that's what it is
It sounds very steely down there, so let's see if I'm right on the
Day 19
Number three
I know what boys like
I don't know who sings it, but I know what boys
God, that's an old one
That's a tough thing
Give me the answers
Okay, here the answers
Number one
I'm here's number two
Yeah, hey 19
Yeah
Give me some props
Number three
I know what boys like
So do I want it
I know what's fun
So how did you do out of two out of three
My friend
Thanks for joining us on this week's Backtracks podcast quiz
You can visit Backtracks podcast on the web at
Backtrackspodcast.com
Again, I have to work on on the cue points
All right, thank you very much
Awesome Backtracks podcast
This is a Carmen Tyler, Carmen with a Y and Tyler with a Y
Remember we played a couple of her songs
Which turned out to be covers
Well, she uploaded one of her own songs
This one I guess she wrote and composed that she's got
I think she has a team that she does this with
And this is just a demo she wanted me to say
But I definitely wanted to play it for you
Because this is her own work
You can find it on the pod save music network
at music.podshow.com
This is drifting
Hey guys
Was not so distant
But fine
You're sweet melody
Playing close to me
It's gone
Now all I have in me
Are all those memories
Of so long
Drifting
Far away from me
What am I supposed to do?
My heart is still in twine
Oh yes, my love was blind
But now I realize
Where through
Come out to me
In my mind so distinct
You said you would remain
Close to me
We said our last goodbye
With tears in my eyes
No
I can't be on my stake
Oh how my heart is break
No
Drifting
Far away from me
What am I supposed to do?
My heart is still in twine
Oh yes, my love was blind
But now I realize
Where through
Drifting
Far away from me
What am I supposed to do?
Carmen Tyler
Drifting from the pod safe music network
You can find
Fuck
God damn it, I hate that shit
Why is it doing that?
Stupid ass mega-seg
Carmen Tyler
I almost want to do that again
Can I do that again?
Forget about it
That's irritating
Miss the end there
Okay, I'll fix all that stuff
So what am I going to try to do for
For the weeks that I'm out here at the condo
I'm going to try and keep in the rhythm
Now that I'm in the
Kind of in the get up very early mode
I was up at 515 this morning
I had set the alarm for 630
I really didn't get going
So I started recording the shows as you know
Around 10 past 7
I'm going to try and keep that up
So that we can have the show
Nice and early to you
That's the problem
And being on the west coast is your behind the times
You really are
Want to thank the sponsor for today's show
Logitech
On the show notes check out there
MM50
It's a great box
I use it
So there's an endorsement for you
And thank you Logitech for putting the upper
In the upper class
When I fly version of landing
Everybody have yourself a great week
Have yourself a great start of the week
This Monday
And we'll talk to each other tomorrow morning
Right here from the Curry condo
So take care
And bye bye
Need to fill this thing up
Talk to you tomorrow