Delta Sarah Charlie two two one ladies and gentlemen. The pod father is down. May they made it. The pod father is down. I repeat the pod father is down
Okay, well now you have the attention over you. All right ladies and gentlemen as you all know we are in the big NYC
Represent if you didn't hear that I did do the chest banging thing. Yes, we have the official represent sign
So as you all probably heard on the on the weblog my dad does have the flu and it is beyond sucking it now officially
So
The flight the flight was actually amazing. We had first class, so I'm just gonna do the briefing here on the
On how the vacation is going first class. We all sat in one of those little pods. You know you're like little
Closed off little thing with a little foot rest. You got your little pimped TV. It's just like pimped my right episode on the airplane
So we all sat a bar like a playboy sort of thing going on as some flight tendons with a short skirt to give you massages
Especially it's like a cheap version of my high clock
It's really good
Oh
There was one of the little beeless celebrities Johnny von no it's not as good any crane
Johnny von is a radio show host in England and he thinks a lot of himself
He's pretty much a dick. We were on the airplane and we see him sitting there moms. Oh, I know who he is
He's a mom celebrity spotted. Oh, he's he's from the commercial at all. Oh, oh, the one for dancing in the street
I can't sing it right now, but he's a DJ
So
You know just after getting a few foul looks from the whole time, you know just giving us the eye because we're speaking in
Language she's like once was going on here. I'm cool. I'm English. I understand what they're saying
So
Dad just sits are like
Smash his head
Oh, blatantly and then mom says oh hi
No, but you were like you didn't you didn't like him. He was loud
He wasn't used to get into the night. Let me just explain that this all this jockeys all this jockeys
Are clinging to the lowest rung of the showbiz ladder
And that's why they and they're always hyper particularly morning guys because that's the life and they're always like jittery and jumping around like they've got to read
Yeah, it's like me
If you want to join in, you got to come we'll show you come over to you
I think you have some good stuff to say mom's got some good stuff to say about the flight. Come on. How are you feeling, huh?
Grab a chair, babe
You're still sick
So actually Christina was the only one who was normal you felt yeah, you felt good
But we think mom and dad think that you remember we went to you remember it was less week
We went to the playboy party party and partying and it was very very hot
It was hot. I don't mean like
No hot because it was cool sexy hot was like it was stinking hot and sweaty and muggy and and
That people everyone
No
People were sweating a lot and talking with
We say with consumption
Spring on you
To get really close to here
Now English people are people who love to drink
That's what you don't you don't say
Yeah, so we think that that happens it happened over there
Oh definitely someone had some germs and then this germs jumped on me
And they may have jumped on you
But you have a different flu you don't have it as bad
Now you have a flu and I have just a heavy cold
We're coughing and we're waking up in the middle of the night
It's looking at each other
Rogitason
Nice
Because we took Nike
And Nike actually
Getting sleep
You don't know anything until four o'clock
Then you start to cough again
You have to grab some other drugs probably
In fact, we had so much Nike
I had a insurance test for tomorrow morning
tomorrow morning. I cancel that because I think I'm a crystal meth addict. No, because you're
happy for me. If I look at your arms. I'm totally stone from this shit. Yeah, they are very
big. The people's are very dilated. And that's a stuff that's in there. So, Adam, it doesn't
not a very good start to the vacation. No, I'm sorry. Christina and I. But my voice does sound
really fucking cool now, doesn't it? In a world where less beings are nothing but women who
were comfortable shoes. The big hell. The less humans are nothing more than the big hell. Nothing more
than now. 65 million years ago hung like a horse. That's all I can do. I don't know
more power. We have to say that you find a very nice hotel. I have to get used to the boutique
hotels. Didn't even know what it was. I thought that boutique was, you know, where you buy your clothes.
It is boutique hotels. That means not much in the room. Mm-hmm.
Very minimalist, minimalist. One stick of bamboo, just, you know, a single stick of bamboo in a square
base. It's art. Yeah, these sort of things. Very trendy. But it's not, it was the only two bedroom
suite in New York. It was available. But very beautiful people in the lobby. I could see that.
What hotel is it? You might as well tell them. The Alex. Yeah, give me a plug. Yeah.
Guys with black suits outside with earphones. Yeah, like secret service. Yes. Yes.
It's totally got all the bullshit. The man in black. The bullshit. One of the men in black guys in
a very nice restaurant next to it belongs to the hotel. The food is very healthy. Good health.
Now, very good. A little bit, you know, sort of a Chinese kind of a feel to it. Very, very healthy.
We ordered a couple of times. Nothing for children. Now, let's get back to Johnny Vaughn.
Johnny Vaughn. I remember you asked him on the airplane. Well, that was not your first of all. We saw him.
And he had a vault spot. No. And I said, we're sitting here. Now, we said, God, this guy is so annoying.
Look, he's jumping around before we went into the plane. Remember that?
And so we noticed him right away. He was talking really loud and a bit. Yeah. And he had this little
fat kid's sidekick with his dad that probably ate a few other kids. And his kid was like,
everything's so funny with that. You know what that was? I think that guy was also traveling in upper
clubs. He was, he was, no, no, no. I think he's a television producer or something who works in England.
You've definitely successful. Somebody will be jumping up to somebody there. I think Johnny Vaughn was
sucking up to a fatso. Because he seems, he wants to, of course, see if he can do something else.
Well, apparently he's on some TV show. He was, because he was reading a script.
Can you ask him? So what do you up to? And you are, he said, oh, well, it's a surprise.
And he said, no, no, no, no, no. I said, oh, you're going to do something exciting. And he said,
oh, if I told you when beats that exciting. And that was like, fine, blow me up. I mean,
you don't want to say this. Oh, you were probably, everyone was thinking, I don't think you can
give her the money. Oh, she said horrible things. You were totally thinking that. I
doesn't want to tell you. So I go find them. I'm not going to talk to you. He's horrible.
But mom was talking to him. I didn't say anything. I just, you were probably thinking that.
Because I'm sure you were, of course, I was thinking that. I said that you were probably thinking
to unconscious dad is to arrogant. He doesn't want it. He wants it doesn't want to talk.
But I'm about to Jay status now. I'm on one road above the lowest road. I talk to anybody.
He doesn't matter. Yeah, that's why people usually people and people person. Yeah, people like, oh,
we can say that people love talking to you. Anything I want to know about it. I want to know why
people are this hyper. Yeah. What excuse me? Yo, why are you so goddamn hyper?
I think exactly sorry. So that's why I thought because he was so busy showing off and letting
people know that he was reading a script. Yeah. You know, it was pretty good. So that's why I said,
okay. But let me tell you, having done a morning show for a year, it doesn't even make
it. But it makes you fucking wacky. I mean, you have no likes any flies. Yeah, no life. Any flies
to New York every weekend to do the whatever show he's doing over here. So this doesn't
hurt him. Oh, it's not so like for eight weeks or whatever. Yeah, we're just little tiny bag,
nothing, nothing important in there. Believe me, that's so messed up. That is, so we have to have
respect for for morning people, but somebody has to do it. Right? Okay. So now we're in a hotel here.
And we slept him around today. We wanted to go to see a couple of things. It is very muggy and very
also hot. We actually we skipped the weekend. We've been here Saturday and Sunday. Now it's Monday,
Saturday and Sunday. We just, you weren't there. Well, you went out. You went out. I went out with you.
Yeah, you went out with you. You don't even know you were there. Sunday, where are we going?
It works around like a zombie named Central Park. Yeah. We went to Central Park. We went into Central Park
in the opening and sat down on a bench and then went home. Yeah, right. This set to sit up. Yeah,
and I said, this is even better than in a fashion show because it's nice to see just all those
people passing by. It was. Sorry. So now we're here and we just been outside. You know,
you have a little Madonna accent happening, you know that? Oh, I hope so. Yeah, you have a little
bit of the, for Dutch people that is absolutely fabulous. No, but I mean, like the Madonna English
accent. Oh, it is. So you're like an abstract. Yeah, I'm English American now. Yeah, English
Dutch English American. Wranglish. So now we're sitting here. It's very muggy. One time I said,
now, it's about four. Yeah. And Edom was sweating. We are going in and out of stores and Edom was standing
outside and the poor guy was sweating. You were sweating like it was so high. I'm cold medicine.
I didn't say that. I was just like dripping on everybody. I was actually, I was sad I didn't have
my microphone because I mean, I couldn't say anything because I was just too tired to talk, but
a lot of interesting sounds. Yeah. Very interesting. Yeah, all different languages. If you're just
standing on one spot in New York and listen, interesting sounds and people on cell phone conversations.
We were walking near a Chinatown. No. Which is always I like that. I like to go to
to these sort of parts of the city. Because that's interesting. Christina, how is it to be back
in New York, your mother country? I'd never live here. It smells dirty. Sidewalk is like one big
puddle of grime. We're purple shoes that are not purple anymore. It's maybe when I'm back in
New Jersey for a while. I think, oh, I remember it's a suburbia. I'm used to suburbia. I'm not
a little New York thing. But you see a lot of interesting people. But the other day, I've just been
noticing that England is actually more obese than America now, but I did see one particular person
where the big McDonald's like backpack, you know, like the extra big takeaway bags. And she was
saying to us, but look at subway over the, I don't eat subway. So I said little dinky toppings.
And I was thinking, have another burger. I mean, what do you eat this morning? Your children?
She was so big. It reminds me a lot of England, actually. Everything's kind of really close.
American England, kind of close to England's a little bit, maybe more classy. But still,
it's good to be back to see and compare what I've been away from for a while.
People like Haiti. Yeah, really. It's true, though. Everyone's obsessed with fat people.
But they're all fat. Is it how? I'm just, you know, they need to be, I mean, I've been
you're, I'm kidding. And skinny. It's just they can't all be skinny. But the fact that they're just like,
you know how subway is, the sound, which is like a meter. Well, I personally think that America,
you know what? The terrorist don't have to do anything if they just leave America alone will eat
ourselves to death. I'm telling you. No, just eat a look at what we're eating.
No, but they're trying. You can see the TV. I mean, basically it's all about eating shit here.
It is really. But in, like, when we're all dead, that this generation, fast food won't be around anymore.
It won't be. I don't think it will. I was talking about it with my friends once.
We don't think that fast food will be around anymore. That's just temporary thing for this generation.
And that eventually it will be against the law to be served. There will be against law to serve fast food,
because it's, well, we heard, we heard, and if you look on TV, we haven't been watched American TV for a
long time. It's almost unwatchable. Yeah. Yeah, we noticed that it's actually a little bit disappointing.
Don't you think so? Yeah, I do. I'd like to hear from you. Why? It is very empty.
Don't you think? Yeah, it's very empty. It is all about, if you look, if you look at the presenters,
there's so much, there's so busy, puking, as we say, puking that, I, you know, Adam taught me that,
that is a proper way. Hey, now, you know, they're so busy. No, they're projecting. Really
loudness. So you understand exactly. Yeah, because there's a way to talk in the way and be seen by
it. But if you listen, they don't say anything. They don't say anything deep. They don't say,
they don't say, they don't say, there's actually no information. There's no information. It's about
stuff you're going to die from. The kids are going to get killed very negative. Very negative,
the news. Where's produce Pete? I miss him. Yeah, I'm not eating produce. But not many happy things
that they have to write. Sorry. Yeah. No. So we noticed that, but it's, of course, it's holiday now.
So they have repeat, repeat everything that we see in England too and in Holland. We've seen
already everything. But no, I don't think the quality of the American television is better. No, no,
I'd say it's exactly the opposite. Actually, I'm disappointed. What if I compare it with the English
television? It is better. Yeah, it's much better. Yeah, information is better. I talk about BBC
or series. BBC and ITV. It's more serious now. And if they have the news, it's more serious
and more, they have more information. Don't you think so? Oh, yeah. And also the presenters and
the quality of them. Yeah. And the shows. We have lovely shows in England. Thank you,
thank you, thank you. Beautiful big bands. And, and, and, and, and, and, and this is how it's turned this morning.
I had heard him in a while. And you know what I said? Oh, yeah. I said, actually,
how it's turned sounds like a podcast. You know what? Show. Yeah. You know the way he speaks the way
his tempo is no, not at all. No, no, no, no. I don't even know how to do that. But, um, and it also, again,
he's talking about. Was it in-out? Content? Content? Content was nothing special. No, that's where he
differs. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And people that make podcasts shows, they have really, you know,
something to say and something to tell you, something explained to you. Yeah. But, um,
listening to it this morning, it was, uh, I laughed now. And then, because it's funny. And, uh,
play was nothing special. It wasn't like, to, uh, all wife's. I love it shocking because it's an
American. He's talking about poop and sex. No, he doesn't. He does. Yeah. Oh, but you're a little bit
of vulgar. But that's already, you know, he doesn't have to do that. It's still like in the
American. Like, oh, that sucks wrong. He's no meant to say that. I think that's the same reason
why we have shows like the old world. But it's not what he showed. What was very interesting. He said
that the television, um, even the sports shows and everything. If you hear some interviews with sports
guys, now you know that sports guys are using a lot of bad words. That's the way they speak. Yeah.
And they, uh, who said that we are shouldn't, um, uh, shall I let it go for them now?
Sense. Sense for themselves. If you can, they censor so much. He said it's ridiculous.
One of these days, you will not even, you know, get people to, to do interviews or anything,
because you cannot anymore. You cannot do that. There's nothing going to be left. He said,
what's going to be left of, of interviews and all sorts of other shows because they're
bleeping and bleeping. And he was, he was, um, having an example. And so we were listening to
something and they bleep, they bleep constantly. And it was just a couple of sports guy telling
that it wasn't their, their day. They said she's, you know, stupid things like it sucked or anything.
They bleep, suck. They bleep that. Really? So they, they're not even allowed. Yeah. They
don't even allow to to say, uh, use these words. No. Oh my goodness. Not that you would use those.
I do. Yeah. I do actually a lot. Oh, that sucks. You know, it's not that bad. But even that word,
and it was one of the sports guys said, oh, I really suck today. That is normal. That,
it's not bad. So they bleep and bleep and bleep. And he said, you know, that's why people
love to listen to podcasts and to how it's turned probably because it's, the guy still says
anything he wants. And really, just though, he talks, the way people talk. Yeah. I think that's,
that's why he's such a success. It's the puking. It's going to be worse. The radio and
television. Oh, yeah. Because you noticed that. Yeah. Don't bring your puking to our podcast.
No. No. No. Okay, Christina. Puking is active. You want to wind it up?
What? I don't know. You started it off. What do you want me to say? But I don't know.
I'm too afraid. I'm going to shock the world. I don't know. Do all that. Don't say anything. That's
there. You don't know. How have you been enjoying yourself? I mean, it does suck the
appearance of sick. That does kind of blow. It's still been good. I like the view from
the hotel room. I've seen a lot of it this week. No, it is really good at night. All the lights. It's
beautiful because we have windows down to the floor. Down to the floor. So that it's, it's amazing.
When all the lights go up, you stand on the couch. You feel like you're setting on the edge of the
building, looking down everything. I'm on top of the world. Yeah. And you know what last night when
Daddy was already asleep, we stand on the couch. It's naked. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I only are underwear.
And it was just like we were floating, you know. That's about to soon. It was wonderful. I was
already sweating. Yeah, you were sweating too. I'm not just sweating. I'm experimenting. Yes,
it's nasty. Juice is a float. Thank you. You're flowing out. It's theater of the mind. Yeah.
Okay. So we'll do another podcast tomorrow. All right. If I can talk. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're really, you're still
staying Charlie and chocolate back three tonight. What? We're still staying Charlie and the chocolate
factory. If I don't collapse up, you happen to go with you. You have to walk over to time square
right. Yeah. But you know that the movie theater here are very loud. People are very loud.
Yeah. Stinky throw off stuff in the screen. I know. You know, on the floor, everything is
cracking on your feet and, you know, a bottle's and dreams thing. And don't find it. It's pretty
good. Sometimes. We're not going to get us to get us. That's the way they are.
It's New York. It's New York. It's New York. Yeah. Because we have a few small ones in England.
Yeah. But we noticed that it is a dirty city. Wonderful. Wonderful. It's just one. It's just
no. There isn't no other city. There's our city. Oh my god.
Yeah. But it is overwhelming. It is overwhelming.
Overwhelming? Yeah. Everything. The buildings.
It's big. It's so big and so high and so huge. And you feel so small and you're a little hotel room.
Well, particularly you from the only restaurant. Yeah, it's a lot of other tribe members though.
Yeah. I'm going to see what's got your shorter. People are going to think I'm so small,
but I'm not. But it's just an amazing hotel. The Hobbits are amazing. I know that tall.
You are for 14-year-old. Yeah. You're tall. Yeah. Well, Ellie's shorter than you. She's not going to grow.
Her hands are like, if you bend your fingers and your knuckles at her hand, you should see her clap.
But it's so cute. Well, actually now all we noticed is that you're a horrible child.
Yeah. Everyone makes fun of her too. There are a lot of tiny peoples. I feel very much at home. Really?
Yeah. You and Willy Wonka. Yeah. No, Willy for you. Okay. All right. We'll talk to you all tomorrow.
That was 25 minutes. I hope people are interested in listening to all that.